Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 32]
Chen Xiyi!
#1 in sales this month. Congrats!
Treat us to dinner!
Liu Jie...
Your performance declined the most. Old rule, you should be fined.
Director Yuan, I admit it.
Cai Yihui,
congratulations!
This month you're not last.
There's someone worse than her?
Cai Yihui, ¥520,000.
Zhang Zhizhi,
zero. Zhang Zhizhi,
didn't I give you a client? Where's the order?
The client kicked me out.
And then?
And then you never contacted the client again.
You're so arrogant.
Not contacting the client again after being rejected by him.
A person that arrogant should become a CEO.
What kind of sales persons are you?
Zhang Zhizhi,
I demand that you must get this client's order this month.
If you can't, then you can leave.
Cai Yihui, you must not want her to leave the most. Right?
As long as she's here, you won't be last.
Give some mercy to her.
Oh, you're nice now.
All right, one more piece of good news. This month
our sales group received a team award. Congratulations!
Thank you for your hard work. Let's keep on!
Good luck.
Zhizhi. Zhizhi,
are you all right?
We got paid.
Don't we always get paid today every month?
Basic salary plus all kinds of subsidy,
plus the bonus of the outstanding group.
The salary is 30% more than the salary of the admin department.
But you're leaving next month.
I have to stay here.
This company cheats!
Hey, bro! Bro!
Why don't we talk? Why don't we talk?
Come out!
- Where's your boss?
- I'm her.
Your people beat my husband and they didn't compensate any money!
What?
Move away!
Guan Xiaotang, are you okay?
They hurt people!
Let me go!
Can you stand up?
Go downstairs!
- It's okay!
- Are you okay?
My husband is their customer.
Her husband
rented a new battery but returned the old battery at our Laidianle service point. He was caught by our staff and they started to fight.
My husband was beaten seriously.
The medical expenses are thousands of yuan per day. They didn't compensate us at all.
The staff who beat him have already been detained by the local police.
That staff is in a contractual relationship with the franchisee.
The franchisee should bear the joint liability.
Our Laidianle and the franchisee are independent civil subjects.
So we shouldn't bear the liability, should we?
Are they reasonable?
My husband was beaten like that! They don't want to give any money!
Is it reasonable? Is there any law to punish them?
Let's listen to the police, okay?
Enough! This is the police station.
Police officer,
my husband is in an ICU unit right now. We need money to save his life!
We don't have any choice.
If you want compensation, you should go to the franchisee.
But now, you went to beat Laidianle's staff and smash things in their office.
You've already committed a crime!
Do you accept  mediation?
Mediation is okay. But I have conditions.
First, apologize to us. Second, compensate for all the losses we had.
What? You want us to pay a debt to you?
Older Brother.
This is the list of losses including the expenses of the renovation, furniture, and labor. This is the estimated price.
¥20,000!
It can't be less than that by a penny.
Sister, can you lower this a bit?
When you smashed things in my company, why didn't you think to hammer less things?
No, little sister, my older brother didn't mean to do it. He was just agitated at the time.
I apologize to you on his behalf. I'm sorry!
I'm begging you.
Fine, fine. I won't make you guys pay the debt.
But you need to write a written guarantee that you don't harass my company anymore!
You can't come to cause us trouble because you fought with our franchisee!
This...
All right. Think about it and decide quickly.
I will write it.
Police
Director Li.
I was worried before that our brand would be affected by the fighting issue.
I didn't expect that after you said those words,
our company would be extricated completely.
Wasn't I too cold-blooded?
Yes. Cold-blooded and cool.
Go to contact the franchisee there.
Let them pay the medical expenses first.
I asked them. They said they will compensate according to the court.
But now the court hasn't sentenced, so they won't pay anything.
Xiao Lu, what do you want to say?
Director Li, at some service points, some staff started without completing training before it became active online.
This one is one of those?
You think this incident is because they didn't get enough training?
How come? They used scrapped batteries to replace new batteries. If I were him, I would also beat them as well!
I don't know. I just realized this.
Only we three know this. Don't spread this.
Other points with untrained staff will stop service today.
Until all the staff are qualified.
Okay.
You really don't need to go to the hospital?
No.
Does it still hurt?
I'm used to it.
Do you get hit often?
Yes. I... was hit in the butt last time.
You should also be to blame.
You didn't know how to avoid the hammer? Luckily, it just hit your back! What if it hit your head?
I didn't think too much either. When I saw that they were going to hurt you, I was unhappy, so I just ran in.
You're just dumb.
It's not called being dumb,
it's called love.
What did you say?
I announce,
Guan Xiaotang has been in love with Li Siyu for 33 days and...
48 minutes 7 seconds!
You're a kid, what do you know about love?
I've been an adult for a while now!
I would already have a ton of wives, concubines, and kids if I were in feudal society!
You know I'm your boss, right?
Why can't I fancy my boss?
No!
Yes, I can! Let me tell you...
You hit my butt. You harassed me. If you harass me, then you have to take responsibility!
Are you sick?
If I was sick... then you're the medicine!
Who are you showing me off to?
Hey!
Hey! Li Siyu! Let me tell you!
You must face this!
[Noodle restaurant]
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you hit me?
Seriously what's wrong with you?
It hurts.
Where?
Come... Let's go to the hospital.
Wait, wait, wait!  Slowly!
Doctor, is it serious?
Two rib fractures, thankfully they didn't shift.
Are you stupid?
Two broken ribs and you had no idea!
I...
Many cases of fractures have mild painat the beginning. Plus, different people have different senses.
so not knowing is pretty normal.
Does he need to stay overnight?
No need. Wear a rib brace and don't exercise too much.
You must rest quietly. Come back to have it regularly checked.
In two weeks, you should be back to normal.
Thank you.
Bring this with you.
During this period, don't come to the office. Stay home and rest.
You're suddenly so nice to me now.
Over there.
Let's... well... Let's go and see what they're whispering about.
No, what if what they're saying is not beneficial to our company?
Let's look.
Brother, think of another plan!
The hospital has urged many times. If we still don't pay the money,
what do we do?
Sister-in-Law, listen to me, this is the only way now.
Brother, the doctor said that he's getting better now.
Maybe he will get out of danger in a few days.
I already borrowed what I could and even borrowed what I couldn't.
Right now, I just really can't think of any ways to get more money.
If I had any other solution, I wouldn't have thought of this idea!
If you don't think for yourself,
then can't you think of the two children at home,
or the four elderly?
Let's go.
Go.
A  detestable person must be pathetic as well.
Are you okay?
It's all my fault.
Sister, this has nothing to do with you.
I was too anxious for success.
No!
If they had been trained, they wouldn't have fought.
Sister, don't think about that. This has nothing to do with us.
If I wasn't looking for fast results...
If I could finish all the staff training....
Then this wouldn't have happened.
Director Su, I'll come and visit you again soon.
Mom's home.
You're home!
You made this?
I learned from watching videos by chefs online.
You never went into the kitchen in the past.
You work hard every day. I'm a jobless person at home.
I need to do some things to help you carry the burden.
Yuwei, come and eat dinner!
Sit down. The dishes are getting cold.
You don't have to do that.
After I went to the market I got to know
vegetables are so expensive now.
Our living expenses were so little,
but the quality of food we ate was not bad. How did you manage?
It's pretty simple.
Some vegetables are cheaper in the morning.
Some vegetables are 20% off after 8 P.M.
There are also some that can be snatched online in a certain window of time.
I will need to learn this.
Here, try this.
Dad, give me the fridge!
Which one's the fridge?
This one.
Let me take care of it.
You go and get some rest.
Yuwei, where are the clothes you wore this morning?
I washed them, along with your underwear. I washed them all together.
Daddy!
Tell me another story about a scientist!
Another scientist's story?
Let me read it to you.
No, I want Dad to read it to me.
He knows more scientists than you.
You've only been with your dad for a few days, you're already looking down on me?
No, I just want Dad to read it to me.
Okay, okay.  Daddy will wash the dishes first and then read to Yuwei, okay?
Okay!
Yuwei!
You can't eat this, because it has peanuts or you'll get sick.
Understand?
Why did you buy it for her if you knew there were peanuts in there?
I bought this for you.
Later, after I wash the dishes, I'll go over to find you.
There's not only peanuts in here,
but dates, to help increase your health.
Is she asleep?
Yes.
My junior fellow at school wanted to go back to his hometown.
He wanted me to replace his position.
Will your body be fine?
I can do lab work.
I looked around.
Because the lab hasn't made any achievements all this time,
so the wage is somewhat low. It's only half of the old wage.
However, you cannot carry our family all by yourself.
First of all, you will collapse under the weight.
Second of all, I will not allow it.
Zhizhi,
through this, I've learned my lesson.
Rest assured.
When I get a job, I will pay you back.
I believe our family will one day be the same as before.
What do you think?
Sister Fan.
Director Li.
I'm going to the hospital.
To help that person pay their medical fees.
We don't have enough money to do so.
But if we don't pay the bill,
I won't be able to rest.
All right.
This is really cool.
Guan Xiaotang!
Your hand!
Come to my office.
Go! Go! Go quickly!
Go! Come on, Bro!
Good luck!
I won't be surnamed with Li if I don't break your ribs.
If you want to hit me, hit my butt.
Do you want to flirt with me like this?
Don't you think that we match very well?
Suitable, my ass!
I'm being sincere.
If our website didn't need you, I would fire you now!
I have the power of love?
Who you like doesn't have anything to do with me!
If you hack my computer and photoshop my photos, fuck off immediately!
- If you don't like it, next time I'll change...
- Changing it doesn't matter!
- I don't like you!
- Whether you like or hate me, it's not my problem.
It's enough that I like you.
Leave!
- I'm not done!
- Leave!
Come in.
Director Chen, I just received the notice. We have a meeting at 10:00.
It's in Director Wang's office.
- In Director Wang's office?
- Yes.
- I'll leave first.
- Hold on.
Manager Zhou also participated in the Yunling project, so ask him to go.
I got it.
Nevermind. I'll go by myself.
It's fine, you can leave.
Yes, Sir.
Director Chen.
- Director Wang.
- Director Chen.
You're here, Director Chen.
Let's start.
Where's Director Wang?
For today's meeting, Director Wang will not be taking part.
I invited you to have a meeting here is because our project has made new progress.
Looking at our internal affairs,
the "blue cloud" project pattern is in our hands.
Let's look at this analysis report.
Let's all look at page three.
This is the result of the research. It's very important.
It's the analysis of the customer groups.
We still need discussions around this project.
Director Chen,
we have to take a closer look at this.
- The analysis done is very good.
- Okay.
- Then I'm leaving first.
Ani,
- is Director Wang here today?
- Yes.
Are you looking for her?
No.
Ani,
I also want to know when Director Wang has time in the evening this week.
She's available on Wednesday and the days after.
I understand. Thank you.
Sister Ziru, do you have time on Thursday evening?
I would like to treat you to dinner.
Okay. But why?
I need you to help me figure out something.
Let's meet at 7:00 p.m. at the old place. That barbecue place.
Okay.
Xiaoling,
congratulations for finding a handsome and rich boyfriend.
What's with you again?
This relationship is great.
It's so dull.
Maybe you required too much?
I also tried to convince myself in this way.
I'm already 32 years old. I'm afraid that I can't find a person like this later.
I will bear this first.
By the way, I transferred my job to the sales department.
Sales?
You're working with Sister Yuan?
I was thinking about what you told me before.
You told me that a woman must be independent and be able to take care of herself.
Zhizhi, I have been busy with Laidianle. I haven't had time to see you.
Do you need my help?
- If you need money, I can help you.
- I also have some.
You've helped me a lot. I really appreciate you both.
I can't use your money anymore.
Or come to work at my company.
I have relied on you or Liu Yang all this time.
I've gone through so much.
I can't rely on someone else. I must rely on myself.
So I must start supporting myself this time.
This is not an easy way.
Which way is easier?
Look at you. You're a CEO now and you still have to give a good fight.
Xiaoling, you are so pretty but your boyfriend
won't be perfect.
If you have figured out everything, then I have 2 words for you.
- You can do it!
No worries. I won't be defeated this time.
For Yuwei.
Here.
I will open the door.
Hi, Li Siyu's parcel.
- Mine?
- Such a big box.
What did you buy?
Sister Siyu, such a big box. What's this?
- Let me open it.
- What's this?
- What?
- What did you buy?
I didn't buy anything.
A box of money?
Did you send it to me?
What's this?
Be careful.
There is a card.
Li Siyu, accept me!
Explain. What's going on?
Now people are so straightforward?
Sis, did you receive the present? Do you like it?
Guan Xiaotang, if you continue to harass me, fuck off immediately.
Throw it away.
You don't want it?
If you don't want it, I will send something else.
Why do you still keep it?
If you don't want it, I will take it. This is very expensive.
Who is this?
How young?
Born in 1998.
So young!
Actually, he is not that young. Did he fall for you?
I think he is crazy.
When you want to make a move, you make a big move!
Don't think too much. We don't have any relation.
Right. You should look for a reliable one.
Otherwise, it's a waste of time.
You should look for a man who is older than you and can take care of you.
You can also try. You are available anyway.
You want me to date a boy who can call me "aunt?"
The boy can't be married but he can warm you up.
You just take him as a shot of hyaluronic acid.
I have no words.
This means that we don't belong to the same category.
Even if we are not the same, but we can still encourage each other.
All right.
Xiaoling, come on.
I wish you to have hyaluronic acid forever.
Sister Siyu, I wish you to have a successful career.
Zhizhi, I wish you to get stronger and stronger.
Excuse me, I made you wait long.
Here is your beer.
Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
Xiao Liu, after cleaning this table, clean that table, please.
Waiter, where is my food?
Wait a sec.
Sister Ziru, I'm here already.
Don't rush. Take your time.
[Chen Yiming]
Hello? Ani.
This is Chen Yiming speaking. May I ask where President Wang is tonight?
I don't know. She doesn't have any plans tonight.
Okay. Thank you.
[Chen Yiming]
President Wang, Director Chen is looking for you. May I ask where you are right now?
Hello? Driver Wang,
you are at home.
Okay. Okay.
I get it.
All right. Thank you.
- Hello?
- Sister Ziru, are you okay?
I'm all right. What's up?
If you continued not answering your phone, I was going to call the police.
Yiming, I'm sorry.
I forgot that we had an appointment today. I'm in a meeting right now.
No worries. It's good to know you are all right.
There is a client waiting in my office. I probably can't make it today.
Shall we reschedule for another day?
Okay. I'm okay. Let's reschedule.
Okay. Let's do that. See you.
If you want talk to someone, I'm always here.
President Wang.
You just finished your work?
Yes, just finished.
I'm sorry for that day.
It's nothing.
How about I make it up for you today?
No need, President Wang.
Didn't you want me to help you with something?
It's already solved.
But I need you to help me today.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... Oh... En...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go ♫
♫ all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace ♫
♫  then the trace is left be tears ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫