Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 30]
- What do you want to eat?
- This one?
Hello, what would you guys...?
Juice.
I'm sorry, you cannot bring children in here.
It's fine. Tell your boss that Haowen is here.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Tell me what you've been up to lately.
Yiming, I'm very anxious right now. I hope I can get a job quickly.
I want to help Zhizhi carry the burden a little more.
You can't rush in this kind of situation.
Wasn't I just like you in the past?
Who is classmate Haohao?
He was a classmate in my old preschool.
Do you like him?
Don't tell anyone else!
Of course. Only we know about this.
Don't lie to me!
Let's make a pinky promise.
Don't tell anyone else about this matter.
This is a little secret between the two of us.
I won't. I definitely will not tell anyone else.
Don't lie to me.
I'm sorry. I just asked the boss, and you are still not allowed to bring children here.
Did you get it wrong?
Did you tell him, Huangpu District, Lei Haowen?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I already asked.
Go back and tell him.
No, no. It's fine.
- I'm sorry.
- This place wasn't suited for children to begin with. Let's change places.
You guys can wait for me at the doorway. I'll pay.
- How could this have happened?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, really sorry.
- Come. It's this way, right?
- Yes, this way.
Okay.
- The food and drinks?
- All in place.
And the people who are welcoming the guests?
At the parking lot is Xiaoli, downstairs is Xiao Jiang,
At the elevator's front is Xiao Ming, Xiao Liang is here, and the general responsibility falls on me.
The speech presentation?
I checked it three times. It's okay.
How's the server doing?
Perfect.
Our promotional materials?
They're all in place.
Then we can end here today.
Everyone, go home and rest.
Tomorrow let's bring our best selves to welcome Laidianle going live!
- Fighting!
Tomorrow is your big celebration,
but I have to work overtime,
and Zhizhi needs to watch Yuwei, so neither of us can come.
We were thinking of sending you a flower basket.
Sister Siyu,
for the characters on the flower basket, do you like "profits pouring in from all sides" or "Customers coming like clouds"?
If you must write, then write
"Let's wish for Laidianle to become successful immediately after launch.
Li Siyu's wishes all come true.”
Can I really write it that way?
Why not?
Fine then.
Well, I'm going to hang up now.
Bye-bye.
Hello? Hi.
- Is this Laidiane company?
- Yes.
Your delivery has arrived. Please come downstairs to get it.
What is it?
I think it's your company's handbooks.
I'm going down right away.
Hey, Older Sister. Older Sister, what's wrong?
Guan Xiaotang!
Didn't you say all of the promotional materials were in place?
How come there is still a deliveryman bringing our handbooks?
I forgot about the handbooks!
Hello! Is this the delivery for Laidianle?
Yes.
Please let me borrow your pen.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I-I-I-I was wrong.
Today, you can leave the company.
Y-You can't just kick me out like this!
I can.
Older Sister, you...
No, but this can't be completely my fault.
What are you doing?
B-But the delivery people should have brought them yesterday like they planned.
It was their problem.
Also, I wasn't the one in charge of this,
it was the publicity department's Xiao Sun's job, but you forced him to resign.
I was put on this job temporarily.
No, no! Even if it was my fault,
t-that doesn't mean I should get the death penalty.
I asked you three times and you said that there were no problems, but then such a big mess happened.
If you don't die, then who does?
Aren't they just missing handbooks?
For these handbooks, I worked hard for a whole month,
went to 13 businesse,s and drove four cameramen insane.
Do you believe that I can wreck you, you little brat?
I believe it, I believe it.
It... I-I-It seems like it's broken.
What's going on?
I... I-I-I'll ask.
It was working just fine when I came down.
How could this have happened? Are they purposefully not letting us work overtime?
Older Sister Director Li, Older Sister Director Li.
What's the situation?
There's good news and bad news. Which would you like first?
The bad news.
The bad news is that one of the elevators broke down,
and for safety reasons, they closed down all of them.
What?
The good news is that the elevator repairmen promised that tomorrow, at 10:00 a.m.,
all of the elevators will be finished getting fixed, and everything will work out.
Well, what about the delivery elevator?
It broke down multiple days ago.
You call this good news?
It's fine. Our launch ceremony starts at 10:00 a.m., this isn't going to cause us to fall behind at all.
What about these handbooks?
We can just leave them here. When the delivery elevator gets fixed tomorrow, we can just bring them up.
That can't work.
The guests are coming at 10:00 a.m., and we have to get the handbooks in the present boxes before they arrive.
That's 200 present boxes,
it would take at least two hours.
So we need to get the handbooks into all of the present boxes tonight.
B-But we don't even have... an elevator.
There are stairs.
Older Sister Director Li, our company is on the 12th floor!
Older Sister, how many times are we going have to move them up?
Older Sister Director Li, why is your temper so bad?
Because you worry too little.
Has your temper always been this bad,
or was it after your heartbreak that your personality became like this?
Guan Xiaotang, do you want to be scolded or beat up?
I... Don't want any of those.
I just wanted to get in on some juicy gossip to lighten things up!
There is no gossip.
Well... Well, tell me about your ex-boyfriend.
In the stories, he's the one you were going to marry but then kicked you out.
Guan Xiaotang,
do 95-liners not know that when talking to their bosses, they need to be proper?
Not all 95-liners are like this, it's just me. I have guts.
I have nothing I'm too afraid to say and nothing I'm too afraid to do.
Do you believe that I can beat you up right now?
I... R-R-Right, you should conserve your energy to climb the stairs, Older Sister.
However... However, Older Sister, I think you really can talk to me about it.
You can just pretend I'm a treehole. If you have anything you're unhappy about,
just say it. Don't leave them in your heart!  What if your heart grows tumors?
Get out.
Then... how did the two of you meet?
Just tell me.
Tell me, tell me, tell me.
It was a bit of an accident,
and felt a little bit like love at first sight.
Their company had planned an art exhibit.
I don't know what about me attracted him,
but he started to ask me out.
Of course, he was very handsome,
had creativity, and was handsome in the clean sort of way.
How handsome was he? As handsome as me?
If you keep spouting nonsense, I'm going to stop talking about this.
I... G-G-G-Go ahead. Go on.
All these years,
we created dreams together and worked hard together.
Not only were we lovers,
but we were also best friends.
His growth included me,
and mine him.
But we were two people, after all.
Just like two different branches on one tree,
even though we grew up together,
at some point in our growth,
we suddenly realized that we were getting farther and farther from each other.
Our futures pointed in different directions,
but he wasn't willing to give in,
and I wasn't willing to give up.
Breaking up was our only option.
When we were together, we both thought the other person was unnecessary,
in the way, cold-blooded.
But after breaking up, I realized
that half of myself was already gone.
You... explain it in a way that makes me feel pity.
Really.
I know about the things you say about me behind my back.
We were just messing around.
Everything you said was correct.
The only way I can forget the pain a little bit
is to make myself
suffer, fill myself with work, and become tired.
We're the ones who you are making suffer, too busy, and tired, okay?
Li Siyu,
what kind of boss are you? Exploiting your workers to give yourself peace of mind.
Thank you guys for being by my side during this time.
You also have to endure
my extremeness, my insanity, and my cold-bloodedness.
It's fine.
A good older sister admits her mistakes and changes herself to fix them.
I fear that I will be unable to change.
I-I-I'll do it.
Fine, go ahead.
Can you do this?
I... can, yes.
Move.
No, I... You take one, and I'll take three.
I am a mature, able-bodied man.
Am I mature?
I am mature.
We're still not there.
There are still five floors.
I talked so much about myself,
now it's your turn.
What's there to say about me?
Let me ask you. Why do you always act
like you're heartless and foolish?
It could be because my life experience was too torturous.
And if I had a heart, I would have died long ago.
Stupid brat. How could you possibly have life experience?
Really.
When I was two years old, my dad got into a car accident and died.
My mom remarried...
and I grew up with my grandfather.
But my grandfather didn't get much of a salary,
so he had to live by picking up trash.
You're making this up.
I'm not making anything up.
I think there's nothing wrong with picking up trash.
At least that way, I can look at all sorts of gaming devices.
So, that's why I'm so good at video games.
Older Sister,
I also really like Transformers.
When I was little, I took all sorts of Transformers that my grandpa picked up
and put them together, making them one-of-a-kind Transformers.
Then, on birthdays, I would gift them to myself.
When is your birthday? I'll gift you a Transformer.
You lied to me?
Guess.
Guan Xiaotang! Don't move!
You can't kick me!
- Stop right there!
- Catch me if you can.
Older Sister,
Do you think our company, Laidianle, will be successful?
It must be successful.
Otherwise, it makes everything I gave up not worth it.
I climbed 60 flights of stairs with you.
I worked hard and got no credit.
Do I still need to leave the company?
No.
Older Sister,
I think you don't have to be so fierce in the future.
First of all,
being fierce is useless. This is just my personality.
Secondly,
honestly, I've already seen right through you.
You are a person
who is tough on the outside, but in your heart, you are quite gentle.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
I declare Laidianle to be officially online.
Some people said that I couldn't succeed in making this website.
Other people said that I couldn't, in such a small amount of time,
launch this website.
But right now, in this moment,
all of the doubt has been transformed into miracles,
and the creator of these miracles is me, Li Siyu.
I toast this first glass of wine to myself.
This miracle does not only belong to me, but it belongs to all of you as well.
My employees, my franchisees.
You are my allies, as well as my partners in battle.
Without all of you, it would have been impossible to do it alone.
Today, we are all miracle makers.
This second glass of wine is a toast to all of you.
- Great!
- Drain it!
This journey was hard to walk.
But after working together and doing our best,
our spirit of win-win cooperation, we made it finally.
And I believe that if we continue to cooperate well together,
fight and win together, we can not only create a beginning of miracle,
we can also build a splendid future!
With this third glass of wine, let's toast to the future!
Toast to the future!
Don't drink too much, just a little is fine.
- Director Li, congratulations.
- Hey, Lao Bai.
- Thank you.
Today's a day for celebration, let's drink to that!
- Director Li, let us toast to you.
- I'll drink in her stead.
- We're toasting to Director Li. Why would you drink?
- Exactly.
I'm always making older sister angry. Of course I have to drink for her.
Siyu, congratulations!
GM Pan, GM Pan! I know that you've always been taking care of Director Li. I'll drink in her stead.
Go somewhere else. This is the home court of me and GM Pan.
The opening was quite good.
Next step is launching the offline market. It's a tough job.
Right now, how many branches do you have?
Right now we've built 15.
The plan is to build an additional 50 within the next three months.
- Are they all franchisees?
- Yes.
How many cities are you planning on expanding to this year? How many spots?
- The plan is 3 cities, 100 spots.
- Not enough.
We need a minimum of 20 cities, 800 spots.
I fear that if we go too fast, problems will occur.
Okay, Siyu,
even though Laidianle has special qualities, it's still different from Lubao Batteries.
It doesn't have core technology. It's very easy for people to copy it.
If you don't work fast enough, other people will pass you, and then the market will no longer be yours.
But right now we don't have enough funds.
Lubao Batteries will add to it!
Perfect, I've been waiting for these words!
Li Siyu, as your investor, Lubao needs your performance.
GM Pan, don't worry, Laidianle will not let you down.
Okay, I believe in you.
- Wine, please.
- Coming!
Guan Xiangtang, who told you to change this to grape juice?
Give me the real thing!
That kid doesn't understand things.
Then in the future, every time a dream comes true,
- we will light up a firework to celebrate.
- Okay.
GM Pan, look.
Within the next three years, Laidianle will IPO!
Okay, I believe in you.
She really has this potential.
Director Li, we are all hoping that day comes quickly!
Until that day, I will definitely share the internet benefit with everyone!
I promise!
Deal!
- Goodbye!
- Drink less.
Go back!
Go back home and rest, come back tomorrow to clean up.
It was a nicely fought battle.
Why haven't you left yet?
You've worked hard today.
What's up with you?
I poured some grape juice to make you drink less out of kindness. Why did you scold me?
I was happy today!
Just because you were happy doesn't mean you shouldn't care about your stomach.
Take this medicine.
Why are you suddenly thoughtful today?
Oh, learned it from you.
You also have a bad temper now?
Also, learned it from you!
Director Older Sister Li, you really can't drink like that.
Student Guan Xiaotang, thank you.
Don't just thank me with words.
If you wanted to actually thank me, increase my salary.
How come you're always talking about money, money, money?
Because I'm poor.
Xiaotang, trust me.
I will take all of you to achieve our dreams.
I don't really care about dreams,
just don't make me work overtime too much.
Don't worry. From now on, we'll be 007 (bond).
Li Siyu, I want to resign!
You are only allowed to resign your job after our product launches in the market.
No way.
When you finish cleaning up your things, go home to sleep. We need to keep fighting tomorrow.
Oh my goodness, no way.
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow  ♫
Siyu.
On the day you succeed, I— I will definitely stand in the very front to support and applaud you.
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
You must find a wife that treats you well.
You must.
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But are ♫
♫  as lost as others  ♫
Were you waiting for me?
[This is the man God gave you]
Accept it.
Did you buy this on Taobao?
(T/N: A cheap online market)
How much did you spend?
¥200.
- Free shipping?
- Yes.
- Seven day return guarantee, no questions asked?
Send me the link. Our museum could use that for our next cocktail party.
You're not even the slightest bit moved by my gesture?
If you turned all of these into gems, then I would be moved.
You're still crazy truthful.
And you're still as vulgar as always.
Let's go. I'll treat you to a midnight snack.
I want to break things off with you.
Break things off after you eat.
[This is the man God gave you]
The preliminary layout is pretty much complete, and the next step is to carry it out.
- No problem. Go ahead and do it.
- Okay.
- President Wang.
- Yes?
The aquarium store's workers have arrived.
You've worked hard. Put it in the old place, okay?
Be careful. Be careful of the door.
That fish tank is a little bit big.
When we bought the fish they were only 20-30 cm long.
Now, they're so much bigger. We have to give them a bigger fish tank.
Then the old fish tank is unusable now?
No.
Big fish tanks are where we put big fish, and little fish tanks are for smaller fish. It has to be suitable.
The big fish also need more room to swim.
The small tank will have new small fish to inhabit it.
Right?
Yiming, I wanted to buy something recently, will you accompany me?
I just think that your style and fashion sense are quite good.
Can you give me some suggestions?
I... I'm just normal.
You're not willing?
Of course, I'm willing.
- Then it's settled.
- Yes.
Go ahead and work.
Okay. Then I'll leave.
Mister, please fill in the customer information.
Mister, is there anything else I can help you with?
This is what matches the Munsell color pattern. Thank you.
Does he have a problem?
I think he is interested in you.
Why would you think so?
Earlier, he asked what your name was.
Hello, can I please ask what your colleague's name is?
Her name is Gu Xiaoling.
Is she married?
Not yet.
What's wrong with her foot?
She sprained it.
What did he buy?
"Untitled."
The one that costs ¥40,800 by Agnes Martin?
Is he a member here?
Yes.
I asked again,
but your resume really is not good enough.
They all felt bad.
In the end, one department was willing to take you,
and if you work hard enough, you can have a high salary.
I'll go.
Sales Department.
I know that you and Director Yuan have had problems in the past.
More than just problems.
Director Yuan already clearly stated that she is willing to take you.
But whether it's for work or personal reasons, I still want to remind you
that if you choose to go, you must prepare to be tortured.
Are you going or not?
I will think on it. Thank you, Director Hu.
Zhang Zhizhi.
Lately have you been meeting up with Li Siyu often?
No.
I heard she started a company called Laidianle.
Old Pan also gave her batteries at the lowest price.
I don't know about that.
If Li Siyu didn't have Old Pan to back her up, what could she possibly do with her life?
Director Yuan, I still have business to attend to. I'll be leaving now.
Wait. I heard that you wanted to switch departments.
My Sales Department welcomes you.
I fear that I don't have the skill.
Suit yourself.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Hello.
What?
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Ye... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫