Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 8]
Director Wang,
is this the bidding document you made?
Yes, it is.
Have you checked it?
President Lu, I received it this morning.
I quickly went through it. I didn't read it carefully.
Now read it carefully.
The 4th line of the 3rd page of the annex.
Sorry, President Lu.
I stayed up too much so I reversed these two groups of numbers.
Also, the 1st line of the 5th page.
President Lu, I left it out.
I just turned to some random pages, and I had already found some mistakes.
Sorry, President Lu.
The depth and quality of the bidding document,
directly relate to the result of the invitation for bids this time.
This also reflects the management of one organization.
The document you made...
is ruining our reputation!
President Lu, sorry. This was also my mistake.
We will check and rectify it immediately.
Xiao Liu,
you said "stay up" just now.  Did you blame me for not giving you enough time?
I didn't. The time is enough. It's the problem of my time management.
Now I give you two more weeks' time.
If you still can't make it well,
then I'll give this assignment to someone else.
President Lu!
What's wrong with you?
This is okay. This is okay.
These all work.
- This—
- Old Wu.
One minute.
What's up, Brother?
You see, here...
and here.
And here. What's the problem?
Wei Yayun?
Come here!
Quick!
Tell Mr. Liu... How did you do your work?
You did this?
Yes.
Do you not know common sense?
Here. Compared with the previous document,
it's just rearranged a little. You wrote it like this?
Also here.
You don't understand? Or you didn't care?
Mr. Liu, sorry for my negligence.
Because of your negligence, we didn't reach the standard of the document.
You wasted Mr. Liu's time as well.
What are you thinking about all day long?
You want to become a regular staff by working like this?
- I think you should—
- All right.
Go back to your work.
No young people work hard now.
I thought this part of the job was easy.
I also wanted to give her an opportunity, so I gave the job to her. I didn't expect this.
Sorry, Brother. I will change it immediately. Next time, I won't—
No need. I will do it by myself.
You don't trust me, do you?
Old Wu, I'm busy here. Let's talk about it later.
Then...
Then let's talk about it later.
When the kids finished lining up after school,
Doudou pushed Miao Miao again.
- He almost pushed Miao Miao again.
- Really?
He also pushed my William.
Yes, he also teased my Little Xingxing.
Do you think Doudou has ADHD?
Yes. Don't you think that we should call on the school
not to allow a sick kid to stay in the class?
Then, how should we do it?
But is it discrimination if we do it like this?
Doudou almost bullied all the kids in the class.
If the parents don't care and the teacher can't manage him well,
then shouldn't we think of a solution by ourselves?
Then, you say how could we call on this?
How about we write a joint letter?
A joint letter?
Yes. Then let's find more parents to sign on the letter.
- This plan works.
- Yes, let's do in this way.
Sure.
Almost done, right?
Turn on the light.
It's so pretty.
It's beautiful!
- What a happy life the kids are having nowadays.
- Exactly!
It's all because of an excellent mom like you!
The event looks so nice. Let's hold more like this in the future!
You picked the color very well!
Right, you see. The location is also good.
When it's a party, we need to dress up nicely!
For sure! Let me think.
My husband bought a very beautiful dress for me in Australia awhile ago. I'll wear that one.
I bought a new full-dress last month.
I will put on the antique dress my grandma passed to me.
Antique dress?
- I've never seen that.
- Yuwei mom, you can't wear casuals at that time.
I...
Right, Yuwei's mom. You should wear good quality clothes.
Yes. Look at your shoes.
And your bag. You need to change; otherwise, it's too humiliating.
I wear them to work.
Yuwei's mom, come and have some tea.
You have some first. I will finish this.
Thank you.
Which little cat hiding in the blanket?
Let me see?
You came back?
Mom!
- Yes!
- Finally, you came back!
- What's up?
- She disliked my story. We were at odds.
I want to listen to "The Little Mermaid" told by my mom.
- All right
- All right. Your mom will tell the story for you!
Mom will tell the story for you, okay?
Oh boy.
Here.
I will start now.
There were a grandma and six beautiful princesses in the deep of the bottom of the sea.
They don't have legs but only have fish tails.
They are mermaids.
Mermaid princesses are all very beautiful.
Especially the youngest one.
Yuwei, I want to ask you something.
Doudou in your class often hits other classmates?
Doudou likes to tease other classmates but he never hits people.
Has he teased you before?
He put the grass of the garden on me today.
What did you do then?
I just left him alone.
Did the teacher know this?
Yes, she did.
She criticized him and he apologized to me.
But after a while, he started again.
He went to tease Miao Miao. Miao Miao cried.
Other classmates don't like him, do they?
Sometimes they don't. Sometimes they are okay.
Why?
Because he can imitate little animals. I like to watch him.
18th Century.
Rococo. Watteau.
Bou...
Bou... Bou...
Bouchet. Flad.
Bouchet. F...
Bou...
Sixteenth...
The sun rose and the little mermaid
felt light and transparent.
She rose higher and higher riding a rosy cloud.
Higher and higher.
There is one sound from the sky.
Zhizhi.
- What's wrong, Mom?
- Zhizhi, drink this.
- What is this Mom?
- This is something good.
Drink it and you can have a son.
Mom, it's a little hot.
Put it there. I'll drink it later.
You have to drink this medicine hot.
It won't be good if it's cold.
- Drink it.
- Mom, I'm tired.
Why don't you put it there?
Why aren't you listening to me? I told you, this medicine won't work unless it's hot.
Drink it.
What's wrong?
Mom.
My bad!
What sin have I committed?
I put in a lot of effort to make Zhizhi a bowl of medicine,
but she didn't care at all about my good intentions.
My mom is old. Her health is not good. Why did you fight with her?
Grandma, what's wrong?
Grandma's hand got burned.
Mom, I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean it.
- Zhizhi.
Don't think of me as old and troublesome.
I'm doing this for your good.
Don't be mad. I'll drink it next time.
- I'll drink it next time.
- Don't wait until next time.
- Yang.
- Yes, Mom.
There is still medicine in the pot. Hurry and make a bowl
- and drink it while it's hot.
- Mom, this—
My hand is fine. Go ahead.
Hurry and go.
Grandma, I will blow for you.
Hurry and drink it. It's not any good cold.
It's late. Don't cause any trouble.
Drink it.
Who is it?
Save me.
Gu Xiaoling, you owe us money.
It's time to return it, isn't that so?
When did I owe you money?
Miss Gu, we have your signature on the contract.
You guys are from Chuan Feng Company?
Isn't the payment supposed to be due next month?
The contract says
payment is due every Thursday.
How is that possible?
Look at it yourself.
7th page.
[Party B promises to repay the loan amount of ¥6,000 every Thursday from the beginning of this month, and pay a late fee of ¥600 per day for extension.]
Why is it like this?
Okay. It's already Friday.
According to the contract, it's already been 7 days.
You need to pay ¥6,600 now.
You are tricking me.
You are tricking me, wanting me to give you money.
Miss Gu.
Don't be scared.
You ought to know what the consequences are
for borrowing money and not returning it.
What do you guys want?
Hurry and return the money.
Mama, because of you, we get to eat soup dumplings.
Mom waited in line for half an hour this morning to buy these for you.
Thank you, Mom.
Zhizhi, drink this medicine first
and then eat breakfast.
Mom, I can't drink it anymore.
Why not?
I woke up three times last night. I didn't sleep well.
That's right.
Huang Shengshou said that city citizens have poison in their bodies.
This medicine is to help rid your body of these toxins.
Drink it while it's hot.
- Liu Yang—
- I have to go to work.
- This early?
- Something came up, I have to go in a little earlier.
- Did you finish eating?
- Yes, I'm done.
Okay. Then go, don't be late.
Okay, I'll be going now.
Yuwei, be good at school.
Zhizhi.
Here. Drink the medicine while it's hot.
Slowly, it's hot.
Mr. Liu.
Sit.
Here.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
I was a little rough that day the other day.
Don't mind it.
No, Mr. Liu, you were right to criticize me that day.
Old Wu exaggerated this just to scare you.
Relax. As long as you work hard
and don't make that kind of low-level mistake.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
Don't cry.
Wipe your tears and eat.
SIster Ziru, over here!
- Why is it only you? Where is Yiming?
- He is busy.
Working overtime for Caijin again?
Think so.
Sister Ziru, let me report something to you.
Me and Sister Yuan have officially started to battle.
You finally followed your heart?
I was actually forced.
I have a question.
Is there a chance that I and Sister Yuan can go back to the way we were?
Of course, there's a slight possibility.
Let's go.
[Gao Zhengdao's New Battery Energy Lecture]
Some people say that membrane-less batteries
can only be used as
an object of academic interest to learn about and research.
However, on the market,
it hardly exists.
This is complete nonsense.
An extremely dumb notion.
My reason is to combine the advantages of a membrane-less energy storage system
and the chemical properties of hydrogen bromide.
If we put these two limited systems
together, we definitely will get a  better result than any single system.
His views...
are the complete opposite of GM Pan's.
Pan Zhiyong?
Don't talk.
The traditional flow cell battery
an isolating membrane,
a catalyst.
They occupy half of the cost.
But membranless battery,
they not only don't need isolating membranes,
but they don't need cathodal catalysts, either.
We just use a little anodal catalyst.
If the research is successful,
then the current market brands:
Beike, Deke,
and GNB, Lubao,
all of those will die immediately.
He's straight-up slandering Lubao!
If GM Pan came, they'd probably get in a huge fight.
I would honestly love to see that.
That's enough for today.
Professor Gao.
I have a question.
Sure. If the question is too stupid, I'll scold you.
You kept saying that flow cell batteries were walking to their death,
but do you know that
Lubao is going to release a flow cell battery called Lubao 3?
I heard that the Lubao 3
is ranked number one in the market.
We don't have a real hero at the moment, so a chap can become a hero now.
This hero you speak of... Do you mean the membrane-less battery you're researching?
Let me tell you. If my research succeeds,
Pan Zhiyoung's Lubao is going to be forced to kill itself.
So when is your research going to be successful?
When it comes time to be successful, it will be.
Mr. Gao, I have another question.
I feel like I'm playing piano to a herd of cows.
I said I didn't want to come. They wouldn't take no for an answer.
Sister Ziru, are you actually thinking about investing in his project?
I am a little interested.
You might as well invest in Lubao instead!
My company is preparing equity financing now.
GM Pan said it himself.
Sister Ziru, something happened with Xiaoling.
- I have to go over.
- Do you need help?
- Not now. I'm leaving now.
- Hurry and go.
Professor Gao!
Professor Gao, the objects on the market right now,
are basically all updated versions of old research.
Your research is not like that at all.
Your research can be revolutionary.
I finally met someone who understands.
Can I please take a look at your lab?
You lead me.
Professor Gao, how much more money do you need for your research?
¥20,000,000. If I had ¥20,000,000, I could make breakthroughs.
¥20,000,000...
¥20,000,000 isn't that much.
I can come up with the money.
Okay.
But you have to tell the school.
This donation is made specifically for my lab.
I want to join in the form of investing.
That works, too.
Then you have to also talk with the school.
What if I only want to talk with you?
What does that mean?
I want...
to set up a company for you.
You want me to leave the school?
Professor Gao, with my knowledge,
the school has been cutting your funds for some time now.
There has even been word that some people want to close your lab down altogether.
You seem to know a lot about my situation.
The school has regarded your research as pointless for a while now.
I trust that if the price was right,
they would be willing to give up your research results.
And then...
And then you can work in your very own lab
with no limits.
You never have to worry about funds ever again.
There's definitely a catch.
I just want to have some shares within your company.
- How much?
- 60%
¥20,000,000?
For ¥20,000,000, you want 60% of my shares?
Professor Gao,
usually, angel-like investments don't go past 30%,
and they even require that in five years, they get five times the amount in return.
But in my current state, that's impossible.
Yeah.
You can't even guarantee that you'll have a breakthrough with ¥20,000,000, can you?
Professor Gao, the industry trusts your research even less.
More than 50% of people think you are poles apart.
Over 90% of people,
think that you cannot be successful.
The most trusted science magazine predicts that
if membrane-less batteries want to successfully enter the market,
then there still needs to be 20 years.
Then, why are you looking for me?
I am an investor.
I understand the risks much differently than other people do.
I won't accept 60%.
60% does seem high.
But don't forget.
I am putting myself at a 99% risk.
You can leave now.
Professor Gao, I'm telling you.
I trust that not a single person
will take this much money and time
- to invest in a project that has a 99% chance to fail.
- I need to go to work now!
Work.
Okay.
This is my business card.
If you change your mind, please contact me.
I'll put it here.
I'll leave.
[Wang Ziru]
[Chief Executive Officer]
[I'm Gu Xiaoling. I can't pay back my debt. So I'm willing to have sex with you. ¥300 per night. The price is negotiable if you are introduced by friends. I'm driven desperate now. Please help me.]
Don't cry. Talk.
Say something.
I needed money,
so I found a company and borrowed ¥100,000.
If you needed money, why didn't you come to me?
You helped me return ¥130,000 just recently. I couldn't just ask for more.
And then?
I said I'd borrow ¥100,000,
and return ¥140,000 in two years, ¥6,000 a month.
I don't know how it became six thousand a week.
How is that possible?
When I signed the contract, I didn't look very carefully at what it said.
It's such an important thing, how could you not pay attention?
The contract was so thick, how was I supposed to read it all?
Then you deserve it!
Sister Siyu, don't scold Xiaoling. She's already upset enough as is.
They came asking for money yesterday.
I didn't have it, so they...
Everyone in my contact list got this message. How am I supposed to face them?
Who are you guys looking for?
Ms. Gu, you've got friends over? That's perfect.
So, can you return the money today?
I can't return it.
Get your friends to let you borrow some then.
If you send a message like that, who would possibly want to help me?
Wow. You're quite stubborn.
Let me tell you. If you can't return it today, I've got an even bigger trick up my sleeve.
Why are you so rude?
We're trying to solve Ms. Gu's problem.
Not scare them.
Ms. Gu, if you really can't return it, I'll help you.
You can get another company and borrow money from them.
Return ours first.
You're full of tricks.
You definitely can't.
Then you help her return it.
Exactly! It's a total of ¥106,000.
Get the money.
Ms. Gu, you already know our methods.
I even came up with a plan for you.
The rest is up to you.
Let's go.
We will come back tomorrow.
You guys purposefully tricked Gu Xiaoling in the contract. She's an idiot and doesn't understand, so that's on her,
but running into her house smashing and breaking everything is wrong.
What do you want to do?
Right now. I'm about to report you for violent robbery and debt collection.
I'm going to kill you.
If I add assault and battery, you'll be stuck in jail for ten years at least. If that doesn't happen, then my last name isn't Li!
Miss, that would be framing us.
Yes. I am framing you.
You think you're the only two gangsters on this earth?
Zhizhi, call the police!
Don't move! Who dares to move?
Xiaoling, go to the window and scream for help.
Don't move. Get over here.
Help! Help!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We were too rash.
We'll apologize. Okay?
Miss, we're also doing this for business.
Why would you put us in such a place?
If Ms. Gu is willing to return the money, then everything will be fine.
We will definitely pay back the money including the interest by this week.
You guys must apologize and immediately send a text to help Xiaoling regain her reputation,
and promise to never bother her again.
But...
There is nothing to discuss.
Okay.
Sorry.
Send the message.
I will, I will.
You, clean up the mess you made.
- I.. You...
- Xiao Wu, just do it.
Okay.
[I talked nonsense today. I apologize to Ms. Gu.]
Get lost.
Sister Siyu, you're so formidable.
Siyu... thank you.
Why would you borrow so much money?
I signed up for a seminar that cost ¥100,000 as tuition.
To learn what?
Art appreciation and management.
Are you crazy?
I'm not crazy. It was a clearheaded decision.
Our club has started group buying, and the people who come are getting worse and worse.
I need to change groups.
I don't think you need to change groups, you need to change brains!
What's wrong?
You already suffered so much from Lan Ke, why didn't you learn from that?
How come all you think about is shortcuts?
What do you mean shortcuts?
Besides, shortcuts are made for people to walk on!
Why can't it be me?
You need to have the skill to walk a shortcut! What skill do you have?
Do you think rich people are all idiots?
You think you can do whatever you want just because you're pretty?
Siyu, don't act like you're allowed to lecture me just because you helped me return the money.
Not only did I help you return the money,
but I also helped you return your debt! I have the right to lecture you.
I don't need you to return it for me!
That's what you said.
From today on, even if I die on the street, I still won't ask you to help me!
From today on, anyone who ever helps you again is sick in the head!
Sister Siyu!
Zhizhi, don't stop her.
Xiaoling.
Take a look.
Siyu just gave me ¥110,000.
She told me to give it to you.
She said you should hurry and return it to those people.
Siyu was just saying that stuff. In her heart, she still loves you.
Li Siyu,
don't you dare think that just because you helped me, I'll bow down to you.
I will definitely return ten times the amount back to you.
But I never want to see you again.
I made you a wonderful dinner.
I'm too tired today. I'll go see you some other day.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[ Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫