Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 44]
Professor Gao! Professor Gao!
Data! The data!
Where is it? The system!
God.
Professor Gao!
We... We...
We just failed?
Didn't you say we would definitely make it this time?
Professor Gao, didn't you say we would succeed this time?
Lei Haowen,
you... you said we are going to make it, right?
You can't do this to me.
Are you kidding me?
Haowen! Haowen!
Haowen!
Lei Haowen!
Go inside and inspect it.
You two keep the order here!
You didn't bring keys?
Do you feel better?
I can bear this.
Haowen,
I'm not sure if he can bear this or not.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed is turned off.
He turned off his phone.
Is he okay?
I'm going to look for him.
Xiaoling! Xiaoling!
Have you finished? Go back!
It's done.
It's all gone.
Everything exploded.
Let's go back and talk.
- Come on! Go!
- Leave me alone!
If you stay longer, you will get sick! Go back with me first.
Get up.
You go back by yourself!
Are you out of your mind?
Go. Go.
I told you it was done!
It was burned out!
Calm down! Go back first!
- Don't touch me!
- Go!
Are you crazy?
Hello?
It's good to hear he is fine.
Do you want to talk to him?
No.
Don't tell him that I'm looking for him.
Drink this when it's hot. Don't catch a cold.
It's nothing. Just a time of failure.
Not one time.
This has been thousands of times.
So what?
You can start over at the worst.
I can't start over any more.
We ran out of money already.
What if you invest again?
Today's explosion has made the local headlines.
Think about it.
Who will be willing to invest in us?
Gu Xiaoling.
Gone.
[Outbreak of fire in one of Shanghai's battery lab]
Siyu, Director Gong is here.
What's your plan now?
Director Gong,
to be honest, I was also overwhelmed a couple of days ago,
I also thought about giving up.
I just used ten million to learn a lesson.
I understand.
If you decide, I respect that.
But Dubu project
is Professor Gao's whole life research.
So many people have paid for it.
It also includes your investment.
I also don't think that I should give up easily.
That's also right.
I think since we've done this much, we'd better not give up.
What if we think of a way to finance another round?
Let's delay the financing for a little while.
Right. We've prepared to pause the experiment now.
Professor Gao and I will need to go through the experiments,
including all the failed experiments.
After Professor Gao and Liu Yang's result come out,
we can discuss further the next plans.
How long do you need?
Three months.
Or half a year.
It's okay. This is how Professor Gao is like normally.
Director Gong, we will make it definitely.
So, please don't lose confidence in us.
Your investment will be paid back for sure.
Then I look forward to it.
Why don't I see Lei Haowen?
He was more heartbroken than all of us.
Why?
It's a long story.
Haowen,
what if we asked Liu Yang to play basketball together?
No interest.
How about this? I will buy you a few drinks.
What do you think?
Unless you drink with me until I die.
Otherwise, I will suffer more pain.
Cheer up, okay?
No.
Even if Dubu fails,
you still have Yiwen company.
I started up a business for her.
Now she is getting married.
Yiwen company doesn't mean anything to me.
You are both here.
Director Gong,
please sit.
Haowen. Haowen.
Unless we sell Yiwen company,
Then I will get ¥5,000,000. That will make some sense to me.
What are you talking about?
I see I can still earn some money from here.
You are going to sell it?
Director Gong,
I will sell all my shares of Yiwen to you.
¥5,000,000. Do you want it?
Director Gong, he is heartbroken and he is crazy now.
I'm not!
¥5,000,000. Do you want it?
Do you want it?
I found it!
Yes! I found it!
Great!
Everyone had so much hope for this research.
However, I didn't expect this result.
People say failure is common
but a bit hard to accept.
Then, what about you?
I'm all right.
The fact that Zhizhi and Yuwei didn't go to Europe already makes me so happy.
I can't be too greedy and have everything I want.
How is Siyu?
Except for Professor Gao, she's the strongest.
Professor Gao said that this explosion happened because the concentration of the battery was not enough.
If we fix the concentration issue, then we have hope.
I've heard enough of this kind of talk.
You say there are little problems every time.
Every time you say there's a breakthrough.
Every time, you say there's hope.
Every time, you're sure that this experiment will be successful.
But every time, it still fails.
This time, it's real.
Isn't it real every time?
Haowen?
Siyu also came?
Hi.
I'm trying to encourage Haowen to continue.
Okay. Then you two can talk.
As long as we try one more time...
I've been severely damaged by you repeating these words over and over again.
I don't want to hear those words again.
Besides, the ¥5,000,000 that Director Gong invested has all been used up.
We have no money.
Since we've already gotten this far, we have no reason to quit.
When others research batteries,
they spend billions.
We only had ¥10,000,000.
With ¥10,000,000, you expected to change the world? Stop dreaming.
Haowen.
I don't want to lie to myself.
Yiming, come play with me.
I'm coming.
Siyu,
how about we sell Xinlu?
Then we'll have no relationship with Dubu.
Xinlu is simply a dream.
Our investment into Dubu was unique with some shares.
It's worth nothing.
If it's worth nothing, then even if we wanted to sell it, it wouldn't sell for anything.
What if I can sell it for a good price?
Still no.
Why not?
Because Dubu will be successful.
Dubu will never be successful!
It will!
Siyu, sell it!
I'm the chairperson of Xinlu.
If I say I won't sell it, then we won't!
Wasn't the lab destroyed?
Why does Siyu still want to continue the research?
Only parts of it were destroyed. If we get another ¥1,000,000,
we can purchase some equipment and restart the research.
Do you have ¥1,000,000?
Let's not even talk about ¥1,000,000 right now.
We don't even have ¥1,000 right now.
Why did you come back to late today?
I had some things to do this evening.
I'll get it.
Oh, right.
Did you hear about what happened to Professor Gao's lab?
- It exploded, didn't it?
- Yes.
I heard about it.
Didn't you have a disagreement on share and price?
They are suffering defeat now.
I think maybe it's a good opportunity to buy it at a low price.
Investments aren't made according to price. They are made according to worth.
If it's worth it, then it can be invested in no matter how expensive.
But if it's not worth it, then no matter how cheap it is, we still cannot get involved.
We can safely say that their project is now completely worthless.
But I heard that they still have a lot of hope.
If they were to do one more experiment, there's a chance of success.
What they mean by "one more experiment"
is that it is their last gamble.
We cannot trust it at all.
Then if it's like this, I...
I want to sell my house.
In your name,
I will lend this money
to Li Siyu and help them continue the research.
What do you mean by this?
In the past, weren't Siyu and I together?
I don't want to see her lost, so I want to help her,
but I don't want others to misunderstand.
Thinking we have former affection between us.
I think giving her money under your name would be the best solution.
Also, she had a misunderstanding and some prejudice with you, right?
This time, we might
be able to revert back to your old relationship together.
Yiming,
you're so kind and considerate.
I wasn't wrong about you.
So you agree?
I can understand that you want to help Siyu.
The truth is that I also want to help her.
However, this kind of method is not helpful to her. In fact, it will harm her.
Why do you say that?
Professor Gao, Siyu, and I have interacted many times.
I understand that project very well.
Even though all reasoning points to the conclusion that this project cannot be successful,
they just won't accept it.
Professor Gao is such a stubborn person.
It's been around ten years, but he still cannot consider anyone else's suggestions.
Now, Siyu has been affected by him.
She is obsessed with this project.
Yes. The two of them indeed are very stubborn.
So my advice is...
that they do not need support right now.
Instead, they need to stop in order to prevent more losses.
They should stop?
You can't give them more money.
Doing that isn't helpful to them.
This will make them bogged down deeper and deeper into their obsession.
If you really want to help them, you need to coax them to give this project up.
Professor Gao can work in the lab I just bought,
and Siyu...
Doesn't she like starting businesses?
I can support her in other projects.
What do you think?
That's good, too.
The lab is only temporarily closed. Everyone can go home and rest for a while.
Professor Gao, Liu Yang, the other investors, and I
will surely not give up this project.
After Laidianle broke down, I lost everything.
But after less than a year, I stood up again.
So I believe
that this time, we will also be able to rise up.
Sister Siyu, now, everyone outside says that our project is fated to fail.
What would they possibly understand?
Exactly.
Why must we listen to
what outsiders have to say about our lives?
Our own lives are managed by ourselves. Whatever we say goes.
I know.
There are also many people saying that both Professor Gao and I are stubborn,
but we are just chasing after what we want.
Even if we are fated to fail,
then at least we once wholeheartedly believed that
we were once stubborn against all odds and worked hard.
Even if there are no results, at least I won't have any regrets in life.
You've worked hard.
Sister Siyu, as long as you call for us, we will return immediately.
Okay.
Please rest well in this time period.
You've worked hard.
Sister Siyu, we will wait for you.
- Wait for me.
- I will.
Sister Siyu.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Sister Siyu.
Is your mood a bit better?
It's okay.
A friend from the industrial and commercial bureau informed me that our Xinlu company's records there
lack some material. It needs the shareholder's signature.
What file?
Just some amendments to the articles of association.
They've been signed before. Just sign it.
I still want to read it.
Gu Xiaoling is getting her marriage certificate with He Mu next week.
If you should let go, then do it.
Can you let go of Yiming?
Yiming can't let go of you either.
When the two of us went out for a drink, he got drunk.
He kept reciting your name.
Here. Just sign it.
I will send it there first.
President Wang, the purchase of GB is finished.
Got it.
Li Siyu!
Thank you.
The passcode is your birthdate.
This was from Wang Ziru?
It had nothing to do with her.
This was my own will.
Where did you get that much money?
I sold that house.
Are you an idiot?
If you sell that house, it will be very hard to get it back!
But you need money.
Why did you do this?
Siyu,
ever since we first met,
- you were always—
- Stop right there.
Don't reminisce about the past.
Fine.
The truth is that I always had regret.
If back then, I supported your dream—
Don't talk to me about dreams.
Then let's talk about the present.
Presently, we have no relationship whatsoever.
We do.
When I had nowhere to go, you gave me ¥300,000.
I sold the house quickly and didn't make much money.
I paid back the loan of the bank and the relatives.
I only have ¥1,050,000 RMB.
It's all here.
You don't owe me.
Rest assured.
In the future, the two of us will have no connection whatsoever.
Chen Yiming.
Crazy.
Everyone is crazy.
Everything is crazy.
We have signed TS with FCC group.
Now we are just waiting for the accountant's audit report
and the due diligence report.
In the end, what was the price agreed upon?
Tianye Group will take 23% of Lubao's shares
and transfer them over to FCC Group.
The price is fifty billion.
That's wonderful!
We must drink some wine to celebrate this!
- We must drink.
- Yes.
President Wang.
Director Zeng,
Director Zeng.
Toast to the day we are rewarded.
Now it seems like the longest we'd have to wait is three months.
We can say goodbye to Lubao.
Yes.
After three months, when this fund quits,
we will continue the contract with you.
We will invest more money.
Thank you for your trust.
- Wish our cooperation to be happy and successful.
I hope we can continue the harvest.
Please come in.
Please sit.
You know Gao Zhengdao?
Yes. What's up?
We've succeeded!
The membrane-less battery!
A scientific feat!
From today on, we enter a generation of membrane-less batteries.
Membrane-less batteries will be unparalleled in the world!
From today on, it is realized!
The comments say
membrane-less batteries are on their way out.
Some people among them mentioned Lubao especially.
The companies with similar business with Lubao are very active in the comments section.
I reckon that the share price of them will drop tomorrow.
This will definitely draw FCC's attention.
This will also definitely
impact our plan.
It won't. Don't worry.
I'm prepared well for this old man.
His news won't interfere with our plan at all.
Since President Wang is so sure
then I don't have any other comments.
Okay! Let's wait for
President Wang's report after three months.
I won't let you two down for sure.
All right!
Cheers!
Liu Yang,
congratulations!
Why hasn't Haowen shown up?
Right.
Why should we be without him today?
The number you dialed is powered off.
His phone is powered off.
He has been in a bad mood recently.
It's about Gu Xiaoling getting married?
Yiming, Li Siyu told me to
propose a toast to you for her.
Thank you.
Where is she right now?
After Dubu's success was announced, she left.
She doesn't answer phone calls and reply to messages.
President Wang, cheers.
President Wang, I really admire you. Everything is in your control.
I just want to make sure that everything is absolutely safe.
When should I show my hand to them?
The faster the better.
I get it.
By the way, Director Gong,
didn't you say that they will have new progress in 3 to 6 months?
How did they make new progress so quickly?
I heard that Chen Yiming gave money to Li Siyu.
So they started the new experiment so quickly.
But luckily we had your overall arrangement early, President Wang.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫ The sky has finally cleared ♫