Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 11]
I‘ve finished the letter.
It's in both Chinese and English with one topic.
In order to provide a happy environment for kids to grow up in,
the school must persuade Doudou to quit.
- Have you gone back home?
- Socializing with the other parents
What's up?
Go on then.
Senior Brother.
You haven't left?
The newest development of three districts.
That quick?
Mr. Liu, you can give another two districts to me.
You've worked hard.
It's okay.
Is Xiao Zhao the "nail"?
I cross-examined several numbers and
I found that all the mistakes are in Xiao Zhao's part.
So I can conclude that he is the "nail."
Mr. Liu, what should we do next?
I will think it over.
Go home. I also need to leave.
Okay.
Doudou's mom apologized to me.
She said she decided to quit her job and stay at home to educate him.
She said that Doudou will definitely change for the better.
So shall we postpone handing in the letter?
No way.
I have already tolerated as much as I could.
This is not the first time that Doudou's parents apologized.
But does he change? We don't need to bother with them.
- That's right.
- But Doudou's mom is very sincere.
It doesn't matter.
I just feel if we force them to quit,
will it affect the boy psychologically?
You are so muddled.
You are able to think of the psychological impact on Doudou.
He is a little bully.
He a bully every day in school.
You have to think of the
psychological impact he has made on our kids.
I asked Yuwei.
Doudou is a bit naughty and he likes to tease others,
but he cannot be considered a bully.
Yes. Yes. My Linda told me as well.
She said that there are some good points to Doudou.
He would voluntarily help the teacher.
My William said that
he walks back and forth during classtime.
He distracts other kids from studying.
Yes. There is another time.
He blocked the toilet entrance, stopping other kids from going to the toilet.
Xingxing pissed his pants in the end.
You know what he did yesterday? He was even worse yesterday.
Doudou put an insect on Miao Miao's dress.
He scared Miao Miao so much that she cried.
That's right.
This is probably just mischief between kids.
If what our kids attend is a low-end kindergarten with the tuition of ¥1,000 per month,
then whatever happens is fine.
But we have spent so much money
to attend such a good kindergarten, what do we expect from it?
We just want our kids
to grow up peacefully and healthily, right?
Right. We can't tolerate any mistake in education.
Yes. Yes.
Yuwei's mom, if you want to be a good person,
we won't force you to do anything.
Anyway, I must make Doudou leave
in order to have a peaceful and healthy environment for my Miao Miao to grow up in.
I will sign first.
Yuwei's mom,
are you going to sign it...
or not?
Sign it.
All right.
Miao Miao will celebrate her birthday on the 20th.
We are preparing a big birthday party for her at the saddle club.
- Join us on that day.
- Sure.
William likes riding a horse the most.
Have William teach my Linda.
Sure.
Miaomiao really wants Yuwei to join.
Yuwei's mom, on that day, your little Yuwei,
will have time, won't she?
Yes, she is available.
Eat the cake. It's pretty delicious.
Yiming!
You finally came.
I just finished working.
I will get changed first.
- President Wang.
- See you, President Pan.
We'll walk you to the car.
- Please.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye, Siyu.
- Brother Yang.
- Siyu.
I love you, Yiming.
Having you keeping him company is great.
I just arrived as well.
Brother Yang,
I must bother you to play basketball more with Yiming during this period.
What's wrong?
He has really been down recently. He keeps saying that he wants some quiet time.
Then just stays at home alone.
I'm afraid if he continues staying at home,
he will be wasted.
It will be fine after he finds a job.
Yes.
I have to help him find a job as soon as possible,
Brother Yang,
how far have you gotten with the bidding?
The notice will be sent out next week. I'll let you know in advance.
Great. I already put it on record at my company,
so I am representing Lubao in this bidding.
When the time comes, don't give attention to anyone else.
What do you mean? Are there other people?
The competition in our company is getting more and more heated.
Zhizhi said...
someone played you once.
Not just once.
There are public tricks and hidden tricks.
Then, how did you evade it?
Why evade? I need to fight them head-on.
Some people are like mosquitoes.
The more you try to evade, the stronger they come at you.
If you just kill them right away, it becomes peaceful again.
You're correct.
Here.
During a situation like that, I couldn't not sign it,
but after signing it,
my conscience isn't letting me get over it.
- Well, you already signed it.
- True.
I also will get to see what an Equestrian Club looks like. It seems quite good.
The Old Wu from my work, who I've talked to you about before,
is getting more and more unreasonable.
Originally I had planned on letting him off the hook, but now I think I need to counterattack.
How do you plan to do that?
This birthday party is already at the equestrian club, what kind of present can we even bring?
Why must you put so much effort into the birthday of a six-year-old kid?
If you have the time for that, then think of a way to deal with Mom.
Xiaoling gave me an idea about it today.
Can we please talk about something serious?
Is Yuwei's situation not serious? Is having another child not something serious?
Xiaoling gave me an idea.
We can just tell your mom that you have become infertile.
Then your mom will stop.
Are you joking? If this got out, do I not want to save face?
Are you annoyed by your mom's nagging? We have to figure out a solution.
This is not the solution.
Then, what should we do?
It can't be my problem.
The birthday present can't be less than ¥500.
Go to sleep.
Here, Yuwei. Open your mouth. Eat some more.
After you finish, you'll grow as tall as your father.
Yang, I called your Second Aunt Liu last night.
- Which second aunt?
- The one who lives in the east of our house. The wife of that lame Liu.
When you were a baby, she even held you before.
Your second aunt calculated it,
and she said that it's because Yuwei's name is bad,
there's too much water. It repels the little brother.
(T/N The character "Yu" in Yuwei's name means rain.)
That's why you haven't had a son.
Mom, are you really that superstitious?
If you believe that, then my name has even more water. Do I have to change my name, too?
(T/N: the "Yang" in Liu Yang's name means ocean)
It has nothing to do with you.
It's Yuwei who has to change her name.
Dad, I'm not changing my name.
Yes, we won't change it.
How come you guys don't believe what I say?
Yang, in the past, you weren't like this.
Mom, I'm done eating.
What are you looking at? Hurry and eat.
Let's get a medical examination report.
You've thought it through?
Yes. I thought it through.
However, we have to say that there's something wrong with you, not me.
I don't want to lose face.
Fine.
Xiao Zhao...
Sit, sit.
I checked the data you were in charge of. It was very detailed.
It saved me a lot of work. Thanks for your work!
I'm especially busy these days,
and I'd like to trouble you with summarizing this file for me.
Finalize it into a formal bidding document.
Sure.
Thank you.
Come, just up this flight of stairs. It's this apartment here.
I told you I have many friends. It's all based on your requirements.
Here, let me give you the shoe covers.
Take a look.
If you don't like it, then we'll find another place.
Please come in.
Come in.
Take a look.
Here's the bathroom.
This is the kitchen.
An apartment with one living room and one bedroom now...
Look over here.
Look at the surrounding. It's very stylish.
It's very suitable for girls like you.
I looked at a bunch of apartments.
My friend said, "This one suits your girlfriend best."
Future girlfriend, I mean.
Take a look at the balcony.
This is the highlight.
Does it remind you of the Old Shanghai style?
This house is too old.
The house might be old, but the remodeling is new.
What's most important is the location.
This is in the city center but it's quite quiet for such a bustling area.
If it's so close to the metro, won't it be noisy?
Listen. Do you hear anything?
Do you know why? The flow of people from the metro station is northward.
This house is located south of the metro station.
But there is a snack street nearby.
People in and out, it'll be so noisy.
Having a snack street is great.
At night, when you're hungry, you can go and get a midnight snack.
- How convenient.
- Then won't I easily become fat?
You won't. I've already thought it through for you.
There are three gyms right over there.
There's a discount right now for memberships, too.
Is he the realtor or are you?
He is.
Come here.
- I'll introduce you.
- Miss Gu, what do you think?
Do you like it?
How much is it a month?
¥4500 per month and 2 months' rent as deposit.
- That expensive?
- It's not expensive.
Is he the realtor or are you?
- He is.
- Then shut up.
My old place was only ¥3,800.
W-Well, then ¥3800.
It's that easy? Then let me change my price. ¥3,500.
Wait, wait, wait.
You see, we have to have honor. Right?
If you said ¥3800, then it's ¥3800.
Do you take a commission in the middle?
God can bear witness. How can I take your commission?
Do I have a commission?
Then, why do you keep talking for him?
If you really don't believe me,
I'll give you my heart to show my sincerity. Here.
It stinks. Who wants to see that?
Miss Gu, then let's go to the office and sign the lease.
¥3500.
Brother, can't you step a step back?
For meaning's sake.
- Deal.
- Then can I move in tomorrow?
Once the lease is signed, I'll give you the key right away.
Okay. Deal!
As long as you like it. Take another look.
You really are something. A few words and I have to pay ¥500.
Bro, look at your girlfriend's appearance.
It would have been worth it even if it was ¥5,000 extra.
Go away, go away.
How is it?
- This bed—
- Don't touch my bed!
W-What? This bed is really
comfortable. Lie down.
Director, the new bidding document.
How was it? You won't have any more mistakes this time, right?
If there are any issues this time, I won't be able to face President Lu.
Okay. Leave it here. I'll look it over.
If there aren't any problems with it, I'll immediately hand it over to President Lu.
There definitely won't be any problems.
It's just that if we follow this proposal,
it will cost us over ¥8,000,000.
Liu Yang, what do you mean by that?
Director, the document in your hand
is the one that Xiao Zhao and Old Wu worked on.
I have another one here.
I, myself, verified all the data
to fix it.
The biggest difference between the two files is that
the first one has some sections done by Xiao Zhao and Old Wu,
so there is a very wasteful budget proposal;
while the other one doesn't have Xiao Zhao and Old Wu's contributions.
Look at this.
Yes.
This. Put this in the annex.
All right.
Let's eat lunch together. To celebrate.
Old Wu. Xiao Zhao. Director is looking for you.
- The braised pork you ordered.
- Thank you.
Let me tell you.
Director Wang didn't say anything in front of me.
But he transferred Old Wu to go retrieve and send files.
He transferred Xiao Zhao to reception.
I'm so happy to hear about it.
Oh right! Director Wang has agreed
to you joining my team officially so you can take part in the bidding project.
Really?
Then, does that mean I can learn real skills from you?
When the bidding is successfully over,
I'll personally go to Director Wang and have you officially stay on.
Thank you, Brother Yang.
I mean, Senior Brother.
Sorry, I don't know why I called you Brother Yang.
You can call me whatever you want to call me.
Then if I call you Brother Yang,
then don't you need to call me something different, too?
Then, from now on... I'll call you... Little Sister Yun.
Okay!
Here, Little Sister Yun.
This time, I have to thank you.
If it weren't for you, then I don't know how big of a trap I would have fallen in.
Oh, Brother Yang, what I did was nothing.
With your talent and skills,
those little people can't touch you.
But it's still bothersome.
Brother Yang, from now on,
I'll be in your care.
Is the news accurate?
My uncle works there.
He said they were making a bidding document already.
- How much is it?
- Over ¥20 million.
By how much are we ahead of Li Siyu's team?
Only ¥300,000.
Didn't we close a deal of ¥5,000,000 with Daneng Group?
We didn't get it.
Sister Yuan had been negotiating with them for more than three months.
They said they found a new supplier.
I haven't asked about the specifics of the situation.
Then we must get this project.
Yes, if we get this bid,
then Sister Yuan becoming Sales Director will be set in stone.
Ask your uncle who will be in charge of the bidding,
and I'll need to know his personality and hobbies so I can get to know him better.
Okay.
President Guo, it's so hard to make an appointment with you.
It took me so long to be able to finally meet with you.
Then, today, we must finish this bottle of wine, or else no one can leave!
President Guo, I've been having some problems with my stomach recently.
I don't dare to drink.
How about just one cup?
I'm really not lying. Let me show you.
My bag is full of medicine for my stomach.
Okay, okay. You won't drink.
I'll drink, okay?
- Next time.
- Excuse me, let me take this phone call.
Hello?
All right, I understand.
Pay special attention to that matter for me.
I don't care about education or age.
I just want talent.
Right. Okay.
Take care of it, please.
Bye.
President Guo, is your company looking to hire?
Our Publicity Department needs a director.
Then, should I recommend someone for you?
Great!
Pass it.
Kick it in.
Yes! Yes!
Almost. Almost.
It was too dangerous.
Yiming,
why are you drinking water? Drink alcohol!
I drove today, I can't drink today. I'll drink with you another time.
Hey, Yiming. How come I heard that you're looking for a job?
Fenglin Company is in need of a copywriting planner.
Are you interested? I can recommend you.
Do you know how to speak?
Yiming was a planning director before.
Now you're telling him to apply for a copywriter position. Is he out of his mind?
Doesn't it degrade him?
Don't listen to Haowen. I just want to take a break.
I don't want to think about applying to jobs at the moment.
- Okay, I got it.
- Thank you!
Cheers, guys!
Send me your newest resume.
Yes! Yes!
Drink!
?
Nice!
Quick, quick, I'm waiting for you!
[Chen Yiming's Resume - Sent]
What company is it?
What position?
President Guo, I've just sent the résumé to your phone.
I got it. I'll send it to our Human Resources director immediately.
President Gu, thank you.
A toast to you!
Didn't you say you can't drink?
I'm happy today so I must even if I can't.
Okay!
Sit, sit. Cheers.
[What company? What position?]
Where are you right now? Who are you with?
Little Sister, look. We've collaborated for so many years,
and you've always been so delightful.
That's why you are the Big Bro.
Our Director of Human Resources asked
if this Mr. Chen Yiming...
- can come to the company tomorrow to have an interview?
- He can.
No problem. What time tomorrow?
10:00 a.m.
I'll let him know right away.
President Guo, thank you so much.
I must make another toast to you!
There's no more.
How about we have another bottle?
- Another bottle!
- Waiter, one more bottle!
I'm going to go make a call.
President Guo, I'm going to take this call.
Waiter!
- Another bottle of wine.
- Got it.
- Hey, Siyu.
- Yiming, I have good news.
Go to the company tomorrow at 10:00 a.m. for an interview. I'll send you the address on WeChat.
Did you drink? Didn't you say you weren't going to drink today?
I have a lot of good news today.
I just signed a contract and found you a job!
Send me the address. I'll go pick you up right now.
Is this curable?
I have blocked fallopian tubes. It's incurable.
What if the doctor made a mistake...
This was diagnosed by the hospital's director. It can't be wrong.
I went with Zhizhi. This specialist is pretty famous.
We wouldn't have even been able to see him if we didn't know someone with connections.
- Mom!
Are you okay?
Let me take some time...
Mom!
This worked well.
I'm a bit worried now.
I'm worried that she can't take such a big disappointment.
I think she is a bit disappointed.
We should show her more concern.
Let Yuwei spend more time with her.
It will probably be fine.
Let's hope so.
- I'll help you.
- No, I'll help you. I'll help you.
- I'm fine.
- I'm fine. The car is there.
- The car's here. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- I'll help you.
Be careful. Walk slower.
President Guo, I'll be honest with you.
The Mr. Chen who's interviewing tomorrow
- is my boyfriend.
- Really?
He's really outstanding.
Otherwise, I wouldn't like him.
That's true. Let me tell you.
A guy that can hold onto someone like you
definitely wouldn't be someone ordinary.
You definitely won't regret it if you hire him.
How about this?
He doesn't have to do an interview.
Just tell him that he can come to the company tomorrow and directly complete the paperwork to be employed.
- Really?
- Really!
- President Guo, thank you so much!
- I have to thank you.
Don't worry,
- I definitely won't treat him badly.
- Thank you so much.
You don't have to be so polite to me.
I'm not being too polite to you. I'm worried that you drank too much.
All right then, just don't worry.
I'll help you watch him.
Thank you, Big Bro.
Okay, I'm leaving.
- I'm leaving.
- Be careful.
Yiming?
Why didn't you get here a minute earlier?
If you were a minute earlier, you could've met President Guo.
What's wrong? Smile a bit!
What's wrong?
Yiming. Yiming!
Can you give me a kiss?
Honey water.
Drink some honey water to alleviate the alcohol.
I got it done.
President Guo said that you don't have to interview.
You can go straight to work tomorrow.
Publicity Department Director.
It just so happens to be your profession.
I'm not going.
Why not?
Be safe, sit properly.
Yiming, you said that you want to take a pause, calm down,
and think it through. I support you.
But you can't think forever.
You can't just keep staying at home.
If you keep staying at home, you'll become a waste.
You have to go out. You have to go out and work.
I've already found a job.
You found a job?
Which company?
Fenglin Enterprise.
- Is the company big?
- It's okay.
What will you do there?
Copywriting planner.
President is offering you the Publicity Department Director position.
Even though his company isn't big,
but it's very stable in the industry.
- And last year it was labeled as China's top ten—
- Forget it.
I'm still going to Fenglin.
- Why?
- No reason.
Is it because...
your salary at Fenglin is really high?
Or the company's prospects are great?
It's not any of that.
Yiming, I don't really understand.
Any normal person would choose President Guo's company.
Then just consider me not normal.
What is it? Tell me the truth.
I don't want you to...
suffer because of me.
I didn't suffer.
I just drank a bottle of white wine with President Guo.
Are you unhappy because I drank with a client?
- I'm not that selfish.
- Then what's the reason?
You should still go to President Guo's company tomorrow. Tomorrow morning at 10:00.
I've already told you. I won't go.
You—
Are you done? If you're done then go and rest.
Why does it have to be like this?
Why must they treat me like this?
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫