Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 19]
- Sister Siyu.
- Hey.
Zhizhi, where are you going?
Sister Siyu, I'm here to ask for a leave. I have some things to take care of.
What things?
Heart bypass?
The results of the radiography say that coronary artery disease is very serious.
A big part of the artery is obstructed and needs surgery immediately.
How much would that cost?
The amount that I have to pay... isn't a small number.
Why is that?
Hey, Liu Yang.
What?!
All right, I'll be right there.
What happened?
Liu Yang's mom ran away from the hospital. I need to go find her.
Wait, wait, wait! I'll go with you. Let me go get my keys.
I was just going to give her an IV. She kept complaining she wanted to go home. She didn't want to do the surgery anymore.
I was just starting to persuade her. I turned around and she was gone.
What's going on with you family members? Why don't you guys accompany the patient?
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Mom!
She's not at the hospital. She's also not at home.
All right, you go to the train station and I'll go to the bus station.
Hello. Chengdudong, Sichuan.
Hello. Two tickets, please.
Sister Siyu!
[Train: G2193 To: Chengdudong]
Excuse me, I need to get through.
Thank you.
Mom! Mom!
Sorry.
Mom.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Do you know that you must still stay in the hospital?
I'm fine. I'm fine now.
What do you mean you are fine? You must get surgery immediately.
Come back with me.
Those doctors don't know anything. Don't listen to them scare people.
Mom, are you worried about the money?
Don't worry. I have enough money.
Yang, I overheard your phone calls.
I don't want to make it that difficult for you. I don't want to become your burden.
Mom, I have my ways.
What kind of ways do you have?
I'm really fine. I'm fine now. My body is strong.
Look, I'm completely fine. I can even jump. Look at me.
Why are you jumping? Mom, mom, mom!
Mom!
Mom, careful. Where's your medicine?
In my bag.
Do you feel a bit better?
Yeah.
Mom's fine. I'm fine.
Mom.
If something happens to you, what should I do?
Yang,
Mom knows of your hardships.
Mom doesn't want to become your burden.
Okay?
Mom,
I'm useless.
Stupid child.
You're great.
You're fine. Come on, let's get up. Send me off.
Mom.
Mom, don't worry.
Even if I go bankrupt, I will get your diseased cured.
Mom, don't cry. Let's go home.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Did he find her?
Yeah, Liu Yang is bringing his mom back to the hospital right now.
It's good that he found her.
Then I'll take you to the hospital.
Why do you think Liu Yang's mom suddenly ran away from the hospital?
It's because of the surgery costs.
Have you guys still not gotten enough?
We've borrowed from here and there, but we still don't have enough.
Zhizhi, why didn't you ask me?
Liu Yang said... that right now is not the right time to ask you.
Why?
He said that you are bidding.
Let's go.
I can go up there myself. You should go back to the company.
Then if you need anything, remember to contact me.
Okay, be careful on your way.
Is Mom okay?
She's temporarily stable.
Zhizhi, come out for a second.
Our house, can we get a mortgage loan?
The bank definitely won't give us a loan.
We can only ask outside companies, but...
the interest is too high.
I can't care too much about that. We need to get enough money for Mom's surgery.
Okay.
Hey, family of bed 34's patient, your surgery is scheduled for next Wednesday.
But we haven't paid for the surgery costs.
You guys paid. How else could we schedule the surgery?
Who paid?
I don't know about that.
Look, Li Siyu.
Such a big favor, how can we pay her back?
Mr. Liu, I put the report on your desk.
Brother Yang, why are you here?
I'm worried about work.
If there is no urgent work, just stay at the hospital with Aunt.
- I will call you if there is something.
- Okay.
How is Aunt?
She is good today.
But we can't delay the surgery anymore.
Oh, right.
What's this for?
Brother Yang, sorry, I don't have much money.
I only have ¥2,000. Just take it.
You are just an intern.
How much can you earn monthly? How can I take your money?
Even though it's not much,
you must take it.
This is my regard to Aunt.
I accept your kind regard but keep the money.
- Take it!
- No worries!
I collected enough money.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Zhizhi's cousin paid a part for us.
Welcome back home.
We have a bath tub!
The bedroom is pretty big.
Take a look at the living room.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
We finally have a home now.
Let's celebrate.
We don't need to be afraid of the rent increasing anymore.
We also don't need to worry that the landlord selling the house anymore.
From now on, we will be mortgage slaves.
We have finally become mortgage slaves.
The city is really quite magical.
It can instantly
make you proud and self-satisfied.
It can also, instantly,
make you feel like you are nothing.
In the one moment,
you thought the future was already at your fingertips.
In the next moment,
you may lose everything.
Why do you feel like that?
In these three months,
I felt like I was on a roller coaster.
Overnight,
an elite young man
becomes an unemployed person.
I was struck down
and rejected constantly.
When I lost all my confidence,
I got everything back suddenly.
Right now, I really feel
like everything's unreal.
I don't know which one is the real me.
I also don't know
if i can grasp onto
what I have now forever.
What?
- What are you doing?
- Come here.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Don't move.
♫  Your voice is light and soft  ♫
♫  Forms the love I want  ♫
The past, the present,
and in the future, I will be
in your palm all the time. You can always grasp me.
♫  The world suddenly became quiet  ♫
♫  As if someone pressed pause  ♫
♫ How much luck did I exchange ♫
♫ in order to meet you  ♫
♫  Your hair is fanned out in the wind  ♫
♫  That is the forest I want to be lost in  ♫
♫  It's the beautiful scenery that I want to go to  ♫
♫  It's all hidden in your eyes  ♫
♫  I want to give all of me to you  ♫
♫  Even my bad temper  ♫
♫  We're getting closer  ♫
♫ so let me fall in love ♫
♫  In this lifetime, I just want to tightly hold your hand  ♫
I think...
♫  As we slowly walk and slowly feel  ♫
that when we renovate the kitchen,
we must make it feel like a game.
Then when we wash dishes, we won't feel like we are doing housework but like playing a game instead.
Makes sense.
The study room...
needs to be in a night market style. That way,
when we work in the study,
there is an illusion that we are not working,
but strolling around the night market.
That also works. It can be considered some kind of psychological comfort.
Hey, I am more concerned with the bedroom.
I haven't thought about it.
Would it be... in an evil but charming style,
like me; or in old-fashioned style to suit you?
Old-fashioned?
No.
The impression that I left for you in the bedroom during these 5 years is "old-fashioned?"
Then would you be evil yet charming like me?
I think so.
Hey,
let's use your credit card for the renovation costs.
Why? Did you max out your card again?
You probably don't know.
Liu Yang's mom had a heart attack. She needs to get surgery urgently.
I paid a part of the surgery fee for them.
So I don't have any credit left.
I didn't know that. You didn't tell me.
How much of the surgery fee did you pay?
More than ¥30,000.
I was thinking,
if they can repay it then they should repay it. But if they can't,
then we just consider it as sponsoring them. You wouldn't be against it, right?
I, of course, wouldn't be against it.
What's up?
I remembered that you told me
you submitted a bid in Liu Yang's project, right?
- Yes.
- At what stage is the project right now?
These two things are not related at all.
I'm waiting for the result.
Don't wait for the result. Take the initiative to back out.
Why?
If you look at these two things together, it really seems like like you are bribing him.
I absolutely don't have that intention.
I know you don't have that intention.
But its hard to explain clearly to others when you are in such a suspicious circumstance.
I did this purely to help Zhizhi and Liu Yang!
Yes, it's because you want to help them,
so more reason why you should take the initiative to back out.
Why?
How come you don't understand? Think about it.
If they find out about the situation and it gets out, what are you going to do?
Liu Yang will get into a lot of trouble immediately.
Won't Zhizhi also get involved?
No one will know about this.
There is "no impermeable wall in this world."
(T/N: nothing can be a secret forever)
Chen Yiming,
are you saying this because you are Tianye Group?
What do you mean?
If I back out of this bid,
then ¥28,000,000 will be gone.
My President Pan will be in a disadvantageous position again with your President Wang.
In front of  your President Wang,
you would have another contribution.
Do you really see me that way?
It's not like you didn't do something similar before.
I admit...
I had my own selfish desires when I did that.
I wanted to quickly prove my worth.
But this time it's different.
I am really thinking about you
and Liu Yang.
How about this?
I will resign from Tianye.
I won't work there anymore. Will you trust me now?
Where are you going?
I'm going home to write my resignation letter right now.
You don't have to resign.
I trust you.
Siyu, I really am not joking.
I comply with you.
Back out immediately? Why?
I don't want my friend to be suspected of taking bribes.
You have a clear conscience. What are you afraid of?
But this situation is really hard to explain.
President Pan, we will still have a chance next time.
Li Siyu, we don't have another chance.
No way.
Right now, I'm negotiating with Wang Ziru.
I believe that Lubao is worth at least ¥4,000,000,000, but she doesn't think so.
You know about the report.
She believes that Lubao is only worth ¥3,000,000,000.
If you lose this government project,
then in her eyes, Lubao will probably only be worth ¥2,000,000,000.
But aren't there two other companies?
Two weeks ago,
both of them suddenly backed out for no reason.
Now, only Tianye Group is left.
I want to change how things are right now.
Lubao3 must be mass-produced,
but it needs an investment of at least ¥800,000,000.
Yet, the current company's shareholding structure
can only give up 20% of the shares at most.
That's why Lubao's valuation must not go down! This government project
must not be lost! We must win the bid. We must!
- But...
- Not only does this affect the future of Lubao,
but it also puts all of the livelihoods of Lubao's employees
and the dreams of the two of us on the line.
Brother Yang.
What?
Okay... I got it.
What happened?
President Pan, we won the bid.
What did I say? This is the result I wanted!
This is the result I wanted.
Xiao Ai, notify Tianye's President Wang immediately.
Tell her that I have time now and can meet her at any time. Any time.
Now let's see how Wang Ziru bargains with me.
Li Siyu, this time, I will reward you heavily.
I must reward you heavily.
President Pan, I'm still
- a little worried—
- Let me tell you, this news is worth at least ¥300,000,000.
It will allow me to open another lab.
I'll be able to start another production line!
Li Siyu.
We're going to make China's best power batteries!
We're going to make China's biggest new energy enterprise!
Just you wait. We will definitely
be able to get China's energy to drive civilization forward.
Definitely.
Doctor, these indexes are quite high. Is there a problem?
Doctor, these indexes of hers don't seem to be going down. Why is that?
It's mostly due to her old age. It would be more ideal if we used imported medicine,
but you guys requested to switch to domestically produced medicine
so the effects will happen slowly.
Thank you.
Liu Yang, what did the doctor say?
You have the nerve to ask.
Wha—
Mom.
Auntie, we came to visit you.
Auntie, we brought some things for you.
- Let me. We can put them here for now.
- Thank you.
- I'll put these here.
- Okay..
You came at the wrong time. I was about to leave.
So hasty?
It is because of your company.
We have a meeting today to confirm the purchase contract details.
Brother Yang, I know there are things that I can't make clear right now,
but trust me,
all the ways you've helped Lubao and me, I have taken them to heart.
Don't say that. I didn't do anything.
I get it.
Mom, rest well. I'm going to work for a meeting.
Go ahead.
I'm leaving then.
- Bye-bye.
Sit down, Honey.
Liu Yang.
Liu Yang!
What's with your attitude toward me just now?
Let me ask you. Why did you change the medicine?
What medicine?
How much of a cost difference is there between Chinese and foreign medicines?
You can't even bear to spend that little bit of extra money? That's my mom!
No!
Then, why did the medicine get changed?
I didn't say to change it.
The nurse's office wanted me to make a deposit. I asked if I can do it in a few days,
and they said that we could discuss it.
Discuss it?
Was the result of the discussion was to change the medicine?
I know that you and my mom have conflicts,
but she's already like this!
Can't you have a conscience?
How do I not have one?
Why would you say that I don't?
Then, why did you agree to let them take such measures?
Don't we have no money?
I asked you to come first thing in the morning to take care of Mom.
You didn't come until noon to come. Why?
I needed to go to work.
You couldn't take leave?
I've already taken leave three times this week! How could I ask again?
Why would it be so hard to ask?
An elementary kid could do your work1
Yes.
My work is not very important.
But I still get a few thousand a month.
I can't just give up those few thousand yuan.
Zhang Zhizhi, in terms of relations, you are Liu Family's daughter-in-law.
In terms of logic, you were the one who angered Mom so much that she's in this condition.
Thus, no matter what,
you should be the one who pays your filial piety at her bedside.
I have to go to work as I take care of our child,
I even have to bring soup and food. What more can I do to pay my filial piety?
What do you mean by those words?
Yes.
Yes, I'm the one who angered her into this condition, but she has had a heart problem for the last ten years.
That should have nothing to do with me, right?
You're absolutely unreasonable and hopeless.
Xiaoling's gallery is showing an exhibit these days, so she's very busy. She said she'll come visit you in a few days.
Okay, okay. Thank you.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Mom, is the height of the bed okay? Do you want me to make it higher?
No, it's fine this way.
It's fine.
It's okay. That's fine.
Yiming.
Yiming, wait for me!
Yiming!
Chen Yiming!
Are you mad about the bidding thing?
What do you think?
Didn't you promise me that you would back out of it?
It's not easy as you think it is.
It's you who made it complicated.
How did I make it complicated?
This doesn't just affect me. It also affects President Pan and the few hundred workers of Lubao.
This isn't something I can decide by myself.
Then what about Liu Yang? Have you thought about him?
I have. Liu Yang and I are clean.
I give him money because Zhizhi is my cousin. My conscience is clear.
This is your one side of the story.
But more people will think that this is a transfer of benefits.
The truth is that we don't have a transfer of benefits.
How are you so stubborn, Li Siyu? No one will believe your one side of the story.
How is it just one side of the story? Only you would think that!
Can you stop lying to yourself?
Let me ask you. If something really happens, what then?
How would others see you? They would think that you, Li Siyu,
would not care about her friends and play dirty, just for a better sales performance.
I would not care about my friends and play dirty?
I had many things that I could do to win, but I didn't do anything
because I believe in the quality of Lubao's products and the fairness of the bidding.
I can't just ruin Lubao's interests and Lubao's workers' livelihood
just because I want to prove that I'm innocent. Right?
Lubao won't be ruined.
As long as your President Pan isn't so eager for quick success.
Chen Yiming, just because someone doesn't play dirty doesn't mean he is eager for quick success.
Then, what about you?
Would you dare say that you are trying so hard to force us to back out isn't even a tiny bit for yourself?
I do dare.
What is there for you to dare say?
Did you forget that you just apologized for your own selfishness?
Importunate.
Currently, there are still some details that still need consulting.
If it's successful, then next week
we can officially sign the contract with the government.
Congratulations, President Pan.
After getting this government project,
there are a lot of friends in the financial circle
who have become interested in Lubao. This is very realistic. So, President Wang,
I cave easily with temptation.
You have to work harder.
Isn't that why I'm here?
All right, then let's just get down to business.
¥800,000,000, 20%.
¥500,000,000, 20%.
President Wang, if you can't even offer ¥800,000,000, then let's stop talking.
¥800,000,000 is okay, too. Then I want 30% equity.
Impossible.
Then, how much do you think is doable?
I can give you at most 21%.
President Pan, Lubao3 still has many problems that need to be resolved.
22%
President Pan,
compared with similar companies,
Lubao's estimated worth doesn't reach ¥4,000,000,000.
Also, Lubao isn't unique.
Lubao is unique.
22%
If you keep trying to bargain, then we don't need to discuss any further.
Only sellers with sincerity would keep bargaining.
29%.
President Wang, let me tell you the truth.
There are already some new funds investors who have contacted me.
My starting price was 18% for ¥800,000,000. They're very interested.
But a new negotiation would waste a lot of time.
So, I was willing to work with you again.
But if you only have this little sincerity,
then I don't mind starting over with new partners.
President Pan,
I will also tell you very responsibly that every fund negotiation is like this.
They all start off very sincere.
However, once you start to give up on other partners to negotiate with them,
they will start asking for more and more from you.
Then we won't negotiate.
Financing or not...
will not become the deciding factor between the life and death of Lubao anyways.
Worst comes to worst, I will have to work very hard for a few years.
28%.
22%!
22%.
This share offer will only be valid for 24 hours.
Otherwise, we will really end this negotiation.
Director Liang, I have an appointment with a client at 3:00 p.m.  It ends at 4:00 p.m. I will find you right after.
Okay. Then see you later.
Kuai Zi!
Yes! The file that was sent to us is downloading. I need three more minutes.
Are you still angry?
You haven't contacted me in a week.
You're courage seems to have grown.
Today, I will be off work before 10:00 p.m., let's talk?
Are you working overtime today?
Should we discuss this nicely?
President Wang.
Yiming.
What's wrong? Are you in a bad mood?
No.
Have you met Lubao's Pan Zhiyong before?
Yes.
According to your observation, what kind of person is he?
He is quite capable.
He has insight, courage, and is resolute.
However, he is also a little bit headstrong.
Then, do you think a person like that
would risk bluffing?
Well, that's hard to say.
He is quite unpredictable.
Later, I've asked a few people to come and discuss
the deadlock we have reached with Lubao.
Will you come?
Me?
It's not a formal meeting.
Then... Then in that case, I think it's best if I don't participate.
Okay.
Pan Zhiyong already told me that there are other financing companies that have contacted him.
This is very disadvantageous to us.
I found that one of Lubao's bank loans is about to expire.
This should help us a lot in our next negotiation with them.
That doesn't necessarily mean that they are in need of money though.
Could it be that Pan Zhiyong is bluffing?
Pan Zhiyong has the personality of a typical leader.
He might be a little bit headstrong,
but he definitely would not bluff.
I think that getting Pan Zhiyong to agree to raise from 20% to 22%
is already a huge breakthrough.
But our goal is to have at least 23%.
Should we reply with 25%?
Would that anger Pan Zhiyong enough to stop discussing with us entirely?
People with a leader type personality do not anger easily. They just fear being looked down upon.
Then we should insist on 23%.
But should we give them a little more valuation?
But I think that 22% is already their limit.
Otherwise, why would they give us a 24-hour limit?
President Wang, must we give a response within 24 hours?
Yes.
We only have 14 hours left.
You all can go back. I'll think about it.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫