Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 20]
Come in.
Director Li, Xiaoshi Group is asking for their order to be delivered earlier.
I remember that the contract we signed said that it was to be delivered next month.
Yes, but their production plan just changed, and they are hoping that we can cooperate.
What does the production group say?
I asked, but they said that there was no way they can produce that much in time.
Then give the merchandise originally for the General Group to them.
The General Group...  Are they not your clients?
Yes, they are my old friends, so I understand their situation.
They will be fine with a half a month delay.
Thank you, Director Li.
What's the situation with the Red Rose Electric Car?
We've been talking to their vice president for a month, but we haven't gotten any breakthroughs.
Wait a moment.
This is my analysis for the electric car market where I have also integrated Lubao's products.
Take a look and see if you can make a breakthrough from this angle.
This really is what I needed.
It's my treasure. Keep it a secret.
I got it. Thanks, Director Li.
Go work.
Sister Siyu.
In the past, I was worried that since I was a part of Sister Yuan's team,
that you would bully me when I start working for you.
But I really didn't expect that not only did you not mind, but you also went out of your way to help me.
In the past, I didn't see you as someone capable enough to serve, but now I do.
I was actually mentored by Sister Yuan.
Even though in the end, there were some misunderstandings,
but I remember how Sister Yuan helped me.
Everything I'm doing now was taught to me by Sister Yuan.
There are many areas in which you are similar to her.
Of course, there are also many areas where you two differ.
Oh, right. What has she been doing recently?
She opened a dining bar.
That seems like a huge difference.
She says that by opening a dining bar, her son can have a warm meal at any time,
and it's also very close to the school, so she can talk to the teachers easily.
Go work.
Be careful.
Try to find a thicker vein to stick into.
Didn't I say to find a thicker one?
How many times have you poked by now? How much blood have you spilled already? Are you capable?
What are you trying to turn my mom into?
I told you to do it lightly! Look, it's all swollen now.
You have already poked her three times.
I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
This family member, please calm down. If you have any problems, please let me know.
Please get me a different nurse for this.
This nurse has no issues with her technique.
She's new so she may be nervous. Could you please cooperate?
Okay, okay. I'll cooperate. More or less, it's the same. It doesn't hurt.
This is flesh! How could it not hurt?
Change the nurse for me. Change her right now.
Okay, okay. Please wait a moment. I'll get you a different nurse.
Let me take a look. She poked you three times. What was wrong with her?
It's fine. I'm really fine.
How could you be fine? She...
Zhizhi, look... During this period of time, you've been at the hospital, at work,
at home, taking care of the child, and me. You are tired, right?
I'm fine.
I'm such a burden to you.
Mom, let me get you some water and help you wash up.
No, no, no.
I haven't showered in many days. I smell horrible.
Do you think I will be ashamed of you?
No, I'm ashamed of myself.
Look... My mom died early. I didn't really get to take care of her.
I'll take this as making up for a missed opportunity.
When did your mother die?
When I was 19 years old.
Poor child.
In the past, I also bickered with her all the time.
So sometimes when I bickered with you, I hope you didn't take it personally.
I didn't.
That's enough. Don't be so busy. Sit down and talk to me.
Zhizhi,
your illness... don't give up.
There must be hope. Medical science is advancing now.
We can go to a large hospital and find great doctors. You can succeed.
Mom, have you not given up on having a grandson?
I can't give up on that. I can't.
Not only for our Liu family,
but it's also for you, silly girl.
Mom, it's not important whether it's a girl or a boy. It's filial piety that's most important.
Take a look at the auntie on the bed next to you. She has three sons,
but what's the use? They are all not filial. It would've been better if she didn't have them.
That's true.
This time, we couldn't get enough for the surgery.
It was my female cousin who took the initiative to pay what's left.
Your female cousin?
Female cousin...
In the past, I always heard Liu Yang talk about how his father passed early.
You were the one who singlehandedly brought him and his younger sister up.
If we're talking about capabilities, then how many of the males in your village could've possibly been more capable than you?
Mom, we're both also females.
Why would we look down on women?
Listen to what you say. I didn't say I looked down on women.
I just think that having a son makes me feel more at ease.
After getting sick, I have thought about a lot of things.
Say, once a person passes away,
that person can't control anything.
From now on, everything will be up to you guys.
Okay? Go do whatever you guys want to do.
Mom.
Zhizhi, in the past,
I did many things wrong.
Please don't take it to heart. Don't hate me.
What are you saying?
Where's Liu Yang?
I feel like each day, I barely even get to see his shadow.
He's busy with work.
- Work?
- Yes.
There are very many female colleagues in the workplace.
There are many young female colleagues as well.
He's always walking around with those little girls.
You... You need to be more concerned.
Mom, I trust Liu Yang. It's going to be all right.
- Let's wash up.
- All right. All right.
I heard that our superiors have already started to discuss about the candidates for the Deputy Director position.
If all goes well, then it will be you.
If I become the deputy director, then it will be partly because of you.
I didn't do anything!
You don't have to do anything. Just like this, staying by my side every day
makes me feel much less stressed.
Hey. What's wrong, Brother Yang?
Nothing. I think it's just low blood sugar.
Let's go over there and rest for a bit.
Be careful.
Brother Yang, you've gotten much skinnier these past two days. Are you really tired?
My mom is in the hospital and there's a lot to do at work.
How could I not be tired?
I really wish I could take care of your mom in your place.
The good thing is that in two days, she can be discharged.
Then I'll go visit her in these two days.
If I wait until she's discharged, I'll have no opportunity.
It's not suitable for me to go to your house to visit.
I've met her once and we chatted very happily.
Don't you want her to be a little happier?
All right then.
Write properly. Why are you randomly drawing again?
Check!
Okay, coming.
Write.
It's ¥53 in total. You are still missing ¥3.
That's not right. It should be ¥50.
It's ¥53.
This is ¥16, ¥14, and ¥20.
It's like this. These two dishes' prices were raised.
Just let it be ¥50.
I'm really sorry, but we are a small business so I can't do that.
Look, I come here to eat every single day.
You should at least give this little discount.
I can't give you a discount. ¥53.
I'm never coming here again.
Sister Yuan.
Why are you here?
I heard that you opened a dining bar and came to take a look.
Are you done looking? If you are, then leave.
I haven't eaten yet.
I want to order two-topping noodles.
They're sold out.
- Then spicy noodles would work, too.
- Don't have any.
Are you still angry at me?
I'm angry at myself. I married a bad husband and I made bad friends.
Sister Yuan, we've known each other for seven years.
Even though the last three months were extremely unpleasant,
but in the days before that,
we were always the best master and disciple; the best friends.
The last three months negate everything before that.
We both had faults in the last three months.
At least I wasn't the one who started the conflict.
Who let down whom the most, who hurt whom the most,
that's already no longer clear now.
Since it's not clear, we might as well just write it off.
The method you used to become the sales director hurt me,
yet now you're saying we should just forget it all?
Li Siyu, aren't you too greedy?
Sister Yuan, I didn't hurt you.
Let's wait for when I become the sales director again,
and then we can talk about writing it all off.
Sister Yuan!
I'm closing. Leave.
28%!
22%!
22%. This share offer
will only be valid within 24 hours.
Otherwise, I will really end the negotiation with you.
President Wang, is there anything else you need me to do?
No. You can go home.
Okay.
[Reading Area]
- You're still working overtime?
- President Wang.
It's time to get off work.
I still have a few e-mails. I'll get off work once I reply to them.
Have you not even eaten your dinner?
Once I got busy, I forgot about it.
I haven't eaten either. I'll treat you.
Oh, sure.
Then I'll clean up.
How about we call Siyu?
If she's available, we can eat together.
Siyu... Siyu is definitely going to work overtime today.
That's unfortunate.
I heard that the superiors have already started discussing about promoting Liu Yang to Deputy Director.
Mr. Wu, if you continue to not take action,
then you will have no chance in this lifetime.
Rest assured.
On the day they announce that Lubao won the bid,
I will have already made my move.
Then, how come there is still nothing going on?
It's coming.
Before you came, I had actually reached a deadlock with my negotiation with Lubao,
but your report on investigating Lubao3 not only broke the deadlock,
but also pushed the negotiation forward a huge step.
Then it looks like I'm still somewhat useful.
I should've treated you to this meal long ago to thank you for adding value to the company.
No, I need to thank you, President Wang, for providing me with such a great platform.
Thank you.
Yiming,
were you the one who wrote the newest work plan for the Planning Department?
Yes.
After reading it, I found some contradictions.
Tianye Group is kind of dull right now,
but your proposal
changes people's understanding of the traditional financial field.
Of course, if Tianye Group does not change,
then there wouldn't be great progress that can be made.
However, if we change completely according to your plan, it seems too risky.
GM Wang, this step seems risky, but it has huge benefits.
Most of the financial institutions in China right now
do not take brands into account when building strategic assets for marketing.
So whoever takes that step first,
will become the winner of the whole market.
You don't have to be so anxious in persuading me.
Let me think about it.
Sure.
However, there is one point that I'm certain of right now.
Putting you in the position of Planning Director
may have been a mistake.
With your talent, insight, and perspective,
you deserve to stand on a bigger platform.
President Wang, I will drink this.
Drink less.
Waiter,
please add a few more dishes.
No need, President Wang. This is enough.
There are a few dishes that Siyu really likes. Take them back for her.
There's really no need. Tonight—
Tonight, Siyu and I... will not meet tonight.
You won't meet?
If you guys are not meeting up, then you can deliver it to her.
There's really no need, President Wang. Siyu and I...
Actually, we haven't talked in a week.
Why?
I'm sorry. Is it something that I shouldn't have asked about?
No, no. I just think...
no matter how close of a relationship two people have together,
there are some problems
that are impossible to communicate about.
What exactly happened?
Siyu is very competitive and subjective.
I advise her that some things can be done while others should not be done.
There are some things that if she does, people will think that she is playing dirty to get a high sales performance,
but she...
She thinks that me advising her this is me being selfish.
That... That I have other motives.
Could it be that Pan Zhiyong is giving her too much pressure?
Yes. President Pan has put the finance, the sales performance,
and even the entire future of Lubao onto her shoulders.
The pressure she has is unimaginably large.
However... However, no matter how much pressure you have, you must have morals and limits.
I agree with that.
You don't need to be so anxious and don't force her. Just give her some time.
Siyu is such a smart girl. She'll understand.
I'm sorry, President Wang. Today, I drank too much so I talked a little too much.
Eat some food.
Okay.
Take care.
Thank you.
Do you really not need me to take you home?
No need, I'm fine.
Then I'm leaving now.
Okay.
See you at the company tomorrow.
I think we can respond to Pan Zhiyong now.
¥800 million and 25%?
No. He wouldn't let the negotiation fall through.
He really needs money right now. Yes.
His stress is way bigger than we had imagined.
Okay.
[Siyu]
Hello, I am Li Siyu from Lubao.
Hello, Mister Tang.
Compare data?
Okay, please wait a moment.
[Hengshan Rd. Station]
Hey, Manager Tang, I'll tell you now.
18650 is 10.4 watt-hour.
18650A is 11.2 watt-hour.
Our 21700 is
17.76 watt-hour.
Yes. That's settled then.
Then I'll contact you later.
Your leg hurts often, so I bought you this.
Wrap it like this.
Then, plug it in.
This way you can have a massage. It can even be heated.
- How much did this cost?
- Not much, a little over ¥300.
Over ¥300? That expensive?
I don't want it. I really don't want it.
When my leg hurts, I can just use my hand to massage it. Return it, we don't need to waste this money.
Really.
Put it on. It's not expensive. How does this count as expensive?
Before, Liu Yang gifted me a cup, that was expensive.
It was over ¥200.
I went to return it, but they just gave me a voucher.
I used the voucher and added ¥100 to buy this.
That's still over ¥300.
As long as your leg feels better, ¥300 is fine.
- Oh, you.
- Here, let's try it.
How is it? Is it hot yet?
It's hot now. It even shakes a little.
Auntie, Xiaoling and I are here to see you today.
- Oh, you guys came.
- Auntie, how are you now?
Better, I'm getting better and better. Thank you for coming to see me.
Bed 34, it's your turn.
- Get this off.
- Slowly.
Okay, you talk amongst yourselves. I have to go for a small exam.
- Do you want us to come with you?
- No need, the doctor will be with me.
Talk amongst yourselves. Let's go.
- Careful.
- Okay.
I'm going. You all chat.
Here, sit.
- She's recovered quite well.
- Yes.
Here, sit.
Sister Siyu, I'll talk to Liu Yang
about our mom's surgery fee. We'll pay it back to you in installments.
Aiyo, I don't urgently need it.
We'll talk about it once you guys are not so tight on money.
After my mom is discharged, you and Xiaoling should come over for dinner.
Bring Brother Yiming and your boyfriend.
Why have so many people over? Xiaoling and I are enough.
No, we definitely have to invite Brother Yiming.
I just don't know if inviting your boyfriend to my house is appropriate or not.
I'll ask Weixiang and see when he is available.
Did you have an argument with Chen Yiming again?
Why?
It's just a small issue.
How long have you been fighting for?
We've haven't talked for more than a week.
A small issue yet you haven't talked for more than a week?
Enough. Let's not talk about that.
Hey, Xiaoling. There's something I need you to help me do.
Let's talk about this first. You two are about to get married. Fighting like this isn't normal.
I'm begging you guys. Can we not talk about it?
Xiaoling,
I'm at work.
Are you coming to see me?
No...
You are suddenly being so nice to me. I'm not used to it.
Let's do this. At 12:45 p.m.,
wait for me at the company's entrance.
Don't be early or late.
Okay.
In a bit, I'll treat everyone to lunch.
Really? That's great!
- Is hairy crabs all right?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Thank you, Brother Lei.
You finally came. Did you know, these past few days,
your wife had to take care of me and Yuwei—
Mom, this is Xiao Wei from work.
Aunt, hello. I came to see you.
Come, sit down.
You guys are so busy at work, yet you still made a trip to see me.
No matter how busy I am, I still have to come and see you.
Auntie, your complexion is so good. It looks like you recovered well.
Auntie Qiao, have you seen this thing?
My daughter-in-law bought this for me.
My daughter-in-law treats me so well.
She feeds me this and that as well as buys me things.
A few days ago, my son bought my daughter-in-law a thermal mug.
It was over 200 RMB.
My daughter-in-law returned the thermal mug
and added 100 RMB to get this for me.
This thing, when you wrap it around your leg and plug it in,
it gets warm. It's very comfortable.
- This is called a massaging device.
- Oh, wow. That's hard to get.
- I also want one.
- Aunt,
I'll go wash you some fruit.
Why did you bring her here?
She has good intentions. She wanted to see you.
What is there to see? Aren't you afraid that you guys will bump into your wife?
Zhizhi is at work right now.
You... You better cut it off with her.
Mom, cut what off?
Cut what off? You're my son.
- Do you think I wouldn't know your thoughts?
- Mom,  you should rest—
Zhizhi is honest and sincere towards you.
But to save money,
she changed the imported medicine into domestic medicine. I can't forgive her.
I was the one who asked the doctor to change the medicine.
Don't you know how expensive imported medicine costs? You also can't get reimbursed.
- You were the one who asked for the change?
- That's right.
Zhizhi didn't know about it.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm telling you... Only being admitted into the hospital,
I realized how rare it is to find a wife like Zhizhi.
You need to cherish her.
Quickly break it off with this girl.
From now on, live your life with Zhizhi.
Mom, it's really not what you think.
What am I thinking of?
Break it off. You must break it off. Completely.
What? Do you want to anger me to death?
No, Mom.
Sit, sit, sit. I got it, I got it..
Auntie, eat some fruits.
Mom is a bit tired. How about this?
You go back first.
Auntie, rest well.
I'm leaving now.
Thanks for coming to see me.
- Look! A hot girl!
- What hot girl?
That's a goddess.
What's wrong, Brother Lei?
- Why did she wait there?
- Who?
Is she here for you?
Stop acting.
I don't believe that she knows you.
She really is my ex-girlfriend.
I told her that I didn't like her anymore, but she keeps clinging onto me.
We broke up months ago.
In a bit, I'll make a detour over there to get back to the company.
You guys help me. Say you didn't see me.
Haowen. Lei Haowen.
The crabs from lunch were good, next time...
So you were here?
Are you looking for me?
Obviously, who else would I be looking for?
Did you wait a long time?
What do you think?
The wind is big out here.
There's a coffee shop up ahead. We can talk as we walk.
Lead the way.
Got it.
Has Chen Yiming been acting strange recently?
- What are you doing?
- Taking pictures.
Stop it!
Look, Xiaoling. How come your lipstick is smudged?
Are you talking about Yiming? I haven't seen him in a while.
What's he been busy with?
Busy with work. Didn't he just join a company?
Say, they are at the stage of the relationship where they're about to get married, why would they fight like this?
Who said that you can't argue just because you are about to get married?
But not talking to each other for a week is too abnormal, right?
Then if the two of us fought, how long would be considered normal?
How could our relationship possibly be the same as theirs?
How is it not? Each relationship is between a male and female.
I will give you a task.
I will most definitely complete it.
Are you not going to ask what the task is?
I either have to sell my soul or devote myself to something. I'm good at both.
- Mom.
- Hey, you're here?
- How are you today?
- Give it to me.
Pretty good.
I stewed you some fish soup.
Do want to eat it now or later?
Later. I'm not hungry right now.
- Sit down and rest for a bit first. You're too tired.
- I'm fine.
Zhizhi, rest for a while. I can do it.
I even steamed a squab for you. It's said that it can heal heart problems.
Squab?
That can't be cheap, right?
Hey, did someone come and see you today?
What? Oh, a few of Liu Yang's colleagues came.
Oh.
I'll go wash the chopsticks and spoon for you.
Give them to me. I'll go.
See? Such a great wife. What else could you want?
Zhizhi,
the changing medicine thing had nothing to do with you. I wrongly blamed you.
Please don't be angry, all right? I was wrong.
I apologize.
All you know how to do is bully me.
How about this? Hit me a few times to release your anger.
Hello, Yayun?
Are you at work?
Please wait for me there after work. I have to talk to you about something.
Brother Yang?
What's wrong with your foot?
It kind of hurts. I'm guessing it's because I've walked too much these days.
Then I'll go buy you some medicinal patches.
No need.
Yayun,
I have something to tell you.
Wait.
I have a present for you.
What?
I knitted this myself.
I also embroidered this myself.
For me?
What do you think?
I'll tie it for you.
It suits you quite well.
I stayed up for several nights.
You could have just bought one.
Things like this cost so much time and effort.
No. I want to knit it thread by thread
and embroider it stitch one-by-one. This way, it has meaning.
When it starts to get windy, wear it.
Okay.
How come Yiming is still not here yet?
- I'm here.
- What took you so long?
You're so anxious. Isn't there no ballgame today?
We can't sit together without a ballgame?
Could it be that we are brothers only on the surface?
Liu Yang's mom is still in the hospital. I really have been quite busy these days.
You've already come, so you might as well sit with us.
Look.
Who is the real sweet guy?
Liu Yang, how's your mom's condition?
She's already been discharged. She's planning to go back to our hometown to rest in a few days.
That's good.
Let's talk about you.
Thank you.
What happened between you and Siyu?
How did you know?
What's my relationship with Gu Xiaoling right now?
Liu Yang,
there is a serious problem with what Li Siyu did.
What problem?
In order to avoid suspicion, she should have backed out of the bid.
Yiming, you are overthinking.
Although I'm the team leader of the bidding, what I do is a supportive job.
The experts decide. When they evaluate, I can only stand at the door. I can't even enter the room.
But the risk is still very large.
At my workplace, there is risk everywhere.
Unless you are unselfish and have no desire.
I think you shouldn't blame Siyu anymore.
I need to thank her for paying my mom's hospitalization expenses.
I understand now. If you argued with Siyu about this,
since Liu Yang has declared his opinion,
then just let it go.
I think she shouldn't have done things in that way.
Why not?
Yiming, you are good at a lot of things but you are too fussy.
It's such a small issue yet you are making it such a big deal.
What are you talking about?
Did I say it wrong? Think more about Siyu's good qualities.
She's been with you for so many years.
Has she ever spent your money?
She cries with you, laughs with you. She has fun with you.
She even repays the mortgage with you
and pays the down payment with you. There not many good girls like Siyu nowadays.
Those are two different things.
How? This is one thing.
We can't let Siyu, such a good girl—
How-How did it become "we"?
Huh?
You, you, you, you.
Take the initiative to make peace. Then, you can start your happy life together.
I can also give Xiaoling an explanation on my end.
I will tell her that you don't have a mistress.
You don't have the seven-year itch. You don't have a marriage phobia.
It's just your regular fussy self.
Wait.
They suspect that I have a mistress?
Look at yourself. You haven't been normal recently.
Their imagination is too rich.
Women.
Haowen, did they talk about me?
You? No.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫