Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 29]
Twenty years ago, I quit my job to start up my own business.
Everyone said that I was crazy.
Fourteen years ago, I invested all my money into the research and development of Lubao1.
You all said that I was crazy once again.
Within five years, I insisted that Lubao must be transformed and upgraded.
You all still said that I was crazy.
Reality proves that I am not crazy and that I succeeded.
President Pan,
the market before is different from the current one.
But courage and insight
are never irrelevant in any era, right?
President Pan, cautiousness is also something that doesn't become outdated.
President Wang, that is a requirement of the financial industry you're in.
For us industrialists, we only have one way,
that is pressing forward with an indomitable will.
With all due respect, there are many ways to make Lubao great,
yet you chose the dumbest and riskiest way.
But it's the most effective one.
Wait five years before making any money?
It's too slow.
President Wang,
if you want to make money quickly, you shouldn't have invested in Lubao at the beginning.
Because the original goal of creating Lubao,
is not to make money but to make history!
It's settled! The next step for Lubao
is to create another industrial zone and another production line!
I object.
Invalid objection.
Whether the objection is valid or invalid, let's vote by a show of hands.
Very well.
If you agree to creating another
two production lines for Lubao3, please raise your hand.
4 votes.
Fang Zhan, are you abstaining?
I vote to object.
I object.
Five votes of objection.
Since the result is out, let's discuss the next thing on the agenda.
Let's discuss President Wang's proposal to revise our business layout and create a concept for the future.
First, let's have President Wang to introduce the context of the proposal to us.
Okay.
Chairman, every board director—
There's no need for an introduction.
I object. According to the company's rules,
when the board of directors
is discussing important issues, the chairman doesn't have the ultimate decision-making power
but he has the right to veto.
For over ten years, I have never used this right.
But I decided to use it today.
Moreover, I will use it often from now on!
I have finally seen Pan Zhiyong's forceful way of ruling today.
This is his style.
Don't make any money in the next five years? I can't believe that he said that!
Making money has never been Pan Zhiyong's priority.
But as an investor,
my money didn't come to me from nowhere! (T/N: lit. the wind didn't blow money to me)
I have countless limited partners behind me!
They have certain performance requirements for me!
Does Lubao really have such a rule?
Yes.
It was created when the company was founded.
But we have never used it so I almost forgot about it.
Can we change it?
That would be very difficult.
You have worked with Pan Zhiyong for over 10 years,
do you have any methods that can be used to persuade him?
That's basically impossible.
He is very stubborn. Once he has made a decision,
nobody can stop him.
What a coincidence.
There is also no one who can stop me from doing what I want to do.
What's up?
What are you looking at that you must hide?
I asked, what's up?
I came to hand in my homework.
Go away!
For once, you are reliable.
That's it?
What else do you want?
No salary increase?
Didn't you just want a job with a low salary?
Why are you asking for a salary increase?
Well... the premise of a low salary is little work.
How much work have you assigned me recently?
Yes,
you did promise me that I could come in late and leave early. I left at 3:00 p.m.
But at 11:30 p.m. at night, you still sent voice messages to me in regards to work.
Why shouldn't I ask for a salary increase?
Rest assured.
Once Laidianle launches online, you will get the reward you deserve.
You better keep your word.
Why aren't you leaving yet?
I think you should give me a few more praises.
Your performance has been well recently.
Continue to do so.
Older Sister President Li,
you haven't been scolding people as much as before.
Your performance has been well recently. Continue to do so.
That's all for today.
The meeting is over.
Chen Yiming, stay.
Go somewhere with me.
You don't need to take that.
Okay.
President Wang, where are we going?
President Wang, I think you should tell me in advance so I am prepared.
Get into the car.
Oh, Sister Ziru, you're here. How can I help you today?
Today, it's not me but he who needs a haircut.
Come here. Help this gentlemen wash his hair.
- President Wang, I—
- Go on.
Hello, this way please.
Go.
This way to wash your hair.
Watch the steps, please.
It's not too tight, right?
This is fine.
How would you like to have your hair cut today?
You decide. I'm fine with anything.
All done.
This is the Chen Yiming who wants to overturn the brand strategy of Tianye Group.
This is the deputy director that I look fondly upon.
Miss Gu.
Thank you.
The crepe here is quite delicious.
To be honest, it's just okay.
Our family used to have a chef who made desserts
that were amazing.
So are you still able to eat that chef's desserts nowadays?
If I want to eat them, I'd have to go to France.
He is from Marseilles. He went back after he retired.
I quite like France.
I don't like it.
The overall feel of Europe right now
is that it has fallen behind.
If my family didn't do business there, then I would never go there.
Then, where's your favorite place?
To be honest,
when I left the country at age 18, I was very unwilling.
What I like most are the Han and Tang dynasties.
(T/N: Han and Tang Dynasty are considered as the most prosperous dynasties in China.)
Those are what you would call magnificent.
What year did you go abroad?
In the year 1986.
That year you... were 18?
I'm 51 years old this year.
Is the proposal that I want done?
No.
Tonight, before 12:00, you must send it to me.
Then I'll wait till 2:00 in the morning for you to finish it.
If at 2:00 a.m., you still can't turn it in to me,
then I will drive to your house and hit you in the middle of the night.
Let me bother you for five minutes.
Today, I met a guy.
Out of all the men I've met in the past six months, he has the best conditions.
What category does he belong in?
He belongs to the category of "born with a good life"
and "social climber." We added each other's WeChat.
In my experience,
we should exchange at least a few words on WeChat after the date,
but after the date, he hasn't sent any messages.
He doesn't like you then.
There's no way. We had a really good conversation at dinner.
If you think you have a chance with him,
and he doesn't contact you, then you contact him.
That... would that make me seem like I have no self-restraint?
From a sales perspective,
it is never wrong to take initiative.
Have...
you...
slept yet?
What are you doing?
This bastard deleted me!
What happened?
Are you laughing at me? You're laughing at me! He deleted me and you're laughing! What's wrong with you?!
He doesn't like you!
How is that possible? I'm so good-looking, how could he not like me?
Ms. Gu, hello.
Where is Sister Zhou?
Hi, Ms. Gu, I'm here.
Sister Zhou, is number 57 whom you introduced to me a swindler?
What kind of nonsense is that? Did you have some kind of misunderstanding?
Here, don't be too anxious yet. Let's sit over there and talk about it.
Let's go.
Bring me the iPad.
Thank you, Sister Zhou. We're leaving now.
Wish you guys happiness! Bye.
Sit here, sit here, sit here.
Let's take a look.
The number 57 you mentioned...
Is it this Mr. Zhao?
Yes. It's him.
You guys went out on a date?
Yes.
When we met up, we got along pretty well, but the second we separated, he blocked me.
Say, doesn't this kind of action mean that he is a swindler?
How can he possibly be a swindler?
Then that makes no sense.
We even made plans to go to the Arctic Pole to see penguins together.
Two hours later, I couldn't contact him in any way.
It is pretty strange. How about this? Don't panic just yet. I'll ask for you.
I'm sure there's some sort of misunderstanding.
Fine. Turn on the speaker.
All right. No problem.
Hello, I'm Jerry.
Hello, are you Mr. Zhao?
I'm  Miss Zhou from the "Turns Out to be You" Club.
Oh, Miss Zhou. What's the matter?
Oh, it's like this.
I want to collect some feedback from you.
When you and Ms. Gu met,
did you have good feelings?
She's quite pretty. We got along pretty well.
Do you think there is a chance that you two would further develop the relationship?
I think being friends is okay.
As for marriage, she seems a little old.
You feel that she's too old?
I prefer girls under the age of 25.
I didn't even mind that you're too old! I—
- Ms. Gu.
- Please give me a moment to calm down.
Ms. Gu. Drink some tea. Don't be angry.
How old do I look to you?
26. At most 26.
Let's do this.
I have a 58-year-old professor with over ¥100 million in assets I can introduce to you.
His conditions are very good, and he likes women like you, around age 30.
He should be able to—
Have I gotten to the point where only old men will like me?
Ms. Gu. You know this,
a woman's age is inversely proportional to her value.
For men, age doesn't matter as much.
You just said I look to be at most 26 years old.
No matter how good you preserve yourself,
your ID is still there.
- This one is nice. I want this one. Send it to me, send it to me.
- Sure.
I will send it to you.
Yeah. Yeah...
[Do you want to know the secret to eternal youth?]
[Caijin Company]
Come pick me up.
I knew something good would happen today.
Did you win the lottery or buy new stocks?
The things you say,
so vulgar.
Then, what's the good thing that is happening?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
I'm leaving. Cover up for me if the boss comes over here.
Bye-bye.
Don't be afraid! I'm here to save you.
Aren't you being a bit dramatic?
It's rare of you to twist an ankle, can't I cherish this moment for a bit?
What are you saying?
Look.  Which do you like?
Put the ice pack on it first.
Give me your foot. Slowly.
How did you sprain it? It looks so severe. Does it hurt?
It hurts!
What are you doing?
Bare with me.
Endure it, endure it.
Mommy! Butterfly!
Yuwei! Yuwei, don't move! No! Yuwei!
I'll help you catch the butterfly, okay? Don't move!
You can't catch butterflies like this ever again, got it?
What did you go out to do?
I went to buy groceries.
How could you leave Yuwei home all alone?
You didn't even close the window! An accident almost happened!
It was just the market downstairs. I figured I would be back in five minutes.
Even if it's only five minutes, that's not okay!
She's so small and full of energy! She also doesn't know what dangerous is!
You can't tear your gaze from her for even five seconds!
Also, the downstairs market's
vegetables cost ¥0.50 more than the vegetables at the farmer's market!
The cost of scallion, ginger, and garlic are double there!
If you don't know how to buy things, then don't buy them from now on!
Yuwei, you can't climb that high again, do you understand?
It's very dangerous.
Daddy is so pitiful.
Why are you saying that?
You scolded Daddy, and Daddy didn't say a single thing.
Here. Put on your shoes.
Go play in your room, okay?
My tone of voice was a little too harsh just now.
There's something I need to tell you.
There is a Fangcao Kindergarten in the Changsheng Community.
I'm planning on transferring Yuwei there.
I know that kindergarten. It's a lot worse than Lantian Kindergarten.
Their facilities are a bit worse
but the tuition is half of the other.
Zhizhi,
I was opposed to you sending Yuwei to Jinguduo Kindergarten
was because the people there were in a much higher social class than us,
but isn't this Fangcao Kindergarten
a little too low for our social class?
Before, we weren't good enough for Jinguduo
and now we can't even afford Lantian.
Except for Fangcao, we don't have any other choices.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault,
but I still...
worry that if Yuwei goes, she won't be used to it.
She will eventually get used to it.
Zhizhi.
During this period of time, you've worked hard.
Didn't the old Chinese medicine doctor tell you to avoid certain foods?
You are nagging so much.
Can you drink less?
Drink it!
Can't you drink less?
Pour it for me!
- Don't drink so much!
- Pour!
Pour. I'll pour it.
You're going to drink to your death. Come on! Drink up!
Lei Haowen,
I'm going to ask you something and you must answer me honestly.
Giving you an honest answer depends on the method of torture you will use on me.
Pepper spray and torture-rack don't work on me.
If you use seduction,
I will give in and answer you honestly. I will also give in to your seduction.
Say, how old do I look?
If you stop drinking, I will tell you.
If I say that you look like you're 18 years old,
it seems like I have ulterior motives for you.
If I say you are 26 years old,
it seems like I am jealous of you and depreciate you.
So to be transparent and fair,
you are 24 years old.
I'm young and pretty, yet why
am I still not married?
Perhaps, the one who you are fated to be with has not appeared yet.
When will the fated one appear then?
There is another possibility. The fated one has appeared.
But you haven't realized it.
Stop drinking!
- What are you doing?
- Stop drinking!
You aren't listening to me! Gu Xiaoling!
Nobody wants to marry me anyway! Why did you take my beer?
Gu Xiaoling, can you please have some pride?
Didn't you say that you wanted to fight for 10 more years? How long is it has just been?
What's wrong? What do you want to do?
Don't put your face on the table. It's dirty.
Get up. Get up.
Fight for another 10 years?
Fight for another 10 years then I will be 40 years old.
It'll be even harder for me to get married!
The table is dirty.
Get up to talk, okay?
If you want to get married, wouldn't it be easy?
Stop crying.
I don't like any of the people who like me.
All the people I like don't like me.
Stop crying.
If you keep crying, you won't be beautiful.
Don't cry, okay?
If you continue to cry, I-I...
I will take ugly pictures of you and make them into memes.
I'll post them on my Wechat moments. My goodness, look here!
Lei Haowen, you dare?
You will see if I dare or not! I'm taking the picture!
You think if you turn around I can't take pictures? Keep crying. I'll take more.
From all angles.
This angle. Cry, cry. Continue to cry.
Unless you promise me you'll stop crying. Here, take a selfie.
Hey! Y-y-you, sit down.
Only if you promise to stop crying.
Sit down.
That's right. Don't cry. Let's eat, okay?
Don't cry anymore, okay? Here, I'll get you some vegetables.
Lately, I have been really frustrated.
Really frustrated?
Lately, I have been really, really, really frustrated.
Yes, very frustrated. Very frustrated.
Ugh, I want-I want to find a boyfriend.
I want to get married!
God!
Please find her a boyfriend! Don't let her go crazy!
God! Where is my man! Give him to me quickly!
I want... I want to eat this!
This?
Up there!
Okay, no problem. I'll help you pick them.
Which one?
Up there. That one.
- This one?
- Yes.
- Are you okay, Xiaoling?
- Lei Haowen, hurry and come pick me up.
Come bite me, come bite me.
How come there's another one?
Lei Haowen! You heartless asshole!
- Come, come, come. There's more than one dog. Come on, I'll carry you.
- Hurry, come here!
Lei Haowen, my crutches! Hurry, hurry!
Run! Run quickly!
How is it? Did the three dogs follow us?
No. They didn't follow us.
I'm so tired. So tired, so tired.
Why are you laughing?
My mood suddenly became better.
Say,
I asked god for a man.
Why did he give me some cherries?
Cherries are good.
In Chinese traditional culture,
cherry means "cherish the people who are in front of you."
Is that true?
Of course, it's true.
Even Confusious
once said, cherry
represents tying the knot with a man.
It's known to be propriety, justice, honesty, and honor.
Stop the nonsense.
Really! Really.
Really!
Keep the show on your good foot to use.
Stop being so noisy!
Liu Yuwei's  mom,
the financial department informed us that they haven't received Liu Yuwei's living expenses for next season.
Please pay as soon as possible so her schooling won't get affected.
Manager Hu, is there a chance I can switch to another position?
I don't want to go to this kindergarten. I want to go to the original one!
Yuwei, be good. This one is also good.
I don't want to! I don't want to!
I want Teacher Dai and Teacher Liu. I want to play with Susan.
I want to play with Xiaoxiao and Older Brother Haohao.
Yuwei, be good! This kindergarten also has many good teachers.
It also has many other good kids!
Yuwei, be good! If you don't go inside, I'm going to be late.
I don't want to! I don't want to!
Teacher, what should we do?
All kids are like this on their first day of kindergarten.
It depends on whether the parents can walk away or not.
Come on.
Mom! Do you not want me anymore?!
Don't leave me!
Mom, don't leave me!
Hello, President Wang?
Yiming, are you at the company?
Yes, I'm here.
I'm in my office.
I have a problem. You're the only one who can help me out.
Okay. I'll go up there right away.
Great.
The files in here are all very important.
If I ask anyone else to fix it, I won't be at ease.
Let me try to insert this memory bank again.
Why exactly won't the computer turn on?
I just checked. There are no problems with the memory bank and mainboard.
Perhaps it's the system.
It was working fine yesterday...
It's fixed!
I didn't plug in the charger correctly?
I think so.
It's fixed.
Am I really stupid?
If you're stupid, then this world does not have smart people.
Don't tell anyone else about this.
This is a little secret between us.
I won't. I definitely will not tell anyone else.
Don't lie to me.
We clearly sold ¥20 million, but you want me to write it as ¥100 million, is—
Director Fang. Director Yuan. I'm leaving.
Bye-bye.
Isn't that falsifying information?
This is not falsifying information. This is called creating data.
Pan Zhiyong will not agree with us doing this.
This is a decision I made with President Wang.
Which President Wang?
She's an expert in this area.
But right now, Sales is managed by Pan Zhiyong.
He checks the report every day. He also comes to my office to ask me.
If there are any differences, we will not be able to keep them a secret from him.
Then we'll make two versions.
One will be for him to see, and the other will be for us to use.
This...
This type of thing... I've never done it before.
This concerns your own interest as well.
You will get your equity very soon. If Lubao's valuation increases,
your assets will also increase accordingly.
Xiaoling said that Siyu's company will be launching online next Monday.
She always feels like there is a wolf chasing her.
Xiaoling also tries to persuade her to not wear herself out.
Of course, she can't be persuaded.
Gu Xiaoling has recently been very hurt by her blind dates.
Do you think I should take advantage of the situation right now and swoop in?
Lei Haowen, if you're looking to die, then go ahead. I'm not going to stop you.
Quick, greet your uncles.
Yuwei, how come you came?
Do you miss me?
Zhizhi said that she had to go out, so I offered to take care of Yuwei,
but you guys suddenly asked to meet up and I really wanted to see you guys.
Isn't this place not very suitable for children? How about we go somewhere else instead?
It's no problem, I'm friends with the boss here.
Yuwei, Uncle will order a juice for you. Okay?
Sit.
Has Yuwei gotten used to her new kindergarten yet?
For the past two days, she's stopped crying,
but I can clearly feel
that she's very unhappy.
Well, how are the people at the new kindergarten?
They're all right.
At the time, I really should have listened to you.
If I had switched positions and gained some professional skill,
then I wouldn't have to let Yuwei suffer so much right now.
You were not confident at the time.
Thinking about it now,
I was actually just lazy.
I always felt that as long as I had Liu Yang to rely on,
I would be able to live life no matter what happened.
Who would have known that
Liu Yang is unreliable at times
and that
it would be so hard to get by each day.
In this world,
you can't rely on anybody but yourself.
How are you and Liu Yang?
All right.
The other day,
he suddenly said sorry to me.
He also said "you've worked hard" to me.
Say, we've been together for so many years
and he has never spoken like that to me.
Now when we are almost divorced,
he suddenly said that to me.
I really don't know
if I should feel happy or helpless.
I can only say, people will change.
That's right. People must change.
All people will grow old.
Why are you so sentimental?
I'm not. I don't have time for that.
I've been racking my brain thinking of better ways
to hold onto the person who I want.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫