Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 45]
Who is it?
You sold the house?
Yeah.
You still gave money to Li Siyu?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you not to do that?!
I felt like I should do that.
I treat you so well!
Why do you have to go against me?!
I didn't.
Do you still love her?
The person I love is you.
Then, why did you sell your only house
to support her?!
I just felt guilty towards her.
Okay. You go be guilty then.
Ziru.
President Wang has already left.
I want to see you.
Director Gong.
Would you like to drink something? Tea or water?
No, thank you.
Are you the only one here?
Professor Gao and Liu Yang went to see the factory.
They entrusted me to represent them.
Okay.
However, I can't seem to get in touch with Haowen.
It doesn't matter if he is here or not.
Lei Haowen is also a shareholder of Dubu.
He should be here, right?
He is no longer one.
What do you mean?
I called everyone here today because I wanted to announce that
Dubu Project's subsequent research is going to be put on pause.
At the same time, mass production will be stopped.
Director Gong, do you know what you are saying right now?
What you heard is what I want to say.
Why do you think you can do this?
I'm the largest shareholder of this project right now.
Your Huangjin Investment only possesses 49% of the shares.
Xinlu Investment, Professor Gao and Liu Yang,
together hold the majority of the shares, 51%.
Director Gong,
in Dubu's project, you don't have the right to decide.
Ms. Li,
did you forget
that Lei Haowen and you have sold Xinlu Investments to me?
What?
In addition, all of Xinlu Investment's Dubu shares were transferred to Huangjin Investment.
Xinlu's 6.63% plus Huangjin's 49%
equals 55.63% in total.
Sorry,
I make the decisions for this project now.
I never signed this contract.
Do you not recognize your own signature?
[Your account ending in 4823 has received a transfer from Lei Haowen of ¥6,000,000.]
What material?
Some amendments to the articles.
We have already signed them. You can just sign it.
Here. Just sign it first.
Lei Haowen.
He won't pick up your call.
You bribed him?
You are also one of the investors.
How does stopping Dubu's research benefit you?
This is our largest shareholder's decision.
You just need to comply with it.
Who?
I can't tell you.
When she walks over there, the lights here need to be turned on and you guys need to start playing the music.
Okay. Okay.
Also, the music should be slow. Don't rush it.
Play the music according to the pace at which she's walking. Then I will most likely
walk in this direction to propose to right here.
Okay. Okay. No problem.
Lei Haowen.
Contact me immediately. Otherwise, you will suffer the consequences.
Okay. You guys go set up first.
Rehearse the music well.
Okay. Okay.
Let's prepare.
If you dare to keep hiding from me,
then I'll make it so that you can never see Gu Xiaoling ever again!
Are you crazy?
Why did you sell Xinlu at such a low price?
Why did you trick me into signing the contract?
What on earth do you want to do?
Siyu, I need the money to save Xiaoling.
Are you stupid?
Do you think she will agree to marry you if you do this?
I know that you all think I'm stupid.
However, what is done is done so I hope you can understand me.
Do you know how many people's
hard work you are ruining for your obsession?!
Sorry.
You are breaking the law!
Come back immediately!
Xiaoling, come here immediately.
There is something very, very, very important that I want to discuss with you.
[Li Siyu]
Do you know what Lei Haowen did?
♫ Always believed you would appear ♫
♫ in my life ♫
♫ Always sure that you're ♫
[This is the man that Heaven is giving you.]
♫ the love I'm waiting for ♫
♫ Even if time is pressuring us ♫
Xiaoling,
when I proposed to you last time,
you wanted the lanterns to be diamonds instead.
I've done that now.
♫ Don't know if we could meet again in our next lives ♫
♫ In this lifetime, I just want to watch the scenery with you ♫
♫ Give the best of myself ♫
♫ To my dearest you ♫
There is ¥5,000,000 in here.
Marry me.
Where did you get the money from?
I earned it.
How did you earn it?
Investment income.
You scammed Li Siyu of her money! You sold Xinlu Investment at a cheap price!
Siyu invested ¥3,000,000 into it.
I gave her ¥6,000,000. She didn't lose money.
That company is worth over ¥100,000,000
yet you sold it for a mere ¥10,200,000!
When I sold it, it was not worth a cent.
Are you actually stupid or just evil?
Xiaoling,
isn't the person I am right now
whom you've always wanted to marry?
You right now
is a shortsighted asshole who is blinded by greed!
I really love you.
I'm really, really disgusted by you!
I'm wrong!
I can't live without you.
Why did I ask him for ¥5,000,000?
I'm also not a good person.
Gong Jing planned this from the beginning.
Yes.
We were all tricked by him.
Professor Gao! Professor Gao!
Professor Gao!
You must provide sufficient evidence
to prove that you were tricked into signing this contract.
That way you can ask the court or an arbitration institution
to cancel or change this transfer agreement.
Are there any other ways to go about this?
If Lei Haowen or Gong Jing confess to their crime
and admit to fraud, then this will be easy to take care of.
You can call the police.
It's all my fault. I misled him.
If someone's to be blamed for this, then blame him for being so muddle-headed and blame me for being careless.
If it weren't to stop me from marrying He Mu, then he wouldn't have betrayed you.
This has nothing to do with you.
He is an adult. He knows what he is doing.
Don't call him anymore.
I have already left messages on all of his social media. He hasn't replied to me at all.
We must find Lei Haowen.
I think your ideas and
creativity for this project are all very good.
Our collaboration this time was a very pleasant experience, President Chen!
- I hope we can continue working together next time!
- Yes.
Okay. Goodbye, President Chen!
- Okay. Take care.
- See you.
- Bye-bye.
Hello? Xiaoling.
Do you know where Lei Haowen is?
I haven't seen him for a while, either.
Do you know what he did?
Rest assured, President Wang. I've already prepared everything.
Come in. All the media outlets will speak about this at the same time on that day.
Director Gong, Chen Yiming is looking for you.
President Wang, Chen Yiming came looking for me. Should I see him or not?
Treat him well.
However, you should know
what should be said and what shouldn't be.
I know.
Have him come in.
I am hanging up then, President Wang.
Yiming?!
What brings you here?
Where is Lei Haowen?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking you, where is Lei Haowen?
How would I know?
Gong Jing,
I'll give you another chance.
You can either confess your crime of fraud,
or tell me where Lei Haowen is right now.
Chen Yiming, please pay attention to your tone.
I'm your investor.
Who is your largest shareholder?
I can't tell you.
The contract didn't say that I can't beat you up.
Chen Yiming!
You don't look very well.
Did you not sleep well last night or are you not feeling well?
According to the road conditions right now,
I think we will arrive at the civil affairs bureau in 23 minutes.
Then we will use 15 minutes to complete the procedure.
Then I will use 32 minutes to get back to the company
at 16:30. I will be just in time for the video conference.
Are you in such a rush?
My life is calculated in minutes.
In addition, after we get the marriage certificate,
we can start preparing for the wedding.
Siyu: Is there any news of Lei Haowen today?
You must choose four of them within one week.
Then make a table with the pros and cons
[No.]
of these four companies.
We will then decide on which wedding planning company to use.
Remember this.
[Shanghai Changning District Civil Affairs Bureau]
Be careful, there are steps.
What's wrong?
He Mu,
can we...
can we get the marriage certificate another day?
According to the plan,
we should have gotten it two months ago.
I'm in a really bad mood right now. I feel very confused now.
We are here already!
In one hour,
I have a very important meeting.
Just give me a few more days.
I already made all the plans that come after this.
A plan can never keep up with changes.
"A plan can never keep up with changes."
is the excuse that those who fail use.
Those who succeed
would never let a situation deviate from its expected course.
I'm not a successful person.
Okay?
Xiaoling,
I've already sacrificed a lot for you.
Can you not be so wilful? Okay?
But I don't want to get this marriage certificate today!
Can you control your emotions?
That is a basic ability of adults.
Do you think I'm not controlling it?
Let me tell you.
From the moment I saw today, I've been controlling myself
and haven't relaxed for even one second!
This is a public place.
So what if this is a public place?
Do I need to wear a mask and be fake just because I'm in a public place?
He Mu,
I hate healthy food. I only like junk food.
I don't like watching Discovery. I only like to keep up with gossip.
I have zero interest in elegant things.
I'm not graceful and calm.
I'm just an ordinary girl with vulgar taste.
This is the real me.
He Mu, I'm sorry, but I don't love you.
He Mu, I don't love you!
I finally said these words to you! I feel so relieved right now!
What did you say?
Here is your money.
From now on, we don't owe each other.
Wait.
If it really is how you said it is
and you were pretending before,
it means you did put in the effort for me.
Are you sure you want all of that effort to be in vain?
Yeah.
For a failure like me,
deviating from expectations is very normal.
Don't say anymore, brother.
Life is still long. Let's say goodbye here.
I wish you happiness.
Remember to pay!
Lei Haowen,
I broke up with He Mu!
Where are you right now? Show up!
I want to see you.
This Huangjin Investment is quite complicated.
This is its shareholders' situation.
There are 9 shareholders in total. MH Group
holds 89% of the shares. It's the largest shareholder.
This is all material on MH Group.
MH Group is Langfei Investment's holding company.
That's right.
This is Langfei Investment's material.
Zhilan Group then owns the majority of the shares of Langfei investment.
However, Zhilan Group isn't the final, true controller.
Tianye Group is Zhilan's largest shareholder.
So I'm sure
that Tianye Group's President, Wang Ziru, is Huangjin Investment's largest shareholder.
A friend just told me that during Lubao's bidding crisis,
a company called Langfei spent ¥40,000 on an "internet water army"  (T/N: a group of people posting certain content in accordance to those who paid them; very common and controversial in China)
to make negative comments about Lubao.
Then the person who is truly controlling Langfei Group is...
It's also Wang Ziru.
[To Lei Haowen: Lei Haowen, where are you? Reply. I want to see you.]
[Young and Dangerous 2]
"Young and Dangerous"
(T/N: a Hong Kong movie based on the manhua "Teddy Boy" that is about the protagonist's life in the triad)
is the movie that decided my life dream.
You still have a dream?
Of course!
I wanted to make lots of money and become a "big bro."
(T/N: what a leader in the triad is called)
Thinking about it now, it seems silly. However, back then, I vowed
to go to Macao once I became successful.
I want to be free and enjoy priceless friendships.
- Get out!
- What are you doing?
Don't drag me out!
I still have money! Don't drag me out!
Let me go!
Lei Haowen.
Lei— You— Where have you been?!
Miss, stop!
I'm his wife! I'm controlling my husband! What does it have to do with you?!
Go!
Where have you been?!
Why did you disppear?!
Why didn't you answer my phone call?!
You—!
Why didn't you dodge that?
Just hit me. Just kill me.
It's meaningless for me to live anyway.
You scammed my older sister out of everything. Now you think it's meaningless for you to live,
aren't you ashamed?
What else can I do?
A friend of a friend was defrauded by me.
I've missed out on a business deal that happens once in a thousand years as well.
Besides eating, drinking, and waiting for death,
what can I possibly do?
Lei Haowen.
Lei Haowen, look at me!
I didn't get married.
I broke up with He Mu.
What?
I admit that
I'm superficial and vain.
I only want to marry a rich man.
I'm still superficial, vain, and love money now...
But I discovered something.
Besides money,
I also want something else.
What?
The sound of dogs barking when I'm stealing fruits.
The fighting that happens when I'm eating large intestines.
Broken high heels.
The nonsense spewed after getting drunk.
Plus, having someone help me fix my window after the storm.
Lei Haowen,
I want you.
In order to trick me into going back, you really are willing to say anything.
Yes!
In front of you, I can say anything but I've never said any lies.
I've disliked you before.
I've hit and cursed at you before.
We've cut off all ties with each other before.
I've very deeply hurt you before but I've never lied to you before.
It's already too late to say those things now.
Not too late.
I-I-I'm saying it's too late for me.
I can't go back anymore.
The present I prepared for you before.
Before I could gift it to you,
we broke things off.
I made it myself.
I just recently found out
that in order for me to live more comfortably,
you helped pay a part of my rent every month.
I'll repay you for that.
However, in regards to your good intentions,
I don't want to miss out on it anymore.
But I'm a disgrace now.
Why are you doing this? I'm not worth it.
Because I can freely
be the most authentic Gu Xiaoling
only when I'm in front of you.
Haowen,
go back with me to confess your crime.
Confess my crime?
I will go to jail if I confess.
Shouldn't you go to jail and accept your punishment after doing what you've done?
You just said so much yet you still want me to go to jail?
Yes! I want you to go to jail and accept your punishment!
If possible, I would go to jail with you!
But are yo-y-you willing to be with someone who has been to jail before?
Lei Haowen,
whom I want to marry is a responsible man
with the courage to admit mistakes and change.
Not a wretched and weak coward!
I'll be in jail for at least three years for the things I've done.
Isn't it just three years?
Isn't it just three years? Can you wait for three years?
I've already waited for thirty years.
Would three years make a difference?
Xiaoling,
are you really willing to be with me?
Are you really willing to wait for me?
I am.
But I'm warning you!
I will only wait three years for you.
I won't wait for even one more day than that.
Therefore, get in there earlier so that you can get out earlier.
Xiaoling,
I, Lei Haowen,
won't let you down anymore.
[Serving the people]
Xiaoling, wait for me.
I'll wait for you!
I'll wait for you! I'll wait for you!
During the negotiation, it's normal to have some setbacks.
Yes.Yes.
Director Zeng. Director Qiu. Rest assured.
The final result will surely satisfy you two.
Okay. Okay.
Come in.
It's you?
It's me.
Why are you here?
Ziru,
Dubu will definitely restart.
This is the plan that I made to enhance Lubao's brand image
in response to Dubu entering the market.
Even if Dubu restarts,
they need at least three years to enter the market.
After three years,
I believe Lubao will surely have new products to compete with Dubu.
I don't need your plan.
No.
You need it for sure.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have instructed Gong Jing to bribe Lei Haowen into
obtaining Li Siyu's signature through fraud.
When did you find out?
Before, when we went to eat at the club.
The man I met was Gong Jing, right?
What else did you find out?
The reason why he invested in our company,
is not because of our talent
but because of your instructions.
I instigated him
because I really believed in you.
Thank you.
Thank you for protecting my self-esteem carefully
while you helped me.
Thank you.
What else did you find out?
At that time, Li Siyu
helped Liu Yang pay a portion of his mom's medical fee.
It was also you who hired an "internet water army"
to worsen the situation
and lower the valuation of Lubao.
Buy low and sell high. This is my talent.
Are bribery and fraud also your talents?
Since I am already so unbearable to you,
why don't you just directly break up?
Why did you write this plan?
Because I want to save our relationship.
I'm negotiating with FCC right now
to transfer the 23% of Lubao's shares that I hold
to them in exchange for  ¥5,000,000,000.
If, at this moment,
someone says that Lubao will die in three years,
then would anyone be willing to buy Lubao?
So you decided to sell Lubao first and then unfreeze Dubu?
That was what I was originally thinking of doing.
In the end, Gong Jing ruined everything.
The FCC called me just now.
They say they want to reconsider. They plan on canceling this purchase.
I remember you spent almost ¥800,000,000 to buy Lubao.
That's right.
However, you have
49% of Dubu's shares.
The market value of Dubu is at least ¥5,000,000,000.
Even if Lubao fails, you won't lose money.
Because I added (financial) leverage when I purchased Lubao.
The agreement was to turn that ¥800,000,000 into ¥3,000,000,000 in one year.
So if this purchase fails, then I'll lose all of my assets!
As well as all my Dubu shares!
So that's the situation.
I'm already standing on the edge of a cliff now.
The reason why I'm using fair and foul  methods
is I'm in a difficult position as well.
But what you did is wrong.
Yes.
I regret it very much as well. I shouldn't have asked Gong Jing to do that.
Are you still willing to accept me now?
What do you plan to do next?
I haven't thought about it yet.
Ziru.
The whole situation isn't as bad as you think.
I can immediately modify the plan and try
to regain the public's trust towards Lubao in the shortest time.
Thank you,
but I don't think that's necessary anymore.
It is. I think it is necessary.
Even if it's the last gamble, I want to try it.
This method...
will probably produce very little effect.
But I don't want to give up.
Ziru.
You've always supported me.
This time, let me support you.
Okay?
Thank you.
It's early in the morning yet all of you aren't working.
Why are you all standing here?
You're back so everyone is happy.
What's there to be happy about?
We've already wasted a lot of time.
- Stop standing here.
- Everyone, go to work. Go back to where you should be.
Professor Gao, do you want to rest for a moment?
Are you okay? How about you sit down for a bit?
Liu Yang.
Look at my blood pressure,
blood oxygen, and heart rate.
They have all gone back to normal.
Everything is good now. Everything is good now.
♫  Holding onto ideals,  ♫
Wang Ziru is suspected of being involved in a hostile takeover
and disrupting the system of economic and financial management.
She has already been arrested.
I heard that she lost in her gamble as well.
She is heavily in debt now.
She deserves it!
When is Haowen getting out?
The lawyers are doing the paperwork for his bail.
I'm guessing soon!
Xiaoling, I really never thought
that you would give up on money and marry someone you love.
Says who?
Money and love, I want both.
I can testify that she didn't compromise.
Siyu,  do you have any new plans?
Keep fighting for another ten more years.
Let us fight for another ten more years!
Fight for another ten more years!
♫  More scars  ♫
♫  Maybe that's just how it is  ♫
♫  Becoming stronger through tear streaked smiles  ♫
♫  Spent days confused and lost  ♫
♫  We grew up again in those moments  ♫
♫  Maybe that's just how it is  ♫
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫ The sky has finally cleared ♫