Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 9]
Hello, Mr. Liu.
Hello.
You forgot about 2017's data in the report you gave to the director yesterday.
It's okay. I added it for you.
Pay attention in the future.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
It's nothing.
Mr. Liu,
I wasn't the one at fault last time.
It was Mr. Wu who made me write it like that.
I even specially asked him if it would be approved like that or not.
He told me not to worry about it.
Really?
I even heard him calling someone, saying
as long as you make another mistake, you won't be able to become the team leader.
It's a pity you've already started to suspect him so that guy took the chance.
Who is "that guy"?
I don't know about that.
Mr. Liu, be careful.
Hello?
Yes. Yes, it's me.
He didn't tell other people about that thing.
Come out for a moment. I have something to talk to you about.
Mr. Liu.
Why didn't old Wu avoid you when he made the phone call?
I was too homesick that evening so I cried in the corner.
He thought there was no one in the office.
Have you told other people about this?
I haven't told anyone.
Why did you tell me then?
Mr. Liu, you are a good person.
I don't want you to get played by them.
Mr. Liu, you must trust me!
You are so nice to me. I would never lie to you.
I trust you.
Then... what do you plan to do?
I'm fixing the plan.
The most urgent thing now is to verify all the data.
That's... Isn't that a huge workload?
Yes. I definitely won't be able to finish it by myself.
Mr. Liu, I can help you.
I can do overtime and stay up.
Thank you.
Even if I include you, it's still difficult to finish.
The most important thing is to find the hidden "nail" Old Wu placed on my team.
(T/N: the person creating trouble)
Xiao Tian, it's your turn.
Sister Siyu. Sister Siyu!
- Everyone. Take a look over there.
- Are you all pigs?
You just look at me every day. Are you guys waiting for someone to feed you?
Do you think you can take orders just by sitting in the office? Sales depend on legs! Get out there! Move!
Why are you standing here? If you can't reach the sales target for this month then leave!
Sister Yuan is yelling at everyone. She is about to breakdown.
What are you all doing? Get out!
Of course, they are about to breakdown. We've already exceeded them!
Don't talk about others. Xiao Jia, report your number.
¥2,000,000 this week.
¥2,400,000.
Sister Siyu,...
¥2,500,000.
- Sis, I can't.
- ¥2,600,000.
Fine.
¥2,600,000 then.
¥2,600,000. Work hard!
Lin Ling, where are you? Why aren't you here for the meeting?
Sister Siyu, come rescue me!
- What's wrong?
- I've been talking to Meiyi Group's representative for three months.
We were going to finalize the contents of the contract today,
but Liu Jie came as well.
It's your client, why did she go?
I can't explain to you on the phone.
Come quickly! I don't think I can handle her myself.
Wait for me.
You guys continue.
Didn't Li Siyu teach you about the company's rules and regulations?
- Sister Yuan.
- What rules and regulations?
Meiyi Group was filed by Liu Jie. It has nothing to do with you.
- But she had given up.
- I've never said this.
- You said it personally—
- That's enough. Stop. Go back.
I won't. I've been following up on this client for three months. Why should I give it to you guys?
It's not "give." I'm telling you to quit.
Why quit?
- You also came?
- Sister Yuan, we have to be reasonable.
Liu Jie didn't want this client. Lin ling picked it up. She has been working hard on it for three months.
Now that the deal is almost closed, Liu Jie wants to take it back. Who would be willing to let it go?
Who said Liu Jie gave up? She just put it aside for a moment.
Sometimes the client needs to be dealt in a cold way. Didn't I teach you this?
Thank you for your lesson back then.
I remember Sister Yuan also taught me to seize the opportunity and not let it go.
I passed that lesson to Lin Ling.
Don't talk smack with me. The company has its rules and regulations.
Even rules and regulations must be reasonable.
Hello, Director Luo.
- Director Luo.
- My bad, my bad.
Our original appointment was at 3:00 p.m.
But I was having lunch with the mayor. So I'm a bit late.
It all right.
Director Luo, do you still remember me?
- You are also from Lubao Group, right?
- That's right.
Hi, Director Luo.
I'm the Sales Manager of Lubao Group, Li Siyu.
Okay.
Director Luo,
I'm the Sales Director of Lubao Group, Yuan Huizhong.
You have so many people here.
That's right. It's so you can see our sincerity and your importance.
- Who do I discuss with?
- Me!
Director Luo, I was the one who was communicating with you before.
There are a lot of details that only I know. If you discuss it with me, it will save you time.
Then that means.... Are you guys not together?
We are together, of course.
But if you discuss it with me, we can get everything done in one step.
Director Luo, we are all subordinates of Director Yuan.
We all listen to her.
- Tian Siyu?
- Yuan-Yuan Huizhong.
Ah, Yuan Huizhong. Right, right.
Please. Please come to my office.
This way.
Why didn't you expose her?
If we fought with our own people in front of the client, it won't do Lubao any good.
What do we do now? It's a ¥5,000,000 order.
What exactly is the deal with this client?
When I was an intern with Sister Yuan, my friend introduced me to Director Luo.
But Sister Yuan said I was short of experience at that time, so she asked Liu Jie to guide me.
Liu Jie and I spoke with Director Luo a few times but she said he didn't seem sincere so she gave up on it.
Later on, I was transferred to your team, then Director Luo contacted me.
This time, the meetings went quite smoothly. We were just preparing to sign the contract.
Liu Jie heard about something and she came as well.
When the client was put on records in the company, is it your name or Liu Jie's name?
I'm not sure. I was very new to the company at that time. I knew nothing.
When Liu Jie gave up this client, did she go to cancel the record?
I don't know.
Let's head back first.
Hi, where are the medicines for colds?
The ones for coughing are also here?
- Young man, you caught a cold?
- Yes.
Let me take your pulse and diagnose you.
There's no need. It's not that serious. I just need some medicine.
How about this? If you think what I say is right,
then you listen. If you think it's not right, then don't listen to it. Okay?
You have time anyway. Come on.
Your pulse is floating and tense.
Your cold is most likely caused by external chills.
It was probably because I got wet in the rain the other day.
Based on your health condition, rain
shouldn't cause such a serious cold.
The cold is just a superficial symptom.
The left guan and chi are not smooth.
(T/N: guan and chi are two of three areas used to feel the pulse in order to diagnose illnesses in Chinese medicine)
and the right-hand pulse is tight and rigid.
The inner cause should be depression and anxiety.
Then, what medicine should I take?
There are many medicines for cold.
As for depression and anxiety,
if you can't let it go yourself right now, taking medicine will be useless.
Let go of what?
Let go of what you bear in your mind constantly.
According to traditional Chinese medicine, all illnesses
are all basically psychological illnesses.
The psychological illnesses of modern-day people are usually connected to six words:
"Cannot be obtained. Afraid of loss."
The "let it go" you said means
to not work hard anymore. If you cannot obtain it, then don't obtain it.
If you are afraid of loss, then just let it leave.
What I mean is, you must be aware of your real situation.
Ginseng and pilose antler are both good things.
Many people become fresh with energy after they take them.
But if it's you have poor health,
then eating them will harm your body.
Let me prescribe you a medicinal recipe.
Thank you, Doctor. I'm okay. If it is indeed like what you said,
and I can recover by letting go, then I will try it.
No worries. I will still pay your consulting fee.
Thank you.
Liu Jie didn't cancel it.
She didn't.
Then, how do we count it?
Hello?
Li Siyu, President Pan asked you and Lin Ling to go to his office.
All right, I got it.
Let's go to GM Pan's office.
GM Pan. VP Fang.
Li Siyu, what happened today?
Meiyi Group?
What else can it be?
It was Lin Ling's client originally.
I checked. It was recorded with Liu Jie's name.
GM Pan. VP Fang. The company had stipulated
we report the client's name in advance. We aren't allowed to steal clients and lower prices in competition for clients.
But Li Siyu and Lin Ling completely didn't take the rules seriously.
I think it's a serious problem.
We can't allow these bad habits into the company.
Sister Yuan, you don't have to take it that far. Right?
Why not? The interest of the company should be above everything.
I'm saying that you don't have to take it as far as to confound what right with wrong,
and fight to tell on us first because of such a small order.
Li Siyu, who's the one "confounding what right with wrong"?
The company has the rule: the client belongs to the salesperson who reports it to the company.
It it not allowed to have cutthroat competition within the company. You encouraged your subordinate to close deals by any kind of means to reach the target!
- Who used any kind of means?
- You!
Enough.
This is not a supermarket.
We talk about work. We talk about facts and key points.
The first person in contact with Meiyi Group was Lin Ling.
The person who ended up confirming the order was Lin Ling.
Lin Ling has all the Wechat records of the whole process.
President Pan, I was the first person in contact with Meiyi Group.
Also, Director Luo is an old friend of mine.
Please. He doesn't know you at all. He met you for the first time today.
I know the situation.
I also know this Director Luo. Huizhong introduced him to our company at the beginning.
It's been about 10 years.
Oh, that's how it is.
President Pan,
actually I already finished discussing the contract with Director Luo.
It's just that they had a problem internally,
thus we didn't sign the contract this whole time.
But I didn't expect that Lin Ling would get in between
and quote a lower price.
Luckily, Director Luo regards me as an old friend
so the order was signed at my price.
You signed the contract?
Yes. ¥5,000,000. The deposit will be paid tomorrow.
How much did you quote?
My final price is 2% more than Lin Ling's.
You even pretended to be the sales director today!
Lin Ling, let me tell you.
When I was a little manager, for the sake of the business,
I told others I was the vice president.
President Pan is the same. To get the respect of others, he will say he is the chairman of some association.
Isn't it normal?
President Pan, I think this is a very serious issue.
If everyone is like this, stealing clients, quoting randomly, and creating a mess at the company,
then we can't work here anymore.
Meiyi Group was my client!
- The facts are all here yet you still want to spout nonsense?
- I am not spouting nonsense.
I am not going to waste my breath on you! I have nothing else to say.
- I just hope GM Pan, you will give me justice.
- You are lying!
Shut up!
Meiyi Group is Team One's client.
This order and the ¥5,000,000 in performance belongs to Team One.
In addition, Lin Ling violated the company's regulation. She will be fined ¥5,000.
Li Siyu, as her supervisor,
careless about monitoring the work of a subordinate. She will be fine ¥10,000.
Notify the whole company of the punishment.
Sister Siyu. Sister Siyu. Sister Si—
- You knew it was Liu Jie's client. Why did you go to contact them?
- I didn't know.
You should have known this!
Now that you've lost the client, the order, and was slapped in the face, how does it feel?
I'm wrong, Sister Siyu.
Siyu, after work, come over here earlier.
What's up?
I cooked a table full of good dishes.
You found a job?
No!
Then, why are you so excited?
Can't I get excited even though I don't have a job?
I saw an old Chinese medicine doctor today.
Chinese medicine? What's wrong?
I caught a cold because I got wet in the rain a couple of days ago.
I went out to buy some medicine. I bumped into him.
Are you interested in hearing about it?
Yes.
The Chinese medicine said I was depressed
It's all because I was thinking too much. I didn't learn to let it go.
Are you listening?
I'm listening.
So that's why I'm planning on not caring about anything.
I will take good care of myself. Even though I'm unemployed,
I have a healthy body at least.
What's wrong, Siyu?
I feel like your mood is off.
It's nothing. I have just been following up on orders.
Siyu, are the sales performances that important to you?
The sales performance decides if I can get the position of Sales Director or not next month.
So what if you get the position? So what if you don't get the position?
Since I've joined the competition, I need to work hard and get it.
This is probably what makes us troubled all the time.
We want to obtain yet we are afraid of loss.
What are you talking about?
The old Chinese medicine doctor told me this.
He said "cannot obtain" and "afraid of loss."
What?
After being unemployed, haven't I been sending resumes,
interviewing, sending resumes, interviewing, sending resumes...?
Haven't I been failing?
Failure is temporary.
I asked many friends. They all said that right now it is the offseason of job recruiting.
So don't doubt yourself.
I believe you will receive good news in the end as long as you persist.
Siyu,
I plan to stop applying to jobs for a while.
Yiming, are you overthinking too much?
I think I ran too fast before.
I thought too little.
It's not right to think too little. But you can't not run fast.
Even if you can't get it in the end, you have made efforts for it at least.
Worse comes to worst, you can start over after failing.
If you are always overcautious and indecisive, then you can achieve nothing in the end.
You have never failed before.
Siyu, starting over is really not that easy.
I said, I just lost a round.
Are you still coming tonight?
I will probably be late.
Do you still have work?
I have to go out.
Where to?
To see a client.
To get back the ¥5,000,000 which I lost.
[Esteemed Gu Xiaoling, your debt has been settled in its entirety. Thank you for your cooperation.]
Li Siyu, even though you say some foul things, I still have to thank you.
[Your message was sent, but it was rejected by the receiver.]
[Classy dresses]
Yuwei's mother, you can't dress so casually when the time comes.
Okay... I...
That's right, Yuwei's mother. You need to wear some classier clothes.
Also, the shoes and your bag...
You need to change those. Otherwise, it will be a disgrace.
Everyone, we'll gather at the dessert shop on Wednesday evening at 7:30,
to discuss about our joint letter to the school.
I hope all parents will understand the importance of this and attend.
Please excuse me. I have to attend to something tomorrow evening.
Got it.
[Are you sure you want to delete these two from your cart?]
[Delete]
You're back?
- Are Mom and Yuwei already asleep?
- Yes.
Why are you coming home later and later every day?
In the future, I'll be coming home even later.
Why?
Old We wants to be the team leader as well. He's creating traps for me to fall into.
If I don't want to be put in a bad position,
I can only do everything my self.
Is he that evil?
There are too many people like that in the workplace.
True. Since Sister Siyu
began competing for sales director, she's constantly being messed with.
Early this morning, President Pan called her to his office to penalize her.
Now you understand how difficult it is to work in these positions, right?
So, from now on, don't go out so much.
Stay and take care of things at home, so I don't get distracted.
I go all out for Yuwei's sake.
Everyone says that in today's society,
it's all about resources and connections.
I work so hard to maintain my connections with those mothers...
aren't I doing that for our Yuwei?
In the future, she'll be able to operate on a higher platform.
But the problem is... isn't this too early to think about all that?
It's is not too early at all.
We're not starting from the same place as them.
We have to start our efforts in the locker room.
Then, according to what you're saying, people like me who come from the countryside,
don't even have the qualifications to get into the locker room.
But did I still get out?
That was before.
You students from poor and humble families still have opportunities.
It's not the same now.
I have to get Yuwei into those elite circles while she's young.
Then in the future when she grows up, she can become an elite.
By the way, there's a parents meeting tomorrow.
They say they want to write a joint letter to the school.
So, mothers and fathers all have to get together.
I just told you.
The office competition has entered a red-hot phase right now.
Even working overtime isn't enough.
Where would I find the time to go play those games of yours?
How can you say they're games?
This concerns the direction Yuwei will take in the future.
Zhizhi, you and I are not part of the elite.
You are trying so hard to squeeze into that circle. Don't you think it's too tiring?
Even if it is tiring, I am the one tired.
Can't we just take things as they come?
Isn't it great to just live our own life?
Are you hungry? I'll go make you a bowl of dumplings.
- I'm not hungry.
- They'll be ready soon.
Let's eat lunch together?
If Li Siyu will be there, I won't go.
Just the two of us.
Okay, then.
[Zhang Zhizhi]
Zhizhi.
Sister Siyu, you're not at the company?
I'm going to solicit an order. I'm on my way back now.
How did it go?
¥500,000. Too little.
Hey, Sister Siyu.
I discovered a great little restaurant.
Let's try it out for lunch. It might change your mood.
Let's go.
It'll be my treat.
Between the two of us, does it matter who treats who?
Gu Xiaoling won't be there, will she?
Do you want ask her to come?
No. Just the two of us.
Okay. I'll book the table right away.
- Miss Zhang's reservation.
- This way please.
You two got here before me.
I still have something to do, I'm leaving.
You still have to eat first.
I also have things to do.
Xiaoling...
Sit, sit... Please sit down.
Zhizhi, do you not know that I already cut ties with her?
I know.
However, don't you guys cut ties multiple times a year?
Also, you guys never cut ties for more than a week,
so I guess it's almost time to end this.
So I invited you two here.
There's no way I'm going to reconcile with her this time.
You said that last time you had a falling out.
Last year when you guy had a falling out, you two also said that.
And three years ago, you said a similar thing.
You two are both over thirty,
how are you still acting like children?
You cut ties for every little thing.
Even Yuwei doesn't act the way you do.
She blocked me first!
Yes, she blocked you first. But before she blocked you,
she transferred you ¥110,000.
Sister Siyu, last time when you were framed in the company and were in a bad mood,
we all could not contact you,
you don't even know how worried she was.
I'm going to the bathroom. I'm telling you...
If I come back and either one of you has disappeared,
then I'll be angry.
No matter what, thank you anyway, for taking care of my urgent need.
I have been always taking care of your urgent needs these past few years.
But you've never appreciated it.
I have also helped you quite a bit.
When dad found out that you wrote a love letter to a boy before
the college entrance examination, I was the one who took the blame for you.
You wouldn't even pass the graduation exam without my help.
When you first came to Shanghai and had no money, I was the one who sent you money.
When you had no place to live in Shanghai, it was me who gave you half of my bed.
Every time you argued with Chen Yiming, when did I ever not help you?
How have you guys started arguing again?
Zhizhi, tell us, did I help her more or did she help me more?
Did you take note of it all? Come on, take out your little notebook.
We can see who owes who with one look.
You two have known each other since you were 12,
you've been sisters for over 10 years.
Isn't helping each other a given?
All you guys think about is how much you've helped the other,
but can't you guys think about each other's good traits?
To me, even though you have different personalities,
you two are generous, loyal sisters.
Seeing you two like this, I really am about to take back my admiration for you two.
I admit...
in these past years...
she may have helped me more.
In these years, with her being noisy and messing around,
I'm not lonely anymore.
I know.
You two want to take a bit out of each other often,
but isn't the scolding towards each other for the good of the other?
This way when an outsider hurts one of you,
both of you would not care about anything else but to protect the other.
My attitude that day wasn't great,
I'm sorry.
You don't have to say sorry.
I need to thank you.
I'm going to go to the bathroom again.
Between these two areas, add another two to three light positions.
Okay.
Are you tired? There's a place to sit over there. We can rest for a minute.
Okay, let's go.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Liu.
You've worked hard.
No, it's not hard at all.
Let me see how much we've walked since we've left today.
We've walked over 20,000 steps.
That's nothing.
When I was in school, I used to walk 20 kilometers back and forth
- on mountain roads.
- Are you from a countryside village?
Yes.
I am too.
Mr. Liu, we were actually schoolmates.
Really?
It's not easy to be admitted to SJTU.
I was the top scorer in my class.
So was I.
I know.
It wasn't easy for either of us.
Mr. Liu, can I call you Senior Brother?
Of course, you can.
Senior Brother...
Are you used to living in the city now?
I'm used to some aspects, but there are some aspects that I'm still not used to.
Such as?
Not speaking of other things, let's talk about food.
No matter how much I eat, I can't taste the flavors of home.
Exactly. I have that feeling as well.
I remember when I was younger and got hungry,
I would go dig up some potatoes.
Then threw it in the woodstove.
It would be ready for a meal if cooked. Then take it out.
Peel the skin and dip it in soy sauce.
Or chilly powder.
- You ate it like that, too?
- Of course!
That taste and that texture
is so great.
Such a pity. Nowadays, the imported potatoes
don't taste like before.
By the way, Yayun. I thought of
a good way to find the "nail"
but  I need your cooperation.
Okay, I will help you.
Zhizhi, do you have diarrhea?
You went to toilet so many times.
Liu Yang's mom is here.
Auntie is here?
To help you look after Yuwei?
Also, to urge Liu Yang and me to have a son.
Every morning and evening, I must drink
two bowls of Chinese medicine made for having a son.
It has caused me to have diarrhea.
What era is it!? She is forcing you to have a son?
This is too unreasonable.
She just feels that since every family in her village has
a son, so our family must also have one.
You can't give birth to one. This is... This is outrageous.
What age is it? That is way too strange.
If you didn't tell me, then I wouldn't believe it.
Yes, Aunty is... is a bit...
Shit. It's over ¥3,000.
- Over ¥3,000?
- Yes.
- I can't tell.
- You sell batteries,
it will be weird if you know the price of clothes.
- Xiaoling, can you help me with something?
- Tell me.
Yuwei's class is holding a party.
The other moms attending usually dress really well.
You also know that, I usually wear... these clothes.
No need to say more. Come to my house this weekend. Clothes, bags, shoes; you can choose whatever you want.
Thank you.
I'll toast to you two good sisters.
With you two by my side, all problems are no longer a problem.
We would also like to thank you for having us reconcile with each other.
Thank you.
Sister Siyu, can you come over for dinner tonight? Help me talk to Liu Yang's mom.
No problem.
I know that you are busy so I don't even know how to ask you
but I really can't get through Liu Yang's mom's stubbornness.
It's no problem. I haven't been to your house for a long time anyways.
Sort these out. Thank you.
- Sister Yuan, heave a seat for now.
- Okay.
How is it?
Don't worry, Sister Yuan. You are still ahead.
By how much?
¥1,130,000.
Only ¥1,130,000? Did I just got a ¥5,000,000 order?
Correct. Plus that ¥ 5,000,000 order,
you are ahead by ¥1,130,000.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears.  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫