Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 16]
It's true. Right in front of me,
Sister Ziru called the Resources Department
and figured out the annual salary and position. All you have to do is show up.
Wait, stop talking.
Let me calm down and digest this information.
There are so many talented people out there, why did she pick me?
Because you're talented.
Be honest. How did you beg her?
Or what promise did you make her?
Nothing.
Sister Ziru always admired your talent.
All I did was say that you were out of work, and she immediately offered to take you.
It was really that easy?
Yiming, rest assured. Sister Ziru's not an idiot.
If you were really talentless, she wouldn't take you.
Still, I've only met her twice.
Well, you have an impressive resume.
Impressive resume? I've sent that exact resume to fifty different companies.
It barely got any recognition, how come suddenly—
Not every single director has a good eye.
Not every unemployed job seeker
has a girlfriend like you.
I didn't do anything!
Siyu, thank you.
Don't thank me.
I did it for myself, too.
Yiming, I don't want you to leave.
I don't want to have a long-distance relationship with you.
I don't want to face an uncertain future.
I don't either.
Huizhong, I'm sorry.
It's fine, Senior Brother. I know that you did your best.
I told many of my friends about your situation.
They are interested in your ability and qualifications.
Don't worry about finding a job.
Senior Brother, thank you.
I... don't want to work anymore.
Then, what are you planning to do?
Today, Mengmeng's teacher called me and scolded me.
Said I was unqualified to be a parent.
These teachers really...
I really am a failure.
I worked at the company for 13 years.
Eventually, I got kicked out.
I brought up a
proud disciple,
yet she defeated me.
I had a son...
who comes in last on every test.
Don't be too disappointed. People like Li Siyu
can't be happy for too long.
Lubao and Li Siyu
can do whatever they want.
I just want to find a job that will give me more freedom.
I don't care how much money I make.
This way, I can protect Mengmeng every day,
and help him with his health.
I can also help him improve his grades.
That's good, too.
I need to go. Mengmeng is taking an afterschool class. It's almost ending. I need to pick him up.
- I'm leaving.
- Okay.
Bye.
Right now, even Wei Yayun can order me around.
I really have fallen from grace.
I don't have it good either.
I graduated during the 985 project.
Always helping others pour water and tea.
Mr. Wu, are our lives really going to be like this forever?
Of course not. We still have opportunities.
Opportunities? Where?
With my experience,
all bids have some dirty tricks.
Liu Yang deliberately kicked us out
because he thought we were in his way.
But we've already been kicked out.
Even if there was stuff happening behind the scenes, we still wouldn't know.
If there's nothing going on behind the scenes,
then start thinking outside the box.
I have a list of all the companies that have sent in pre-review documents.
Look them up.
I'm sure one of these companies has something to do with Liu Yang.
How do I look them up?
The internet is so up-to-date nowadays, do I have to teach you?
I feel very honored to be able to join the Tianye Group.
I'm also very happy to become colleagues with everyone standing here.
I have hope that in future days, the Planning Department
will become Tianye's most important department.
We trust that under Director Chen's supervision,
the Planning Department's quality of work will become even better.
Thank you.
Director Chen, your office is in here.
Everyone, sit.
Director Chen, is there anything else you need?
Not at the moment.
Then I will go back to my office.
Thank you.
[Chen Yiming]
[Planning Department]
Why did you take me out to the middle of nowhere?
What are you doing?
You also got me drunk.
What is your intention?
Tell me. Today, I'm happy. I'll do what you say.
I don't really have any intentions.
I just want to take a walk with you.
Walk?
Be careful!
Why are you so slow? Hurry!
There's fireworks!
Let's celebrate!
Okay.
Congratulations on finding your place in society again.
Congratulations on achieving your dream of becoming the sales director.
Then in the future, every time a dream comes true,
we will light a firework to celebrate.
Sure.
- So should we pick a bigger one today?
- Sure!
♫  Your voice is light and soft  ♫
♫  Forms the love I want  ♫
♫  Your eyes are innocent and clear  ♫
♫  Like the ripples in the middle of a lake  ♫
♫  The world suddenly became quiet  ♫
A drone!
♫  As if someone pressed pause  ♫
♫  How much luck did I exchange in order to meet you  ♫
Help me hold this.
♫  Your hair is fanned out in the wind  ♫
♫  That is the forest I want to be lost in  ♫
♫  It's the beautiful scenery that I want to go to  ♫
♫  It's all hidden in your eyes  ♫
♫  I want to give all of me to you  ♫
Siyu, your husband is here for a job.
♫  We're getting closer, so let me fall in love  ♫
♫  In this lifetime, I just want to tightly hold your hand  ♫
♫  As we slowly walk and slowly feel  ♫
♫  With each breath, all our vows ♫
♫ remain as time goes by  ♫
Actually I should have assumed office earlier,
but I wanted to give you a better me
and a more assured future.
So I delayed for so long.
After going through so many difficulties,
to myself, to you,
to us,
I have a deeper understanding.
So Siyu don't worry,
you can rely on me.
I will work hard.
I will prove with the rest of my life that I am the best.
You have the best taste as well.
♫  In this lifetime, I just want to tightly hold your hand  ♫
♫  As we slowly walk and slowly feel  ♫
♫  With each breath, all our vows ♫
♫ remain as time goes by  ♫
♫  In this lifetime, I just want to tightly hold your hand  ♫
♫  As we slowly walk and slowly feel  ♫
♫  To spend every day and night with you  ♫
♫  Just want to tightly hold  your hand ♫
You just proposed.
I just proposed.
Fantastic. Great! I'm so happy!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Is it because of this painting?
Xiao Ling,
I've been looking for you.
I've been here all the time.
Ten years ago,
when I saw this painting for the first time, I cried as well.
Many people didn't understand why.
But only I know...
what touched me.
Xiao Ling,
we are the same group of people.
Be my girlfriend.
You understand me. I also understand you.
This exhibition includes clothing,
sculpture, fine arts, and interactive installation, etc.
What you see is the change and influence that social media nowadays has made
to people's thoughts
and behaviors.
Hi, Danny!
Hi, Bruce.
Long time no see.
Your exhibition is great.  It's really nice.
I like all the paintings and I also like all the history.
- You like this?
- Yes.
[Add story]
Nice.
Every moment is certain.
But every next moment is uncertain.
Where did you go to act today?
Who are you sending a message to?
See? The top of that house.
I told you it was the apartment of a famous collector.
Look, it's so low key.
It is very low key.
Liu Yang, Sister Siyu accepted Brother Yiming's proposal.
Great! Congratulations to them.
I want to invite Sister Siyu and Brother Yiming
over for dinner.
Would you come to join as well?
- I'm in a meeting.
This is magical.
I still can't believe it.
You can't regret now.
Do we really need to get married?
You think it can be fake?
Yiming,
actually I don't know
how to be a wife.
You are saying like I know how to be a husband.
This is our first time getting married.
But I believe,
we can make it.
We learn together and work hard together.
Explore together.
What are we going to do next?
The next step is a realistic one.
Is it to discuss
bride price and dowry?
To discuss the house.
Siyu,
I've saved about ¥1,000,000.
This is just enough for the first payment of a two-room apartment.
Let's buy a 3-room apartment.
We have a room and our kid has a room.
In case Zhizhi and Xiao Ling fight with their hubands,
they run away from their home, we prepare one room for them as well.
But a 3-room apartment with a good location
are around ¥5,000,000.
I don't have enough money for the first payment.
I have ¥500,000.
No. Your money is your money.
How can I use your money?
How can you just fancy my looks,
but don't fancy my money?
Siyu,
we've been together for so many years.
You sacrificed a lot.
But if the first payment of our apartment
also needs you,
I really can't accept it.
Chen Yiming, let me tell you. Either you accept my money and beauty together,
or you get nothing.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? What do you want to do?
It's just ¥500,000.
You're going to be working for me for the rest of your life.
Actually, it's me who got lucky.
Siyu.
You can also entertain people.
I heard a new director came to your department.
- He came last week.
- How is he?
- Not that great.
- Yet he can still be a director?
I heard that it was some leader's son-in-law.
Boss Wang had no other choice than to transfer Mr. He somewhere else
to give that position to him.
I was thinking about why Mr. He suddenly transferred away after he was doing pretty well.
Mr. He actually got lucky because of this mess. He went from the director of planning
to CEO of the branch office.
Director Chen.
Director Chen, you didn't go to the meeting?
- What meeting?
- The regular meeting every Wednesday.
Every director has to attend that meeting.
Thank you.
¥800 million takes up 20% equity.
That means that Lubao's expected worth is ¥4,000,000,000.
This price, a few years ago, would've been pretty fitting.
But now, according to the general circumstances, this price is too high.
Then how much money do you think is fitting?
According to the Finance Department's prediction model, it should be ¥3,000,000,000.
I still think that ¥3,000,000,000 is still a bit high.
Sorry, I didn't get the notice to attend this meeting.
Amy, next time we have a meeting,
make sure you notify Director Chen.
Oh, okay.
Director Chen, sit here.
No, it's fine. I'll just sit here.
Director Chen, your seat is here.
Director Wang, how much do you think is fitting?
Let's put that aside for now.
What's the newest news regarding the financial market?
I-Isn't today's meeting specifically about Lubao's estimated worth?
We're nearing our next round of negotiations.
We have to agree on and confirm this today.
I got news that
the upcoming policy is mainly focusing on adjusting indirect financing.
What else?
Director Wang, I suddenly realized that I made an appointment with a client
to talk about the brand image strategy we will put in place in the future.
Okay. Then go ahead.
Okay. I'll be leaving.
I'm so sorry, everyone. I'm leaving.
Continue.
Oh, right, even Xingxing's father liked the cookies you made.
- Really?
- I liked them, too. They're delicious.
Then I'll make more and bring them tomorrow.
Stop making cookies. Make some Napoleans. I love those.
- I love Napoleans as well!
- Aren't they good?
- They're also quite simple.
Okay. Then I'll make some for you.
Thank you so much, Yuwei's mom. School's out.
- They're out now.
- Get in a line, get in a line.
- Get in a line.
- Your kid...
That's our grandson.
Are you okay? Are you injured?
- How could you do that?
- Come here.
How could there be no problem? Look how big this bruise is!
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
How about we go to the hospital and check?
Of course, we have to! What if he got a concussion?
Okay, okay, grandma. I'll come with you.
Please wait a second. He has a little sister who's still young,
and when we get her, we can go together.
- No. We have to go right now!
- His sister is still young.
What do you mean young? Do you only care about your own children?
Are you just going to leave my child for dead?
- Grandma, please stop.
- It's fine.
- Get out! Get out!
- Why would you hit me?
- I didn't do anything wrong.
- So what if I hit you? You deserved it!
It's your fault you cut in and got into my business!
- Please stop.
- Please calm down.
Why did you guys grab me?
She was the one who hit me.
Why did you guys stop me, not her? Are we even friends?
Okay. Okay.
Come here, come here.
Yuwei's mom, we did this for your own good.
Think about it. That old lady is so old,
if you really hit her and caused her to be injured,
then you'd be in big trouble.
That's true. Even if you didn't hurt her,
if she purposefully pretended you did, then what could you do about it?
Wouldn't that also be bad? Right?
Exactly! Yes. We did it for your own good.
We just let her hit you a few extra times
to help her calm down.
Was that not it?
Do you know who her son is?
He's the principal of the international elementary school.
Do you know how many rich parents want to get into the school but can't?
The principal said that in the next three years, he would consider our preschool's kids first.
Why? Because his child is here, too.
If you hurt his mom, then he'd take his child to a different preschool.
This promise would be gone.
Then nobody in this preschool would be able to get into that school!
Including Yuwei. Do you get it now?
- The kids are out.
- Let's go.
- Miao Miao.
- Miao Miao...
- Xingxing.
Come here. How are you?
Yuwei's mom, don't forget to bring me Napoleans.
Don't forget about tomorrow's cookies.
I want some extras. Let's go.
Yuwei's mom, I drove today. Do you want me to take you home?
I'll be going.
Mom, what's wrong?
Mom?
Mom? Why are you crying?
Mom, are you okay?
Liu Yang.
Change this sentence for me.
I'm going to the restroom.
[Wife]
Hello, the number you called is temporarily unavailable.
Sorry, the number you dialed is not—
Let's go home.
Hi, kid. Want to sign up for the Chinese study class?
Hello? Hi.
I saw your listings on the app.
I want to make an appointment to see a house.
Okay. Then we'll talk more about it on the WeChat app.
Okay. Bye.
- Director Wang.
- Yiming.
I want to explain what happened at the meeting today.
It's fine. No problem.
Did you know that we are discussing equity financing with Lubao?
GM Pan and I have talked multiple times about Lubao's valuation.
In theory, you are the person who understands Lubao's valuation best.
However, at today's meeting, I purposefully ordered the Administration Department
not to tell you.
I understand.
You were worried that I would expose the company's secrets.
No. I trust your work ethic. You wouldn't leak our secrets.
I just didn't want to put you in a hard place.
You and Siyu. One is Tianye's executive, and another is Lubao's executive.
If Siyu asked about Tianye's strategy,
if you said it, then it would hurt the company;
but if you didn't, it would hurt your relationship.
So, I felt it would be better if you didn't know.
Thank you.
Thanks for thinking for me.
- I hope you understand.
- I do. Of course, I do.
Who was doing the brand valuation for Lubao before?
Xiao Wang did it. He already left work today.
I have some backup files here.
Okay. Then please give me all of your files on Lubao.
Got it.
Director Chen.
- Are these all the files?
- Yes.
Good. You can leave normally. I have nothing else.
Okay.
You still haven't gone to sleep?
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
You called?
It doesn't say that you sent me any messages or calls.
Are you not going to ask why I called?
Tell me.
I want to take Yuwei
and return her to the old Blue Sky preschool.
What did you say?
I'll get the paperwork done tomorrow.
To get Yuwei out of Blue Sky and into Golden Flower,
did you forget about how hard we worked get her in? And now you want to take her back?
Then the money, time, energy,
and the kindness we took from others were all for nothing?
Even if they were for nothing, I still want to transfer her back.
Yuwei was fine at Blue Sky.
You were the one who said she needed better education and forced us to change.
Now, Yuwei is also doing fine,
yet you want to mess around again? What exactly are you trying to do?
I was wrong, okay?
I don't want Yuwei to have superior education anymore.
I just want Yuwei to be a normal kid. Is that so wrong?
What are the two of you doing this late into the night?
- Zhizhi really wants to transfer Yuwei again?
- Yes. It's true.
- What happened?
- I don't agree.
It doesn't matter whether or not you agree, she must go. Tomorrow.
What has gotten into you so late at night?
Yuwei has finally gotten used to the new environment at her new preschool, and you want to transfer her again?
Aren't you afraid that it will leave a shadow in her heart?
Besides, we recently paid the tuition for this trimester's class.
If we leave now, then they'll only return half of the ¥30,000 we paid.
- Then I still want to transfer.
- No way.
You guys only think about money.
Today, I was bullied by someone and then everyone ganged up on me.
What happened exactly?
- Mom!  Mom.
- Coming, Grandma is coming.
Yuwei, Grandma is here.
- Go to sleep. Go to sleep, okay? Good girl.
- They all banded together to bully me.
- Good girl.
- They even... They even said that it was for my own good.
You two, be quieter! Don't wake Yuwei up again!
I told you long ago not to hang out
with people like Miao Miao's mom.
You just wouldn't listen.
Now that Yuwei has entered Golden Flower,
you should at least let her finish the term.
As for Miao Miao's mom and the others, just don't interact with them.
Can't you think about me?
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Just because of some issues with parents, you're making Yuwei change schools?
You're making such a huge deal out of something so little!
This isn't that! I was being bullied!
Will you stop acting so fragile?
You think I'm fragile?
Fine. You're not.
I'm telling you. In life,
this kind of thing happens so often.
- If you endure it, you'll get over it.
- I can't!
If everyone was like you, I would've resigned so many times.
Would anyone in our family still be alive?
It's not the same thing!
- Then tell me what it is!
- I...
Zhizhi, we're all adults.
Adults need to be able to fix their problems.
Why do we have to transfer schools all the time? What kind of family does this?
Yuwei can't stay in this preschool!
Then let me ask you. If you let Yuwei go back to Blue Sky Preschool,
and you get bullied and hurt again,
will Yuwei have to transfer again?
- No matter what, Yuwei must go.
- If you must transfer, then you take care of it.
I'm not going to bother with this anymore.
How could you not care about this big waste of money?
This... What does this mean?
Is she going up to the sky?
Yang, how about you sleep in the bedroom
- and I'll sleep on the couch?
- It's fine, I can sleep here.
What kind of wife is this?
- She's absolutely, absolutely—
- Mom.
Let me tell you!  You can't lower your head!
She needs to control her temper.
- What even—
- Sleep, sleep, sleep.
How is it? Do you like it?
Sister. Brother. This house
has many people wanting to make reservations to see it on Anjuke.
You should take it! Don't hesitate.
Okay. We'll continue looking.
We can discuss it later.
How do you like it?
Should we buy this one?
I've been looking at it for a long time on Anjuke.
I observed its real-life map, the floor plan,
and the VR video.
I think there are no problems with the location and direction.
The layout is also nice. Later, we could add some furniture
and get married right away.
Get married right away?
Wait, wait, wait. You've been thinking very actively these past few days.
- What other plans do you have? Let me prepare my heart for them.
- Nothing else.
I just want to buy a house.
Buying a house is a huge thing. We should be more cautious.
Cautious? Of course, I am.
Aren't I discussing it with you?
Just tell me. Are you unsatisfied with any part of this house?
Nothing, but maybe there are better ones.
Siyu, there's no perfect house on this planet.
If we live in it,
it will become our home.
I think that's the best.
You're right,
but I still think we should look at more.
I don't want to look at more.
We should just get this one. I'm tired of looking. I don't want to look.
You can't be too rash when buying houses.
I am though. I'm so anxious to get it over with.
I just want to buy a house quickly and get married to you quickly.
What? You're regretting it?
- You don't want to get married anymore?
- No, no, no. That's not what I meant at all.
Then, why are you so picky about houses?
I'm not picky, I'm...
Just let me think about it longer.
- Hello? Brother Yang?
- Siyu, I just wanted to let you know that Lubao qualified.
The prequalification and sample testing are all within the requirements.
Great!
You guys should prepare to send the files.
The next stage will be given to the expert evaluation team.
We are only assisting
in order to avoid suspicion, it is best that we do not contact or meet each other during the process.
I understand, I understand.
Brother Yang, could you please just let me know
if Lubao's possibilities are big or not?
The only thing I can tell you is that Lubao's score is pretty high. Good luck!
Thank you!
Are you angry with me?
- No.
- You're lying.
Listen to your cold voice.
I was wrong. I was wrong, okay?
It's not that I don't want to get married!
I just... I've been under a lot of pressure lately,
¥5,000,000,000 is weighing down on my brain,
and you just recently joined a new company.
I just haven't had the ability to concentrate on thinking about marriage.
At least your apology was honest.
Never mind. There's nothing else.
Okay.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
- Are you Mr. Chen?
- Yes. I made a reservation earlier.
Come in, come in.
[Green Treasure Charging Station]
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫