Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 5]
Hello, Sister Siyu.
Sister Siyu!
Thank you for taking me in.
But I think... it's better for me to leave.
- Why?
- I heard from Xiaojia,
that because of me, you were scolded by GM Pan.
You can leave,
but that means I got scolded for nothing then.
I got scolded in exchange for another chance for you.
GM Pan said that as long as you can sign a new client within a week,
you will be in the clear immediately.
A week? I can't.
Lin Ling, I believe in you.
If I say you can, then you definitely can.
I definitely can.
Among the customers you've met before, which one is most likely to sign?
Youyou Rabbit.
Why didn't he sign in the end?
Their company suddenly stopped production and switched models.
The new production line will be put into operation after half a year.
They won't need batteries until then.
So you just gave up?
I asked Sister Yuan about this. Sister Yuan said to just to keep in touch with them.
We will talk about it again in half a year.
- Let's go.
- Where to?
- To visit Youyou Rabbit.
- There are still five months left.
You have to go out there in order to know where the opportunity lies.
Opportunities never come to those who wait. You must fight for opportunities.
- Siyu.
- Sister Yuan.
I want to talk to you.
- Then you go back and wait for me.
- Okay.
Close the door.
Next time you take someone in, can you tell me in advance?
Don't rehire someone I fired.
To others, it might seem like there's a problem between us.
You didn't tell me in advance when you took
elites like Huang Bibo, Kuai Zi and A'Fu into your team.
Are you still upset about that?
I didn’t think it through well enough and didn’t tell you in advance.
I apologize to you.
No need, it's in the past already.
All right. I will treat you to dinner and you can pick the place.
I'll pick an expensive one then.
Sure.
Fire Lin Ling.
Why?
She's not saleperson material.
Why are you wasting your time on her?
I think she has potential doing sales.
Are you not going to listen to even my advice now?
It's not that I'm not listening.
I just promised to help her to sign a contract within a week so that she won't be fired.
- That's even worse.
- Why?
Siyu, I'll be honest.
I guided her for three months yet she had no breakthrough.
If you help her sign a contract within a week, aren't you giving me a slap in the face?
Sister Yuan, I'm not sure if Lin Ling can get a deal.
Even if she gets one, it's because of the foundation you helped her establish.
Others won't think like that.
As long as the two of us have no ill feelings, then what others think has nothing to do with us.
Saying that is easy!  But right now, the both of us are leading teams.
How can we not care about other people's thoughts?
Sister Yuan, Lin Ling's father is seriously ill.
She needs this job.
If you really want to help her, there are a ton of ways to do that.
Why must you use a method that would embarrass me?
It is better to teach people how to fish than to just give them fish.
She already has a foundation. It's a pity if she gives up now.
For a Lin Ling, you are harming our relationship.
Don't you feel pity?
Sister Yuan, aren't you overthinking?
Siyu,
don't forget.
You promised to just run alongside me.
A mere Lin Ling shouldn't have much impact, right?
Today it is Lin Ling, tomorrow and the day after, it will be some other people.
Sister Yuan, I already promised you.
But you still don't believe me and always keep a wall up towards me. Is there any point in that?
Li Siyu, ask your conscience.
Will you be where you are today without me?
Right now, I'm just asking for a small favor but you say one thing and do another. How should I think of you?
- When did I say one thing and do another?
- Then fire her now.
- Hello.
Is this Dayu Investment Company?
Yes.
Hello, I-I-it's like this,
a few days ago, I sent a job application email
but never got a reply so
I want you to help me check on it.
No reply means you are eliminated.
Then I want to ask, what the reason was for being eliminated?
I'm not quite sure about that.
Thank—
Hello?
What are you doing?
Meeting.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
I-I'm just talking to a customer
and it's not going that well.
What's the matter?
Nothing. I just wanted to talk.
Why are you all just sitting there?
It's been two weeks and you guys haven't gotten it done. You are basically helping me lose face.
Sales depend on legs! One phrase, go grab!
Go grab the customers for me!
Here.
I haven't even finished the one you gave me last time.
Have it as backup. Your stomach isn't good. Pay attention to what you eat.
Lin Ling, come here for a second.
Sister Siyu.
Lin Ling.
I'm sorry.
Sister Siyu.
Go to the Human Resources Department and complete the resignation procedures.
Sister Siyu, you said you'd take me under your wing.
I regret, okay? I'm going back on my word, okay? I don't honor promises, okay?
Sister Siyu.
Don't start with nonsense and get out!
Why would a workaholic like you show up here at this time?
I don't want to go to work today.
What happened?
It's just the stuff happening at the office.
Just watch "Empresses in the Palace" a few times and you won't have as many troubles.
Oh right!  If you see Chen Yiming, apologize to him for me.
His friend, Lei something, I didn't show him any respect today.
Lei Haowen, he is a bit self-righteous and loves to brag.
- But he is good person.
- Yeah, right.
I was wondering why Chen Yiming would have a friend like him.
Chen Yiming... has been strange lately.
He always says he's meeting with clients yet I don't see the clients.
Why are you by yourself? Where's your client?
The c-client just left.
Also, he always looks like he has a lot on his mind.
He also keeps secretly looking at his phone.
- Could it be that he has a mistress?
- That's not possible.
Those are the symptoms of men who cheat.
Chen Yiming wouldn't.
Why do you trust him so much?
If we do not have at least that much trust, why would he propose?
Let me tell you. You must not
let down your guard just because a guy proposes.
Also, didn't the proposal not go through?
- Isn't it because of you?
- Hey, don't shift the blame on me.
Isn't it because you're scared of marriage?
Afterward, he didn't mention proposing again.
That is also very strange.
You, oh, you. When he proposes, you are conflicted.
When he doesn't propose, you are also conflicted.
Why don't you just ask?
How do I ask?
"Chen Yiming, when are you going to propose again?"
You are a novice in terms of love.
You're saying that like you understand it very well.
At least I have met more players than you.
Let me tell you. Some men are just restless.
It's just whether there is a chance for it to be revealed.
Phone.
- Xiao Jia.
- Sis, GM Lin of Arad Company asked for a quote.
What do I say?
Give him the price for old clients.
Okay. That's it then, Sis.
Hey, that...
Did Lin Ling finish her paperwork?
Lin Ling? I think she went to Youyou Rabbit.
Why did she go to Youyou Rabbit?
I don't know about that.
- Are you leaving?
- I have something to do at work.
Chen Yiming, you have to be careful.
Showcase? Booths? Is there at least a red carpet?
Have you ever seen an exhibition that uses this color carpet?
- Come here, come here.
- Can you come or not? At the time we said.
Look at this backplane.
The logo! Where is the Youyou Rabbit logo?
Let me tell you. We've informed leaders. We've informed the media.
Even the distributors are here yet this is what you guys gave me.
Do you still want to hold the exhibition next year?
What did you two say?
What did you two say? Tell me!
Tell me what to do!
- Lin Ling.
- Sister Siyu.
Director Jiang, calm down.
- Why are you here?
- What happened?
They have a big distributors conference tomorrow. But the PR company they hired is not reliable.
They suddenly left and left this mess.
What are you doing now?
I was... helping out.
I already fired you so why did you come here?
Sister Siyu, I want to give it one last go.
There is no chance.
You told me that one cannot simply wait for an opportunity. You must fight for an opportunity.
- Do you listen to everything I say?
- Yes.
You are the only one who has told me...
that I can.
I know that I've already been fired,
but before I leave,
I want to prove to myself
that I can.
Why did you just tell me now?
I know. I know.
I told you guys to set the tables and you guys couldn't do it well.
I told you guys to arrange the chairs and you  guys couldn't do it well. There's no guest list and you don't know how to arrange the seating.
What can you all do?
What about the booth? I told you guys a month ago to prepare it.
- Zhizhi, s the stage from the exhibition at the beginning of the year still there?
- Why are you guys so useless?!
That's great. I need to use it now. Help me start the application process.
Thanks.
Xiao Jia, call everyone to come help at Youyou Rabbit.
All right, Sis.
Team 2, everyone, listen up.
I just got Sister Siyu's call.
Everyone go to Youyou Rabbit to help Lin Ling get the deal.
This is an exhibition.
Everyone should be clear about the situation, right? Everyone knows what they're supposed to bring, right?
- We'll go to it.
- Then let's get going.
- Bring the LED screen.
- Come in.
Sister Yuan, didn't you assign Youyou Rabbit to me?
- Why's it Lin Ling's again?
- No way.
- You guys get in my car.
- Okay.
Put stuff into the other car.
I sent the address of Youyou Rabbit to your phones already. Hurry up.
Be careful when you drive.
- Sister Yuan.
- Li Siyu.
Youyou Rabbit is Liu Jie's client. What going on with Lin Ling poking her nose into it?
Youyou Rabbit has always been Lin Ling's client.
After Lin Ling was fired, I had Liu Jie take over.
Lin Ling hasn't been officially fired yet, right?
Also, the company's record
shows that it is Lin Ling's.
Li Siyu, don't you forget
how I mentored you in the beginning.
Sister Yuan, I didn't forget.
I'm doing what you taught me.
What'd you say?
When I first got into Lubao, I had two straight months of no sales performance.
It was you who didn't give up on me and led me step-by-step.
That was how I found my confidence and breakthrough.
Now, I'm mentoring Lin Ling just like how you mentored me.
Sister Yuan, what'd she say?
- Let it be.
- How can we just let it be?
If I say it's fine, it's fine!
Sister Yuan, someone that you fired
she forcibly took them in. Your clients, she forcibly steals them.
Isn't it obvious that she is going against you?
Get out.
- Where's Sister Siyu?
- She's inside.
You guys, hurry up! They are waiting inside.
Lin Ling, confirm the list and seating arrangement of the guests.
Xiao Jia, you're in charge of printing and placing the name tags.
- Xiao Tian.
- Here.
- You're in charge of the welcome banner.
- Got it.
- Xiao Wu, put the LED lights up.
- Okay.
You two. Go over to the audio setup and help out.
You three, come here.
- Come with me.
- Hey!
Are you guys from the PR company?
We're from Lubao.
GM Jiang, this is Manager Li.
Manager Li, this is GM Jiang.
GM Jiang, I heard from Lin Ling that your company has had some problems.
We can help out.
Don't worry. Even though we are not a professional PR company,
but I have organized all of Lubao's distributor events.
We guarantee that tomorrow's event will go smoothly.
Manager Li, is that right?
I want to tell you that for the next 6 months,
- our company has no plans of ordering batteries.
-That's fine.
After half a year, we may not have those plans as well.
Director Jiang, whether you buy them or not,
I'll be helping you guys today for sure.
Let's go.
Even though life is hard, I still have hope.
I won't give up.
Hello, Liu Yang. When will you come back?
I still have some work to do. I'll be back soon.
Can you hurry back? I have to go out soon.
- We can't leave Yuwei at home all alone.
- Where are you going?
Didn't I tell you? I have a meeting with Miao Miao's mom and the others.
I don't understand why you insist on mingling with that crowd.
I'm doing all of this for Yuwei, of course.
Didn't you realize that ever since Yuwei started to hang out with those kids,
her outlook has become different?
I suddenly got urgent work to do so I need to attend to it right away.
I may need to do overtime and can't go home.
Hey, Liu Yang! Hello?
Little ancestor, don't jump. It's dangerous.
Sit down, baby.
Sister Siyu, I got the proposal that Yiming revised for me.
It's really good. Thank you.
I'm pretty busy right now.
I think I'll be busy until after midnight. I can't talk right now.
Aunt Mei!
- Xiaoling, can you please watch Yuwei for me?
- Me?!
- I'll come get her later.
- But...
I gotta go. Bye.
Hey! Zhizhi!
- Come in.
- Aunt Mei!
Close the door.
It's pretty good.
You picked quite a good picture.
There's a good amount of content.
Yuwei's mom's proposal
is actually quite professional.
It's quite pretty, quite pretty.
I'm flattered.
- Take a look. See what you want to drink.
- Our old ones were also quite high quality.
I drank too much water before leaving. I already feel full. You guys can order.
Let's eat some desserts.
I'm on a diet lately. You guys can order.
- You're so skinny yet you're dieting?
- I've gained weight.
What about this one?
Yuwei, my high heels are super expensive!
Fine, fine. I don't blame you.
Auntie will get you some food, okay?
I only have low-fat crackers and juice. Do you want to eat that?
Auntie, look! I was drawing your mouth!
Zhang Zhizhi, you better hurry up and take your daughter back!
She has already caused over ¥20,000 in damage!
When she grows up, I'm making her to repay me!
Ahhhhhh!
I'm about to be tortured to death!
Auntie, look!
Do you like to draw?
I'll teach you how to draw.
Tomorrow, Yuwei's mom and I will start preparing the decorations for the site.
You guys do what you are assigned then.
Let's end the meeting here for today.
Waiter, check please.
Hello. It's ¥1672.5
Yuwei's mom, we're paying the bill.
I paid already. Let's go.
I'm kind of tired.
Hey, I paid already, too.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hello, Xiaoling. Are you not home?
Where are you guys?
Great. I'll go over right away.
Zhizhi!
- Where's Yuwei?
- Bathroom.
Bathroom?
How could you let her go to the bathroom by herself?
You need to let her learn how to be independent starting from a young age.
What if there's a human trafficker?
The world doesn't have that many human traffickers.
Mom!
Gu Xiaoling!
What is wrong with you? How could you put this much makeup on her?
Mom! Look!
Yuwei liked it, so I did it for her.
Is this poisonous?
All of these are from big named brands. Very safe. Trust me.
She's still a child!
Mom, there's also this!
We walked past a makeup store and got them pierced.
How could you do this to Yuwei?
Come here.
- Come here.
- But they're so pretty!
Auntie said that women must treat themselves well!
Yuwei is correct!
Gu Xiaoling, you really are something.
- Bye, Auntie!
- Bye, Yuwei!
Zhang Zhizhi, do you want me to watch Yuwei tomorrow as well?
Never again!
Hello? Haowen, send me an email.
It doesn't matter what the content is. I just want to see if my email still works.
Great. Hurry.
[What are you doing?]
Hello? Call my number.
What's with the nonsense? If I asked you to do it, then just do it.
[Lei Haowen]
Liu Yang, thirsty? I'll pour you some water.
No, it's okay.
How come everyone is working overtime tonight?
If you don't leave, then it's not right for them to leave either.
- Why?
- Cause you're the team leader.
Tell everyone to hurry home. I'm about to leave as well.
Mr. Liu said that everyone can go home now!
Oh, right!
Never mind. Hurry home.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Liu Yang, you're back?
- Yes.
What's going on?
I had Xiaoling take care of Yuwei,
and the result is this.
How could you let Gu Xiaoling take care of Yuwei?
You had to work overtime and I had a meeting.
I was only able to find Xiaoling to help.
You still went?
Don't argue in front of her.
Are you hungry? I'll make you a bowl of wontons.
What filling do you want?
Do you want three meats or cabbage?
You decide. You won't listen to what I say anyway.
You're the head of the family though.
Is there anything else you'd like to eat? I can make it for you.
- Lin Ling, I'm going to head back in a bit. Keep an eye on things here.
- Got it.
Manager Li, you're here?
Director Jiang, I have some things to discuss with you.
The welcoming staff have already been trained.
The flowers will arrive tomorrow before 6:00 a.m.
The tea cakes will be here before 8:00 a.m.
The contact names and numbers have already been given to Secretary Wang.
In addition, the agenda has already been discussed with the host. Everything's been discussed.
All of the activities have already been discussed with the people in charge.
The plan is already in order.
Thank you. Thank you. I'm really grateful.
Director Jiang, don't be so polite. Thinking and worrying for the client is our duty.
The most important point is that our company is not your client.
Even if you're not our client, you're still a friend.
Aren't friends supposed to help each other?
Manager Wang.
- Director Jiang.
- Manager Wang,
Go and create a contract immediately.
Our business will order 500,000 batteries from Lubao ahead of time.
Notify the finance department to prepare the deposit.
Our production line will not be operating until half a year later.
Director Jiang, you don't have to do this.
Didn't you say that we are friends? I also consider you guys my friends.
Just take this as my personal thanks to you
as well as our company's sincerity.
- But—
- Yes.
But sincerity needs to be realistic.
What? You don't trust my abilities?
Well, then... Thank you, Director Jiang.
Fine. Let's strike while the iron is hot.
Lin Ling, regarding the contract's specifics, you, Director Jiang,
- and Manager Wang should talk about it.
- Okay.
Director Jiang. Manager Wang.
[Chen Yiming, Work Experience]
[Desired Position: Planning Director
Desired Salary: ¥400,000/year]
Desired Salary: ¥300,000/year]
[Desired Position: Planning Director
Desired Salary: ¥250,000/year]
Desired Salary: ¥300,000/year]
[Hello, this is my resume.]
[Successfully sent]
Are you asleep?
I just got off work.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Are you asleep? I just got off work.]
[Siyu: Are you asleep? I just got off work.]
I just finished work as well.
♫ This city is too magical  ♫
♫  Everything's within reach but falls apart with one touch  ♫
♫  Just like childhood  ♫
♫  wishes  ♫
♫  I've never fulfilled  ♫
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
You cannot park here.
- I'm sorry. I'll leave right away.
- Okay.
Thank you.
♫  loneliness  ♫
♫  Lights are dimming  ♫
♫  yet I'm awake  ♫
♫  Love and bittersweet joys  ♫
♫  Regrets  ♫
♫ You were by my side ♫
♫  The world turns quickly  ♫
♫  Yet footsteps slow down  ♫
♫  Who's shouting?  ♫
♫  Strong yet ordinary  ♫
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears.  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫