Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 6]
Last night, I worked overtime until about 4:00 a.m. again.
Group Two members! Hurry! We have to gather together!
Everyone got a ¥20,000 reward!
I'm sorry. I woke up too late this morning. When I saw your text,
I was so busy thinking about the company and I have been busy ever since.
Sister Siyu! Sister Siyu! The company gave us all prize money!
Calm down, calm down.
"Group leader Li Siyu gets a 20% raise,
as well as prize money of ¥20,000.
Lin Ling gets ¥10,000 as a prize, and everyone else in group two gets ¥20,000.
¥20,000!
What? Let me see.
"In recognition of the hard work and pursuit of perfection by group two,
the company has decided to give awards."
Did you see? A raise of 20% and a reward of 20,000!
- The cake! The cake. Sister, we're leaving now.
- Bye!
The company gives a bonus of ¥50,000 for a ¥500,000 order. Does the company still have rules?
Our company does have rules,
but they don't apply to Pan Zhiyong.
His word is law? Is this company run singlehandedly by him?
He's the major shareholder, as well as the chairman and general manager.
You're also a shareholder. You're even the vice president of this company!
Yes, I am the vice president, but
I have no control over the Finance Department or personnel.
I'm in charge of the security guards, customer service, and sales.
Only one core department, the Sales Department.
And because of my care, it has threatened you. My management even threatened your position.
Senior Brother, I don't blame you.
Sit.
To be honest, according to seniority and skill,
you are the best candidate for the sales director.
But Pang Zhiyong ignored my words at the conference.
He insisted in selecting the sales director in this way.
The most obvious reason
is that you will be led by me instead of him.
My leader has always been you. Of course, I'd listen to you.
So, in his eyes,
you're not his employee at all.
He won't give you this position.
Then...
Li Siyu's his?
In the past, maybe not, but after notice,
he sure seems to think so.
Siyu promised me before that she wouldn't fight me.
Then why did she, for a ¥500,000 order,
make all of her employees work until dawn?
She's already started to battle you.
You're still denying it?
Siyu isn't the type. She takes friendships seriously.
People change. Especially when it benefits them.
The Li Siyu now is not the one from before.
At least now you have time. Don't hesitate any longer.
Let me think about it.
Indecision invariably leads to trouble.
- Sister Yuan.
What's wrong?
We want to ask if there's anything else we need to do?
What else could there be? Go steal some orders.
- Cheers!
- Keep fighting!
Sister Siyu.
Thank you.
Why thank me? You were the one who got the order signed.
Thank yourself.
Without you, this order wouldn't exist.
Without you, it wouldn't exist either.
Honestly, before yesterday,
regarding my father's illness,
I had already given up inside.
But after getting the order signed,
I have gained hope again!
As long as I don't give up, as long as I persist,
my father's illness can definitely be cured.
Lin Ling, we will keep fighting with you.
There will definitely be miracles! Hang in there.
- Yes.
- Keep fighting!
Close more deals following Sister Siyu!
Get more bonuses!
- We will keep getting better!
- Keep fighting!
They're so arrogant.
I'm announcing...
I am giving my prize money and commission all to Lin Ling.
Use it to pay for your father's medical bills.
Sister Siyu!
I will follow you for the rest of my life!
It's just a few tens of thousands.
You act as if you've never seen the world before.
Sister Siyu, rest assured.
For the next three months, I will work as if my life depends on it.
Both for myself, and for you.
I will bring you up to the Sales Director position!
- Yes!
- Sales Director!
Please don't say that.
I'm saying it! We're definitely going to beat sales group one
and let Sister Siyu become the Sales Director!
- We must win!
- Fighting!
Everyone, listen up.
I...
My stomach feels uncomfortable.
Sister.
I'm not going to say anything else. Let's take a picture together as a memento and get back to work.
Great!
Here.
Closer!  Closer!
1, 2, 3. Yeah!
- Let's cut the cake!
- Yes!
It looks good.
I'm in a meeting.
Eat this!
Hey, you're here again today?
A radish is ¥1.50.
It's fresh today.
- Edamame?
- Yeah.
- Please weigh some edamame out for me.
- All right. How much?
- Like... 500 grams.
- All right
Here, that's ¥10.
- How much is it?
- ¥10.
I remember that yesterday you sold it for ¥12. Why's it ¥10 today?
Is it wrong if I reduced the price?
This is the same stuff as yesterday, the same quality as yesterday,
how could you just say you're going to reduce the price?
I can't sell them. You won't let me reduce the price?
I don't want it.
You're crazy.
There is nothing in life that can't be solved with a delicious meal.
If there is, then eat two meals.
So that's saying that good cooking skills is the root of happiness in life.
Cook the oil on medium-high heat. Then quickly pour it over the pepper rings.
Cut the red peppers,
onions, and leeks into strips.
Put the well-marinated chicken into a pot with pieces of garlic, ginger, and sauces.
Cook until tender.
Immediately immerse it into ice water.
Soak the dry peppers in hot water.
Start taking the meat off the well-marinated chicken.
- Why're you here?
- You're home?
Use this type of pepper oil that can be found in the city.
You need to add more pepper oil.
Then add the chicken soup.
After mixing it well, let it sit to let the flavor sink in.
After it's done, sprinkle on some white sesame seeds.
Weren't you in a meeting?
Did I come at the wrong time?
Xiaoling was right.
Some men just want drama.
What?
Chen Yiming, tell me the truth.
Who did you make these dishes for?
Myself.
You're still trying to lie to me?
I'm not lying to you.
I knew early on that something was wrong.
I just didn't say anything.
There's nothing wrong.
Do you dare to give me your phone?
Siyu.
Siyu!
Siyu! Siyu.
Don't touch me! Don't.
No, wait, no. It's not what you think.
- Why don't you come back and I'll explain?
- Let go.
Siyu.
Let go. Let go right now.
Don't make me fight you.
I don't have a job.
I lost my job.
What?
I-It w-was two weeks ago.
I got fired.
How's that possible?
Yeah, I thought it was impossible as well.
B-But it happened.
S-So every day, I have nothing to do.
So I make food to pass the time.
That's great.
That's great!
Are you okay?
What's so great about this?
Turns out that you lost your job.
I thought that you had a change of heart.
Dad!
- Where's Mom?
- She went out.
- When did she leave?
- She left after eating.
Your mom left you alone here? She's so irresponsible!
Son,
- you're home?
- Mom.
Have you eaten yet? I'll make something for you.
- I brought back your favorite—
- Wait, Mom!  When did you come back?
- I came in the afternoon.
- In the afternoon?
Zhizhi said that you work late and that you're busy, so I didn't call you.
- Yuwei. Mom. I'm home.
- You're home?
You're home, too?
Why didn't you tell me as soon as possible?
I was planning on telling you after I found a new job.
Then are you looking?
Yeah. The first day I came home, I started looking.
But I  haven't found one yet.
That's fine. You just lost your job.
It's not like you lost yourself. It's not that bad.
A company like Caijin, that's greedy and lacks insight,
staying there is just wasting your life.
Them firing you is one of the luckiest things that has happened to you.
There must be a company that is better and more powerful than Caijin waiting for you.
I also thought that.
These past few weeks I've sent out almost 50 emails applying to different jobs.
But I've been getting almost no responses.
That's because you haven't met your fate yet.
Finding a job is like finding love.
It depends on the right time, right place, and right people.
Then maybe I have to re-evaluate my own abilities.
You don't need to. You are the best.
What am I good at?
You are able to not believe in yourself but you can't not believe in my judgment.
The men I like definitely aren't lacking.
Siyu...
thank you.
Go take a look.
- A new job is knocking on the door.
- I'm not looking.
- Go. Just go.
- No.
Come on, just go.
Just go take a look.
What is it?
I got rejected again.
I already lowered my desired salary.
But still no one wants to employ me.
[You're here]
[I'm here]
[This is Shanghai]
[We're working towards our dreams]
This is all what you liked to eat when you were little.
Zhizhi called me
and said that Yuwei missed me. And I missed her, too.
So I just got moving.
Mom, you should've still told us. Then we could've gone to the train station to pick you up.
Isn't all of that heavy?
It's not heavy. This is nothing.
I've already come so many times.
After getting off the train, go straight to 34th Street,
then go eight stations. Once I get off, I'm home.
Mom, now that you're here, just stay a few more days.
Didn't you say your heart hurt? Let's go to the hospital for a checkup.
No need. I'm fine.
Oh yeah. Zhizhi will go make an appointment for you tomorrow.
No need. I know my own body.
Moreover, I brought medicine.
Look, there's medicine for the heart, for leg pains...
and stomach medicine.
These days there are big fluctuations in the weather. If you guys are feeling unwell, you guys can have some, too.
You don't need to go through so much trouble.
Mom, don't just take medicine. It's better to go to the hospital.
All right, I got it.
Grandma, Grandma, play with me!
I'm coming. I'm going to play with
- my baby granddaughter.
- Mom,
we still have to go to the hospital.
If something's wrong then we can treat it. If nothing's wrong then we'll stop worrying.
All right, I got it. I got it.
Why didn't you discuss it with me before telling my mom to come?
What are you saying? This is your mom.
Also, I didn't tell her to come.
Mom said that her heart doesn't feel right.
I naturally had to respond.
So I said, well then come and get it checked out.
What did I do wrong?
Don't think I don't know what you're thinking.
You just want Mom to take care of Yuwei,
so you can hang out with those so-called privileged mothers.
I did this for Yuwei.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Let's sit down here.
- These type of people.
- That's right.
You guys... how do you feel about this
I'm saying this...
Just give up!
I have been selling cloth all these years, can't you see?
This is about my family.
How can you be like this.
Second Uncle. Fourth Uncle. Stop bickering.
These three pieces of cloth are all from Shanxi.
- No way!
- Yeah, it's impossible!
I cut these off of the weaver.
I don't think so.
This is not it.
- Hello?
- Hi. Are you Mr. Chen Yiming?
Yes, I am.
We received your resume,
and it really suits our company's needs.
Do you have any time this afternoon?
Our chairman wants to interview you.
Yes. I have time. When and where?
I will text you the specific address and time later.
Great. Also, what's your company's name?
When you meet our chairman, you will know.
West Nanjing Road at 3:00 p.m.
3:00 p.m.
Xiaochen?
I'm here.
Siyu.
How come you're here?
I have an interview here at 3:00. They're almost here.
Mr. Chen. I'm the one who is conducting the interview.
Please don't joke about this.
Mr. Chen. Please introduce yourself briefly.
I don't have time to fool around with you. I really have an interview at 3:00.
Fine. Your introduction is on your resume already. I don't need it.
Right. What are your strengths?
Are you actually the person who brought me here?
How are your driving skills?
Nonsense.
I have an offer for you.
How about you take a look?
The annual income of this position is ¥0,
but you can get a promotion.
You can be promoted into a father,
grandfather,
and if you live long enough,
you could also be promoted to a great-grandfather.
It's not impossible.
I know. Recently, you kept getting rejected,
but it's not because you're not skilled. It's because it's not the right time.
Take a look. Our company saw your strengths,
and immediately made a move.
Don't be depressed and don't
look down on yourself.
Also, our company has also prepared a welcoming gift.
What is this?
Take a look.
[The Best]
Siyu.
Thank you.
Mr. Chen, if you are interested in this position,
please bring a diamond ring to work.
I trust that you will be a very
perfect husband.
Siyu,
I'll keep the offer.
The present,
I will also keep.
I will definitely take the job,
but not right now.
Why?
I think...
I don't meet your needs.
Please...
give me a little more time.
I will bring you a real offer
to start the job you offered.
Thank you.
This is our company's new product introduction and brochure. How many copies do you want?
Please ask Sister Liu.
Okay. This is our company's new product introduction and brochure.
Ask Sister Liu.
Hi. This is our company's new product introduction and brochure. How many copies do you want?
Group one doesn't want them. Let the administration department store them for us.
Okay.
The marriage proposal failed.
How is that possible?
No way!
Why?
- Miss Gu.
- Coming!
You deserved it.
Have some more.
Take this.
I can do it myself.
Yuwei usually doesn't eat extra after coming back from preschool.
Today, she ate such a big bowl of rice.
Grandma's lion head tastes so good!
Good.
- Hurry and thank her.
- Thanks, grandma!
Don't thank me. If you like it, I'll make you nice things every day.
- Mom, you've worked hard.
- No.
Does Liu Yang always come home so late?
Yes. Recently, the company has been kind of busy.
He's been working overtime a lot.
I'm finished. I need to go.
Please take care of Yuwei for me.
Sure. Go work.
She can't eat peanuts or watch too much TV.
I get it. I'll take care of her, rest assured.
Listen to grandma, okay. I'm leaving.
Go, go, go.
- You're back?
- It smells so nice.
You're back? Hurry and wash your hands.
I made you a lot of food you like.
You're leaving again?
Mom is here. It won't hurt you.
Hurry.
- Where is your mom going?
- She's preparing for a party with Miao Miao's mom.
- What does that mean?
- "I Love Mom."
What are you saying? I don't understand.
Mom, don't ask.
Let her do whatever.
Hurry. The food is going to get cold.
I'm washing my hands.
These things can all be found online, and they're half as expensive.
Things online don't have texture.
Linda's mom made an estimate.
Everyone who goes to the party has to pay 1.5 thousand.
Do you think that's too low?
1.5 thousand is low?
Well, if they gave three thousand,
then we could invite children's drama clubs from abroad over to perform.
If it's 1.5 thousand,
we can only invite one from in the country.
Well, they're all putting on makeup and masks.
I don't think you can tell the difference between foreign and from here, right?
The difference is gigantic! Even if it was all from abroad,
London and New York are such different places.
- They're completely different things.
- Really?
Right, Yuwei's mom.
Did Yuwei ever come home and tell you
that Doudou likes to hit people?
No.
Miao Miao has cried about it multiple times.
She says that Doudou always pulls her hair
and kicks her all the time.
Did you tell the teacher?
Of course. There's no use.
Today, Doudou still stole her toys.
Really?
Who do you think her parents are?
How come they don't discipline her at all?
[Mr. Chen Yiming personal delivery]
[Job Hunting Network]
What did you eat for dinner today?
Have you finished your homework?
Did you memorize your text?
What about vocabulary?
Good. Leave it there.
When I come home, I'll sign it.
- Continue.
- Sister Yuan,
Group 2 is acting like a bunch of crazy people.
Yeah, Sister Yuan. Lin Ling works overtime until 12:00 a.m. every day.
The interns in group two act like they're high on drugs.
Xia Xiaotian is the worst of them all.
She's already starting to bug my clients.
This is exactly the effect they want.
But I heard that Xia Xiaotian's performance these days
already surpassed our Huang Bibo.
- Really?
- I also heard that
Jia Shu from Degao Batteries wants to come to our company
and specifically said that he wanted to be in Li Siyu's group.
If it actually happens, I fear that we won't even be worthy opponents.
You look down on Sister Yuan.
But Li Siyu's group has so much momentum.
Sister Yuan, I also think we cannot let our guard down.
The current Li Siyu is not the same one as before.
You still have some time. Don't hesitate.
Fighting!
My target today is 5 effective visits.
Then I'll continue to communicate with the A Lai De company.
Then I'll continue talking with the new clients.
Come in.
Sister Siyu, Director Fang wants you to go to the conference room.
Okay. Wait for me.
We have hope for this one.
This is from last month.
Director Fang.
- Director Zhou.
- Please sit, Siyu. Director Zhou has some things to discuss with you.
This is the invoice you gave the Finance Department last month.
- Yes.
- Please explain what this ¥500 is doing here.
What you claimed is the PR fee on the 25th.
But the invoice was from the 4th of last month.
This ¥500 was overtime money.
Overtime money has its own application process.
It's because the application process for claiming it was too confusing,
So I used the restaurant invoice as replacement.
Sister Yuan knows about this. She signed here.
You think just because Yuan Hui signed this, you can be let off so easily?
General Manager, what are you trying to say?
It's clear that you misreported the PR fees.
I can sell 100,000 kilowatt-hours in one year. Do I need to make a false report about this ¥500?
On the one hand, you earn hundreds of thousands in commissions;
but on the other, you find ways to take smaller bits of money from the company.
- I've dealt with so many people like you.
- How dare you say that?
- There's evidence.
- Go conduct an investigation of the Sales Department before drawing conclusions!
Li Siyu, just because you became a group leader doesn't mean that
the company isn't afraid of punishing you.
Punish me however you want. I didn't misreport the fees.
He Zhou, you guys should leave.
I'll talk to Li Siyu alone.
Li Siyu. Sit.
Li Siyu,
the Corporate Finance Department has already investigated the invoices you made these past few years thoroughly.
There is a total of ¥7,000 that was misreported.
All of that money was what I earned from overtime.
Strictly speaking,
you have committed acts of fraud and embezzlement.
Then that means everyone in the Sales Department is also committing crimes.
But they didn't report others' issues.
They only reported yours.
These files are in our office.
The Finance Department advises us to report you.
I talked to some lawyers.
According to the law, if you misreport over ¥5,000, the shortest sentence is 3 years in prison.
What?
If this really happens,
then your life is ruined.
Telling you the truth,
these years, you really did a lot for our company.
The company doesn't want to go through extreme measures.
We decided to let you make the decision.
As long as you resign and leave Lubao,
the company will turn a blind eye to your actions.
I won't resign.
- Why?
- Because I didn't misreport even one RMB.
There's already so much evidence. You still won't admit it?
If I didn't do anything, why should I admit it?
- Then the company will be forced to report you.
- Go ahead!
Did you know that even if we reported you, you would still have to leave?
When it causes a big scandal and the whole company is influenced,
do you still want to stay in the industry?
- I trust that the police will find me innocent.
- Do you actually think you'd be able to get through the investigation?
If I can't, then nobody here will be able to get through it!
You want to bring everyone in the Sales Department down with you?
I'm telling you. It's impossible.
There's only one way to solve this.
Resign!
I will not resign over this accusation.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Li Siyu, the company has already given you a chance.
If you really insist on taking this road,
don't blame the company for being indifferent.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫