Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 21]
They suspect that I have a mistress?
Who told you to behave so abnormally recently?
Their imagination is too rich.
Women.
Haowen, they didn't talk about me, did they?
You? No.
You don't have any issues, right?
No.
Is there something new with you?
No. Nothing.
Don't just say no.
Talk about it. We will analyze for you. We won't tell anyone.
It's different from what you think.
What is it then?
My office has an intern.
- Girl?
- Nonsense! Would he have any issues with a guy? Continue.
There's really nothing between us. Towards me, she just has a little girl's devotion. Admiration.
Sounds quite dangerous. Would you not be able to control yourself?
It's not that serious.
Having said that,
sometimes I feel tired and bored with Zhang Zhizhi.
But with her even if it's working overtime,
I feel relaxed and interested.
These things are just refreshing in the beginning. Try doing it a long time.
I was talking about my feelings. I didn't talk about the time length.
Don't avoid the topic.
I am the most qualified to speak about this. Your personality is not suitable for an ambiguous relationship.
How is it an ambiguous relationship?
You are not like me. You are not as free and easy as I am. You are not as heartless as I am.
You will put yourself in a difficult position in the end.
You not only will put yourself in a difficult position, but also will put both you and her in a difficult position.
Moreover, Liu Yang, you have an elder person and a child at home.
If anything happens to you, the whole family will be in trouble. Also, you work for the government right now.
From the perspective of investment risks,
your risk is larger than your earnings now.
Don't have any illusions. Don't give yourself any leeway.
Also, I think... you have been with Zhizhi for so many years. That's really not easy.
You need to cherish her.
- Think about it.
- Think about it, Brother.
Tomorrow is your last opportunity to have an assessment.
If you still can't pass,
I suggest that you should buy ¥30,000 worth of batteries to put at home.
How are you supposed to use them? Give them to your girlfriend to use!
When I called, your phone was busy the whole time.
You didn't reply to my messages and WeChat messages.
I've been scolding people.
I bought some skewers and porridge for you.
It's a bit cold now. Heat it up a bit before you eat it.
When did you come?
Around 40 minutes ago.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Even if I need to wait a lifetime for you, I am willing to.
You haven't said anything like that to me in a long time.
Siyu,
during this week of ignoring each other,
I have been very unhappy.
I was unhappy, too.
During this time, I kept thinking...
thinking about what the problem is between us.
To be honest, I still don't agree with what you did,
but the root of the problem is me. I didn't do well enough.
I made you feel insecure.
That's why you're so desperately working to earn money.
That's why you did that.
Sorry.
I didn't take care of things well.
I was wrong. Forgive me.
Yiming...
Doctor! Doctor!
Li Siyu's report has come out. Could you take a look for me?
She is just 32 years old?
That's right.
Young people nowadays...
Look, she has sinus arrhythmia. And her blood fat, blood pressure and blood sugar are all higher than the normal range.
Look, her stomach and intestines also have serious problems.
Then, what should we do?
- What's her job?
- Sales.
Does she drink and stay up late often?
Yes.
Then change jobs or take a complete break for a while.
If she can quit the alcohol, recuperate,
exercise regularly, have a light diet
and balanced nutrients, she might recover.
- Are you awake?
- Where am I?
This is the hospital.
- What happened?
- You suddenly passed out.
Don't move. Don't move. Lie down, lie down.
I'll bend your bed up.
- Is it okay?
- Yes. That's fine.
Your blood pressure, blood fat, and blood sugar
and also your uric acid are all higher than normal.
Your stomach, kidney,
liver, and thyroid also have problems now.
Yiming,
it might be something important.
No matter how important it is,
it will never be more important than your health.
The doctor probably took your ring off when she examined your body.
I'm fine.
How can you be fine?
You stomach hasn't been well for a long time now.
Take the medicine first.
The doctor told me you should take a long break from work and better your health.
If you continue with your situation now and don't fix it, your body will definitely become useless.
It's that serious?
Take a look for yourself.
So, you should rest well right now.
Here, take the medicine.
Be careful. It's hot.
But it's a critical time for Lubao's financing.
Everyone is working hard, how can I take time off work?
Unless I resign and quit.
That's also pretty good.
You want me to resign, right?
Siyu,
you want me to be your backing so you can go out and work hard.
Why do you always think that I am thinking of myself?
That's how it is.
Can you look carefully?
These... are the facts.
I earnestly advised him for hours.
He deeply realized his wrongdoings.
That night, he went to meet Li Siyu, and then they made up.
How did you know?
Yiming called me in the morning. He wanted to find a reliable person
to buy some health care products for Li Siyu to better her health.
That's good then.
I completed the mission which you gave to me.
I guess you were reliable this time.
How are you going to thank me?
Tell me. What do you want?
- Will you give me whatever I want?
- Yep.
I want a girlfriend.
Haowen, if you go out this door, turn left, then turn left again,
there's a hotel. You should get a room and have a good sleep.
You can dream about whomever you like.
Gu Xiaoling.
Make sure you get a receipt. I'll reimburse you.
If you continue to be like this, then no one will help you in the future.
As you wish.
Fine. Remember what you said today.
- How about I treat you to dinner?
- Just keep your "sugar-coated bombs."
(T/N: metaphor for seeming sweet but actually dragging others into trouble)
Mom, I want to watch cartoons.
You already watched one today, you can't watch any more.
Grandma, watch cartoons with me!
Your mom already said you can't watch, so we won't watch. Be good.
Zhizhi, put this in there, too.
Mom, there's still some room in this bag.
I'll give you some clothes that Liu Yang doesn't wear, you can give them to our relatives.
Okay. Zhizhi, your third aunt's little granddaughter,
her height is close to yours. If you have any clothes you don't want, give her a couple as well.
Okay.
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi!
- Yeah?
- What are you looking at?
Oh, it's nothing.
Pack this up, too.
Yuwei.
What's this?
- Car.
- And this?
White Dragon Horse.
Have you packed everything yet?
Pretty much.
I will leave work at 4:00 p.m.
Okay. When you're almost here, give me a call.
Okay.
You want me to go to a different department?
Yes.
Is it because my performance isn't good enough?
No.
Your work performance is very good. It's my problem.
Brother Yang, I want to continue to learn from you.
That can't happen.
Why?
It's for your own good. And for my own good.
We will have a normal leader-subordinate relation from now on.
Did someone say something?
No.
Then why?
Is it because your wife knows something? I can go and explain to her.
It has nothing to do with her.
It's my own decision.
That's it. I'm going back to work.
Slowly.
Mom, get in the car.
What are you doing? Get in the car.
Where's Yuwei?
Chinese Studies class.
Have you packed up all of mom's stuff?
Yes.
Go back.
Mom left so we can go back to normal now.
- It's been days.
- This contract has been delayed for so long.
- Same here. They keep pressuring me for it.
- They've made me really nervous.
- Sister Siyu is here.
- Sister Siyu.
Sister Siyu, we're sorry. You were sick and we didn't even go and visit you in the hospital.
Sis, we were wrong.
It's fine. It's fine. Let's just talk about work.
Sis, I can't handle Daneng Company. You need to make a trip over there.
Sis, sign this. The client is just waiting for you.
This is a fax from Ningbo.
There is also this contract. Take a look. If there are no problems, then sign it.
We've received the final payment from Tianyou Energy. Please sign for it.
Okay, I got it. You all get to work.
Come in.
Sis, this is a package that was expressed delivered.
Okay, give it to me.
Thank you.
Sales performances belong to the boss. Your body belongs to yourself. You belong to me.
Remember to take medicine. Keep your stomach warm. Chen Yiming
First, how the website design influences the website's page views.
[Siyu]
That is the first point.
Another point is how the design and technique will influence the website's visitation.
I'm in a meeting. I will call you back in a moment.
Come in.
Sister Siyu, the latest financial statement.
We surpassed our target for this month.
We created a new record again.
Notify everyone. I am treating everyone to dinner tonight.
Okay!
Sister Siyu will treat us to dinner tonight to celebrate a new sales record!
Yeah!
Thank you, Sister Siyu!
Weren't you going to treat me dinner? I'm hungry.
Gu Xiaoling,
you need to keep your promise. Please fulfill your promise.
The best foods in the world,
the best alcohol on this earth,
and the most handsome boy are all waiting for you.
Who is it?
Me!
Coming.
Why are you looking for me so late?
Let's talk inside.
Talk here.
Aren't you going to let me in to have some water?
Go downstair to buy it.
I saw your boyfriend.
I'm here to warn you that his face looks like he has a bad personality.
You understand reading faces?
Didn't you see? There are hanging needle patterns between his eyebrows. It means his wife is fated to die.
Really?
He also has so much white in his eyes. That means he's ruthless. Finding a boyfriend like that is like signing your death wish.
Then what type of face am I supposed to look for when finding a boyfriend?
You should find a man who is 180 cm, 70kg, born in the year of the tiger, cancer zodiac sign,
and has a pair of eyes that are deep yet clear,
clear yet warm, warm yet hot,
and hot yet full of affection. A hot-blooded man.
You're just recommending yourself.
Don't be so straightforward.
Lei Haowen,
I consider you a friend, but how come you won't stop having wicked intentions towards me?
I also see you as a good friend.
Good things should be shared with good friends, right?
I wanted to share myself with you, is that so wrong?
Pei! (spitting sound)
That guy has a problem.
Even if he has a problem, he's better than you.
- In what way?
- Every single way.
At least I didn't scrounge through a recycling trash bin to get you a present!
Scram! Scram! Scram!
Gu Xiaoling, if you suffer, don't come crying to me.
I wouldn't go to you even if I were dying!
Just you wait, you'll regret it.
Shut up!
[Wang Li]
[Wei Xiaotian]
[Wei Yayun]
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi?
What are you doing?
Did you not have enough intimacy with your colleague at work?
What do you mean?
You and that Wei Yayun, what's your relationship?
Colleagues.
What kind of colleagues?
Normal colleagues.
What did she sew for you?
"You love me, I love you." Normal colleagues?
Who are you trying to trick, Liu Yang?
I thought there was something serious going on. You're freaking out over this?
This scarf belongs to Wei Yayun's boyfriend.
Her boyfriend's name is Li Lei. Did you think just because there is an "L" that it's mine?
Really?
How about we invite Xiao Wei and her boyfriend
over for dinner together one day? You'll know then, right?
Then, how come her boyfriend's scarf is with you?
That day, we had to work overtime until really late at night.
My body felt a little bit unwell.
Xiao Wei lent me her boyfriend's scarf.
You borrowed her boyfriend's scarf?
Couldn't you have left it out somewhere?
Why put it at the very bottom of the storage box?
To treasure it? It was also in a present bag.
Also, your phone.
Why are her call and message logs completely deleted?
I have nothing with her!
You deleted them because of a guilty conscience.
Say whatever you want.
Good morning, Dad.
Good morning to you, too.
Do these Youtiaos taste good?
(T/N: Youtiao is a common Chinese breakfast food that is made of long, fried dough)
Let me try.
Mm... They're really good.
Did you buy them at the new store?
Yuwei, is this soymilk good?
Yes.
Cheers!
Mm.. It's so good.
Dad, can you take me to the Chinese Studies class today?
I can't today. Today, I have to work overtime.
You work overtime every day.
After I'm done with work in a few days, I'll take my annual vacation days.
Then we can take Mom on a vacation out of town. How's that?
Yes!
Yeah!
Then I'm going to work now.
Okay.
I'm going to work.
Listen to Mom.
Okay.
Mom, when are we leaving?
Soon.
Wait for me.
Sister-in-Law.
Is Liu Yang here?
Teacher Liu Yang went to the construction site.
- Where is Wei Yayun?
- Wei Yayun seems to have also gone to the construction site.
Team Leader Liu, you're here.
Thank you.
Be careful up there.
Okay. Team Leader Liu.
Teacher Liu Yang.
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell Xiao Lu to take over your work?
There is some work that needs to be handed over on-site.
So I will continue to work hard until the last minute.
- Where is Xiao Li?
- He hasn't arrived yet.
Take a break then.
Xiao Wei, come here for a moment.
Coming.
- What's up?
- What's this?
It's here. This one.
Xiao Wei? Wei Yayun?
I... You are...
I'm looking for Liu Yang.
Teacher Liu Yang is over there. I will call him.
Teacher Liu Yang!
What's up?
Later, install that one, too.
Why are you here?
You read it before sleeping last night. You left it at home.
I brought it for you. I was worried you would need this today.
You guys talk. I will go back to work.
Xiao Wei.
You gave the scarf back to her, right?
I brought it here. I will give it back to her later.
Okay.
Xiao Wei, didn't you lend me your boyfriend Li Lei's scarf the other day?
Your sister-in-law misunderstood.
Oh.
Thank you for the scarf. Sometime soon,
bring your boyfriend to come to our place for dinner.
I'm leaving now.
Why do you have this cup?
Did you give it to her?
I? I...
Didn't you tell me that there is nothing between you and her?
Xiao Wei, tell your sister-in-law that you bought the cup by yourself. Quickly.
Brother Yang, you gave this to me.
What else do you want to say?
Sister-in-Law! Don't blame Brother Yang. He has done nothing wrong.
Shut up!
Sister-in-Law, Brother Yang and I couldn't help but like each other.
You seduced another person's husband and you are so righteous! How did your parents educate you?
Did they raise you to be a mistress to another person''s husband?
- Zhizhi, let's talk back at home.
- Is it reasonable to be a mistress?
- Why are you saying such nasty things?!
You are still protecting her!
Are you human?
Are you crazy?
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Hello?
Don't cry! What's wrong?
Where are you?
Siyu! Siyu!
Zhizhi.
- Zhang Zhizhi, look!
- What are you doing?!
- When someone slaps you, you slap back!
- What do you want to do?
Hitting women, what kind of man are you?
If you have the skill, fight me 1-on-1!
- Siyu, calm down!
- Whose side are you on?
- Calm down.
- Let's figure out what happened first.
Liu Yang, why did you slap Zhizhi?
Why do you ask him?
You must apologize to Zhizhi!
I was wrong for hitting her.
I apologize.
I gave my heart and soul to you.
How could you do this to me?
How can you still face me?
I didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything?
You still say you didn't do anything?
Did you give her that thermal mug? Did she give you that scarf?
How could you do this to me?
To say the least, even if I did something,
you shouldn't create a scene. How do I face everyone now?
You want face? If you wanted that, then you shouldn't have done what you did!
I already said I didn't do anything.
All right. Everyone, calm down first.
I think for this issue, you should make a statement.
Pay attention to this in the future. Don't always make Zhizhi worry and confused.
Let's both forget about it for now, okay?
I can't let it go.
If we can't clear this up, I can't continue living with him.
If you can't then don't. If anything, just divorce.
You want to make it big now?
Divorce? If we are to divorce, it should be me bringing it up!
If we are to divorce, it should be me bringing it up! What gives you the right to bring up divorce?
- Why are you crying?
- Try yelling at Zhizhi again!
All right! All right! Siyu!
- Let's go!
- Asshole!
Calm down a bit. Calm down.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
En...
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage.
Don't back down from the crowd ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫