Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 13]
Mom, listen to me. Get everything together,
and then at the entrance of our house,
there's a public bus numbered 106.
Then, Mom, ride the bus for five stops. Only five stops.
After you get off the bus, go pass a stoplight,
then cross a road, and you've arrived, Mom.
I got it.
Okay. Be safe.
Okay, okay, okay. Don't worry.
Yuwei, when you're in class,
make sure to listen to the lesson, do you understand?
Mama, I want Dad to take me in his car.
I can't today, Yuwei. Dad has work to do.
Yuwei, be good. Dad works really hard.
- Dad also has to do homework, you understand?
- Yes.
Hey, can't you take her?
I want to. I also want to stay with you.
I've promised those moms. I can't stand them up.
Then have my mom take her.
Okay, okay. I'll go. I'll take her.
Yuwei, Grandma will take you in a bit.
I'll buy you candy to eat.
Mom, Yuwei already has cavities, she can't eat any more candy.
I'm just saying that.
I was just saying it so that she'd come with me.
Then, be safe.
I got it.
- I'm going now, Mom
- Go, go.
- Yuwei, make sure you listen.
- Okay.
- Liu Yang.
- Yeah?
I'll just go alone.
Why does such a little kid need to go to early classes?
Here. Drink some water.
Loot at your dad. He played with chickens and ducks all day when he was young.
He just played like crazy and didn't learn anything. Now he has become a talent, hasn't he?
Mom, the environment Yuwei is growing up in is different from the one I grew up in.
What's different? I don't think anything's different. In my opinion, it's just a waste of money.
Zhizhi said that daughters must be raised in riches.
Raised in riches. She's eating all your money yet she still wants to raise her in riches.
- Zhizhi. Zhizhi.
- Yeah?
Don't look so miserable. Come choose clothes.
Xiaoling, do you think my fight
will get Sister Siyu into trouble?
You've been talking about this since you arrived. Aren't you annoyed by it?
I'm just worried.
Don't worry. Li Siyu is like a cockroach that cannot be killed.
You need to pay close attention to Liu Yang's issue.
Zhizhi, hurry and come choose.
Come over and choose for yourself.
Here, this one.
This won't work, right?
This one. Take it or leave it. If you don't want it, there's no other choice.
- Hello, Aunty.
- Hi, we're here for school.
Okay, school is this way.
Okay. Come quicker, follow the teacher.
- Hello!
- Hi, Teacher.
Hi, what's your name?
I'm Liu Yuwei.
Hi! This is for you.
Take it.
Excuse me, you are...?
Grandma. I'm her grandma.
Grandma, please wait outside. We are about to start.
Okay. Yuwei, study well.
- Don't waste money.
- Yes!
- Go on.
I really can't get it on.
Step down!
How is it?
Chest out. Relax your shoulders.
Relax. Put your leg forward.
- How?
- Put your leg forward. This leg.
Put your leg forward. This way.
Suck in your stomach. Hurry up. Suck in your stomach.
You have to remember that the you right now...
Isn't Yuwei's mom or Liu Yang's wife.
You are not an admin worker of Lubao. You are a beautiful woman.
Beauty.
Look at your skin, it's glowing and so smooth. And your eyes,
are big and bright. Your chest... well, it's not as big as mine.
And your waist... your waist is so thin, your legs are so long.
Zhizhi, put your hands down and look in the mirror.
So charming and seductive.
Is this still me?
Of course, it's you.
Stand up straight. Put your hand down.
We should start to learn English early. We are afraid we will fall behind at the beginning.
Definitely. English must start at a young age.
How old is your child?
- 4 years and 1/2 a month.
- My child is 48 months.
This class is recommended by others. It's too expensive. More than ¥20,000.
It's so expensive yet I don't know how the teacher is.
Ask the kid when it finishes. If the teacher is not good, then we ask for a refund.
We can get a refund?
Aunt, you don't know.
If you aren't satisfied on the first day, you can get a refund for the whole ¥20,000.
¥20,000?!
Aunty, are you really not going to wait until your child is done with class and listen to what she says?
We don't need her opinion. I can decide. Refund.
- I'm in a rush. I have to go now.
- All right.
Xiao Zeng, please help Aunt with the refund.
- Here, drink some water.
- Okay, okay.
Aunt, Liu Yuwei's tuition was paid by a credit card at that time.
According to our rules, the money will be returned to the account in 20 workdays.
- That many days?
- Yes.
Those are our rules.
All right. Then refund in this way.
- Okay. Refund for her.
- Got it.
Don't be anxious.
I'll return these clothes, shoes, and bags to you on Monday.
They say we are just rehearsing today.
Just return the dress. The shoes... well, I won't call them a gift. The bag goes with the shoes, so just keep them.
No, that won't do.
I can't take this bag, it's probably really expensive.
It's not.
How much was it?
Not much.
Look at my bag.
¥58 on Taobao including the delivery fee.
You can even use that?
Yeah, it can hold a lot of things. Look.
Zhizhi, if you are not particular about anything, then others will also overlook you.
If you use a facial cream that's less than ¥100, people won't gift you skincare products over ¥1,000.
If your own bag is cheap, how could you expect others to gift you a Hermes?
Who would give me a gift?
Also your sighing! You really need to change it.
And don't say negative things.
Energy is mutually attracted. You can attract positive energy only if you yourself have positive energy.
You're right. If I always think of bad things,
then bad things will happen for sure.
That's Murphy's Law.
Xiaoling, I didn't expect you to know so much.
In the past did you think that besides loving money and being pretty, I wouldn't understand anything else?
No, I've never thought that.
It's fine if you thought that. If women are jealous of me, it means I'm charming.
Right?
Yuwei! Yuwei, come here.
Is it fun? Here, drink some milk.
It's more fun than early education classes, right?
Aunt!  Aunt, sorry.  Eating is not allowed here.
It wouldn't be good if the kid chokes.
- I get it. I get it.
- Sorry about that. Thank you.
Yuwei, let's go there.
Yuwei! Come here.
Come here.
She pushed you, why didn't you push her back? Are you foolish? Go push her.
Push her.
- Push her, push.
- Hey!
Why did your child just push my daughter?
Your daughter pushed my granddaughter first. Didn't you see it?
Even so, you can't teach the kids to fight.
Who's fighting? It's you who didn't teach your child well.
The apple does not fall far from the tree!
- Let's stop fighting. The kids are here to have fun.
- What kind of behavior is that?
What do you mean "what kind of behavior"? Do you have good behavior? You are uncultured.
- Who is uncultured?
- Let's go.
We don't play with this kind of people. Let's go.
- Let's forget about it.
- Such bad manners.
You are well mannered!
Come here. Let Mom take a look.
You have to be fierce. Don't be as weak as your mom. She can't get anything done.
- The clothes is nice, right?
- Miao Miao's mom, sorry.
- We are late.
- It's okay.
Oh, I tried on some of those formal outfits last night.
I gained some weight recently. I can't put them on anymore.
- Really?
- I plan to wear cheongsam.
I'm going to wear a cheongsam, too.
- We better not have our outfits clash.
- That's right.
Let's go. Let's go. Hurry.
Doudou.
Why is he here?
Come on.
Doudou, behave well, okay? Let's go home.
The teacher told me that the principal has already informed them
to not come here anymore.
Our letter worked.
Doudou, let's go home.
Put it down. Let's put that down, all right?
The more I see him now, the more annoyed I get.
The car is here. Let's get on the bus.
You get on first.
Doudou, don't go there.
The left one.
Stop playing. Let's go home.
Let's go.
The kid is too naughty.
What's the color of your cheongsam?
Green. What color is yours?
Mine is blue.
I want to wear a crystal brooch with it.
Crystal... What color of ear rings can I wear?
Gold. Gold looks nice.
Does gold go well with a green cheongsam?
It depends on how you put them together.
Sister Siyu,
the municipal lighting project has been assigned to Sister Yuan.
- What?
- That's what the Customer Service Department said.
The bidding of the municipal lighting project was clearly mine. Why did you assign it to Sister Yuan?
Because she put it on the records first.
Please look carefully. I clearly put it on the record first.
I will check one more time for you.
Yuan Huizhong recorded it on 10th. it's very clearly written here.
Impossible!
Xiao Jiao, could you please check the records for me again?
Which one?
The municipal lights bidding one.
10th.
Sister Yuan recorded it on the 10th.
Impossible!
Xiao Jiao, the last time we checked, she recorded it on the 16th. Right?
I forgot.
You are the one who checked it for me, how could you forget?
There are so many people coming to me to make and check records every day, how can I remember it all?
I got it.
Did they find out?
The Customer Service Department says they didn't change any data.
The IT Department didn't find out the trace of changes.
The security department checked all the surveillance videos. Everything is normal.
Can I investigate it myself?
Is there a need for that?
Then... does that mean only she can represent Lubao for the bid?
What do you think? That it would be you?
Sister Siyu, you should have taken a photo.
I didn't think they would do this.
You should have known what they are like from the overtime pay issue last time.
I underestimated the enemy!
What do you plan to do now?
I admit defeat.
Now?
If it was only ¥1,000,000, I trust that I can beat them.
But this order is ¥28,000,000, I won't be able to catch up no matter what.
Then she will be the sales director?
I can only leave Lubao now.
Maybe even you
will have to leave.
Sister Siyu, listen to me. I have a solution.
I can ask Liu Yang not to pick Lubao.
This way,
Yuan Huizhong can't get the order. If she can't, you still have a chance to win.
That can't happen.
Why?
First, President Pan needs this order.
With this order, he will have more cards to play when they do equity financing.
Secondly,
that would be unfair. Liu Yang would be breaking the rules.
Elder Sister...
Xiao Chen,
our renting contract will end next month. Will you continue?
If you want to continue, I need to increase the rent.
How much do you plan to increase?
Not much. 15% more.
Hello?
Hello? What do you think, Xiao Chen?
So much more?
If you want to continue, just send me the money for next season's rent.
It's a total of ¥22,000.
If you don't continue, then I will check you out next month.
All right. Got it.
Bro, Sister Siyu had some issue at the company. She is in a very bad state right now.
You should go see her.
I wasn't able to reach you on the phone, so I could only wait here for you.
It's okay.
Ever since President Pan had the talk with me,
I started to be attacked by overt and covert means.
But I survived.
I thought the position of Sales Director was mine for sure.
But who could expect this?
When it comes to getting orders and managing the team,
I don't think I'm worse than Sister Yuan.
But in other aspects,
I will never be Sister Yuan's rival.
Are you happy that I failed?
How could I?
Then, are you mocking me?
Mock you?
How could I mock you?
I'm a failure myself.
Then, what were you laughing about?
Siyu,
come to my hometown with me.
How could I?
Before I came here I gave Zhu Xiaobai a call.
I told him our situation right now.
He said that they have a sales director position that they can give you.
Chen Yiming,
what are you thinking?
You and Sister Yuan have already gotten to this point,
after she becomes the sales director, then there's no way you can stay at Lubao.
Even if I can't stay, I can still go to other companies!
Based on my ability and resources, what job can I not find?
I also thought that 2 months ago.
I was as confident in myself then as you are now.
Was that useful?
At this point,
I am even willing to be a copywriter,
yet still no companies want me.
President Guo wanted you.
Can we not talk about that?
Really.
It's only after...
you really lose your job,
that you realize...
that this market
isn't what you thought it was,
and you yourself
aren't what you imagined yourself to be.
Sister Ziru asked us to dinner tonight.
I won't go.
I have a video conference with Zhu Xiaobai and them tonight.
Are you really leaving?
I only have this much self-confidence left.
And a little bit of self-respect.
I want to...
I want to protect that.
I don't want...
I don't want to continue to waste my time in Shanghai,
and use up money without having any income.
If this is how it's going to be then,
why don't I take a step back?
The sky and sea are boundless, right?
Xiaoling,
you have a lot of things.
You have 88 pairs of shoes. Are you a centipede? Can you wear them all?
It's none of your business.
I spend my own money, buy my own shoes, and walk my own path.
What are you doing?
I have to go in your car. These are all my babies.
I didn't agree to take you to your new house.
How about you beg me?
I'll be benevolent.
All right.
I'll be a nice person until the end.
- Here, seatbelt.
- Hey, I'll do it myself.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Okay, this is the last box.
I'm so exhausted.
Just this little bit of work.
What do you mean by "a little bit of work"?
Your makeup alone is probably about 20 catty.
(T/N:  catty = 1¹/₃ pounds, about 600 grams)
Not to mention your shoes and bags.
Enough. I'll treat you to a meal in a bit, all right?
Let's not go out for dinner.
I can start the fire and help you warm up the place.
You can just cook two of your best dishes for me.
Okay.
My specialty is boiling water.
Then I guess we should go out to eat.
Okay. You choose the place, and I'll pay.
Okay, go out for a second. I'm going to change clothes and then I'll be out.
Just change your clothes here,
I won't watch. I'll close my eyes. I won't look at you.
Hurry and get out.
Believe in my character, I won't look at you.
- I need to change. You get out!
- If I really go out, people will think I'm having an affair with you.
Go to the bathroom and change.
Helping you move is so exhausting, can't you be nicer?
Xiaoling,
we can go and have street food later.
Not a Michelin-starred restaurant.
Don't wear 10cm heels.
8cm is fine.
Also, your precious bags.
Don't carry your Chanel and Gucci.
Or else, you will blame me if they got splashed by oil.
Are you going out with me like this?
What?
Isn't this too casual?
Don't you usually do makeup or something?
That depends on who I'm going with. I'm going with you, so there's no need.
Gu Xiaoling, nobody will marry you if you are snobbish like this.
I don't need you to worry about that.
What if I need to be responsible for you in the end?
No, you won't be needed.
Let's go.
Why don't you understand what I'm saying?
Hurry!
Siyu,
I ordered a soup for you. It's good for the stomach.
Sister Ziru,
how did you know my stomach was not good?
If a saleswoman's stomach is fine,
then her sales performance is definitely not good.
- You get me.
- Drink it while it's warm.
Hey, Siyu.
I remember last time President Pan told me
that there are another two companies in talks about equity financing with him.
What were those two companies called again?
They're on the tip of my tongue, I just can't remember.
That happens to me often as well.
GM Pan didn't talk to you about those companies?
I only really talk to GM Pan about sales.
He usually doesn't tell me about this type of thing.
Oh.
What did he say to you after we met last time?
He didn't say anything.
Is the soup good?
Yes, it's quite good.
You look very down today.
Did you get in touch with everyone on the list of names that I gave you last time?
I went through it.
There are three of them with intentions of cooperating.
That's great. Are your sales performance well then?
What wrong? Is it not enough?
It's fine. I'll have Annie organize another list for you.
Sister Ziru, thank you.
I don't think I'll be able to use your client lists.
What happened?
My competition with Sister Yuan...
ended early.
Wasn't it for 3 months? It hasn't been 3 months yet.
I've already lost.
Why?
- Be careful.
- Please come in.
Your specialties. Each type, one dozen.
- Little spicy.
- Super spicy.
And four bottles of beer.
Four bottles between the two of us?
I only ordered for myself. Order more yourself if you want some.
You are amazing.
What are you looking at? Have you never seen such a pretty girl before?
Are you still Gu Xiaoling?
What do you mean?
Gosh, you aren't normally like this.
Then how am I normally?
You are a goddess in my eyes.
You are a bit goddess—
Think before you speak. Or else, I'll poke you with these skewers.
What I mean is... Aren't you normally elegant and cold?
You are a bit rou... comfort!
I'm feeling very comfortable today.
I'm feeling very comfortable.
It's good to feel comfortable. I'm surrounded by beautiful and rich ladies normally.
I feel nothing.
Because they can never make me comfortable.
Okay, okay. Stop acting.
Don't you get tired of acting like a rich second generation heir all day?
I'm tired.
So tired.
You don't even know how tired I am.
Every day when I go home, I lie on my bed...
I need to gain new insights through reviewing old material.
I have to think, "did my lines today...
have any holes in them"?
"What kind of story should I tell tomorrow?"
You tell me, wouldn't I be tired that way?
Help me.
You can't even open a beer?
Amazing!
In the field of new energy batteries,
when it comes to cost performance,
there is basically no products that can compete with Lubao.
So no matter who goes, he/she will get the order.
Siyu, I feel
that your competition with Yuan Huizhong hasn't ended yet.
Under President Pan's personal interrogation,
the results were the same.
Do you think I still have a chance?
Everything is possible.
Based on my working experience,
as long as it isn't the final moment, I won't admit defeat.
As long as I don't admit defeat, then I still have a chance to turn the situation around.
Sister Ziru, what do you think I should do?
First, tell me about your loss this time.
In what way did you lose?
I think I didn't lose in terms of capabilities.
I lost for being indecisive.
In actuality, I was just soft-hearted.
Siyu, you have the wrong idea.
I must correct you.
Decisiveness is a capability, isn't it?
A little girl being softhearted,
it means she is kind. She values her friends.
That is a very good virtue.
But in the workplace,
especially in the managerial position,
this is not a good trait.
The workplace only looks at your performance.
Your performance needs you to have a shrewd and calm mind,
and decisiveness.
What you mean is I'm not professional enough?
At least in your competition with Sister Yuan,
your positioning is not high enough. You are too softhearted and emotional.
But people are sentimental and have emotion!
But mature people are more rational.
You only care about your friendship but don't care about the company's development,
then do you also not care about your subordinates and your livelihood?
Siyu, I'm not saying being sentimental is not good.
But to be an outstanding professional manager,
you must be rational and calm at all times.
For the company's development,
for the success of a career, you even need to be cold-hearted.
But only by doing this, you can go higher and further.
Sister Ziru, what you said...
I don't know if I can do it or not.
If you want to realize your dream,
then work hard in this area.
You will suffer but you will benefit from it eventually.
To survive in the workplace is actually easy.
Do what you need to do in your position.
Don't let the company down. Don't let yourself down.
Do you want to add more food?
Waitress, add another order of intestines!
What's wrong?
Intestines don't fit your image at all.
But I like it.
Let me tell you. I have loved to eat intestines since I was young.
Your taste...
is not only strong but also greasy.
It's all because of my dad.
When I was young, my dad took me to eat intestines in the street every week.
Next time, I will take you to enjoy the best-brined intestines in Shanghai.
But he died when I was 8 years old.
When did your mom marry Li Siyu's dad?
When I was 12 years old.
Actually my stepfather treats my mom and me very well.
The life before that
was too miserable.
It was all because we didn't have money.
How nice it would be if I could get to know you at that time.
Who I wanted to meet at that time was not you!
Who?
I really liked watching "Meteor Garden" when I was young,
I thought I was the girl in the drama and I was waiting for my boy every day.
Guess what I watched when I was young.
- Doraemon?
- No.
“Youth and Danger.”
(T/N: a gangster movie from Hong Kong.)
That movie laid the foundation for my dreams!
You even have dreams?
Of course. I want to make a lot of money,
I wanted to be a gangster boss. Thinking about it now, it seems silly.
But at that time I vowed, if I become successful one day,
I will go to Macau. I'm natural and unrestrained. My friendship is priceless.
I wish your dream to come true.
- Here, cheers to our dreams.
- Cheers!
President Liang, I'm sorry. I'm only just now returning your call.
Don't worry. I will take care of your order very well.
Manager Tang, I've already signed off on the contract.
I'll send it out tomorrow. When you come to Shanghai, I'll treat you to a meal.
President Xu, I'm so sorry.
I had something come up unexpectedly yesterday, so I didn't have time to respond to you.
If it's convenient for you, I'll go visit you at 11:00 a.m. tomorrow.
Okay. Then I'll see you tomorrow morning.
Just now, Zhu Xiaobai called, asking me when I can go back.
Have you thought about it?
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫