Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 14]
Today, I ate so happily today.
Exactly! The most important thing as a person is happiness!
Besides happiness, you also need money!
Happy, happy.
Xiaoling,
can I consult you about something?
What thing?
Be my girlfriend.
I promise you,
I'll be super successful in the future.
Okay?
Lei Haowen, I see you as a brother.
I can't believe...
I can't believe you think of me that way.
Miss, it's not like that.
What way do I think of you?
But I don't want to just be your brother.
Then don't be my anything.
Is there no room for negotiation?
We could also be best friends.
Fine. We will be best friends.
Hey, slow down.
- My shoes.
- One, two.
Two. One, two.
One, two.
Okay.
Two.
One, two.
I'm sorry. Let's take a break.
When did you get here?
Just got here.
Didn't you go out to eat with GM Wang?
We just finished.
Today, Sister Ziru said some things that confused me deeply,
but Sister Ziru said something else,
that really encouraged me.
So I came to find you.
Is that so?
Yiming,
I'm not leaving Shanghai.
Why?
First:
my competition with Sister Yuan isn't finished yet.
Second: even if I lost the competition and got kicked out of Lubao,
I still wouldn't want to leave Shanghai.
Yiming, don't leave either.
We can fight together.
I'm going to go change.
There's a traffic jam.
There are traffic jams all over this city.
The house prices are high, the living cost is high.
If we can't save money, then the air quality is also bad.
You forgot one more thing. Here, success is hard.
But failure is easy.
But there are opportunities here.
Siyu,
there's a ready opportunity right in front of me.
In the past, when we worked so hard on studying and entering college,
and forced ourselves to get into good colleges,
wasn't that so that we could find a developed place and see the world?
We've only just recently gotten some small achievements, why do you suddenly want to go back?
These small achievements might matter to us, the things we've gotten,
in this city, mean nothing.
We've worked hard for seven years, the money we've saved,
the statuses we saved, and the resources we've saved
all got used up so fast.
Yiming, all of these things you're facing right now are temporary.
It'll all pass over.
The only things that are temporary are our feeling of success from the past.
If you think our ways of living are a problem,
then we can choose not to buy a house right now.
Our income is enough to stay and live in Shanghai.
Siyu,
it's not that I can't live in Shanghai.
I just don't have confidence in this city.
If I stay here,
I worry that I'll lose every last bit of self-dignity I have.
It couldn't be that bad.
Do you know why I didn't go work for President Guo?
It's because I'm petty, I'm narrow-minded.
I kept doubting for no reason,
how we could have turned out like this.
Because I feel inferior.
And I'm scared of losing you.
I really hate... I really loathe resigning like this.
But if I stay in Shanghai,
I know I will become like that.
But if it's like that,
then we'll have to be in a long-distance relationship.
Yiming, stay.
Siyu,
leave with me.
The car is here.
I'll take you.
♫  Like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
It's this one.
Here.
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
- Is this the car you called?
- Yes.
Please drive slowly. Be careful.
♫  Getting through long nights  ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But is as lost as others  ♫
Yiming, stay.
Siyu,
leave with me.
♫  Never giving each other the chance to breathe  ♫
♫  Thought that being loved by you  ♫
♫  Thought that we wouldn't age  ♫
♫  Wouldn't separate  ♫
♫  Yet as I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
- Hi, Sister Siyu
- Good morning.
Lili.
- Sister Siyu.
- Where are the rest of them?
They said...
that our group lost. They were scared you wouldn't come.
So they gave themselves a break.
Then, why didn't you go on break?
I knew you wouldn't give up that easily.
Notify all of them. We're having a meeting immediately.
Okay.
The demon has returned. Hurry, everyone, let's have a meeting.
Liu Xiaojia, do you think that
because we've lost, you can give yourself a break?
You aren't contacting the clients anymore,
you've stopped calling, and you've stopped chasing contracts.
It wasn't like that.
I'm telling you.
Even if we admit defeat, it will be after the three month period is over.
If the time isn't up, then we still have a chance.
- But—
- But what?
You think that just because they're beating us by 20 million,
we won't be able to catch up no matter how hard we try. Right?
Yes. I also don't think we'll be able to catch up.
But even if we can't catch up we should still try.
We can lose this battle, but we can't lose the war!
Yes, we have to endure it and not give up.
Are you enduring it? Have you not given up yet?
I have been.
Are you under the impression that making 30 calls a day counts as persevering?
I'm telling you.
Today you make 30 calls, tomorrow 35, and the day after that 40. That's what counts as persevering.
Everyone, get in better spirits!
Sister Siyu, don't worry!
We will all improve!
Fighting! Fighting! Fighting!
Sister Siyu, come out for a second.
Yuan Huizhong has been colluding with people in and outside of the business.
They've tricked the company out of more than five million batteries.
That can't be. Who in the company?
I've heard it was called... Meiyi Group
Meiyin Group?
GM Pan got the Legal Department to investigate that company,
and he said that the business license, their office, their official site,
and their news links are all fake.
What?
That four million is my fault. I am willing to accept any punishment that the company gives me,
but I really didn't collude with those people.
Then why did you, in front of me and Pan Zhiyong,
admit that you knew them?
I- I was just saying that.
I trusted your word. I even came up with evidence to help you.
The Legal Department has already reported this, and the police department has also started its investigation.
I've been to Meiyin Group before,
and I've met the director of their office.
Were you tricked, too?
They had originally contacted Lin Ling,
- but Sister Yuan stole the order.
- She deserved it then.
- Sister Yuan is also a victim.
- No, she's not!
I heard that she's known that group of con artists for many years.
That's the reason why we suspect her of being in on it.
No. Sister Yuan really doesn't know them.
Liu Jie can testify for me.
On the day of the signing, it was also my first time ever meeting those con artists.
Liu Jie is on your side. How could anyone believe what she said?
Li Siyu and Lin Ling were also there.
They... Would they really help you?
Hey! What are you doing?
I'm going to find GM Pan and tell him what's really going on.
You're helping her? Don't you remember how she treated you?
But she truly did nothing wrong.
She's wronged you so many times.
Don't be stupid. The company has rules.
If she really was tricked,
then four million, even if it was forty million, would no longer matter,
but if she really did collude with them, then she will be fired.
But Sister Yuan didn't collude with anyone.
All she did was make a mistake.
I heard that GM Pan is already convinced
that she and those con artists are working together.
He wants the Supervision Department to fire her.
Fang Zhan was staring at us the entire time.
They've fought multiple times.
If you stand up for her now, wouldn't you be creating a mess for GM Pan?
At the time, they were trying to steal my order, yet they somehow took a bad one?
What a reversal of heart.
Lin Ling, at the time, when you were with that Director Luo,
did you not notice anything out of place?
That Director Luo was quite strange.
How so?
He always vanished and liked to talk the big talk,
so after talking to him twice, Liu Jie gave up on him.
How did you discuss the contract with him?
He didn't really care about the price.
But his one condition was that after the deposit was paid, we needed to send him the entire supply of batteries.
Our work is quite tight,
so we don't want to stall every phase.
How about this, after sending you the deposit,
you will send me the supply. Within a month,
I'll give you the rest of the money. Is that okay?
This...
seems to be a little problematic.
I remember that earlier, there were two others. One was named
Li Siyu? Manager Li? I wonder if she would agree.
Hey, Director Luo,
How about this?
You can pay a deposit of 20%
and I will agree with your payment methods.
However, I have a condition. You must sign the contract now.
Sure. Sure. No problem.
No wonder. The price Sister Yuan negotiated was quite good.
Sister Yuan definitely gave him an advantage on the way of shipment.
We're in so much danger.
Lin Ling, do you think
we should help Sister Yuan clear her name?
Clear her name on what?
Right now, GM Pan is convinced
that Sister Yuan and Director Luo were working together.
However, we both know that before this, they didn't know each other.
Sister Siyu, if you want to help her, you can go.
- I'm not.
- Lin Ling.
Don't forget how they treated us before.
You should go back.
She brought it on herself.
- Were you looking for me?
- GM Pan.
I also had some things to say to you. Come in.
Here, sit.
You've heard about the things regarding Yuan Huizhong, right?
There have been rumors.
The company cannot tolerate her behavior, so the government program
and the management of the Sales Department have been all given to you.
- Me?
- Yes. You!
You need to prepare yourself ahead of time to take care of all of the work you will do in Sales.
GM Pan, how will the company punish Sister Yuan?
She let the company down to serve her own self-interest.
We must kick her out. No one will be able to get her out of it.
So you have to be ready to take over all the work.
Did you have something to tell me when you came?
No.
- Sister Siyu.
- Hi.
[Sales Department]
Come in.
Why are you closing the door?
- Sister Siyu.
- What?
I heard that you're officially being announced as Sales Director tomorrow.
- Who told you that?
- Everyone is talking about it!
Did you know, Sister, Kuai Zi, who always looked down on me, is now calling me Sister Jia?
- Isn't she older than you?
- Who cares? I'm her superior.
If they won, then she'd be my superior.
Also, Sister, Huang Bibo and the others are very worried
that you might fire them when you become Sales Director.
Zhang Siting, Sister You, they're both looking for new jobs.
- Why are they doing that?
- This time you won.
If they had won, then we'd have no food to eat, and no job.
Sister Siyu, should we celebrate a little early?
We still haven't won, what would we celebrate?
- Tell everyone. They need to stop spreading this.
- What?
Is there anything else?
Then I'll leave first.
Tomorrow morning, 10:00 a.m. The office will discuss your punishment.
Li Siyu and Ling Ling's testimonies are very important.
Li Siyu, you are just a poisonous snake who wanted revenge.
I'm going to be the sales director.
No, I'm going to be the sales director.
What else is there to think about?
Go to the Supervision Department or go find GM Pan.
Tell him what you know. Or you could go straight to Sister Yuan.
Tell her that you can prove that she doesn't know this liar.
If I do this, it doesn't benefit me.
But you should do this.
If I do this, then Sister Yuan can stay at the company.
As long as she stays in the company, she can represent Lubao and bid.
As long as she takes this bid, then she becomes the Sales Director!
Then what about me? I'll have to leave Lubao.
If you have to leave, then leave. What are you afraid of?
You can go to a different company.
You could also go to my hometown with me.
Zhu Xiaobai's company has a sales director position for you.
You just want me to leave Lubao and go to your hometown with you.
Li Siyu, do you really think of me as that kind of person?
Then why do you want me to dig a hole for myself?
Because this is the right thing to do.
It's not as simple as right and wrong.
I know that the situation is complicated,
but your choice is simple.
What do you mean simple?
This not only affects my future,
but it also affects my group members and GM Pan.
It even affects Lubao.
How about I put it like this?
Sister Yuan leaving will be good for everyone.
- Well, she shouldn't have to leave in this way.
- This is the way she would've wished for me to leave.
You should be the bigger person here.
That's you.
Sister Yuan's phone call.
You have to do this. You must.
I must.
Sister Yuan.
Everyone in the company has been talking,
saying that I have been connected with the con artist for a long time.
You said it yourself.
You know that it's not true.
Tomorrow, at 10:00 a.m., the company has arranged a meeting to discuss
whether or not I should be fired.
Siyu...
You need to help me tell the truth.
I can't be fired, not for this.
Siyu...
Please help me.
I can help you tell the truth,
but you need to tell me the truth as well.
What?
The government bidding project
was recorded by me first, not you.
I would help you with anything else, but not this.
Why? It was my performance originally.
Whoever gets this twenty-eight million will be able to win faster.
That might not be true.
All along, what you wanted wasn't the project.
It was the sales director position?
Think what you want.
I just want to take back what was mine originally.
I wanted you to testify for me because I wanted to stay at Lubao.
I wanted to stay at Lubao because I wanted to be the sales director.
Now that you use this as a condition,
do you think there would be any point in my staying at Lubao?
At least we would each do what was fair.
Let me tell you what "fair" means.
I worked so hard for Lubao and gave up so much for it. If I were the sales director, then it would be fair.
Then, what about justice for me?
You stole clients from me one after another, shouldn't I get justice as well?
You shouldn't have made me an enemy then.
You were the one who forced me into such a position.
Tomorrow, are you going to help me or not? If you do,
then I can forget about everything from the past.
Give me the government bidding project back.
Li Siyu,
I'm going to ask you one more time.
Will you help me or not?
Give me the government bidding project back.
Did you finish discussing with Sister Yuan?
If you give that project to her,
then your chances of being the sales director are gone.
But after tomorrow, if I have to leave Lubao, then I'll lose even more opportunities.
Who said so? The results of tomorrow's meeting
are still not decided.
Senior Brother, it looks like I really can't stay at Lubao.
Trust me.
You have us.
Enter.
Sister Siyu, when are we leaving?
- How about 11:00?
- Sounds good.
- Hello? Sister Siyu?
- Zhizhi,
where is the meeting at 10:00 taking place?
Let me take a look.
10:00... The director's office.
I understand.
Are you really leaving?
Lin Ling, what's wrong?
What's wrong with her?
- I... I'm writing my resignation letter.
- You're doing perfectly fine right now.
Why would you resign?
Last night,
when I was working overtime, Director Fang approached me.
I'm sorry, I can't help Sister Yuan with this.
Lin Ling, I didn't ask you to lie.
I just want you to tell the truth.
If Yuan Huizhong is removed from the company because of this,
wouldn't your conscious hurt?
Director Fang, I'm on Sister Siyu's team.
Whatever I should say and do...
are up to her.
Lin Ling.
Don't act like I don't know.
You were the one who approached that con artist.
If we really need to find someone to blame,
then the first to be fired would be you.
Director Fang, I don't know what you're saying.
Don't forget.
I'm still this company's vice president.
Did you think that she could protect you?
So, that's why you're resigning?
I won't help them speak,
so they definitely won't let me go.
A few days ago,  Feiyu Batteries was still scouting me.
I didn't want to go at first,
but now, it seems to be an exit path.
How far have you gotten on your resignation letter?
I just started it.
[Resignation Letter]
You want to lower your head to them?
I won't lower my head and you don't have to resign.
Lubao isn't run by Fang alone.
Okay.
Xiaotian,
let's go visit the client.
But don't we leave at 11:00?
I changed my mind.
What are you doing?
I was just... cleaning up the things that could be sent by courier.
You're still leaving?
Yes. I promised Zhu Xiaobai
that I will report to his company within half a month.
What happened with Sister Yuan's situation?
I didn't say anything.
Why not?
She doesn't deserve my help.
If you did it, you wouldn't be doing it for her, but for yourself.
I know. You wish that I was kind and magnanimous,
but what would I get by doing that?
My kindness gets rewarded by suspicion.
My magnanimity gets returned by finding all sorts of ways to frame me.
In the end, I get nothing.
- But at least your heart is at peace.
- What could a peaceful heart possibly do for me?
If GM Pan wasn't always standing by me, I would have been kicked out long ago.
So you must treat people
the exact same way they treat you?
I didn't cause her any harm, I just kept quiet.
But that's still so shady.
As long as I am the winner, then that is the biggest glory.
- Is your career that important?
- If careers weren't important, then why would you leave Shanghai?
In Shanghai, you feel like a failure.
You feel like you've lost all of your confidence.
I'm sorry.
Yiming, I never thought you were a failure.
I really don't have the right
to ask you to do what I planned.
Are you disappointed in me?
No, I'm disappointed in myself.
If you want to go back, then go.
Then...
- then we...
- We can have a long-distance relationship, I guess.
Long-distance?
Anyway, I'm not leaving you.
Zhizhi,
- can I not go?
- You have to.
Can't you just take Yuwei?
The whole family has to go make an appearance
at this kind of party. It's the right attitude.
It also expresses that you find your child's education to be important
and also expresses respect to the people who host it.
But whenever I think of Miao Miao's mom's face,
- my heart feels deeply unsettled.
- That was in the past.
Nowadays, we're quite close.
I still have work.
What kind of expression is that?
That outfit
makes you hard to recognize.
This...
Is it pretty?
- Yes.
- Mommy is so pretty!
Let's go.
Come in.
Come on in. Welcome.
Let's go play.
- Be careful.
- Hi, Xingxing's mom.
- You're here?
- Where's Xingxing's dad?
He's... Oh, he's
over there chatting with Weili's dad.
They used to be schoolmates in the Ivy League.
Yuwei's dad, did you go to the states for college, too?
What school?
- Is Xingxing's father looking for you?
- No, we can leave him.
So, did you get your undergraduate and master's degrees in America?
- Honestly.. .
- Honestly, they weren't very prestigious schools.
Compared to Xingxing's dad,
we're too embarrassed to say.
Everyone says that our party
is so much more superior to Vivian's sorority party.
- What do you mean Vivian?
- Do know what her family used to do for a living?
- What?
Her father was a farmer.
No way!
- You're all here?
- Come.
Yeah. Your outfit is so pretty.
Yuwei's father is also here? Hello.
Yuwei's dad, you work at Guangcai Engineering and Construction, correct?
Then you probably know Wang Changhai, don't you?
Yes. He's our department's leader.
Aren't you also a leader?
- Yes.
- Really?
Let me tell you. Wang Changhai's wife was my classmate.
We're often at reunions together.
If you have time, we can all hang out together!
Linda's mom, how are you liking my party so far?
- It's wonderful!
- Really?
- Perfect!
Look at the children, they're so happy.
- Yeah. They love it.
- Exactly. It's amazing.
- Oh right.
Let me introduce some friends to you.
There's a designer from France.
It would be perfect. He could design some prettier clothes for you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Come, let's go.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫