Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 18]
How are you doing lately?
It's okay.
What do you mean by okay? You are doing excellently for sure.
What are you up to recently?
I'm doing research about Lubao.
Research about Lubao?
About what?
You shouldn't ask me. I won't tell you.
Why?
Because GM Pan and President Wang are rivals in negotiations.
We work for different companies. We do our own job.
This is a career requirement.
Why do I feel distant suddenly?
How come?
This is nothing to do with us. It's just work.
What if I feel It's related to us?
If you feel so,
then you need to change your mentality in the future.
I don't ask about your work.
I won't reveal my work to you as well.
Okay!
Then let's change topics.
Are you satisfied with the house?
Absolutely. As long as it belongs to you and me.
I'm always satisfied.
Sorry for keeping you waiting long.
How can I help you?
We decide to buy the apartment we saw last time.
The one on Jiangyang Rd?
Yes.
Mr. Chen called me yesterday and I took it down incorrectly. I wrote down another one.
That one was sold a few days ago.
Let's have a look at others?
Here you go. Thank you.
Okay.
Older brother.
Get one for me.
You bought one the other day, right?
I want to buy another one.
This is for you.
For me?
You said your stomach wasn't well, right? Take this to drink more hot water.
Brother Yang, I know this brand.
It's expensive.
It's just a thermal cup.
Thank you.
Look at you. Why are you tearing up?
You are too nice to me.
Silly girl.
Didn't you say it's an art exhibition?
Yes.
The exhibitors are all selected in Florence Biennale.
They are definitely top-level.
Beautiful.
Actually, jewelry design also has classicism, Orientalism,
abstractionism. They also can be affected by abstractionism.
Picasso's daughter is the representative of surrealism.
Tiffany is modernistic.
What style do you prefer?
Me... My favorite is Tiffany's paper flower series.
It integrates the modern with rigidness and softness.
It's rather romantic and harmonious.
Now I know. Wait for me.
Thank you.
Xiao Ling, you will like it definitely.
You are right.
The designer's mastery of the shadow, color, and lines is wonderful.
Each of the design drawings is art.
It is!
If you say he loves me, he wears an expensive watch.
He drives a luxurious car and lives in such a big villa.
And he just gave me this. If you say he doesn't love me,
he asks me out for food every day. He sends me countless messages
full of love. It's not like acting.
This is not love and romance.
This is being stingy.
If a man really likes a woman, he is definitely willing to spend money on her if it's within his competence.
Xiaoling, break up with him.
No!
Why?
I don't want to regret it when I get old.
There was such a good man in front of me. But I gave up by myself.
But this man doesn't love you.
No. He loves me.
He is just stingy.
It does matter. After getting married, his money is my money. I can spend it freely.
Such a stingy man,
will share his money with you?
Xiaoling, do you love him?
I love money and he has money. So I love him.
If you love money so much, why don't you go and make some yourself? Why do you have to depend on a man?
Li Siyu,
you are smart, capable, and went to a good university.
I was not this type and my family couldn't help me as well.
My only advantage is having this face.
Rich people are not stupid.
Even if they like you, why should they marry you?
So I tried to enrich myself and made myself become more capable.
I work out every day and I play golf very well.
I read all the subscriptions on WeChat.
Can you manage to read them all?
So I learn art appreciation from him.
I changed my job from a real estate company to the golf club and
to the art gallery. My next step is to learn English.
I'm not cutting corners like you think.
It's tiring.
You think that if you marry a guy from a rich family that everything will be okay?
What if he has a mistress?
You think you find a poor boy and there won't be a mistress?
I trust Liu Yang anyway.
Don't listen to her. I think Liu Yang and Yiming are both not like that.
By the way, how are you doing with Liu Yang?
Yesterday, he
bought an expensive thermal cup for me.
A thermal cup makes you this happy?
Well, it's still better than a picture album.
Zhizhi, you followed bad examples! You satirized me!
Don't.
You made peace?
Family issues will never be finished.
Zhizhi, why didn't you wear the clothes I gave to you?
Why are you still using this bag?
They are too expensive. I'm reluctant to use them.
You are not promising.
Zhizhi, I asked you last time.
Are you willing to work for me in the sales department?
Thank you, Sister Siyu.
I've discussed it with Liu Yang.
Yuwei is still very young.
She can't leave her mom. I will think about it in the future.
I told them, Liu Yang
won't cheat on me certainly.
Can you talk about more meaningful topics when you women get together?
Meaningful?
Why haven't you thrown this cup away?
It's still good. Why throw it away?
Use the new one.
They are both the same. Both for drinking water.
Where did you put the cup I bought for you?
I refunded it.
Refund?
It's too expensive.
When I refunded it in the shopping mall,
they didn't let me at the beginning.
They said I didn't have a receipt.
You know what happened afterwards?
I told them that if you don't refund my money,
I will report to the shopping mall about doing business in the street.
A cup...
- It's a whole lifetime.
(T/N: Cup and lifetime sound very similar in Mandarin.)
- Then they finally softened,
and refunded me with a shopping coupon in the end. It's also okay.
When will your mom go back?
I will persuade her step-by-step.
It seems that for the valuation of Lubao, we each
have quite a few disagreements.
I don't think president Wang is confident enough about Lubao.
Confidence should come from strength.
But don't forget I still have
Lubao3, which is far superior to Lubao2.
GM Pan, I heard Lubao3 has flaws.
This is from Gao Zhengdao, right?
To sell his own theory,
he attacks everyone. He's almost out of his mind now.
I will find a time to write an article to fight back
in order to sober him up and ensure the public to have a correct understanding of the facts.
I attended the professor's lecture, but my conclusion
is not drawn from him.
My company did a bit of research.
[Lubao Valuation Report]
Teacher Wu, I inquired a lot.
I couldn't find a chance to strike.
I think he is preventing me on purpose.
What if we reveal
the relationship between Liu Yang and Li Siyu?
It hasn't been verified yet.
But if we don't take action now.
Next week, when those five experts open the bid, we're doomed.
How do you know it's five experts?
Director asked me to entertain them.
I'm working on their travel and meals.
- You know which five experts?
- Of course.
Have a look! Read carefully!
Why did Wang Ziru have this report but I have nothing?
Wang Ziru knows the problem it reflects but I don't!
Why?
GM Pan, we actually are also working on this.
We planned to hand it to you at the end of this month.
It's a dereliction of duty to fall further behind than others!
GM Pan, from the perspective of testing data,
Lubao3 doesn't have issues at all.
User experience is
always much more important than the data test.
But the issues reflected in this report are biased indeed.
But it put me on the defensive in the negotiations.
Li Siyu, don't think you are not involved in this issue.
Answer me. What have you been up to lately?
I'm working hard on the target to closing the ¥500,000,000 deal in 3 months.
- How much have you closed?
- Over ¥200,000,000.
This report made us lose ¥300,000,000!
As sales director, you only care about sales performance,
but neglecting your product, this is also a dereliction of duty!
GM Pan, I think this report reminds us
that before Lubao3 reaches perfection,
if we promote this into the market on a large scale,
I'm afraid it's a bit risky.
Let me ask you... What's perfection?
What is perfection?
It's already perfect to upgrade the product!
Is it risky to improve the performance of the product while it is in use?
If it takes a risk, then I will certainly do it!
Look into this report.
Find the weakness. I must win back in the next round of the negotiations.
That's all for today. Li Siyu, stay.
- How is the bidding going?
- Almost done.
GM Pan, before printing and packaging, would you like to have a look?
No need.
Not even check the quote?
You decide by yourself. I only have one requirement:
You must win this bidding.
GM Pan, no one can promise this.
You must promise me.
Li Siyu, this is the situation.
This report...
makes our only hope uncertain now.
So we must win the bidding. Otherwise, you and I
will both be kicked out.
This is from you, right?
Yes.
Why did you secretly investigate Lubao?
First, I didn't secretly investigate.
I did it open and aboveboard. Second, I mentioned it with you before.
But you didn't say you were investigating Lubao3.
Could I tell you all?
Do you know, your report makes my hard work for the whole month in vain.
That means you didn't do your job well.
Why do you talk like old Pan?
You were scolded by Old Pan?
Yes. Very angrily.
This means that Old Pan got beaten in the negotiations with President Wang.
You are even laughing now!
This means I did my work well. Of course, I should laugh.
What work? Look at your wording. It's complete slander!
Every word in this report is true.
Lubao is worth less than ¥4,000,000,000. Is it true?
If Lubao3 can solve the problem that I put forward,
then Lubao could reach a value of ¥4,000,000,000.
But now, it definitely can't.
Why do you just focus on the problems but neglect the advantages?
This is my job!
My job is to remind my boss to avoid trouble and to be careful.
Have you ever thought about if
my boss was to know that this was from you. What would he think of me?
These are two different things.
This is the same! He will even think that I revealed something to you.
Wang Ziru will also think of this.
So you are sacrificing me.
I'm not.
I'm doing my job. You didn't know anything.
Who will believe this?
Believe it or not, we have to
try to do our own jobs.
The problem is that you could have done a lot of things, but why did you just work on this report!
This is the biggest project in Tianye.
Since I've started working in Tianye,
I have to do something to prove myself.
The result of proving yourself is to put me in danger.
This is exaggerating. Does it have something to do with us?
I said this is a game between two companies.
We started to play a game between our companies.
I didn't want to play games with you.
You can cheat yourself. But don't cheat others.
Siyu. Siyu!
Come up with your solution based on this report.
Give it to me before you start work the day after tomorrow.
[Yiming]
Remember to keep it confidential.
Spreading rumors are absolutely not allowed.
That's all.
[The name list of the experts in the street lighting bidding]
[Yiming]
Thank you, Brother Yang. Thank you in advance for your care in the bidding.
I will put it straight. Even though I'm the team leader,
I can't decide on the result in the end.
It all depends on the product.
I know.
Don't worry. I won't make you feel difficult. Everything follows the rules.
I just ask if you have some internal information,
let me know in advance so I can be better prepared.
As long as it doesn't violate the principle,  as long as I won't be accused of practicing favoritism,
I will try my best to help.
[Liu Yang]
Next step, we will hand the job to the expert team. We will just assist.
To avoid arousing suspicion, let's not meet each other for a while.
Are you all right?
You decide by yourself. I only have one requirement.
You must win the bidding.
GM Pan, no one can promise this.
You must promise this.
Director Li. Director Li?
- Director Li. GM Pan went out.
- Oh, okay.
Never mind.
[Print]
[The name list of the experts in the street lighting bidding]
- Zhizhi.
- Yeah?
Liu Yang just called to say he's working overtime and won't be home to eat.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Didn't you just finish eating? You're hungry again?
Here, come on.
- What are you eating?
- Potato chips.
Who gave you these?
I gave them to her.
Mom, I threw these potato chips in the trash because they were expired.
Why did you take them out and give them to Yuwei?
They've only been expired for a few days.
This is food that we eat.
I tasted them; they were fine.
That's not good either. And you gave them to Yuwei. They expired.
Why can't we still eat them?
It's just a girl. She doesn't need to be so fussy and picky.
Mom, Yuwei is my daughter. I didn't pick her off the street
and didn't adopt her either. She is my own daughter.
I'm willing to give her the best things on this planet.
I can't allow her to eat those expired potato chips.
You can do whatever you want. You think you are meritorious for giving birth to a girl?
Ridiculous.
Mom!
I've told you, when you say things like that it's hard to hear.
I always endure it but I can't endure this time.
I'm telling you... If you talk to me about how to raise Yuwei again,
then don't stay at our house anymore and go back to your hometown.
On the basis of what? This is my son's house.
I'll live here however long I want.
You want to kick me out? No way!
Let's go.
Grandma!
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
If you won't leave, then I'm leaving!
Don't call her grandma! She doesn't deserve it!
Mom!
Mom! What's wrong?
Hello?
What?
Dad!
Liu Yang.
The family of bed no.34, please go to the doctor's office.
Yuwei, wait here for Mom. Come on.
You didn't send her here late. It's not life-threatening for the moment.
Doctor, what kind of sickness does my mom have?
The tentative diagnosis is acute myocarditis with a probably blocked artery.
Is it serious?
We will know the details only after a coronary angiography.
The patient needs to rest in bed and have a light diet during this period of time.
Never stimulate the patient's emotions.
I understand.
Prepare for the angiography for now.
Why did my mom get sick all of a sudden?
We had a fight.
I knew it.
I didn't know it would be like this. If I knew I would have...
Normally at home,
you always argue a lot with my mom.
How can you have such a grudge?
How can you not distinguish black from white?
It's okay for you to lose your temper with me.
My mom is old and her health is not good. You fought with her. You did it deliberately!
Dad!
Come here.
Brother Yang, is Aunt okay?
It's not life-threatening at the moment.
Are you okay? Can I do anything?
Thank you.
Mom gave Yuwei some already expired chips that were in the trash.
So we fought.
Usually, I can tolerate what Mom says.
But when it comes to Yuwei, I can't.
The things I said before were a bit strong. I'm sorry.
[Will Aunt be okay?]
Go sit and rest for a bit.
You finally answered your phone.
I'm a bit busy now.
Where are you right now?
The company.
I'm coming to pick you up.
Now?
Siyu, I want to see you and talk with you.
Let's meet tomorrow.
I don't have time today.
No. I must see you today.
I assumed you didn't have dinner.
I made some congee for you.
I don't have an appetite.
You have to eat.
Let's go.
Are you still angry with me?
No.
I have thought about it today.
You questioned me today that I can do so many things,
but only did this one?
Indeed, I didn't consider your situation well.
I was rushed to prove my value in Tianye.
The most important thing in Tianye now is the negotiation with Lubao.
So, I first seized this breakthrough point.
Also, I habitually thought
the investigation into the brand had nothing to do with the sales director.
Sorry.
It was my fault. I apologize to you.
It was not your fault.
It's a problem with our work.
I've already assigned work to my team.
Try to make up the loss caused by your report.
Here you are.
What's this?
When I investigated Lubao3,
I asked in passing
the situation of Lubao's advertising and post-sales service.
You should give it to your President Wang.
She doesn't pay attention to this. But as a sales director,
I think you need this.
I wrote my suggestions on the last few pages.
I hope I can smooth over a fault.
Thanks.
Siyu,
let's go to check the apartment tomorrow and sign the contract.
What's up? Are you still angry with me?
No. I was thinking about other things.
What?
Lin Ling has a client.
It's very important to her, to everyone, and to the company.
She must get it.
We have a grey zone now.
It can increase the assurance of getting the client.
Do you think if she should try the grey zone?
What do you think?
I... I don't know.
You just said it was a grey zone.
It means you already have your own judgment.
But I'm afraid of losing this client as well.
Siyu, we've known each other for five years. You are never afraid of losing clients.
Even if you lose them, you can find back others easily.
Am I so capable?
Of course.
Actually, it's not terrible to lose the clients.
What's terrible is that you will lose other things that
you can never find back.
Let's buy a house and sign the contract tomorrow!
- Liu Yang,
- Director.
I want to ask you to do me a favor.
Anytime. Go ahead.
My mom is hospitalized now. I want to borrow some money from you.
This... Wait a minute.
- Who is that?
- It's Liu Yang.
It's Liu Yang. His mom is sick and wants to borrow some money.
Borrow money? How much? Is he able to pay it back?
Did your cousin pay back the money?
Mom,
how are you feeling now?
I'm okay. Better now.
Drink some water.
No. I don't need it.
I'm really okay.
I'll go outside to answer the phone.
- Hello?
- Liu Yang.
My wife doesn't agree. I don't have a solution.
What if I give you ¥5,000 out of my own pocket money?
No worries, Director. I will think about other ways.
Sorry for being unable to help.
What are you talking about? Thank you all the same.
Lao Xiao, I want to ask you to do me a favor.
My mom is in the hospital waiting for bypass surgery.
You just bought a house.
Congratulations!
Old classmate, may I ask you to do me a favor?
I got it. It's not easy to start up a business now.
It's okay. I will think about other solutions.
Sure. Let's catch up soon.
Hello?
Hi, Sir. We just started to sell a new commercial property. Are you interested in knowing more?
No need.
Bed No.34, have you paid the surgery fee?
No, I haven't.
Don't take too long. There are many people queuing for the surgery.
If you pay earlier, you can have the surgery earlier.
Yes.
Mom, what would you like to eat? I will ask Zhizhi to cook and send it here.
How much will the surgery cost?
You don't need to worry about it. I have already saved enough money.
I don't want to do it.
Mom, you have to have it.
Do you really have enough money?
Enough. No worries.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫