Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 26]
Take a look at the one in my hand right now.
This one is more Western style.
These outfits. Look at these.
Also, the ones in the back are more modern.
These are the app patterns that we designed recently.
You can take a look yourself.
There are Western styles and more.
Really, the app's style...
impacts the user's experience.
Right now, the flat design is getting very popular.
The flat design looks very simple and natural.
And then these models are a bit more modern.
There are also more that are more traditional style.
Take a look and see which style you like more.
Okay. I think I've mostly understood.
Okay.
If you run into any problems when you're using it, you can send me feedback.
- It depends on everyone's—
- Excuse me.
- Hello?
- Do you like western style, modern style
classical style, or simple style?
Simple style.
I understand.
Why are you asking me so suddenly?
It's a secret.
Oh, right. What are you doing right now?
Let's pick a simple style then.
Simple style.
You can look at these ones if you like the simple style.
Okay.
- I'll order this one.
- Okay.
I booked our wedding photo shooting from "Love in Nice."
It's the best package. Look.
As for hotel, I booked Yuehua Hotel.
Even though it's a little farther from the city center,
it's outdoor and indoor settings are quite good.
For honeymoon, I chose Maldives.
Look. These are a few islands that the vacation planners recommended.
What's going on?
I've been pretty free recently.
I wanted to use this time to plan the wedding.
But I have more important things to do.
Are there things more important than getting married?
I want to build a shared platform for battery renting.
I want to do a new mobile energy service.
Right now?
This has been my desire for so many years.
Right now is the best time.
Tell me.
Today, there are over 300 million electric bicycles in China.
But it's always a problem to charge the bikes.
To use the platform that I build, the users only need to download an app.
They can go to any charging station in any network at any time.
It's like sharing a battery for phones, right?
Yes. But it's too small. They charge by milliampere.
Mine is kilowatt-hour and gigawatt-hour .
When the business of electric bicycles takes off in the market, I also want to provide service for electric cars.
Then it will be a revolution for the whole battery industry.
What's your advantage of doing this?
I've been working in this industry for 7 to 8 years.
I know almost everything about the battery industry.
- But you don't know about the internet at all.
- I can learn.
I can invite professional people to do professional things.
Have you thought over the profit model?
To make a profit, I need to collect users' deposits and rent.
In other cities, I can charge initial fee.
Also, as long as the platform is built, I can get investment.
Those shared power banks for phones,
they get over tens of millions of investment from Tianye Group.
What about the cost?
I calculated it. To start out, I probably need around four million yuan.
Including building the platform,
build one hundred physical branches and the money to buy the batteries.
I also contacted some battery manufacturers. They are all willing to offer me the lowest price.
Then what about the advertising cost?
It's included.
That's not enough.
As long as the platform starts to work, I can get the investment.
As long  as I can get the investment, the subsequent cost is not a problem.
Siyu.
Hearing you talk about this, I think
you made it seem too simple.
No. I know that this is going to be hard,
but I must do it and I must do it immediately.
I think you need to think twice
about this thing.
If I think twice, then someone else might snatch the opportunity.
We'll have nothing.
Right now, there are a lot of opportunities on the market,
but... but right now...
I want you to stop this right now.
I can't stop! I have to regain what I've lost!
I think we should get married first.
We can get married, but I have a condition.
What are your conditions?
I need money to start my business. Let's sell the house.
What?
Also,
I need a CEO.
Yiming, you should resign. We can start a business together.
Are you insane?
What do you mean?
Siyu, I think you need to calm down.
Yiming,
I need your support.
Siyu, I can't support you right now.
If you don't support me, then I will not marry you.
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow ♫
♫  like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But is  ♫
Hello, are you at the company right now?
I want to talk more about the system structure with you.
Okay. I'll go over there.
♫  We love with no room for anything else  ♫
♫  Never giving each other the chance to breathe  ♫
♫  Thought that being loved by you  ♫
♫  Thought that we wouldn't age  ♫
♫  Wouldn't separate  ♫
♫  Yet as I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
- GM Wang.
- Director Fang.
Come in.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Please have a seat.
In the past, I've never really had the opportunity to talk to you properly.
I hope, today, we can speak freely with each other
and be honest.
Director Fang, before I decided to invest in Lubao,
I looked at all of Lubao's reports from the start till now.
I noticed a problem.
The years that Lubao were most successful happened to be the years' GM Pan only dealt with R&D
while you did all the rest.
GM Wang, you overcomplimented me.
The fact that Lubao can make it today is not a miracle that was achieved alone,
it was the result of everyone's hard work.
Director Fang, you're quite humble.
I'm just telling the truth.
Starting from last year,
the policy of the country has been adjusted. This industry entered a more difficult time.
I noticed that Director Fang proposed the strategy of cutting expenditure.
My style is more practical.
I agree completely.
Didn't Buffett once say
that he wasn't trying to jump over a seven-foot fence,
but he was looking for a one foot
fence to jump over.
Director Fang, Pan Zhiyong told me that he had a plan.
He wanted to open three more Lubao3 production lines.
That's thanks to the eight billion Tianye Group invested.
That's what made GM Pan's ideas become reality.
I want to ask you
in the current market situation,
if you make your production bigger,
isn't that going to be a little risky?
I've discussed this problem with GM Pan.
He believes that this is a good opportunity to beat others on a curved road.
I worked for capital for so many years. I  don't see people succeed in cutting corners often.
However, many have ended up in terrible accidents.
I also want to ask GM Wang,
with your experience, what is the safest thing to do on a curved road?
Why does it have to be a curved road?
Why can't you just go on the airplane runway?
Airplane runway? You're talking about...
Director Fang, if I remember correctly,
Lubao's profit last year was about one billion, yes?
The cash flow of last year was too tight.
This year, with you, we hope we can go past two billion.
That's too little.
Within the industry, our performance is considered very outstanding.
If I was in charge, I could guarantee
that within a year, I can turn Lubao's valuation from 35 billion to 200 billion.
200 billion?
Then we'd need to make ten billion more in profit.
If we calculate it, the very least amount of production lines we'd need to add is ten.
- We don't need to.
- We don't need to add production lines?
All we need is a new packaging.
Director Fang, you work hard on the profit and market value
in order to increase your company's valuation?
Why don't you work directly on the company's valuation?
If we get Lubao's valuation to 200 billion,
the eight billion you invested would become forty billion.
The hard work of you and the rest of the executives
would also have a huge return.
Then Lubao3's production lines,
are they still going to be added?
You must spend the money on the most important thing.
Pan Zhiyong will not agree.
If he chooses to do something, no one will be able to change his mind.
That's not necessarily true.
Didn't he wholeheartedly want Li Siyu to be the sales director?
That didn't work.
Lubao is our Lubao.
It's not just one person's.
A toast to our Lubao.
Sister Yuan is back?
- Sister Yuan! You're finally back!
- You've finally returned!
- Long time no see.
- You haven't changed at all!
Sister Yuan missed us so much.
Sister Yuan, I just knew you'd be back.
Sister Yuan, your complexion is great today.
Sister Yuan, we cleaned up your office for you.
Quick, come take a look!
It smells very nice.
Sister Yuan, we finally got you back.
We missed you so much!
Sister Yuan,
- did Li Siyu mistreat you guys?
- Of course.
Sister Yuan, you didn't know...
Didn't Siyu make you go to Changsha three times
and give you all the commission?
Why did she do that?
She said you helped her that way in the past.
- Behind my back, she probably said a lot of bad things about me.
- That's actually not true.
She always said that it was pretty sad that you guys had a bad relationship in the end.
She wished for an opportunity to make up with you.
Sister Yuan, telling you the truth, Li Siyu is actually a pretty good person.
She's pretty much the same as you.
No, no, no. She's still a little worse than you.
Sister Yuan, hi.
Come in.
Hello, Senior Brother.
The sales department's performance has been dropping lately.
We need you to take control immediately.
- I got it.
- Also,
give me the name list of all the people you plan to fire from the sales department as soon as possible.
Why would people from the sales department be fired?
Li Siyu's team members.
You want to leave them here and cause you trouble?
After I left, Li Siyu didn't fire a single one of my team members.
If I come back and fire all of her people,
wouldn't it seem like my magnanimity is worse than hers?
You're going to leave every single one of them here?
I took a look. They're all very capable people.
Not only do I want to keep them, but I also want to use them in multiple areas.
Li Siyu also came up with some sales plans that are very useful.
I want to continue using those as well.
You lost to her in the past
because your heart was too kind.
You always thought I was too kind, and that's why this happened.
But on the flip side, if my heart were even kinder,
maybe there would be a different result.
Director Zhang, you only need to invest four million and then the project can start.
Three million is also acceptable.
Two million?
I will guarantee you
as long as we have increasing users, the cash flow is not a problem.
Okay. I'll get in touch later.
Hello, Miss. When can we bring the food?
Please wait a while longer.
Hello. The subscriber you are trying to reach is currently unavailable.
Sorry—
Sorry, the subscriber—
Sister Siyu, I'm so sorry. The meeting just ended.
It's okay, it's okay. Take a seat.
How come you're the only one? Where are the others?
Director Yuan said that since the meeting went late, she'd treat everyone to a meal.
Xiao Jia and Xiao Tian also went with her?
Sister Yuan really likes them.
Sister Siyu, please don't be angry.
What's there to be angry about? I was the one who brought them up.
If they are respected by a new leader, then I should be happy.
How come you didn't go?
I thought that by inviting me here, you must've had some very important thing to share,
so I should at least come over and see.
Did Director Yuan embarrass you?
Everyone says that Director Yuan changed a bit after returning.
How so?
I'm not sure either. I think that she's more gentle than she was before.
Sister Siyu, the truth is that everyone misses you greatly.
One day, Xiao Jia even said that one day, if Director Yuan leaves,
you could come back to be the director again.
Director? I'm now too good for that.
Now what I'm going to take is at least a general manager or chairman of the board.
Sister Siyu, you'll definitely be able to.
Okay. Let's stop the small talk.
Lin Ling, I plan to start my own business.
It's a great project. I plan to put it on the market in five years.
Now, I am officially asking you to join.
Then... I have to resign from Lubao?
Of course. Before the project is out, we have to be dedicated to it 24 hours a day.
- But...
- Trust me. If I want something to happen, it will.
I've thought about it multiple times. It's going to be successful, there's no way it will fail.
This is my marketing plan. If you read it, you'll understand.
Sister Siyu, I'm sorry.
I only just got used to selling batteries.
You also know my dad's situation.
I think... It's better if I have a steady job.
This is a once in a lifetime opportunity.
But I...
I might not be suitable.
Didn't you say that you would follow me for the rest of your life?
I meant in Lubao,
I would follow you.
I get it now.
Sister Siyu, I promised Director Yuan
that I'd go over to her after meeting you.
If you have nothing else,
I'm going.
Okay, go ahead.
[Laidianle Shared Technology, ltd.]
[Huqiu Road]
♫  This city's too magical  ♫
♫  Everything's within reach but falls apart with one touch  ♫
♫  Just like childhood ♫
♫ wishes that I don't fulfill  ♫
♫  Nights are filled with loneliness  ♫
♫  Lights are dimming yet I'm awake  ♫
♫  Love and bittersweet joys  ♫
Come here. Come.
♫  You were by my side  ♫
♫  The world turns quickly  ♫
[Let's make up.]
♫  Yet footsteps slow down  ♫
[Yes.]
Yes. But I just paid a deposit.
I'm waiting for you to decide on the themes and costume.
♫  This city's too magical  ♫
♫  Everything's within reach but falls apart with one touch  ♫
[I will go have tea with GM Pan tomorrow morning. I'll be free tomorrow afternoon.]
I can ask leave in the afternoon.
♫  Just like childhood wishes that I don't fulfill  ♫
[Then let's go to pick the themes and costumes of the wedding photos.]
Okay.
♫  Nights are filled with loneliness  ♫
♫  Lights are dimming yet I'm awake  ♫
♫  Love and bittersweet joys. Regrets  ♫
♫  You were by my side  ♫
I want to be discharged from the hospital today.
The doctor said that many of your indicators haven't dropped to a normal level.
Buy some medicine and take them at home.
I've already paid the surgery fee.
You don't need to care for me.
I need to go to work.
I will leave the meal here. Help yourself.
- Please enjoy it.
- Thank you.
I met Lin Ling in the company.
She said you wanted to start a start-up business.
Yes.
What project?
The project is called "Laidianle"
(T/N: means the electricity is coming)
It's a renting platform of a shared storage battery.
It's innovative. How is it going?
I already decided to give it up.
Why?
When everyone listens to my idea, they all say it's good.
But I can't handle the investment.
There is no one willing to join.
How much do you need to prepare to start?
- Four million yuan.
- How much have you collected?
If I add the money after selling the house, it's a bit over one million.
Lubao will invest three million.
GM Pan...
This is my project plan.
Good. I don't need to read this.
I just need to see the person.
GM Pan, I replace alcohol with tea.
No worries. I won't let you down for sure.
After half of the year, I need to see the result.
Sure!
GM Pan, how is Lubao going?
Not good.
Why?
I prepared to build additional two of Lubao3's production lines.
It was vetoed by Wang Ziru and Fangzhan together as a result.
The two of them together?
I doubt at that time
the vote which she gave to Yuan Huizhong
is a good gesture for Fang Zhan.
I asked Sister Ziru about this.
She did that because Chen Yiming requested this.
Chen Yiming doesn't hope that I work hard outside.
He hopes that I can return home.
Li Siyu, do you believe it?
It is true. For this, Chen Yiming and I almost broke up.
Wang Ziru, this woman,
will do so much for a subordinate's request,
on the issue that involves so much interest,
will she consider for a subordinate in the end?
I don't believe it.
You think?
I think who she voted for
was after she deliberated carefully.
Besides, she and Fang are so well together.
It is definitely closely related to that vote.
I don't think so.
I should have kept that 22%.
I don't understand.
You don't  need to understand.
Just do this well. I can handle the company.
Xiao Han, I'm Li Siyu.
I was planning to start a company in your business park.
I stopped for a while. Now I have decide to restart.
- No problem, Director Li. Can you come to apply now?
- Now?
Today is the last day of our park's promotion.
If you apply after today, something like the rent discount,
you can't get.
I will come right now.
[Siyu]
Siyu, where are you now? I'm almost there.
Yiming, sorry, I have to deal with something now.
How about we cancel today?
What do you need to do?
I will go to the park to hand in the application to start up a company.
You haven't given up your business plan?
There is some change now. I want to...
Come over here now. Let's settle the wedding photo first.
Yiming,
can we postpone this?
No.
I really can't make it today.
Siyu,
I'm at the gate of the wedding dress shop. I'm waiting for you.
Director Li, this is our project introduction.
Now we reduce 5% of the tax revenue every year.
This is our...
- This is the material you want.
- Yes, yes.  Thank you.
Director Li, this is our preferential policy.
Investment purpose. Regional advantage. The product fostering.
Thank you very much.
You are welcome, Director Li. It's my job.
Director Li, I will walk you here.
- See you.
Hello, how can I help you?
Mr. Chen, my boyfriend
booked the afternoon to try on the dress.
He just left.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
[Siyu]
- Hello?
- Hello? Mr. Chen.
Ms. Li's phone is busy all the time. I had to call you.
What's wrong?
I checked your apartment.
Now you can sell at 5.2 million.
But you will suffer a loss of the transaction tax.
Who told you that we wanted to sell the house?
Ms. Li told me. She asked me to calculate the price.
Hello?
Where are you right now?
The framework of the project and system both have been shaped up.
Now what I need is—
I will call you back later.
You are selling the house?
Yes.
Li Siyu,
are you really that crazy?
I'm not.
This is a demonstration that the expert made for me.
Their conclusion is that this project perfectly solves the problem of the electric bicycle riders.
Any business model's success must be an efficient solution to the problem in the market.
Can I not listen to you saying this?
Why not?
This is the evaluation of the industry's experienced people.
They all said this project was a combined innovation of new energy and the internet.
- It is another revolution to lead people's transportation.
- Enough!
It is enough.
GM Pan decided to invest three million to me.
Add one million from the house, I have all the money to start the project.
GM Pan. Li Siyu, I think you were completely brainwashed by him.
Three million.
This is not called brainwashing. This is approbation.
Let it go. Okay?
I got three million from nothing. Why should I let it go?
Because you've already lost your reasoning and judgment.
Chen Yiming,
everyone says it's a very rare opportunity to start a business.
You say I lost my judgment.
Everyone says it's a good opportunity.
You said I lost reasoning.
There are many good projects.
You have to see if it's suitable or not.
Opportunity is important.
But you need to see if you have the condition or not.
I can create the condition but the opportunity doesn't wait.
You can't mess things up!
Then what do you think is not a mess?
- For example—
- Getting married, for example?
Chen Yiming, I'm going to say this one more time for you.
I'm already over 30 years old and I have achieved nothing.
Also, you know,
I was just beaten by others. It's impossible for me to give up now!
Then I will ask you a question.
Do you still want to marry me?
How can you not understand me?
- I want to counterattack. I want to win it back. I want to try to bring credit to myself!
- I'm asking you now!
Do you still want to marry me?
I'd prefer to continue my business rather than marrying you!
If it's like this, then we have to break up.
Siyu...
Siyu,
- I didn't mean this.
- I agree.
We should break up.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow  ♫
♫  like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫ the days have yet to come ♫
♫  Yet as I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories   ♫
♫ won't let me escape ♫
♫  As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories  ♫
♫ won't let me escape  ♫
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫