[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 34]
GM Pan, have you come back?
- I came back. I have time on Friday. Come to my office to talk.
- Okay.
What's wrong? You start your diet again?
- I want to break up with He Mu.
- Aren't you happy with him?
I'm happy with his money.
- Isn't it enough?
- But he is like a robot.
I feel like I'm becoming a robot being together with him.
Do you love him?
What's love?
You and Chen Yiming were in love before, right?
But you broke up in the end.
Don't mention my relationship.
So, love is not important. Money is the most important.
Since you think money is the most important,
you've got what you want. Why are you still not happy?
But every time I date him, I feel I am in a math class.
Every time I send him Wechat, I feel I'm doing math homework.
It sounds painful to you.
When others date guys, they will receive cosmetics, bags, and shoes.
What I got are Excel sheets, bar graphs, and pie charts.
I don't have much time left.
I must break up with him!
You are late.
It's 10 mins today.
You are down today.
Yes.
Appropriate exercise, music, and self-suggestion could help with moodiness.
- In addition—
- He Mu.
We've been together for a while. Do you think we are compatible?
What a coincidence. I also want to talk about this with you.
You also felt this?
Feel? I don't trust feelings.
I only trust data.
That's also okay.
Xiao Ling, I'm very cautious about selecting a partner.
Five years ago, I made a plan with four categories,
nine programs and eighty-seven indexes in all for my future life partner.
I didn't do well for sure.
After the inspection of these days, for these eighty-seven indexes, you got sixty full marks.
7-90 points, 8-80 points,
6-70 points, 3-60 points, and you only failed 3.
I did very well?
You are far from well.
Excuse me.
But this score makes me confirm that you are my future life partner.
You... What do you mean?
Since we have made it clear, I hope the communication between us doesn't need to stay at the "getting to know each other " level.
Instead, we should take more time and effort to discuss our wedding and marriage.
You...
You... You... Are you proposing to me?
You can say this.
But among those three fails, one is self-emotion management.
I hope you can work hard to improve this in the future.
I will also improve and enrich myself in all aspects.
I hope we can become perfect partners for each other.
Let's eat.
Didn't I come here to break up with you?
Please come in.
I don't eat these. I'm on diet.
These are for your son.
I made some for Mengmeng as well when I made cakes for Yuwei.
The oil, eggs, and flour are the best.
Feel free to eat them.
- Thank you.
- I will leave now.
Zhizhi,
don't start by introducing your own product immediately when you meet clients.
Talk about their product first.
Thank you, Director Yuan.
- What's next?
- Put some vegetable.
This is also a vegetable. There are a lot. Shall we put them all in?
Yes.
- All?
- Yes.
- Then continue, right?
All right.
Mom, you're back!
Did you eat?
Yuwei finished. I was waiting for you.
- Don't wait for me.
- I must wait.
- Did you take the report from the hospital?
- Yes.
How was it?
The indexes are normal now. The doctor said it was okay as long as I take medicine on time and pay attention to food and daily health.
Then I don't need to worry about you.
What's this for?
I got paid today.
Sit!
I can't drink. So I'll use juice.
What's this for?
Zhizhi, when I thought of before,
how muddled I was. I treated you like that.
Sorry.
It's already in the past.
Zhizhi, give me another chance. Let's start our life over.
Yuwei,
dad and mom are talking with each other. Can you go to your room to play?
Okay!
Go.
Liu Yang,
let's divorce.
Are you still angry with me?
I already broke up with her!
It has nothing to do with that.
Then why?
I don't love you anymore.
Impossible.
If you don't love me, why didn't you leave me and still take care of me?
We've been married awhile.
You were depressed, you got sick. Taking care of you is what I should do.
Now that you are well and have found a job, I don't have any obligations anymore.
Even if you don't love me, we still have Yuwei.
If we divorce, how can we take care of Yuwei?
I can take care of Yuwei well.
Yuwei is only 4 years old.
Don't you think it's too cruel for her?
I don't want to sacrifice myself for Yuwei anymore.
Zhizhi, before you said you had a happy life,
now you feel suffocated with me.
Zhizhi,
let's not get a divorce.
I swear, I won't do that stupid thing again.
I will cherish you.
I'm not the old Liu Yang anymore.
I'm not the old Zhang Zhizhi anymore.
Zhizhi, how about we calm down and think about it?
Don't make decisions too quickly.
I've already thought about it very clearly.
Zhizhi...
- Zhizhi.
- Liu Yang
if you still appreciate what I did for you,
then agree to my decision.
Am I this bad in your eyes?
It's nothing to do with you.
It was me that was terrible before.
These are not angry words.
I really think in this way.
I don't want to live like before.
Yuwei will be with me. I will take the apartment.
When I have enough money, I will repay some for you.
Look! I made it myself!
Amazing! I will give you a sip of juice as a bonus, okay?
- Yuwei, you made it by yourself? Dad didn't help you?
- Yes.
Yuwei is excellent!
Yuwei,
you should also be like this in the future. No matter what you do, finish it by yourself. Okay?
Let's have lunch together.
No need. I will visit a client during lunchtime.
By the way, your things...
I will tidy up my dorm today and come to move them tomorrow.
If you want to see Yuwei, any time is okay. Just tell me in advance.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
You can go back to do your work.
I just got this.
Is he Pan Zhiyong's trusted subordinate?
This is what Xiaqiang gave to me. He is hired by me.
- Laidianle.
- Li Siyu is the owner.
- I know it.
Do we really need to do that?
- We don't have another choice.
- Over more than ten years, he is always the soul of Lubao.
Lubao won't have today without him.
He was correct before doesn't mean he is correct now and in the future.
Who proposed it?
Wang Ziru.
What does she want to do, huh?
She only has 23% of the shares. She wants to impeach me?
How long has she been here?
This is my company. This is the territory that I built!
Now the company is at a critical moment.
There are lots of things to do. We put this issue aside for now.
Now I'm afraid we can't.
Okay.
- Then let's accept the challenge.
- Okay.
I'll go back to my work.
¥300 for gasoline at number 11.
Insufficient Balance.
Try this one.
I will pay cash.
Should be enough.
Still need 23 RMB.
Scan Wechat.
Still need 21 RMB.
- Okay?
- Yes.
- Wait a second. This is your receipt.
[Your mortgage is overdue 3 months. You should pay back 57449.43 RMB. Your account doesn't have sufficient balance. Please your mortgage on time.]
Why did you still sell your car?
I just gave you ¥300,000.
I'm in too much debt.
"Dear customer, the mortgage you have at the bank has been overdue for three months,
the mortgage amount—"
"Dear Teacher Yiming, your article is—"
The fans really love you.
From your face, are you in love?
What nonsense are you talking?
This person is just a faithful reader.
Yes, of course, it's a faithful fan. It better not progress into an online romance.
You'll become David soon!
What David!
Right now, my funds are very tight.
I'll probably be dead on the way to becoming David.
Then you have to rapidly grow!
That way, I can brag about you with others.
Lately, I've been negotiating a ¥100,000 advertisement.
If it succeeds, then I will no longer be afraid.
What if we can't negotiate it?
Then I will sell my new house.
We have to go fast.
We have to quickly get orders and sell big.
[A warm welcome to LuBao's shareholders coming for the shareholders meeting.]
It is on the right side.
Come on in.
GM Wang, hello, please come this way.
Hello, please come in.
Hello, this way please.
GM Wang, this way.
This way, please.
Please come this way.
GM Wang.
This way, please.
- Sister Yuan.
- Come in.
I've cleaned up the leftover items from Li Siyu's office.
What should we do with the things she left?
Okay, find a place to put everything first.
I'll put it here.
- Okay, put it there.
- Then I'll leave now.
Omeprazole.
(T/N: OTC drug that is a stomach acid inhibitor. Brand name: Prilosec)
[Chinese Restaurant Membership Card]
At the time, I rejected her offers to buy.
Later, her younger sister went and bought them.
Why did she do that?
Director Yuan, in reality, Sister Siyu never saw you as an enemy.
She came at me with blows over an order.
She did that because of me.
Yes, I remember now.
At that time, Liu Yang was still my husband.
I'm sorry, I only knew after.
Don't apologize. It's all in the past.
At that time, I was forced to
use some unwanted methods.
As a salesperson, I understand.
At times, I can't even face myself.
It can't be easy for you.
Is it easy for anyone?
Even including Li Siyu.
Sister Siyu, you came back again?
I'm looking for GM Pan.
- Hey, Sis.
- Hey, hey, hey!
[A warm welcome to LuBao's shareholders coming for the shareholders meeting.]
- Why is Sister Siyu back?
- I don't know.
Hi, Sister Siyu?
- I'm looking for GM Pan.
- Oh, GM Pan is in a stockholder meeting.
- It's still not over?
- Not yet.
- Then I'll wait for him.
- Here, you can sit over there.
Sister Siyu.
If we analyze the company's business performance and the current situation of the industry,
then you'll realize, Lubao is on the edge of a cliff!
And the person who has brought the company to such a wary situation financially is CEO Pan!
For the future of the company and also for everyone's interest, I suggest dismissing GM Pan from the board.
And also dismiss him from the chairman of the board!
As the company's shareholder, I support President Wang's suggestion.
I respect each stockholder and the regulations; however,
I'll take the responsibility to tell you that
in our current circumstances, if the core group is removed from their posts,
then everyone sitting here's interests might not be guaranteed.
Colleagues, I'd like to say two sentences.
For so many years, how much effort has GM Pan made for Lubao's development?  You all see, right?
Now, these people who play with capital want to kick GM Pan out and take Lubao away from us by using their money.
I absolutely cannot agree!
How can you force GM Pan to quit? He made the biggest contribution to the company!
He also owns the most shares of the company. It's not your turn to talk!
Everyone,
these past few years the company has consistently not paid dividends. Have you ever wondered
exactly why that is?
This is the company's strategy. Do you understand it?
GM Pan, please explain why you gave ¥300,000 to the Laidianle company.
There is nothing to explain. I tried to open up the down-stream product for Lubao.
That sum of money was never discussed in a board meeting,
a stockholder meeting, or even a corporate meeting.
You just signed something and gave away all of that money.
- That's because I think this investment is very cost-effective.
- Since it's an investment, where is the business plan?
What's the return on investments? Have you evaluated the risks?
Where is the report of project feasibility?
When you make investments you can't just look at reports and numbers. You also have to courage
and  insight.
Lubao has gotten to today.
Do you still not understand this?
Do you dare to tell everyone who the founder of Laidianle is?
There's nothing bad to say about it. Li Siyu.
You all know her business talent.
¥300,000 obscurely disappeared, and you don't have any explanation.
This was under your supervision.
Spending shareholders' money freely, this is your courage?
To people who seriously impacted Lubao's branding,
you not only don't punish her strictly but also invest in her.
That's your insight.
Pan Zhiyong,
his chaotic management, defective capability,  and inferior personality
don't deserve our trust anymore!
Let's change the chairman of the board!
Siyu, this is what you had left in your old office. The admins put it together.
I want to apologize to you.
Didn't we call it even?
There are some things, now that I think about them, that I feel very ashamed of.
If I don't apologize, I can't live with myself.
Sister Yuan.
That ¥500 overtime work fee...
I'm sorry.
Sister Yuan, I also have things I need to apologize to you for.
You're right for fighting to get ahead.
Even though your perseverance threatened my position, I should have persevered more,
rather than using little cheating methods.
I wanted to say, the thing with Meiyi Group,
I didn't come out and stand up for you.
I believe if I hadn't changed the date of the order, then you would've come out and said something for me.
Siyu, I also take responsibility for that.
Sister Yuan, you'll always be my best mentor.
I will try.
I'll only teach you how to be good, not bad.
[Shareholders'  temporary conference]
I respect the outcome of the shareholders' vote.
I respect everyone's end decision.
But I want to say, you're wrong.
There will be one day when you pay the price for your vote today.
You'll regret your decision today.
President Wang just promised that by capital operation,
in a very short time, she can make everyone's property increase four even five times in value.
I believe she has this ability.
But have you thought about the inflation lacking the real value support?
How far can it go?
Come in.
Manager Yuan and Sister Siyu, look at your phones.
What's up?
GM Pan has been overthrown.
It's not easy to make money by working in an industry.
But doing business, we do it not to just make money,
we need to seek long-term development in a competition.
Business is business. I'm not ashamed to talk about making money. But we should make money for all of the people.
For a company, if the industry is rising then its economy is rising.
The country is strong when the industry is strong!
I insist that self-dependent innovation
and the core technology are the right way to go for a company.
Honestly doing business without distractions
is a company's duty.
All the speculations and packaging will be gone eventually!
I was defeated by the savage  today.
But I believe,
this is not the result in the end.
I will come back!
I firmly believe that the way I set for Lubao,
although it's tough and slow, it is sustainable!
[Green Treasure]
GM Pan, I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I also have some problems.
The shareholders who supported me, in the end, voted for the others.
All in all, it was me that got you into trouble.
When talking about equity cooperation,
Wang Ziru was scheming today.
I promised her 23% of shares.
It fit in exactly with her wishes.
I still can't believe why Sister Ziru would do this.
How did you guys meet?
From a car accident, she didn't ask us to pay for her car and used her own insurance.
She helped you for no reason,
you didn't think there was something else to it?
You mean—
she was using me to get to Lubao?
What do you think?
I work in sales.
Which company?
That new power battery company?
You know it?
I don't need you to repair my car.
You don't need to pay for it.
But it can't be...
Looking at it now, that rumor is true.
What rumor?
At the time, I was talking to three companies about getting an investment.
Huaan and Huyun left the discussion in the end.
Someone told me that they were getting harassed and pressured by people from Tianyie company.
I didn't really believe it at the time.
Because I didn't tell her who the other two companies were.
She didn't pursue further to ask.
GM Pan can appoint you as Lubao's Sales Director. This makes me more confident in Lubao's management team.
By the way, have your executives met with the other two companies that are trying to invest?
You mean Huaan and Huyin?
She knew...
Not possible. How could she have known?
I told her.
How do I have such a stupid subordinate like you!
GM Pan, I'm sorry.
Don't cry!
You continue to cry and I won't see you again!
I won't cry.
I won't accept defeat.
I must get Lubao back.
GM Pan, what do you want me to do?
You, just take care of your own business.
By the way, the second round of funding for Laidianle, I can't do it now.
You have to think of a way yourself, okay?
Rest assured. I will not admit defeat.
[95590]
[Sir, your mortgage has been overdue for many times during this half of the year. If this situation continues, the bank will take legal means to safeguard the rights and interests.]
Teacher Chen, I have approved the business cooperation plan.
But my boss wants to meet you tomorrow to finalize the agreement. Do you have time tomorrow?
Yes, I'm available.
He will have a meeting in a hotel. He has a few minutes during the break.
It would be the perfect time to talk to you.
Okay.
See you tomorrow
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... Oh...En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go  ♫
♫ , all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace
♫ then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫