Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 27]
Is Yuwei asleep?
I still can't believe
that you really broke up with Brother Yiming.
Yeah. How did you suddenly get this point?
Sister Siyu,
could it be that you are being too eager to excel?
Yeah. Can't you just take a step back?
First get married, then start a business. The order is not a big deal.
It's not about what comes first and what comes last.
It's what he wants and what I want most
are different.
Can you not compromise?
I've been compromising up until today. I'm tired.
Is there still a possibility that you'll get back together?
No.
If you want to cry, just cry.
I don't have time to cry.
There's still so much work waiting for me to do.
Fortunately, I still have work.
If you guys are really breaking up,
then you need to figure out the debts between you two.
What debt?
What's going to happen to the house they bought together? How about the mortgage?
You go talk to him.
I don't have time.
This idea is quite good.
You can take care of each other.
You can live at my house to save money.
But let me tell you clearly.
If I have an important date, then you have to go stay at a hotel.
Also, you can't force me to
memorize words, write essays, and do my homework every day like when we were younger.
Also, you can't call me a coquettish girl every time I dress up.
More importantly, you can't report everything I do to my mom.
I won't.
Zhizhi, what do you plan to do?
Divorce.
I heard something happened to Liu Yang.
That girl betrayed Liu Yang.
Liu Yang really ended things with her this time.
So what?
Once you find out
about some things
you can't pretend to be oblivious.
What things?
Liu Yang is very stiff, awkward,
and a dumb man.
He doesn't know how to be romantic
and doesn't know how to take care of people.
But when I saw him together with Wei Yayun, I realized
that he does know how to be romantic
and does know how to take care of people.
It just depends on who he's with.
During these five years of marriage,
our lives have been quite hard;
however, I was willing to go through the hardships
because he loved me
and I loved him.
I was willing to giving everything up for him.
But in reality,
I was just lying to myself.
He didn't love me.
He didn't see me as a lover or a wife.
During this whole time,
he just saw me as a nanny.
But even now,
you still go to the hospital to take care of him every day.
Even though I am completely disappointed in him,
he's still Yuwei's dad.
Zhizhi, you're too kind.
In a marriage,
kindness can't be exchanged for sincerity.
Even if you do get sincerity,
it will be destroyed by the pressures of life.
Enough. You two stop talking.
If you keep saying things like this,
all of us will become dissatisfied housewives.
Isn't it merely five years of your youth wasted for a bastard?
It's fine.
In the next five years, we can live happily to make up for the past five years.
And you! Isn't it just a mere break up?
It hasn't even been half a year and I've already broken up twice!
Look!  Have I been depressed or sad?
You win in the end only if you fight on despite repeated setbacks.
Let's empty this bottle of wine.
Pour it.
Okay. Mine.
I'm announcing that we are going to
leave all of our sorrows, problems, and anger
in the present.
Tomorrow is a new day!
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Is she okay?
She's really well.
How is her business venture going?
You're not even supporting her, so just don't ask.
She hopes... that you will sell the house
and return her the down payment she payed.
If we sell the house then we can't buy it back.
So how about we don't sell it?
She really needs money right now though.
I'll figure something out.
I asked the agent and he said that that house has appreciated in value.
If you sell it, you have to return at least ¥800,000 to her.
Xiaoling,
that house has only appreciated ¥300,000 in total.
I know.
Also, Siyu paid ¥500,000 in total at that time.
She's been with you for 5 years.
Shouldn't you compensate her?
But I don't have that much money to give her right now.
Then write an IOU.
I... asked for an additional ¥300,000 for you.
Who told you to do that?
I was helping you to fight for your rights and interests.
How is that fighting for my rights and interests?
This is blackmailing.
How is that blackmailing?
It's very clearly written on the house deed
that each of you owns half of the house.
Asking for ¥800,000 is not too much at all.
Besides, we need to get some kind of compensation for your youth!
If I knew you had those thoughts,
then I wouldn't have let you go!
From now on, I won't meddle into your business.
Let's change the house deed tomorrow.
I don't have ¥800,000 to give you right now.
We can talk about it after we do the paperwork.
Okay.
I was clearly helping her,
yet she lectured me.
Have you ever met such an ungrateful person before?
Of course, I have.
Last time, in front of the art museum,
I helped a woman get out of the grasp of an asshole,
but she also scolded me.
Who are you talking about?
I'm saying that the two of you are pretty much the same, you can't really judge each other.
Then again,
Chen Yiming is my bro.
You asked for ¥300,000 for no reason. That's a bit harsh.
How is it for no reason?
He hurt Siyu and I helped her get compensation. What's wrong with that?
Wasn't Chen Yiming also hurt?
I saw him yesterday.
He lost a ton of weight.
He deserves it.
If you want my opinion, this really isn't Yiming's fault.
Then are you blaming Li Siyu?
- Li Siyu did act a little too crazy.
- Who's crazy?!
You were just saying how she was ungrateful!
I can insult her, but you can't!
Fine, fine, fine.
Do you think the two of them will be able to make up?
Li Siyu is going to have to change for that to happen.
Otherwise, it will be like last time.
They'll get back together and split again.
Then do you think that Chen Yiming doesn't have to change?
That's true.
Compared to me, Chen Yiming indeed is
not as warm, handsome, or interesting;
but overall, he's considered perfect.
Eat a kebob, eat a kebob.
I can't eat spicy things for a month.
How come?
I had an injection, and the doctor says I need to avoid certain foods.
No way! You look like this yet you went to get injections?
Even though I'm beautiful,  I will eventually get old.
Why are you afraid to be old?
Isn't there a good song about it?
♪ How many people can love your appearance when you were young? ♪
♪ But who will not care about the cruel changes that come with time? ♪
♪ How many people can come and go from your life? ♪
♪ Know I'll be by your side in this lifetime ♪
Are you touched?
Why not?
If I got old, and you were the only one by my side,
then I would be such a failure.
Then having whom by your side makes you feel like you aren't a failure?
He at least has to be a silver-haired
and charming retired billionaire.
Aren't you just describing me in fifty years?
You?
What are you laughing at? Are you looking down on me?
You should do something that makes me not look down on you then!
Deal.
Now the house only belongs to you.
I will transfer ¥500,000 to you first.
The remaining ¥300,000...
I will repay it all within two years.
This is my IOU letter.
[Proof of Debt]
You don't owe me anything.
Siyu!
In regards to our future, I have had
many, many thoughts
but I never thought
this would be the ending.
It was my fault.
I couldn't give you what you wanted.
No, you aren't wrong. The things you want aren't wrong either.
It's just that I—
It's just...
we may be on paths that go in different directions.
No matter what,
I sincerely love you.
I sincerely love you as well.
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow  ♫
♫ like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away  ♫
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But is  ♫
♫  as lost as others  ♫
We finally have a home.
♫  Never giving each other the chance to breathe  ♫
♫  Thought that being loved by you  ♫
♫  Thought that we wouldn't age  ♫
In the past, in the present, in the future,
I will always be in the palm of your hand.
You can always grasp onto me.
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow   ♫
♫  Like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away  ♫
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights  ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  Yet as I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
Hello?
Hello? Yiming?
Mom, could you please lend me some more money?
I looked at the material for number 18.
He's pretty good in all areas, but I think
he's a little bit too old.
I'd prefer the age to not be over 40.
Okay, then I'll wait for your news.
Who were you calling?
My personal matchmaker.
What?
I went on a dating website and registered a VIP account.
Exclusive one-on-one sessions with matchmakers.
Spending tens of thousands of yuan really gets you something different.
The men she's introduced to me are all either rich or have high social status.
I think you can try it, too.
No time, no money, no interest.
I'm serious.
Even if you can't find someone to be with for the rest of your life,
you can find someone who will help start your business.
Right? Right?
What's wrong?
Chen Yiming transferred ¥800,000 to you?
I guess he does have a conscience after all.
Do you have liquor?
Do you want to die? Do you not want your stomach?
I will look for it for you.
[Available Balance: ¥316.99]
[Available Balance: ¥118.00]
[Available Balance: RBM 0.00]
If you don't need any other service, please take out your card.
Yuwei,
Mom wants to talk to you about something.
We won't buy new shoes for now. Wear the old ones for now.
But the teacher said
that my dance shoes are already battered,
and need new ones.
I will help you patch them up.
The other kids are all wearing new dance shoes.
If I patch up your old ones, you'll still be able to dance.
I want new dance shoes, too.
I don't have enough money right now.
Didn't you just take money from the bank?
This is for your dad's hospital fee,
and it's also for your preschool fees,
and our electricity bill,
water bill, gas bill, and phone bill.
Doesn't Daddy get money every month?
Daddy is in the hospital right now. He has no money.
Then is your money enough?
You don't have to worry about that.
Mommy, I have money.
What money do you have?
Today, I was the first to finish eating and doing classwork.
The teacher awarded us this to use at the fairytale hut
to buy crayons and ribbons.
These little coupons can't buy dance shoes.
I don't want dance shoes anymore.
Mommy, you can have this money to spend.
In the future,
Mommy will buy you lots and lots of new dance shoes.
What do you mean?
I've really never met someone like you before.
You are basically asking me to pay for your renovations.
¥26.5.
Ms. Li, you're a boss now.
Negotiating the price by ¥0.5 or ¥1... is there a point?
Brother, I also know that it doesn't really make a difference.
I also want to be able to magnanimously be able to wave my hand and say "Sure, let's do that,"
but my budget doesn't allow me to do that.
Not just ¥0.5 or ¥1.
Right now, I really want to split ¥0.01 in half to spend.
Well, we also need to earn money and eat.
Nowadays, a bento that looks just a little bit decent is already ¥15.
For lunch, I had a bento that only cost ¥8 each.
Ms. Li, how much money can you pay?
My construction budget is only  ¥300,000.
Not a single construction company in Shanghai would accept this job for that budget.
The lowest I can go... ¥580,000.
¥302,000.
If I had known earlier, I wouldn't have even come.
Aren't you just wasting my time?
President Wang.
How come you've been staying up late so often recently?
No, I haven't.
How are you and Siyu?
We broke up.
How about I invite her out, and you two can talk some more?
There's no need. It's fine the way things are right now.
We are both free now
and relieved now.
You don't look relieved at all.
Perhaps, I-I-
I'm not used to- used to being relieved.
This is my stop, President Wang.
Yiming!
If you really want to be free, then you must let it go completely.
If you want someone to talk to, I'm always here.
Thank you, Sister Ziru.
I'm leaving now.
This here, we can finish this today.
- How about over here?
- Don't worry.
We can definitely finish by the end of this month.
Please make way.
Boss Li.
Here!
Sister Siyu.
Zhizhi?
Over there.
If we talk here, it's quieter and cleaner.
How come you're dressed like a construction worker?
I am one right now.
You're not doing this personally, are you?
Doing it personally saves money.
Then what is the construction company for?
The construction company wouldn't make any money with my budget so they rejected it.
I found my own workers to do it.
Will it work out?
I don't have money so I have to make it work.
Why were you looking for me?
Nothing, I just wanted to see if you needed any help.
I'm still short ¥1 million here.
How about you make it up for me?
I'm joking.
- Miss Li, give me a hand!
- Coming!
- Go work.
- Then I'll leave you here.
Be safe!
GM Pan, is there something you need to discuss with me?
Nothing. I was reorganizing my cabinet just now,
and I found something.
It made me especially touched.
Take a close look. This tie is yours.
- Mine?
- Did you forget?
At that time, Lubao was just founded. I was going to visit a senior.
You took this tie off and tied it on me.
At the time, you even said
"GM Pan, you are Lubao's representative."
"I can be a little disheveled, but you must be glamorous."
I think I remember that.
After we'd successfully started the business,
I bought a lot of ties,
but this one is the only one I kept. I didn't have the heart to exchange it.
It reminds me of your contributions to Lubao
and our friendship forged by working hard together.
That's something that happened over ten years ago.
Yes. Over ten years ago.
At that time, I worked with the technicians
staying up night after night in the lab.
You and the sales team went around all of China.
That's how we have this business today.
I remember I had to go on a business trip to Zhengzhou.
Before leaving, your hair was all black.
I was gone for less than a month, but when I came back, all of your hair turned white!
I also remembered that out of the 365 days in the year,
you were on business trips for 300 days.
The other sixty days,
you were mostly working overtime.
Because of this,
your ex-wife divorced you, right?
We gave up too much for Lubao.
Yes. We've both gave up too much for Lubao,
but the friendship between the two of us
can never be replaced by anyone.
You're right.
Sit.
We've been very busy these past two years.
We've interacted a lot less than before.
The company is getting bigger and bigger.
The market changed, and we started to disagree with each other.
Fang Zhan, it's okay.
Here,
in my heart,
you have always been my best brother,
companion, and partner.
Yes.
It was so hard in the past, yet we got through it.
In the future, it might be even harder,
but let us get through it together. Okay?
GM Pan, to tell you the truth,
I'm a little tired.
Why?
Nowadays, doing business is so hard.
We can invest hundreds of millions, but in a year,
we can only earn a few million.
Something that might be hard to hear,
buying a house would appreciate faster than this.
Fang Zhan, Fang Zhan.
When we invested in this industry back then, were we just looking to make money?
If it was to make money, then I would've sold my patent back then.
If it was to make money, then you could've invested in any other field.
Weren't we doing this to fulfill our dream?
Do you remember our old motto?
"The most outstanding in the industry. No.1 in China. The leader of the world. "
"The most outstanding in the industry"? We did it!
We are just one step away from being the "No. 1 in China."
Are you really going to leave now?
- I just—
- I know, Fang Zhan.
I know.
In the past two years, you've worked especially hard.
I am also impatient, so you've suffered a lot because of me.
Fang Zhan, I promise you
that from now on, I will be more aware
of my work attitude and ways.
GM Pan,
honestly, you've been fine.
Lubao being where it's at today
was very difficult.
We must not give up.
Let's continue, okay?
In the next few days, I plan to invite the Board of Directors to a meeting
to discuss Lubao3 again.
I will propose to install another 2 production lines.
I hope that you will support me.
Just like before.
How is Liu Yang?
There are a few health indices that haven't dropped to a normal level yet.
The doctors say that he needs to stay in the hospital for a while longer.
I asked around, and people with this sickness
cannot get overstimulated or tired. They have to recover slowly.
How are you doing?
Hi, Xiao Liu, long time no see.
Your aunt just got paid. Yuwei, you can order whatever you want to eat.
Aunt, do you have a lot of money?
I want to have a lot of money.
Will you share some with mommy?
Yuwei, what are you saying?
When we were eating fruit, the teacher said
that the kids who cannot finish their fruits can share with the kids who don't have any.
These are not the same things.
- Don't you not have money?
- Yuwei!
You are not allowed to talk about it again.
I'll give you another jujube.
[¥2,000]
Let's take a look.
- Xiaoling.
-  I've known you since I was 12 years old.
- Thank you.
- Why thank me? It's nothing.
I'll just buy one less outfit. Later, I'll have Siyu give you some.
Don't. Please don't tell her about this.
What?
Haven't you notice that she's worried about money?
Doesn't she have a lot of money?
A few days ago, I went to see her.
No wonder she takes my hand moisturizer.
Join my team! Trust me. Within three years, we will definitely be the leading brand
within the car battery service industry.
That's great! We'll meet at the company next Monday then!
Great, I just recruited a talent.
What were we talking about earlier?
To be clear, I am paying today.
If we go by the order, it should be me.
Well, I want to cut in. Is that not allowed?
Fine.
What company is it?
Okay. I got it.
Okay. Thanks.
Siyu...
A friend just told me that during the Lubao bidding crisis,
a company called Langfei spent ¥40,000 on internet ghostwriters
to post harmful comments about Lubao.
Come in.
Director Chen, your delivery.
Okay.
I didn't order food, did I?
- Did you order it for me?
- Not me.
All right. You can go back to work now.
Eat well, exercise well, rest well, and work well!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫