Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 3]
It's the middle of the night and you're awake. What are you doing?
I'll be done soon.
What will be done soon?
Are you still planning to associate with them?
Didn't I tell you to just forget about it?
I've thought about it. We can't act without due consideration.
- Why?
- Look...
There's no need for me to elaborate about Miao Miao's family.
Linda is only 4 years old
and she can speak 3 languages.
Xing Xing's parents got their doctorates from abroad.
Also, I've heard that William's grandfather
seems to be from one of Shanghai's, what was it,
very famous families.
What does everything you're talking about have to do with us?
Of course, it has something to do with us.
Say, we've spent so much money
and asked favors from so many people to get Yuwei into such a good kindergarten.
What did we do all that for? Isn't it for
her to be in the best environment
to grow up with the most outstanding kids of her age?
So I've thought about it.
We can't cut our ties with Miao Maio's mom and those other families.
Zhizhi, it's very obvious
that we aren't from the same social circle as them.
Isn't it exhausting to spend so much energy sucking up to them?
It's not exhausting if it's for Yuwei.
Then, do as you like.
How could it be "do as you like"? You must help me.
I heard that Miao Miao's grandmother is also a graduate of SJTU.
(TN: Shanghai Jiao Tong University)
Tomorrow, come pick up Yuwei with me.
I'll give the cookies to Miao Miao's mom.
You help me talk to Miao Miao's mom to form a connection to SJTU.
Then we can just forget about this matter.
- I'm not going.
- Hey, you must go.
Speaking of it, we were the ones who didn't tell them
that we wouldn't attend the group activity, so we were in the wrong.
We need to apologize.
If I knew this sooner, then it would've been great to just attend an ordinary kindergarten. Then there wouldn't be so many trivial matters.
Liu Yang!
Do ordinary kindergartens have this many facilities?
Is there one-on-one tutoring?
Do they organize frequent activities outside the school?
Do the teachers have advanced early childhood education?
Do they have after-school classes that teach Go?
(T/N: an abstract strategy board game, in which the aim is to surround more territory than the opponent.)
What else is the tuition for?
Speaking of tuition. If it were in the past, for a kindergarten with these conditions,
our incomes wouldn't be able to cover it. Fortunately, our country's regulations have changed
so that we can send her to kindergarten with no stress.
If you want to go, you go.
For Yuwei's sake.
All right.
Have you gone to bed?
Not yet. I'm researching auto repair.
Did you contact that spare parts distributor that I recommended to you?
I contacted him. I also contacted some other places.
Okay. Then, get some rest soon.
You, too. Goodnight.
GM Pan.
I've thought it through.
I can't become a team leader.
Also, I won't compete to become the Sales Director.
That is a rare opportunity though.
I'm still young. There will be a lot more opportunities in the future.
Sister Yuan doesn't have it easy.
Besides, with her capabilities and contributions to Lubao,
that's enough for her to get the position of Sales Director.
Did Yuan Huizhong say something to you while she sobbed?
No. This is my own decision.
Li Siyu...
Your personal relationship with her is good.
You coming here to express your stance is a given.
I understand. Go on back.
I didn't come to take a stance. It's what I really want.
Then, was what I said to you before a waste of breath?
GM Pan,
I know that the company needs competition.
But there are some things that I really can't do.
The fact that you can't do it doesn't mean that others can't. Do you understand?
You don't have to sacrifice yourself to help others. That principle does not exist here.
President Pan, I'm going to persist in this.
I got it. You can go.
Hello.
Can you help me make another appointment?
Anytime in the near future,... I am free.
Oh. Okay. Thank you so much.
Come on in.
How did it go?
I told him. I won't become a team leader or compete to be a Sales Director.
What did Lao Pan say?
He kicked me out.
Isn't that the same as you not saying anything?
Siyu, a company will solicit an employee's opinion
before making an appointment of position.
As long as you stubbornly don't agree, even Lao Pan
will have no choice.
Then, I'll go see him a little later.
All right.
Come in.
- Sister Yuan.
- What is it?
Tell me.
Tell me!
Uh... The company just sent out the latest notice.
It concerns...
What notice?
The company's Board of Directors has approved the following decision:
All employees of the Sales Department will be divided into two teams.
The sales department's outstanding employee, Yuan Huizhong is appointed as Team One's leader.
Li Siyu is appointed as Team Two's leader.
The team leaders and members will make a two-way selection.
The appointed team leader must voluntarily serve as the team leader.
Sister Yuan, I'll go on out.
- Where's GM Pan?
- He's left for a meeting.
- When will he be back?
- I don't know.
If there is something urgent, you can call him.
I really don't know how it turned out like this.
When you saw GM Pan today, did you tell him you weren't willing to be a team leader?
Are you doubting me?
I don't want to doubt you. But this is the reality.
The reality is that I told him I wouldn't become a team leader.
If you don't believe me, wait until GM Pan comes back and we'll confront him.
Siyu. Siyu!
We've known each other for 7 years.
I not only consider you my student and subordinate,
but I also consider you my best friend and sister.
I have always been sincere and genuine to you. You have also always been open to me.
Yes, I shouldn't have suspected you.
- I really didn't—
- You don't need to say anything. I trust you.
Since GM Pan has looked fondly upon you, then work hard as a team leader.
Sister Yuan.
I sincerely mean that.
GM Pan has already decided. It's not good to fight him in public.
GM Pan is quite insightful.
You indeed have the potential to become the Sales Director.
But you are the most suitable choice.
Sister Yuan, don't worry.
I will be running alongside you.
I've been right about you since the beginning.
Don't worry. When I become Sales Director,
I will continue to take care of you.
Let's go.
Go on.
Here. Let's cheers to our dear Yiming and send him off.
Cheers.
Boss, what's your plan next?
I plan on resting for a few days.
Then I will look for suitable jobs while resting.
With our boss's reputation, people will be chasing after him.
There are probably a lot of companies in a queue to hire you right now.
They definitely have queued to the Bund.
(T/N: Shanghai's symbolic place where business is booming)
Far more than that, the elevated road is full of them.
Enough!
Yiming,
do you remember Old Tang?
- Who?
- General Manager Tang.
That old GM in Tongli?
Their company needs a Planning Director. He asked if you were interested or not.
- Forget about it.
- The salary and benefits are better than your current job.
That's right, he can.
Right, we can meet up next time.
- I'll pass .
- With such good conditions,
is there no chance that you'll take it at all?
I resigned from Caijin voluntarily.
I have to at least go to a company
- that is stronger than Caijin.
- That's true.
Haowen, what are you whispering about with Boss?
Yes, what are you whispering about?
The Old Tang of Tongli Company, do you know about him?
- I have some impression of him.
He's kneeling and begging Yiming
to go be the Planning Director of his company.
- He won't go definitely.
- He won't go definitely..
That's right. He turned his nose up to it.
Of course! Old Tang's company is just like a roadside stall.
I completely agree. At Caijin, Boss was already doing work that was unworthy of his talent.
If he changes companies, no matter the salary or position,
they must be better than the one before, right？That's for sure, right?
Do we even need to say that? That's a given.
Boss, if you go to a better place,
don't forget about us bros.
That's right. As long as you give the order, we will go to you immediately.
- Go to you!
- Will you go?
I will definitely go!
Cheers! If I become better, I will remember everyone for sure. All right?
Cheer! To our forever boss!
We made the appointment for 16:00, right?
Yes. It's already 15 minutes after.
Could it be that she wants to repudiate the debt?
Maybe.
Sorry. Sorry. I was here long ago.
But I forgot about time chatting with a worker.
GM Wang, you are also here.
Lan Ke,
I just talked to the worker in the maintenance shop.
It was very enlightening.
The damage bill...
This is Mr. Lan's damage bill.
Then let's look at Lan Ke's bill first.
Here, here, here,
here, and here. I have crossed out these parts.
I won't take responsibility for those.
What do you mean?
These parts weren't caused by this accident.
I'm guessing they were repaired before. You can't count them on me.
Also, this and this.
You can just change a component. There's no need to change the whole thing.
Also this,
do I also need to pay for hardware aging?
Lan Ke, we should be repairing the car
and not making me go bankrupt, right?
Which worker told you that these don't need to be replaced?
Master Zhong, Master Ceng, and Master Liang.
The three best mechanics here at your shop.
Libby, ask Master Zhong, Master Ceng, and Master Liang to come over.
Okay.
This bag... at most can be considered 90% new.
Right now, the market price for this is very high.
That is at a specialty store. We are a secondhand store.
This is this year's celebrity style!
¥22,000.
This is sold out in the whole country.
¥22,500.
This color was the most difficult to buy!
¥25,000. No less.
Then let me take another look.
Be a little more gentle.
Master, did you three tell this woman
that these parts don't need to be replaced?
This car owner knows the ropes so we just told her the truth.
Aren't they all together?
They are not at fault.
I lied about my identity and tricked them.
I can understand
that you guys here at the 4S shop have to earn money,
but this money needs to be earned justly.
I definitely refuse to pay for the things I shouldn't be responsible for.
What do you say?
You guys go back first.
We're leaving.
Mr. Lan, I think...
what this woman said... isn't wrong.
Okay, just do as she says.
This way I can save more than ¥70,000.
Oh right! I got a card and charged money into it.
There is a 20% discount during working hours.
That'll save at least ¥10,000.
What is your job?
I'm a salesperson.
- Which company?
- Lubao.
The new battery company?
You know about it?
- I've heard of it.
- GM Wang,
if you want to buy batteries, then just look for me. I'll give you a discount.
Let's talk about the car first.
GM Wang, you need to replace the parts for your car.
Since they were all originally imported,
all of the parts must be shipped from Germany.
I wanted to discuss this matter with you.
Can we do this through my friend?
The price is really discounted
and I can guarantee the quality so you don't have to worry about that.
I don't need you to fix my car or pay the fees.
That wouldn't be appropriate, right? It is clearly my responsibility.
It's okay as long as you pay for that gentleman's car.
I have insurance.
Doing that
will mean no rebate for your insurance next year.
You're called Li Siyu, right?
- Let's add each other's WeChat.
- Okay.
Then I won't call you GM Wang anymore.
I'll call you Sister Ziru.
I definitely want to be friends with you.
Siyu, you're quite capable.
Isn't it all because money forced me to be?
But not everyone can be forced to be capable by money.
Sign here and I'll pay you.
Let me take a last look at it.
[Li Siyu]
[The car situation has been taken care of. Let's meet at the usual place]
I'm not selling it anymore.
Miss, what? Miss!
Miss! We can discuss it again!
I have saved over ¥100,000 now.
I admire myself.
You saved that much money?
That's enough for Yuwei to go to elementary until college.
It's all thanks to Sister Ziru's generosity.
It's all thanks to her being wealthy.
Now you know why I definitely have to find a rich boyfriend! You can't be generous until you're rich.
May I ask where your rich boyfriend is?
He's on his way, running towards me.
Keep an eye on him. Don't let him twist his ankle.
Then, have you already paid off that ¥130,000?
For you.
What's the meaning of this?
This situation was my fault.
But it all started because of Chen Yiming's proposal,
so we should split the ¥130,000 in half between us.
- Do you have money?
- No, that's why I'm mortgaging this bag to you!
Wait until I save enough money, then I'll redeem it back.
Be careful!
I don't have the means to take care of your high-end good. Keep it yourself.
That's fine, then let's just leave it with me for now.
But before I redeem it, the ownership of this bag is yours.
Zhizhi is my witness.
Sister Siyu, if you really need money, we have some.
That's enough from you as well.
Save Liu Yang's bonus for Yuwei to spend.
But to tell you the truth, you're very fortunate that
Yiming can help you pay the loss. Stop being hesitant.
Next time he proposes, just agree.
That's right. Let me tell you.
If you miss this chance, then it will be impossible to find someone who is so wholeheartedly devoted to you.
I have nothing bad to say about how Yiming treats me,
but I keep having the feeling I'm about to be trapped.
There are still a lot of things I want to do.
- I'm scared to lose my freedom.
- Freedom?
The reason he wants to get married to you so early is because you want freedom so badly, and he's afraid that you're too fickle.
How am I fickle?
You are drinking with customers all the time. How would he feel?
A sweet, sporty, straight man like Chen Yiming is in high demand.
You must cherish him.
Zhizhi, just don't bother with her.
Someday, when she gets dumped by Yiming,
she'll stop being so pretentious.
Yiming, I'm really sorry.
For the past two years, my company has been rapidly expanding.
Back then, I was really desperate for talented people.
But in the last few years, the market has changed immensely.
- What kind of changes?
- I won't hide it from you.
About 80% of the companies that I started two years ago
have been closed down now.
I am still shrinking my businesses.
So,... I'm sorry.
It's fine, GM Zhu. I understand.
How about this? Leave your materials with me.
I'll see if my friend's company has any need for your services;
and if they do, I'll definitely keep an eye out for you.
As for my company... I really can't help you.
Well then, thank you, GM Zhu.
I'll take my leave then.
GM Zhu, how about eating lunch first? It's lunchtime right now anyway.
I still have some business to attend to.
The meals have already been ordered. How about I go over there and tell them to cook faster?
There's no need.
I know it's really hard to get a reservation at this restaurant.
How about this?
If I help you get a good job, then you can invite me to a meal.
If I ate this meal with you today,
I would feel in debt to you.
Goodbye.
I'm done here, where are we meeting?
Hidden Prosperity
You can come straight here.
I'm already here.
Hello, Miao Miao's mother.
- You're so early.
- I didn't have any other business, so I figured I should come early.
- Your outfit looks so nice today.
- It just all right.
Hello.
You're here as well?
- Hello, Yuwei's mom.
- Linda's mom, you're here so early.
I made some cookies for you guys.
Xingxing likes to eat Matcha flavor. Here.
Great.
William likes to eat chocolate flavor.
Linda likes little bears.
I happen to have some bear-shaped cookie cutters at home.
Thank you!
Miao Miao's mom, aren't you dieting? I made some without sugar for you.
Here.
Thank you.
You really are considerate.
Look at this. The bear cookies really are quite adorable.
- This is probably Yuwei's father, right?
- Yeah.
- First time meeting.
- Hi, everyone.
- Hello.
Hello.
Miao Miao's mother, he also went to SJTU.
He and Miao Miao's grandmother are schoolmates.
I'm from the class of '04. What about her?
My mother went to Cornell.
I remembered incorrectly.
But I guess my grandfather could be considered a part of SJTU.
May I ask? What was his major?
He wasn't a student. He was one of the board of directors of the school.
That's so admirable.
You don't even know what my grandfather's name was.
What would you be admiring?
Before we were talking about decorating the place,
I can't manage it myself.
- The party?
- Yeah.
What place are you guys decorating?
- Next month, we want to host an "I Love Mom" party.
- That's great.
We want to make the party a bit fashionable, but we don't have enough people.
- I can help!
- Really?
- Yes.
- That would be great—
- We should talk about it a little more.
We'll meet up again then.
Sounds good.
We'll discuss it later.
The children are out!
They're out.
Where's Miao Miao?
[@Everyone, lets have a meeting tomorrow afternoon to discussion the party preparations, don't be late!]
Miao Miao's mom added me as a friend again.
She also added me into the elite group chat.
She says that tomorrow night we're going to have a meeting to talk about the party preparations.
Is there a need to be so excited?
- She took full responsibility and used her own insurance?
- Yes.
- How is that okay?
- How is it not?
You already promised her before that you would take full responsibility,
so you should do what you say.
Sister Ziru took the initiative to offer to help.
I couldn't say no.
So you are at ease with letting her shoulder the burden
of next year's loss of insurance rebate and of the risk of fraud by herself.
Besides, we're not related to her in any way.
We'd owe her such a huge favor. Does this really seem right to you?
It's so much money though.
How many TVs would I have to sell to make it all back?
Siyu,
didn't I tell you?
I can pay this off for you.
Your money doesn't grow on trees either.
You worked hard for it.
But at least it will give me peace of mind.
It's so much money!
I suggest we focus more on...
- Let me take this call.
- ...the technology behind batteries.
- Hello?
- Sister Ziru, do you have time tomorrow?
What's going on, Siyu?
I want to treat you to a meal.
I think I should pay for the car's repair.
I'll take you up on the meal offer, but let's not talk about the car repair anymore.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Sure. Once you've made the reservation just send me the address.
It's a deal. I'll see you tomorrow.
Your annual salary isn't that high.
Why do you think you can make back this money in one year?
I'm amazing.
I... I have a plan.
I have a plan to get the company to give me a raise.
Then I wish you a smooth promotion and salary raise.
Thanks.
Go with me tomorrow.
Sure.
[You are here]
[I am here]
[This is Shanghai]
[Work hard for your dream]
She said she's willing to accompany me.
People even break contracts that are written on paper.
This is just an oral promise.
Li Siyu wouldn't do such a thing.
Then let me ask you. When you wanted to divide the team today,
why didn't she agree?
This time I will be running beside you.
Sit down.
Siyu, take a look at this.
These are the names of everyone in our Sales Department.
Pick some.
I'm picking?
If you're going to be the Team Two's leader, then you need to have people in your team.
Besides the people who have always been with you,
Xia Xiaotian, Liu Xiaojia, look at some others.
These people have always
been with me, so they will stay with me.
- This one, this one.
- Sister Yuan, the company says that the decision must be mutual.
Isn't it a bit inappropriate for us two to already select people here?
Just let them make their own choice.
Wouldn't that just create a mess? What if they all pick to be on my team?
Or all pick to be in your team?
First of all, they probably wouldn't pick me.
There's always a first-come, first-served process.
If your team is full, then even if someone wanted to get in, they can't.
- Good morning, GM Pan.
- Good work.
- Good morning, Sister Siyu.
- Good morning.
Sis, Lin Ling asked if our team still has room for more people.
She says she wants to join our team.
Lin Ling?
- One of the three goddesses?
- That's right.
- Didn't Sister Yuan kick her out?
- Yes.
Sister Yuan stipulated that anyone who doesn't perform well for three consecutive months would be automatically fired,
but now the sales department has completely changed.
I think that if you're willing to take her in,
she can at least intern for three more months.
Forget about it. She can't do anything,
why would I want her?
All right then, I'll tell her.
Oh right!  The Administration Department has set up a new office for you. It's over there.
Really?
- Good morning, Sister Siyu.
- Morning.
How is it?
Sister Siyu, the Administration Department has said
that if you're unsatisfied by anything, just tell them and they will change it.
Sister Yuan's here, I'll head back out first.
- Sister Yuan.
- Hey.
- How is it going?
Is everything organized? If you are missing anything, just tell me. I have everything.
No need. The Admin Department has already help me with everything.
- Are you better?
- Much better.
Do you have to get an infusion today? I can go with you after work.
There's no need, I'm going to the hospital for a check-up in a bit.
But there's a client in Ningbo
that wanted me to go discuss the contract.
Can you make a trip for me?
There is just one last step to close the deal so I won't be at ease sending someone else.
No problem! Leave it to me, I guarantee I'll bring back a signed contract.
Thank you. I've already had Ziting book a 10:00 a.m. bus.
Okay.
Is there anything else?
No, nothing else.
I'll get going.
We just brought a...
- After you graduated from university, have you only worked at one company, Caijin, this whole time?
- Yes.
I'm a pretty nostalgic person.
Director Chen,
you're Haowen's friend so I consider you a friend.
Then I'll just say it how it is.
The best time to change jobs in the workplace is three to five years.
I think your time is a bit too long.
You've worked for ten years at one company and never left.
I wouldn't dare to recommend you to my clients. They wouldn't want you.
Don't businesses need employees who are very loyal?
Yes, loyalty is very important.
Employees who change companies once a year aren't acceptable.
But to develop a business, you need energetic people.
Then, asides from the number of years at a job, what else are they looking for?
Right now on the job market, the ones who are most desired
are either the young ones with new ideas,
or the ones who can bring benefits to the business.
Typically those are directors or higher ranked.
Combining your age and your position at your old company,
it's honestly a bit awkward since you are average.
- Please don't mind. I'm a pretty direct person.
- It's fine.
It doesn't mean that you won't find anything.
It's just that your salary might not be up to your expectations.
Then how much do you think I should ask for?
¥200,000?
- For an annual salary?
- Yes.
That's far from what I expected.
That's how the market is like right now.
- Hello?
- Yiming. Hurry and congratulate me.
- What's up?
- I just closed another deal.
That's great. Congratulations.
- Are you not at the company?
- I-I am.
Does your company play such sad music?
I'm at... the coffee shop near my company. I h-h-had an appointment with my client.
Are you working overtime tonight?
Don't forget, we made dinner plans with Sister Ziru.
I'm going to the subway station right now.
I'll get back to Shanghai later in the afternoon.
I need to go to the company to finish something. Then I'm done.
- Did you have a business trip again?
- Yup.
I'm in Ningbo.
Why do I remember that you don't have clients in Ningbo?
Sister Yuan's client. I'm just here to help.
Sister Yuan needs your help?
She couldn't leave.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I didn't.
What did you not do?
Is it because I didn't tell you beforehand?
No.
Can we not be like this?
I just had last-minute plans and didn't have the time to tell you.
It only takes a few hours to go back and forth.
- I'm really fine.
- All right then,
I'm hanging up.
- Sister Siyu your back?
- Yeah.
Sister Siyu, Vice President Hu is looking for you.
He wants you to go to Human Resources once you get back.
- Give it to me.
- Help me put it in my office.
Thank you.
Come in.
Please sit.
Please choose people for Team Two.
I'm choosing? Isn't it a two-way decision?
Just take a look at the list of names first.
[List of Personnel in the Sales Department]
- Is this the entire Sales Department?
- No.
Sister Yuan already chose all the people for team one.
- So these are all the people who were left over?
-Yes.
Then what is there for me to choose?
VP Hu, I'll be leaving.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Come in.
Sis, Team One's list of names has already been chosen.
- There are Huang Bibo, Kuai Zi, A'Fu Zhou Zhiyu, Yang Tian and Zhang Jiaqi—
- I know already.
I heard that after we left today,
Sister Yuan asked them into her office one by one to talk.
She also made all of them sign an agreement saying that they're willing to follow her.
Really?
So.. .right now, aside from you,
the top ten people in the Sales Department are all in her team.
Sis, were you the lion who was tricked to leave the mountain?
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After pain is when we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from a crowd of people  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫