Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 22]
Was it the intern?
Didn't everyone persuade you to forget her?
I already broke things off with her.
That's good.
I've already sacrificed my emotions and Xiao Wei to go back to my family
but look at Zhang Zhizhi. She still made a big scene.
You can't blame Zhizhi entirely for this.
Then is it completely my fault?
Well, everyone is responsible for something like this.
Liu Yang is so honest. I can't believe he would do something like this.
I suddenly remember something you said.
"In every man's heart lives a jerk."
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
For this family,
I work hard from early morning to late at night. I bear all the hardship without complaint.
I don't know what I did wrong.
All right, don't cry anymore.
In my experience, crying about it is useless.
Letting it out is also good.
Liu Yang, right now, there's no one else. Just us.
Tell me the truth. What are you and that girl—
I already said,
nothing happened between us.
Then, why would Zhizhi act like this?
Between the two of us, we gave some little gifts to each other.
So you had feelings for her?
Liu Yang has such a cowardly and conservative personality,
but his actions today
as well as the little gifts you mentioned like cups and scarves,
I think even if there is something between the two of them, it probably just started.
It can't start though! There can't be anything at all!
As a person who has some experience in these kinds of things, I'm advising her to calm down.
First, you have to  think about what you will do in the future
instead of just getting angry in the present.
What brilliant ideas do you have then?
She's very pure.
Very kind and hardworking.
We both come from the countryside.
So no matter what I said, she would understand.
Being with her made me feel relaxed.
It's like I'm back in my college days,
a time without worries.
No matter how great she is, aren't you married?
As a married man, I don't think I've let down this family.
In order to support the house, car, wife, and daughter,
I wake up earlier than a chicken and sleep later than a donkey.
At work,
I have to pretend to be happy and humble.
After getting home, I have to listen to my wife's complaints.
I have to endure everything at work.
After getting home, I still have to endure things.
My only wrongdoing...
is that I am not a robot.
I'm tired, I feel oppressed.
Yes. You also don't have it easy.
Suddenly, one day,
a person appeared.
In front of her, I could smile.
I could forget about the competition at work.
I could forget the annoyances at home.
Yiming, if it were you, wouldn't you have been moved?
What do you plan to do from now on?
Zhizhi, you've devoted yourself to him for so many years,
and Liu Yang is about to become a director.
If you choose to get divorced at this time, then aren't you letting them off too easily?
Zhizhi, no matter what you choose,
our side of the family will support you.
I won't get together with Xiao Wei.
However, Zhizhi made such a huge scene today,
I really can't deal with her anymore.
Are you really going to get a divorce?
Zhizhi,
you need to think clearly.
What kind of outcome do you want?
Do you really want to divorce Liu Yang or not?
If we really got a divorce,
what would happen to Yuwei?
So, Zhizhi and I will not get a divorce.
I don't want a divorce.
If so many people came to get me after school every day, that would be great.
Bye, Yuwei.
- Bye-bye.
Zhizhi, call me if you need anything.
Hey, Liu Yang.
After getting home, have a better attitude.
Comfort Zhizhi and admit fault, okay?
Be good, okay?
Come on, baby.
Go to your room and play.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Every time we get involved in Xiaoling's and Zhizhi's issues,
you seem to go crazy, losing your sense of logic.
It's so scary.
What are you afraid of? I don't act that way towards you.
I'm not afraid.
I just think that some things require you to be calm.
Especially when it comes to other people's family issues.
If our actions are too rash, then they won't be able to turn things around.
I was just too angry.
He hit his own wife and even did those kinds of things (cheating).
Hitting his wife was definitely wrong,
but we also don't really understand their situation. Right?
I think all things
have their reasons for happening.
You seem to be very understanding of him.
I don't understand him.
I think that as long as we are human,
we will experience all sorts of problems.
When we are met with a problem, we should solve it.
There is nothing we can't solve.
We won't have this type of problem, right?
What are you randomly imagining?
The problem between us now is
when will you resign to better your health?
Let me think about it.
Do you really have the mood to be online after everything that's happened?
Would you let it go already?
There is no way I can just let this go.
Didn't I apologize to you already? What more do you want from me?
I want you to break it off with her.
I already broke things off.
I want you to break things off with her in front of me!
What are you doing?
Call her.
I won't.
If you don't call, then I will.
- What's wrong with you?
- Give it to me!
What are you doing, Zhang Zhizhi?!
- Give? Give the phone to me!
Zhang Zhizhi!
- Zhang Zhizhi, open the door!
- No!
- Open the door!
Zhizhi! Zhizhi, if you have anything to say, can't we talk civilly? Open the door!
- I won't open it!
- If you don't, I'm going to kick open the door!
Hello, Brother Yang, are you all right?
Stop harassing Liu Yang!
Are you insane?
- Mama!
- I'm telling you!  You are not allowed to bother my mom.
I'm going to go to your workplace.
I want everyone at your workplace to know what kind of rubbish she is!
I want to make it so that she can't continue to work there!
If you dare to go to my workplace, then we're getting divorced for sure!
Are you threatening me? You dare to threaten me?
- That is my bottom line!
- You still have a bottom line?
What are you doing?
Put it down. Are you insane?
Bastard!
[Mom]
Don't cry. It's fine, it's fine.
- Hello, Mom?
- Hi, Zhizhi.
Did you call me just now?
No, I think I called the wrong person.
Are you guys doing well?
I'm great, Mom.
Are you well?
I'm great. After getting home, the water and air have been great,
so my health is much better now. All right,
I will hang up now. I have to go and dance.
Brother Yang, are you here?
Earlier, your wife called and scolded me.
It's fine. For you, I don't care.
Even if the whole world scolds me, I won't be afraid.
I still haven't finished the medicine you bought me.
The words you said to me are still in my ears.
The kiss you gave me
still makes me feel warm.
Brother Yang, even if we cannot be together in this lifetime,
I will never forget the love you've given me
during this time.
She continuously jumped.
Just like what the witch said,
every leap
is like walking on a blade.
Mom, was the little mermaid not afraid of getting hurt?
Everyone is afraid of getting hurt,
but loving a person
- will make you—
- fearless toward pain.
hurt even more.
Dad is back.
That's the neighbor.
But she willingly endured the pain.
Beside the prince,
she walks lightly and gracefully like foam.
Are you kicking me out?
I don't want to see you.
[Liu Yang]
I have moved out of the house.
Dad!
Hi, Big Aunt and Little Aunt!
Good. Yuwei, you are so well-behaved.
Yuwei!
Let me see if you got prettier.
You are so pretty!
Look at what I brought you.
Do you like it?
Also, some nuts! You will get smarter after you eat this.
There are no peanuts inside.
There is something else you like.
What's this?
- Do you like it?
- I like!
Take them.
Here. Can you hold it all?
I can.
Go play.
What's going on?
He isn't willing to apologize to me.
He isn't willing to break up with that woman as well.
They are still contacting each other.
Asshole!
But you kicking him out is not a good strategy.
Why do keep a guy like that? Fatten him up to cook for dinner?
If that woman seizes the opportunity to really get with him,
then it would be too late for Zhizhi to regret it.
Mom!
Coming.
What are you doing?
Why are you pulling on me? This is a new jacket. It's very expensive!
Why do you keep persuading her to get back with him?
Can't you let her make her own decision?
Li Siyu, can you not always think about things from your own perspective?
Zhizhi is not you or me.
This family is her life. She cannot survive without this family.
Zhizhi was very independent when she was young. She became like this after being with Liu Yang.
- Can you get her to go back to when she was young?
- She cannot rely on that man.
Maybe it's good for her to leave him.
- How about the kid?
- I can help her take care of the child.
Don't indulge in the wildest fantasy. Are you someone who can lead a family life?
Do you want Yuwei to eat takeout food with you?
Zhizhi,
do you want to divorce Liu Yang or not?
I don't know.
If you don't want to, then ask him to come back.
Siyu slapped him. Consider it as venting your anger.
I think he won't dare to hit you again.
Yiming said that
before you knew about everything,
Liu Yang already broke things off with that woman.
I saw that woman send Wechat messages to him again.
Stop thinking about that right now.
Think about whether you want to continue this marriage with Liu Yang or not.
To be honest, you two have not seen much of the outside world.
Liu Yang's asshole actions are just elementary level.
If you still want to continue being with Liu Yang,
just consider this time a lesson for him
and end it on a good note.
If you don't want to continue being with him,
make a decision quickly.
Sister Siyu,
do you also think that I should forgive him?
You still have Yuwei.
You must first think carefully about
what kind of life you want to live.
If you want to have the family complete and whole,
then there are certain things that you have to let go of.
Didn't you persuade them to make peace? Why did they separate?
Ask Liu Yang.
Liu Yang is actually not a bad person.
He is just too tired.
Hurting Zhizhi like this, is he still not considered a bad person?
The way Zhizhi dealt with things sometimes,
really embarrassed Liu Yang.
What do you think Zhizhi should have done then?
Be understanding of his difficulties? Forgive his cheating?
Or even self-criticize her own mistakes?
Forget about it. You are a sick person.
I'm not going to discuss this with you.
- Liu Yang has hurt Zhizhi yet she still won't get a divorce. Why?
- Why?
Isn't it because the family can't do without Liu Yang? Isn't it because Zhizhi and Yuwei need him?
What are you trying to say?
We have been arguing and going back and forth but you just have one intention.
You want me to quit my job.
Did I say that?
Have I said a word about wanting you to quit?
This is what you want from the bottom of your heart even if you didn't speak it out.
Chen Yiming, let me tell you! I'm afraid that I'll have to suffer like Zhizhi if something happens one day.
- I'm not Liu Yang.
- But you are also a man!
You can't presume that I'm the same as Liu Yang just because I'm also a man.
No one can make any guarantees.
That's right. No one can make any guarantees. But that's the future. What I'm talking about is the present!
The present is the beginning of the future.
I must have my own career.
I hope I can live without anyone.
I know!
You are doing this for my own good.
But...
if you really consider things from my perspective,
don't say those things anymore.
Let's talk about getting married after Lubao's financing.
I'm leaving.
[88 Barbecue]
Boss! One more beer, please.
All right. Coming!
I was over there and thought that it looked like you. I can't believe it really is you!
- What brings you here?
- Sit, sit.
You also sit, GM Wang.
Why are you here alone? Where is Siyu?
Siyu is working overtime.
- Working overtime again?
- That's right.
It's so cost-effective for Pan Zhiyu to use Siyu.
GM Wang, would you like to have some skewers?
Okay! I haven't eaten since noon.
Really?
- Your beer.
- This taste really good.
Yeah?
- Help me heat them up and bring some more lamb skewers.
- Okay, no problem.
- Thank you.
- Please wait for a moment. You are welcome.
It's cold already. Don't eat if it's cold.
Have some hot ones later.
Would you like to have some beer?
I have some good wine in my car. It goes well with skewers.
Sure!
Boss, bring two cups!
Xiao Wang,
bring a bottle of wine here from the car.
- Your cups.
- Open it, all right?
No need for cups.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Wow, it smells so nice.
Just give it to me.
Thank you.
Just wait a second.
- Let me know when it's enough.
- It's enough.
Thank you.
To...
- chance encounters.
- To chance encounters.
How is it?
It's quite...
This wine tastes very interesting with the skewers.
What type of wine is this?
The type is not important.
The important thing is the mood while drinking.
Well, GM Wang, your mood looks very good today.
In places outside of work, just call me Sister Ziru.
Sister Ziru.
How come you're drinking all alone?
Yeah.
Did you have another argument with Siyu?
We didn't argue.
It's just that there are some things
that we can't agree on.
That serious?
What kind of things?
A few days ago, she suddenly fainted.
I took her to the hospital.
They did a checkup at the hospital.
The results said she has exceeded normal values in all aspects.
I tried to persuade her to rest
but she thinks I'm forcing her to resign.
That's not what I mean, but
she just keeps trying to go against me.
Resigning is a huge thing.
Yes, but I wasn't trying to make her resign.
I just think that she needs to first better her health.
Once she is better, she can start working again,
right? But she seems to understand it differently.
Sister Ziru, I really—
I really feel despondent. I just don't understand
why the longer two people are together,
it somehow seems harder to understand each other.
According to my experiences,
it's easy to accept a person but understanding each other is really hard.
Disregarding two people who just started dating,
a husband and wife who want to spend a lifetime together
cannot simply ask for mutual understanding,. It is something that just happens with luck.
Sister Ziru,
you mean that I shouldn't force it.
My point is...
you still need to be more understanding.
Understanding?
Yes.
Of course, being understanding is the most difficult thing to do.
Sister Ziru, I...
I'm not trying to disrespect you.
I just want to ask...
How must women
be so competitive?
That's not necessarily true. It depends on what.
Tha-That's right.
In the past, I always thought Siyu
was generous, took charge,
had a responsible heart,
and was especially independent in life.
I really thought all of that was great,
but now I think
you can't be that competitive in every aspect. Especially in life.
You can't just focus on your career your entire life, right?
I think—
I think I'm a woman who only has a career.
Sister Ziru, I...
Yiming,
you're right.
People can't just have a career alone.
Just like on my way here,
I was actually very lonely.
I was so lonely
that I thought everything was meaningless.
The suffocating feeling of being lonely
made me feel hopeless.
I actually saw your Wechat Moment.
I knew that you were also alone.
That's why I took the initiative to come here
because I was afraid—
I was afraid I would be alone tonight again.
Watching a movie alone.
Seeing someone else's story
to cry a little bit and laugh a little.
Then I'd go home alone.
It's another lonely and long night.
Sister Ziru.
From now on,
if you need someone to talk to,
feel free to tell me.
I will be there for you.
Hello?
Where are you?
Siyu.
If you don't want to resign, then don't.
I only have one request.
Please don't tire yourself out.
Don't work too hard. Don't ruin your body.
If you don't want to get married yet,
then I will respect that.
I still only have one condition.
If you choose to get married,
then that groom...
must be me.
Yiming.
Siyu, from now on,
I will do my best to stand in your shoes when thinking about problems.
I will do my best to understand you.
I will do my best. I will try harder than now.
I won't let you have any more worries
about the future.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[ Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  En...  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫