Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 57
Seeing these autumn leaves,
I get the feeling that growing
old is not that bad after all.
I guess it's newfound
passion for one's final days.
Right...
Well said.
Then, they fall to the ground.
And die.
Youngguk....
Are.... Are you still with me?
Don't you worry.
This is nothing.
Back in the day, you
were a gangster in Myeongdong...
You can't let this bring you down.
Write it down.
Write what?
If you want to get
out of here alive, do it!
I... I don't know a thing!
You really want to die?
I know nothing.
Is it true that the chairman
was arrested by the ANSP?
Don't get involved in this.
What is that supposed to mean?
It's what Dad wanted me to do.
To stop you from getting involved,
in case anything like this happened.
Because if things go wrong, you
and your brother could be in danger.
Who are you calling?
Arresting the chairman is nothing
but a subterfuge by Jo Pilyeon.
Gangmo...
If anything happens to the
chairman, we'll all be in danger anyway.
It's me, Hyung.
What's the matter?
Chairman Hwang
was arrested by the ANSP.
Tell me what happened.
You're back, Chief?
Ohh... Sure.
I'll see you there, then.
What brings you here, Sir?
- Hwang Taeseop Investigation File -
You know Hwang Taeseop has
been arrested, right?
Really?
I think you'll have to
be the one who questions him.
What was he brought in for?
The man responsible for leaking the recent
torture case to the press was Hwang Taeseop.
Find out who he got that
information from, and how.
I'll have to take a look
at the case files first, then.
So you're telling me you have clear
evidence that Lee Seongmo betrayed you?
Here's a photo of him and Hwang Taeseop.
I see.
This is Lee Seongmo for sure.
You've recently been to the
Myeongdong Cathedral, right?
Was this the day?
We're under surveillance.
I don't really remember.
You know Yoo Chanseong, right?
Have you ever received
any account from him?
Why don't you just kill me?
If a little torture could scare me,
I wouldn't even have started all this.
So you're acknowledging those allegations.
After going to hell and back,
every day I live is a gift.
If going through
all this can help me...
gain the right to ask my
late friend for forgiveness,
then, sure...
I would finally be able to die in peace.
What the hell is he talking about?
If you keep this up, you'll force
us to take you back to the underground bunker.
Answer.
Have you ever received any
account from Yoo Chanseong?
If I do answer,
will you do me a favor?
If I die here,
I would like you...
to convey these words to my daughter.
Marry the man you love.
I just feel like I'm responsible
for keeping them apart,
so I wouldn't be able to find peace
if they don't get back together.
So, if I die...
What the hell are you talking about?
Answer the question.
Do you know anything about
that account or not?
Let's try again.
This will be my last
question, Hwang Taeseop.
Have you ever received an
account from Yoo Chanseong?
I really can't figure it out.
Why did he betray me?
A look at his profile and you'd
think he has no recollection of his past.
And for bringing someone like him
to the ANSP, you're really something.
Should I call it "daring"?
You told me there was someone
you wanted to kill, right?
I could see that fire in your eyes
down at the shooting range.
You still bear a grudge against this man?
Is that how it looked?
Isn't it time you finally tell
me what this is all about?
Who is he?
This man you bear a grudge against.
The man who killed my parents.
Ohh... Jaechun.
You remember the people who
helped us with the smuggling back then?
Find out what they're doing these days.
Why are you suddenly asking about that?
I need to verify something.
Just go.
You're not feeling well,
so I'll spend the night here.
I'm feeling much better.
Do you know that my father loves you?
You love him as well, right?
The chairman is just a good
friend I like to hang out with.
No matter how grateful you are, you
wouldn't just fall ill this way if that was true.
You don't need to hide it from me.
I wish you'd just stop hiding
your feelings for each other.
Then, how about you?
President Lee really seems to love you.
You love Lee Gangmo as well, don't you?
Director...
Forget about me, I'd rather see
you be a little more ambitious in that sense.
Life is not that long.
So make everything you want yours.
Be it money, any material goods or people.
I'm just telling you this hoping
you won't live in regret like I did.
We're back!
Hi! Everybody.
Good morning...
Long time no see!
They don't understand a word, see?
That is, "I missed you."
Something like that.
Hyungnim, everything in order?
Order or not, what the hell have
you two been doing all this time?
Was the UK down the block?
You can't imagine how
long that train ride was.
Ohh... Where did they say it was again?
What was it...
- Chicago... Was it Chicago?
- Oh, no!
- That's America. The States.
- Oops!
You still have no clue, do you?
Speak the truth.
Why are you so late?
What have you been doing together?
Oppa, what's wrong with you,
are you crazy?
Wh.... What, crazy?
Are you taking this little rat's side now?
Something is up, isn't it?
Right?
What... What could possibly be up?
I swear on your mother
I didn't lay a finger on her.
You mean it?
You better mean it?!
You're choking me, stop it!
Sotae would never be
capable of that, so just stop.
So... So go ahead and tell me.
What have you been doing?
Ahh... I really...
I worked hard for Gangmo's sake,
and forget being happy
to see me, you even...
Ehh!
Follow me!
Oppa, you should be ashamed of yourself.
He worked his ass off all this time,
how can you treat him like this?
Sotae!
That brat must be out of her mind...
What's wrong with those two?
Hey.... The way I see it...
This is starting to smell.
No way...
When will they let
you come back on TV?
Guess they will sooner or later.
You're done with the ads, and
the composer isn't even bringing any new song.
People will have forgotten your name by now.
Soojeong... Soojeong!
They want to cast you in a film!
A film?!
You know Director Nam Shiyoung?
I sure do!
He's one of the most
successful directors these days.
Right... So the shoot for
his new film starts soon,
and he wants you as the protagonist.
Me?!
That's right!
I guess seeing you on those
Hangang Construction TV commercials...
left an impression on him.
Soojeong!
So... Do you have any acting experience?
Yes... I've been taking acting lessons
since before my singing debut.
Then, I'd like to try a little reading...
Can you do that?
- Affection -
Di... Director...
That's a little...
I'll give it a try.
Soojeong...
So this was the reason
why you abandoned me?
If you did, then you should move on
and enjoy the rest of your life!
You come back?
Seems like she's doing quite well.
Pretend you know nothing about this.
To make it up for all you did
to me, it would take ten...
No, even ten years wouldn't be enough.
So... You must do it.
Aren't you going to come in?
Then...
How is it going with Deputy Han?
Don't talk to me like that.
I'm fine with it, but
insulting the deputy that way...
What are you doing?
On second thought, I was foolish.
Because if there's anything
one wants, he should take it.
There's no need to worry about
your feelings or anything else.
Don't act like this, Minwoo.
But, you know...
I don't feel all that tempted today.
- Did Chief Lee get off?
- Yes.
Your report?
Here... They're all done.
I can go now, right?
Lee Daesu had an older son?!
Yes.
According to the men we sent on his trail,
they said a high school
boy jumped off the train.
That's Lee Seongmo.
But... They were sure he died.
They never verified his body.
Yes... I guess that's true, but...
There were two other people who
threatened me, saying they'd avenge their father.
Lee Gangmo and Lee Miju.
Now that I think about it,
all the lies Lee Seongmo told you...
Lying about Lee Gangmo having
died at the Samcheong camp,
and about Lee Miju having an abortion.
Then, it seems there is no doubt.
Lee Seongmo and Lee
Gangmo must be brothers.
I was too busy worrying
about all my enemies outside...
to see what kind of
danger I was facing up-close.
Lee Gangmo, Lee Miju,
and Lee Seongmo.
So they all were siblings...
Clear evidence?!
Are you sure Lee Seongmo mentioned that?
It's a report that Ji Yeonsoo wrote today.
This Wednesday night at nine,
Lee Gangmo is going to
bring him that piece of evidence.
Lee Gangmo?!
You're telling me this informer is Lee Gangmo?
By now, Jo Pilyeon must have
gotten a hold of the information we spread.
What will you do
when he shows up there?
We must force him to
confess his crimes on his own.
We must never underestimate him.
He's not the kind of man who
would so easily fall into a trap.
I know.
Hyung.
You brought that report on
Congressman Oh's death, right?
I looked at it a few times,
but there was no evidence
pointing to Jo Pilyeon.
Gangmo... Can you figure any of this out?
When he called Seongmo,
Chanseong said he couldn't see a thing.
He couldn't see?
Why would he suddenly go blind?
He couldn't see a thing, but he
was still pushing the accelerator.
And not the brake.
Why would he do that?
In his last call to me, he
mentioned the name Jo Pilyeon.
If they have any evidence
regarding Oh Byeongtak's death,
they could just report it to
the police and it'll be the end of it.
There would be no reason
to spread false information.
Then, what else are they planning?
Whatever that is, it doesn't matter.
What does is the fact that
they have the secret fund account.
Give me a few of your men in support.
If it's just Chief Yoon, I could understand.
But I can't go beyond that.
You can't?
If I can't keep their mouth shut,
my head will be the first to roll!
You still don't know me?
You will face no
repercussions, so rest assured.
And who would ever risk bringing
this up, when it involves the president?
But bear in mind that it's the
last time I'll be able to help you.
It's this Wednesday.
By Wednesday, everyone who's
been bothering us will be dealt with.
If Jo Pilyeon uses Chief
Oh to deal with this,
we'll need Congressman Min Honggi's help.
Right... Better be sure, while we're at it.
I'll meet Congressman Min.
Right... You're taking good care
of the account, right?
Don't worry.
I hid in a place they will never find.
Congressman Noh will soon be
announced as presidential candidate,
I bet you must be really busy.
I believe Congressman Noh
should accept direct elections.
Two tigers are waging
war in the opposition camp.
A consolidated stance
will never bring us success.
So if the party doesn't
decide on a candidate of its own,
I guess Congressman Noh
would have good chances of winning.
Because the moment he accepts
direct elections, his popularity will benefit.
We're about to get our
hands on clear evidence...
proving that Jo Pilyeon killed Congressman Oh.
Did you figure out the situation?
My brother and I will set
up a trap and wait for him.
So I was wondering if
we could count on your help.
If only to help Congressman Oh
find some peace, I can't ignore this.
Tell me.
What can I do to help you?
Congressman.
Why would you even agonize over it?
Without making things
more complicated than they are,
we can just catch
them both in the act, and...
Our goal is that of getting
our hands on that account.
And there is no way they'd
bring the account there.
Then, how do you plan to proceed?
You just wait.
That trap they set up to catch me
will become their own burial spot.
Yes?
It's me, Gangmo.
Ohh! Jeongyeon.
Where are you now?
Here?
Deoksu Palace.
Deoksu Palace?!
And why did you go there?
What's the matter?
Ahh.... Nevermind, Gangmo.
Sorry for getting in the way.
Getting in the way of what?
By any chance, are you and Suyeon...
What are you saying? I'm alone.
Alone?
You went there alone?
Yeah.
I just needed some time alone to think.
Gangmo...
Can I come there, too?
Now?
Yeah... Why not?
All right, then.
Will be there in a moment.
Gangmo.
- Shall we take a walk?
- Sure.
Those falling leaves are so pretty.
I haven't been here
in a while, feels really nice.
Something is up, isn't it?
A look at you and it feels like
you have something to tell me?
Actually... Today we were granted
a permit for the credit institution.
Jeongyeon...
But...
I'm so worried about Dad that
it ruined my day a little.
I wanted to at least tell someone...
I feel really strange, Gangmo.
You should be happy!
And the chairman will be ecstatic as well.
Right.
Dad will be happy, too.
Then, let's do this.
I'm so happy I'm about to go crazy.
I'll be happy for everyone
else, so just watch me.
Our Jeongyeon did it!!
Everyone!!
Jeongyeon did it!
Gangmo!
Jeongyeon!!
Don't be angry, Sotae...
My brother has always
been the suspicious type.
What am I, a thief?
A conman?
Ahh... It drives me insane, really.
Should just marry someone else.
So you'd abandon me and get married?
I didn't mean that,
but Shideok always acts so grumpy...
You said you love me.
That I'm your first love!
The first since I came out
of the Samcheong camp, sure.
You bastard!
Men are all the same!
How can you dare say you'll
abandon me and marry another woman?
Gyeongja.
Can't you trust me?
I'm Park Sotae.
I'm yours already.
Really?
Sure.
So I guess all your apartments and
company holdings are mine as well?!
Company holdings, too?
Why?
Feel bad about it?
Ahh... Who said anything...
They're yours, all right.
I'm all yours anyway.
Ahh... Those lips really...
Hey Sotae, where...
Knock, will you?
You fool, I knock to
go down the stairs?
It's the tracking device you asked for.
Where are you going to use this?
Tomorrow, anything could happen.
So that's why I need it.
Be careful, Gangmo.
I feel like you're being used as a
bait, so I don't feel good about it.
You called Congressman Min, right?
The police will be
planted there waiting for you.
This is our last chance, Hyung.
If we lose it,
we might never get another
opportunity to bring Jo Pilyeon down.
Gangmo.
Once all this is over, I was planning
to accept Hwang Jeongyeon into our family.
Hyung...
I know that you two are still in love.
And I have no intention of opposing it.
I'll be honest.
I really love Jeongyeon.
But I can't marry her.
Miju even gave birth to a child
and broke up with Minwoo anyway.
Chairman Hwang and
Jo Pilyeon are different.
The suffering Miju went through
is no different from mine, Hyung.
If it's because of
me, just don't, Oppa.
I know that Chairman Hwang
did enough to deserve our forgiveness.
So don't let Jeongyeon
Eonni go and marry her, Oppa.
Miju.
Every time I look at you,
I get depressed.
Are you going to grow
old and die all by yourself?
Same goes for you, Big Oppa.
At least you, get married.
You won't find another woman
like Jeongyeon Eonni even if you try.
First, let's deal with all this,
and then we'll talk about this again.
I'll soon have my film debut.
Film?!
I'm going to become an actress.
Really?
Miju, you...
Wow... Lee Miju.
Really?!
Aren't you going home?
Going now.
Aren't you writing reports, these days?
They said I could stop writing them.
So I guess you won't need
to follow me around all day, either.
Wait for me!
I need to make a call.
Let's have a word.
Come with me.
- I have an appointment.
- Cancel it.
It's urgent.
What is going on?
Your brother still hasn't called.
Something went wrong already?!
I guess Jo Pilyeon doesn't plan
to fall into this trap so easily.
What's that supposed to mean?
And what's that?
Listen well to what I'm about to say.
Lee Gangmo.
We need to ask you a few questions.
I have done nothing
warranting an investigation.
I suggest you don't
make a scene and just follow me.
What did you bring
me all the way here for?
You'll have to stay here with me tonight.
So this is surveillance.
Just think of it as a
little night duty with me.
What did Jo Pilyeon
promise you for this?
I'm sure that you're well aware
of the fact that Jo Pilyeon is responsible...
for the deaths of
Chanseong and Congressman Oh.
Hey... Lee Seongmo!
What are you trying to say?
Don't you think that sending Ji Yeonsoo to
write reports and spy on me and Chanseong...
was despicable?
Enough with that crap!
Want me to spell it out?
It was exactly what you did that
killed Congressman Oh and Chanseong.
You got that girl involved and she caused
Chanseong's death without even realizing it.
Whatever you keep yapping about,
it's no use.
Is it?
But if that evidence emerges,
then it's over for you as well.
Since you abetted and
participated indirectly in that murder.
Hey!
You little prick, think I
don't know that you wrote that account...
and had been plotting this all along?
Again with the groundless accusations?
I've really had it with that.
This is the last time you'll
ever play the innocence card.
Yes, Congressman.
We're heading that way as we speak.
Don't worry.
I was particularly careful,
so nobody is on our trail.
That's fascinating...
So we know wherever
they're taking Gangmo to?
Ahh... Will you please stop
with all that nonsense?
Call this number.
All right.
It's past nine already, what is going on?
Yes.
Congressman Min Honggi, right?
I call you on behalf of President Lee Gangmo.
Why is no one showing up?
President Lee has been
abducted by Jo Pilyeon.
What?!
Then, did he find out about our plans?
Not yet.
I'm trailing Gangmo right now.
If you remain there, I'll bring you
to him the moment I find where he is.
No, forget that...
Tell me where you are now.
Yes.
All right. I'll go there.
But before that, you'll have
to set Chief Lee Seongmo free.
And what's that all about?
They're looking for you,
so I redirected the call here.
- Who is it?
- Congressman Min Honggi, Sir.
I ought to...
You goddamned fool!
Didn't I tell you to say I got off already?
It's me, Congressman.
I will convey whatever
you tell me, so go ahead.
Yes.
All right.
I will tell them.
He told me to come out.
We're going to catch Jo
Pilyeon now, care to join us?
I hope you won't ruin your entire
existence because of Jo Pilyeon.
Chief Yoon...
Call Chief Yoon.
What?
I said call Chief Yoon right now!
Go outside and inspect the premises.
All right, Sir.
Search him.
Yes.
What?
All right.
We'll pull back immediately.
You can do it, right?
Or else, what,
should I let them kill us?
I'll bring Congressman Min,
so don't let them spot you.
Ahh... I'm still suffering from
jet-lag, what is all this?
- Be careful.
- All right.
Yes.
Hyung.
It's me, Shideok.
Where is Gangmo being held?
It might have been a
good showing on your part,
but I'm afraid that won't cut it with me.
So let's hear it, what's this clear
evidence you wanted to lure me here with?
Were you so scared of it
that you abducted me?
I wasn't scared, just curious.
And I also came to
get something from you.
Speak!
What on earth is this
clear evidence you talked about?
- Seeing how much you hesitate...
- You forget a little detail,
the fact that abducting me is
like admitting you killed Congressman Oh.
I'm sure that's not your clear evidence...
That's much too sloppy a
trap even for someone like you.
You had no evidence about
Congressman Oh's death to begin with.
Sleeping tablets.
You fed Yoo Chanseong sleeping tablets.
And I'm sure you followed the car
him and Congressman Oh were riding.
Holding the very same
gun you're pointing at me, of course.
To destroy any evidence, you even
had their bodies cremated.
However, despite having
meticulously planned all that,
- you made a fatal mistake.
- Don't make me laugh!
There could be no mistake whatsoever,
since my plan was flawless.
So you finally admitted it.
What?!
You've just admitted that
you killed Congressman Oh Byeongtak.
So you'll kill me?!
Since if I do, any
evidence will be buried along with you.
Will killing me really get rid of it?
Who else... Lee Seongmo?
That fool had the guts to
write that secret fund account.
Even if I get rid of him,
who will ever blame me for it?
The moment you pull that trigger,
the secret fund account
will be revealed to the world.
You really think I didn't take
any precaution before coming here?
So how about this?
In exchange for your life,
Lee Seongmo will bring me the account.
I'm sure Lee Seongmo will value
your life a lot more than that account?!
Am I wrong?
Jaechun?
Where are you going?
Give it here!
Would you do that if you were me,
you sorry-ass son of a cunt?
Come here!
Stop there, you prick!
No way... Don't!
Gangmo is in danger!
This is all we need.
I'll go after him, so go inside!
Come on!
You prick... You're dead!
If you want to survive,
you'll have to ask your brother
Lee Seongmo to bring me that account.
This watch...
Doesn't it look familiar?
I hear they use it at the ANSP.
It's a tracking device, apparently.
It's all over, Jo Pilyeon.
Congressman Min Honggi and
the police are waiting outside.
I've been gritting my teeth
for all those wretched years,
and it was only for this moment.
If you really think you
can kill me, pull the trigger.
Don't do it, Hyung.
I suggest you kill me while you still can.
Or else, your lives will be
ruined for abducting a congressman.
You killed Chanseong.
You're the man who
murdered Congressman Oh!
You know what article 307 clause 1
of the Korean Criminal Procedure Code states?
"Facts can only be
acknowledged through evidence."
Without any evidence, you can scream I'm
a murderer all you want, but it'll be useless.
You know what this is?
Every single word we
exchanged has been carefully recorded.
W.... What?!
You confessed it to me on your own.
That you fed Yoo Chanseong
those sleeping tablets,
and killed him and Congressman Oh!
Criminal Procedure Code,
article 307 clause 1?!
How kind of you to remind me.
You son of a bitch...
Gangmo!
Here it is.
It's evidence proving that Jo
Pilyeon killed Congressman Oh Byeongtak.
Take him out.
You two are incredible.
You managed to bring down
a giant even politics couldn't touch.
So you were able to tape evidence
proving who the murderer was?
Open it.
There's nothing here.
Nothing?!
There is no tape.
What are you saying?
I shot it myself!
What's going on?
There is no way!
I checked the tape with my own eyes!
So why is this empty?
It was him. Go Jaechun.
I'm sure he took it out.
Right... That sorry-ass cunt
took it and ran away.
Send people out and
find Go Jaechun right away!
But, without evidence, we'll
be forced to release Congressman Jo.
They're all witnesses!
Go catch him!
All right, Sir.
Don't worry, Hyung.
Go Jaechun will be caught soon.
So they issued that permit
for your credit institution?
Yes.
But I'm even happier that you're safe.
Unless I see you give me a grandchild,
I'm never going to die, you silly.
But...
Where is Jeongshik?
His father barely made
it out of there alive...
That...
After you were arrested, he
just disappeared without leaving a trace.
Chairman!
Come on in, Gangmo.
Hey... I almost risked
meeting your father, you know?
Gangmo.
Come out with me a moment.
Why?
Ohh... Let's go... buy something.
Isn't it time you let
Jeongyeon call you Mother?
Now that you're
back with us, I should.
Right.
Gyeongok...
I.... really...
It hurt like hell.
You know?
It felt like I was dying.
But...
The thought of dying without
ever seeing you and Jeongyeon again...
hurt me more than anything else.
Gyeongok...
It hurt so much...
Yes.
Minwoo, it's me.
What's the matter?
Listen well, Minwoo.
You're the only one
who can save the congressman.
What are you trying to say?
The congressman has been arrested
for the murder of Congressman Oh.
It's not a situation I
can solve on my own right now.
By now... The police might have
issued a search warrant for me.
Where are you now?
No... No need to come here.
Minwoo, all you need to do is find that.
Will you tell me what's going on?
Lee Gangmo fooled us.
Did you just say Lee Gangmo?
Your father fell right into his trap.
You must find that videotape and get rid of it.
With that out of the picture,
we can save your father.
Where is Seongmo now?
- That's a job for...
- Not Lee Seongmo!
He's a traitor.
What is that supposed to mean?
Minwoo...
Listen well to what I'm about to say.
- Letter of Resignation -
It was exactly what you did that
killed Congressman Oh and Chanseong.
You got that girl involved and she caused
Chanseong's death without even realizing it.
I'm sorry, Chief Yoo...
I'm sorry, Chief Lee...
So he hit me right here,
and started running this way.
And then the car came and hit him.
But then he got up and just... this way...
He ran away.
How about the factory?
I looked all over with Sotae,
but no traces.
If Go Jaechun took it, he might
have already destroyed the evidence.
Then, what happens now?
What do you think?
Jo Pilyeon, that sorry-ass cunt...
will have to be released again.
How can that happen...
First, even if we're the ones
who testify, we must bring him to court.
He still is being
backed by influential names.
Unless we have clear evidence against him,
it won't be easy under this regime.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Are you telling me Jo Pilyeon will be released?
Is there a chance
he'll become prime minister?
Jo Minwoo...
will be given wings, then.
You want me to get rid of Lee Seongmo?
If he finds that tape,
it's all over for the both of us!
I'm sure he's alive.
Before Lee Gangmo beats us to it,
we must get our hands on him.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com