This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 10 ~
You're hurting me!
Keep quiet!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I didn't demonstrate.
You were found with demonstrators.
I was waiting outside 31 Building,
and they just arrested me.
Shut it.
Which college and year?
Your school's name!
I'm not a college student.
Then, what are you?
I...
am a housemaid.
Uh?!
Housemaid.
Housemaid?!
The ones cooking,
doing the laundry and stuff?
Yes.
Are you telling the truth?
Can't you call and find out?
Wow... You sure are lucky.
If it weren't for the police,
you'd all be dead by now.
You know?
Shut your mouth,
you sorry-ass thug!
What?! Thug?!
Think you'll gain any
of that land this way?
Give up while you still can.
Manbo Construction.
Come out.
They've come for us.
Hey.
We'll get going first,
so have a nice rest here.
I'll remember this.
Sit down, sit.
They'll come for us
soon as well, I guess.
I won't forget this.
You went through a lot.
The five companies of
the construction committee...
will pave the way for our win
at the subway construction bid.
I made sure our opening bid will be
0.5 to 2 percent lower than theirs.
That's all fine and dandy,
but is there no way to
reduce construction expenses?
By at least five percent.
Realistically, that's impossible.
I mean, shouldn't we make
a little profit out of this?
Because of the oil crisis,
the price of raw materials is skyrocketing,
and subcontractors will not accept
any renegotiation of our existing deals.
We still have some time until the bid,
so try to find a way.
I will.
I don't think it's something
you should worry about?!
If I meet with the subcontractors
and try to convince them, it'll work.
And I can check our progress
on the field as well.
Look, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Go ahead, then.
Chairman.
If she says she will convince them,
why should we try to stop her?
But let's be clear.
I won't accept any
"I tried, but it didn't work."
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Let's have a word in private.
What are you doing?
Get out of the way.
If you don't, I'll start screaming.
Go ahead.
Let go!
If you can't even deal with this much,
how are you going to face
those rugged construction workers?
You're going to face
something much worse than this,
so how are you
going to deal with that?
It's hard even for men to
deal with people on the field.
It's out of a woman's league,
am I making myself clear?
Let's go, Agasshi.
If I was going to give up for this little,
I wouldn't even have started.
Also, act like this with me again,
and you'll pay for it.
I'm not saying that as
an employee of this company,
but as the chairman's daughter.
I thought I made myself clear?!
That I will take care of her from now on.
Only I can decide where I belong.
Be it past, present or future,
I'll take care of her.
Bother her again,
and you'll have to deal with me.
Do you believe you're in
any position to threaten me?
Don't ignore my warnings.
Please... Look at yourself in the
mirror before you act all feisty.
I'm tired of wasting time with people
who couldn't lace my boots.
We'll see if that's really the case.
Please, don't act like that and
take another look at the estimates.
He's asking for a discount,
do I even need to look at it?
Director...
Go look elsewhere.
Do you know that with this kind
of money it's useless even trying?
I do.
- However...
- Young lady.
What is your position?
I'll soon be a team supervisor?!
It's no use talking with a woman who
doesn't know a thing about construction,
so bring me your male superior!
This is under my jurisdiction.
It has nothing to do with my superior.
What are you doing?
Get this lady out of my face.
Director...
- Don't act like this...
- Please, let's go.
Wait... Wait. I'll go.
I'll come again.
Let me ask you one more time.
Wait...
I can leave by myself!
It's me, Director Kim.
A young lady from Manbo
Construction will be there soon.
Hey... Let's get moving, shall we?
When are we going to finish,
if you keep this up?
Just take a look at
the contract estimates.
Look, young lady.
Before you ask for a discount,
know how much those service costs are?
Forget about the discount for now,
- and start by taking a look...
- Ehhh... You're here again?
I told you to pick
laborers right, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
- Director!
- Wait a moment.
How many did you load?
Go on.
More, more!
A few more.
There. Go, quick.
Director.
I'm not asking for anything difficult.
- Just take a look at this.
- Ehh... How annoying, really.
Director, wait a moment.
Director.
Please, just once more.
Ehh... You really!
Let's hurry up!
Director, please, I'm asking you.
I said forget it!
That damned old fart!
Listen!
You want heads to roll around here?
- Get this lady out of here!
- Yes, Director.
- No, wait...
- Do you know what we risked?
The daughter of Manbo Construction's
chairman facing such embarrassment...
Shideok.
We need to dig into the
subway deal's subcontractors.
Not just the ongoing construction,
but also their work in the past.
Find everything you can.
There has to be
something fishy going on.
Why are you asking, suddenly?
I'll have to help her out.
Ahh... Really...
Why, think she'll be
thankful if you do that?
You're drinking without any side dishes?
- Ajumma, some soup over here.
- Yes.
You know me?
Haven't you seen me earlier on?
I worked at the construction site, too.
They said not to
come anymore, from now on.
Think they won't grow old, too?
Then again, when the
entire country is so rotten,
why would this business
be any different?!
Damned thieves...
What are you trying to say?
Thieves?!
A few days back, I got drunk and
fell asleep at the construction site.
Shouldn't even talk about it...
So they were secretly selling
off raw materials, I guess?
When you get older and
have some money to spend,
choose your house well.
You never know when the buildings
those thieves built may collapse.
That Hwang Jeongyeon.
She's clueless and still has the guts
to take over the subcontractor issue?
Tell me about it...
Daddy's little girl must
have lived up to her pedigree,
considering we got dozens
of complaints today alone.
Is it true that her
real mother was a bar girl?
That's what I've heard.
She cheated on the chairman,
and was even kicked out.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Seeing how she wags her tail around
Chief Jo Minwoo just makes me sick.
Right...
Doesn't seem like he has
any interest in her, anyway...
Any progress?
Yes.
It's going wonderfully,
so you don't need to worry.
Get up.
We urgently need to go somewhere.
Minwoo! Here.
What is this?
I told you.
It's an important meeting,
business-wise.
I'll talk plainly from now on.
- It's better that way here.
- Look, Chief Jo Minwoo!
Hey... Why did you bring her?
Let me make the introductions.
This is the daughter of Manbo
Construction's Chairman Hwang Taeseop,
Hwang Jeongyeon.
He's the second heir of
Korea Group, Lee Jongcheol.
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
And here's the heir and president
of Dongguk Bank, Yang Inmo.
How are you?
Daeyang Trading's youngest,
Jang Byeongsam.
Geosan Auto's Choi Wookseon.
Jeongshik.
If it's Manbo Construction...
Is she your sister?
Sister? Yeah, right.
Since when did we allow illegitimate
children to hang around with us?
Ehh... This is just beneath me,
it's no fun.
Jeongshik, be careful what you say.
Jeongyeon came here as my woman.
And they say it runs in the family...
You.
Since when did you
start seducing Jo Minwoo?
What?
Minwoo.
Let me give you an advice.
You know, her real mother?!
Try to say just another word!
And see what happens.
What's wrong with you?
We haven't met in so long.
Here, let's change the mood.
Jeongyeon, have a drink.
That bastard...
Blood!
Don't go.
Why?
So I can keep watching you
put on airs in front of me?
You're really pathetic.
Do I look that easy a woman to you?
Thought you could just do
whatever you want with me?
Don't kid yourself.
People like you make me sick.
- Are you done?
- No.
I'll say one more thing before I go.
I won't always work under you.
And I'll remember all this.
Because people like you
certainly don't help the company.
Those people are thinking of
investing in Manbo Construction.
With their funds,
we'll make a lot more money...
than what that five percent off of
the subway bid would have given us.
But you just committed a serious
blunder right under their noses.
So before you worry about
firing me later,
first think if you really have what
it takes to gain the right to do so.
So?!
Did you bring me here today
so that I could give up on that?
You'll pardon me,
but I can't give that up.
I won't.
Letting pride move everything you do
despite being clueless...
I'm afraid that's not too charming.
Charming?!
And why should I
ooze charm all over you?
Don't you kid yourself.
I didn't mean as a woman,
just as an employee working for me.
You can find your way home, right?
Now Hwang Taeseop is even
buying land around the subway.
If we let Hwang Taeseop win the bid this way,
it's over for Daeryuk Construction.
But we still have time.
Find a way to stop the bid.
I will.
I really can't figure it out.
Why Chairmen Jo, Baek and Cheon
betrayed me so suddenly.
Have some of this.
We only had fruits.
Leave it there.
Did you call me, Ma'am?
You'll deafen me.
Why did it take you so long?
Long?!
Haven't you seen me
run here like an arrow?
You rotten wench...
I've had to starve
all day because of you.
You told me I had the day off
every last day of the month.
I even prepared you lunch before I left.
Bring me some water.
Just a moment.
Forget the water,
bring me orange juice.
All right.
No.
Just bring me water.
You were bored all day, weren't you?
It's because you want
to play with me, right?
Who ever talked
about playing with you?
Leave.
Get out of my face.
I'll bring you both water and juice.
I'm sorry, Miju.
Nobody ever lasted past ten days.
Until you tell me to leave,
I'll stay here.
Thanks.
I'll bring it to her,
so you can go to sleep.
Yes, Chairman.
Right...
About what I told you last time.
About finding someone for me.
Ahh... Right.
I'm so busy these days...
You said it was your brothers, right?
I'll have someone look into it.
Thank you, Chairman.
Hide-and-seek is long over.
So just show up, will you?
Seongmo Oppa.
Gangmo Oppa.
Are we just wasting our time,
listening to what that old man said?
There are rumors that
subcontractors are in cahoots.
And if we want to stop that,
we must find their weak spot.
And how long do we have to stay here?
It's not like they'll
smuggle that off every night.
Aigoo...
What's this?
It's the curfew siren.
Forget about going home tonight.
This won't do.
We need to find another way.
Finding their account
would be much quicker.
Account?
What account?
If they sold off those raw materials,
there must be some kind
of account listing those deals.
We'll look for that.
Whatever.
Do as you wish.
Gangmo.
Don't fall for Jeongyeon.
Seeing you do all this
for her sake is killing me.
Can you even dream about her?!
It's not that.
Aigoo... I'm sure that's the case.
I'm just worried she'll hurt you.
Still working, I see.
Is it going well?
Don't worry.
The bid result will not disappoint you.
I'm not concerned
about that in the slightest.
Is it going well with
Chairman Hwang's daughter?
I'm just going at it my way.
All right. Now that you've seen her,
what do you think?
What are you asking me?
Once the subway bid succeeds,
Manbo Construction's stature
will rise exponentially.
It'd be the perfect opportunity
to tie the knot between our clans...
So you want me to marry her?
Chairman Hwang and I
have a kind of symbiosis.
Wouldn't it be better
to make that official?
So what you're talking about
is not marriage, but a deal.
Because love or anything else which involves
giving and taking is a sort of deal.
I'll do as you say.
So you give your consent?
Giving consent was always up to you.
I merely followed your wishes.
You might be my son, but I love the fact
we always understand each other.
So?
Are you telling me that brat is prancing
around construction sites to cut costs?
Yes.
And the chairman told her to do so himself.
Ajumma, some fresh water.
Yes.
Mom, what if Jeongyeon really
ends up inheriting the company?
That's never going to happen.
I'll never allow it.
You always only talk, don't you?
You can't get a decent spot
for your only son.
Do you know how embarrassed
I feel with my friends?
She's at work now, right?
Yes, Ma'am.
Tell her we'll meet at the hotel's
coffeehouse down the street.
I can't let this slide.
- See you.
- See you next time.
What do I owe the visit to?
Quit the company right now,
and go live on your own.
I put enough in there.
It'll be enough to rent a small room
and get you by for a few months.
You can take that money back.
You're all grown up, how much
longer will I need to raise you?
I'll leave home, so don't you worry.
But I won't quit the company.
You won't?
And why?
You don't know?
I thought you'd know
that better than anyone?!
You wretched wench.
You're finally starting
to show your teeth now?
Think I'll let you inherit that company?
Do you know what's
your biggest mistake?
Not raising your son properly.
If Jeongshik had been
just a little brighter,
think I would have ever dreamed
of inheriting that company?
That company?!
Don't even dream about it.
The company's right next door.
Don't shame yourself.
What?!
Shame?!
If Dad finds out,
you're the one who'll end up in trouble.
I'd rather leave that company to
a mutt passing by than leave it to you.
Are you going to meet
those subcontractors again?
Yes.
Isn't it hard on you?
I'm fine.
Is pretending to be all right
improving things?
You can't do all that much
in life with stubbornness alone.
If that's all I've got,
I must at least try.
You're here.
Chief Moon.
Yes?
Once the subway contract is confirmed,
we will receive 8 billion won
in investment funds.
Use that money and find a way
to cut costs by five percent.
Understood.
- A hundred? And this week?
- Another hundred.
- That's what the director said.
- It was seventy last week.
- Director.
- Ohh... You're working hard!
Try to find more people like him.
- All in order, right?
- Yes.
It was seventy, wasn't it?
- Shideok.
- Yeah.
That lady handles accounting here, right?
You weren't going to say
she's pretty, were you?
Director Kim.
How have you been?
Ahh... Annoying people
straight from the morning.
Hey... Gangmo.
There... Look.
I bought some makgeolli.
Come here and have some.
Do you call that shoveling?
Move.
There must be an account
with all their dealings.
If we find that, we can stop them.
I know, I do know...
But where can you start looking from?
Look at that mountain of rice.
It's as high as Namsan.
Guess she eats three meals at once.
I really hate fat women who eat all day.
Right, so go hit on her.
What?
Just find out where the account is.
Forget it!
Hey, can you do this to me?
No way!
I can't.
Excuse me.
You're really charming when you eat.
Are you busy later this evening?
Why?
I have two tickets
for this really fun movie.
You know, I have really high standards.
Yes. I thought so myself.
Aww... This is trouble?!
Where do I find a partner now?
Actually, there's this
school festival next week,
but I don't have a partner yet, so...
So, are you a college student?
Yes.
Was it that obvious?
I'm working part-time here
to pay my tuition fees.
I thought so myself.
Thought this line of work
didn't really suit you.
- Left a grain on your lip.
- Where?
See you tomorrow, Shideok.
I really enjoyed myself today.
Did you find out?
Whatever, man...
My first kiss, with someone like her?!
You'll drive me crazy!
Where is the account?
The account.
In a safe box inside the office.
And she said Director Kim
always keeps the keys on him.
Happy now?
I'm so pissed off I could explode,
should we just go and
deal with the damned thing?
If you act in a hurry and fail,
it'll give them a chance to hide the evidence.
Let's come back once
the subway bid is over.
Aww... My lips!
What the hell is this?!
You've become a master sharpshooter.
Director Jo.
Don't you think he's a little wasted?
Using someone as skilled as
Lee Seongmo just to spy on me.
It's a waste of state money, isn't it?
Have you ever spied on Director Min?
Never done so.
Still an expert in wild conjecture, I see.
I'd love to bury the hatchet with you,
but you still seem
to think of me as a foe.
My only foes are those who try
to bring harm to the president.
That's a relief, then.
I'm telling you just in case,
but don't try to compete with me.
Don't want to see you getting hurt.
I'm thinking of leaving this place soon.
Shouldn't people of remarkable patriotism
like you remain here to protect the KCIA?
Seeing he's still as arrogant as ever,
seems like Hong Gipyo still hasn't
mentioned the subway bid to him.
It won't be easy to mention that.
If Director Min ends up
abandoning him over this...
Same goes for Min Honggi.
Won't be easy for him to get rid of the
only money line for his entry into politics.
Anyhow, if Manbo Construction
can win this subway bid,
then it can only pave the way
for your future success.
You said there was someone
you wished to kill, right?
Seeing you practicing down at the
shooting range, your eyes were on fire.
Still want to shoot a bullet
through your enemy's heart?
Is that how I looked?
Don't you think it's time for you
to tell me what's behind all this?
Who is it,
this enemy you talked about?
The man who killed my parents.
You can pay back gratitude when you want,
but vengeance should be
served quick and cold.
Tell me who it is.
If it's troubling for you to
deal with, I can help you out.
I'll just say I appreciate the support.
If you'll excuse me,
there is something I need to do.
Sometimes, those eyes
of his frighten me.
Still, when it comes to being loyal,
he's second to none.
Right. I'm well aware of that.
You just wait, Jo Pilyeon.
I'll soon pierce
that black heart of yours.
Who is it?
~ To Chairman Hong Gipyo ~
Chairman Hwang, you came here yourself?!
You surprise me.
You're acting as best man for
our Manbo Construction in this bid,
of course I had to pay a visit.
- Give it to him.
- Yes.
Here's the bid Daeryuk Construction
will have to present.
We'll be counting on you, Chairman Hong.
Yes, Chairman's office.
Yes.
Chairman.
- Yes.
- It's Miju. An envelope was just delivered.
From where?
All that's written on
the envelope is your name?!
I'll be there in a moment, Ma'am!
No.
Yes.
Yes, I will, Chairman.
I'm coming!
I said I'm coming.
You seem busy.
I'll just get going.
Do you know what I went through
to form this committee?
I pranced around all day trying
to convince those esteemed folks,
as if I was licking their damned feet!
And you want to take
all that away from me?
Even if it ruins me,
I will never let that happen!
Look, Chairman Hong.
You still don't seem
to get what's going on.
It's not just for this subway bid,
you will never get your hands on future
construction bids without my consent.
Just because of all
we went through together,
I'll let Daeryuk Construction...
stay afloat and sit at our table.
Let's go.
Take the phone right now,
and call Chairmen Baek, Jo and Cheon!
I'll fight this to the
bitter end right here and now!
You never know what he might scheme,
so gather the committee members.
There will be no need.
My father is already meeting them.
Director Jo?!
These days, the Inspection Department
is focusing on corporate corruption.
Chairman Hwang Taeseop told me this.
"Don't bother those
three committee members."
"They're like brothers-in-arms to me."
Taken that way, it does sound
like a token of friendship,
but I believe there's no
friendship in business and politics.
Are you by any chance aware of some
fatal weak spot Chairman Hwang is hiding?
What weak spot could he possibly have?
Nothing of that sort.
We're simply moved by
a spirit of friendship.
You can believe us, Director.
So you have faith in
Chairman Hwang as well, is that it?
Of course.
The most important thing
in running a business is faith.
Fine.
So I trust there would be no reason
why that faith would be betrayed.
If any of you betrays Chairman Hwang,
then I'll take that as a sign that
something else's going on, and dig into it.
Is that clear?
Here... Let's have a drink.
Health and prosperity to you all.
You as well.
I doubt any of the
committee members will come.
Have you heard anything?
Why did they suddenly betray me
and stick to Hwang Taeseop?
Is there anything you know about that?
Wouldn't it be one of the two?
You either fell out of favor with them,
or maybe Chairman Hwang
had very convincing "arguments."
Yes.
Could you pass me to
Chairman Hong Gipyo?
Just a moment.
Chairman.
It's for you?!
Me?
Hello?
Did you look at the envelope I sent you?
So you haven't yet.
Inside there is a plan
to stop Hwang Taeseop's bid.
Did you just say
a "plan to stop his bid"?
Who are you?
Are you working for Director Min Honggi?
I know no such person.
So why are you helping me?
Because my grudge against Hwang Taeseop
goes deeper than you think.
That is all I will tell you.
Get off of me!
I said no! No!
You're not touching my nails!
Take a look!
You've let them grow for so long,
they look like a falcon's claws.
A little longer and
you'll catch rats with them.
You're looking down on me, aren't you?
Just because those feet can't move!
You said I received an
envelope, right? Where is it?
It's this one.
Hwang Taeseop...
Is this all you used to
force them to betray me?
Fine...
Let's see what happens when your
own weapon is pointed against you.
Let's see how it'll taste like.
You never know what might happen,
so remain alert until the bid is over.
Seems like we're a little early?!
You said at four, right?
Yes.
How did it go?
They all left their respective offices.
So why isn't anyone showing up?
There is no way they wouldn't.
There are only ten minutes left!
Something is going on.
What could possibly be inside here?
I'll bury into oblivion everything
I've seen there regarding you.
Instead, from now on,
we will return to the original
construction committee.
But, like...
Hwang Taeseop won't
take this lying down?
So are you suggesting you're afraid
of Hwang Taeseop, but not of me?
Look, Chairman Hong.
Director Jo Pilyeon is
on Chairman Hwang's side.
We were even intimidated by him.
All it takes to catch a fox is a tiger.
As for that issue,
you can leave everything to me.
Only Manbo Construction
has submitted a bid so far.
In accordance with our regulations,
I'm here to inform you
this bid has been nullified.
In a fortnight,
another bid is set to take place,
so I hope there will be
no further mistakes.
If you'll excuse me.
What is this?
Find out where they are right now!
They're gathered at the Royal Club.
I just checked.
They followed Hong Gipyo there.
Hong Gipyo?!
That fool...
~ By issuing this special order,
President Park... ~
~ tried to curb the deviating
behavior of selected students, ~
~ but their demonstrations already spread... ~
Yes.
Oh, Minwoo.
What?
Turn off the TV.
What are you trying to say?
And how could you let this happen?
All right, I'll be there in a moment.
What is the matter?
The bid failed.
What?
Those committee fools
stabbed us in the back.
Jaechun, follow me.
How do you explain what happened?
I'll have to go in and find out myself.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
The chairman was adamant
not to let anyone in.
Ehh Ehh...
Move!
What kind of retards
do I have to deal with?!
If there's anything above your eyebrows,
can't you give it a test run?
How dare you barge in here without...
I ought to...
Unless you want
another hole in your mugs,
get the hell out of the way,
you third-rate thugs.
That's not what I meant...
I was just...
Hey... Am I bleeding?
Chairman Hong!
Here you are, Chairman Hwang.
I see you're here as well, Director Jo.
I thought I made myself clear?!
Come on in, Director Jo.
And I'd heard you were going around
threatening respectable businessmen...
So the rumors were true.
Haven't you heard the president's speech?
This doesn't seem like the place
a KCIA director should spend time at now?
What did you just say?
Think all directors are the same?
KCIA or Inspection Department...
What is the difference?
What?
When you were on your knees
begging for your life,
I should have dealt
with you once and for all.
You son of a...
Is that all someone exploiting
businessmen can say?
You're the one who's exploiting them!
While exposing this cesspool
of corruption is part of my job.
- Got it?
- So?!
You're going to expose my "corruption"?
- Think I can't?
- Be my guest, you prick!
Think you'll get away with it?
Think I won't be able to get rid of you?
- Don't let anyone in!
- Yes, Director.
Reporters are waiting next door.
Chairman Hwang Taeseop!
Don't even think of intimidating
the committee members again.
You might find yourself tied upside down
in an underground questioning room!
Didn't you say it was a done deal?
How on earth did you handle all this?
There must have been
a mistake along the way.
A mistake?!
Would that be an excuse,
after getting shot to death in battle?
Whatever it takes,
you must win that bid.
If you fail at the next bid as well,
then you'll have to prepare
yourself for the repercussions.
Think I'm doing all this to rescue you?
Call for a meeting immediately.
We're at a crucial moment.
Our bid must be lower than
Daeryuk Construction whatever it takes!
Were you able to cut construction costs?
I'm still talking with
subcontractors about it.
And how much longer
will you keep just talking?
We need results here!
Jeongyeon, give it up.
Chief Jo, you keep looking into it
until you find a way to cut costs.
All bear this in mind.
If our bid can't beat Daeryuk
Construction's, it's all over for us!
Is that clear?
The boys?
They're all waiting outside.
We started this to help her out,
and now things have
gone out of proportion.
Tell me about it.
If we could only prove that
Director Kim sold off those goods,
then we could certainly deal with
the subcontractors' price-fixing.
And we could also renegotiate estimates.
Let's go.
Gather all the subcontractors.
Will be right on it, Chief.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
If you have any information
that could help us, share it.
You must have at least achieved
something, all this time?!
The subcontractors might
be engaging in price-fixing.
It makes no sense that their
estimates would all be the s...
You were so adamant
you'd succeed and cut costs,
but all you achieve is forcing
subcontractors to get together and fix prices?
You prance around without a clue,
moved only by pride,
so these are the results.
Yes...
Sure, you don't need to worry.
Yes... If we stay united,
even Manbo Construction will be powerless.
Who are you people?
Director!
Who are you?
You've been selling raw materials, right?
Where is the account for all
those stolen goods you sold?
Stolen goods?!
You must be out of your mind!
I'll just call the police...
Go ahead and call them.
We'll see who they
put their cuffs on first.
It's this one.
What is wrong with you?
That's an impressive list.
The police will love
getting their hands on all this.
Help me out just this once.
You don't seem to be the police,
so what is it that you want from me?
The most important thing
for the both of us to convive...
is to reduce the price of raw materials
in a way that satisfies us both.
What else are you trying
to take away from us?
Aren't you being excessive?
We need to make a living as well!
I'm still not done explaining.
Please let me finish.
We have nothing else to listen.
You're just asking us to sacrifice
to benefit Manbo Construction!
That's right.
We can't go any lower
than this estimate!
We need to make it if
you want to survive as well!
That's exactly what we should say.
You need subcontractors
like us to survive!
Isn't that right, gentlemen?
That's right.
What are you wasting our time for?
Let's just all go.
I think all the directors present today...
will have to renegotiate their deals
with Manbo Construction from scratch.
What is he talking about?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Find Daeryuk Construction's bid price.
Gangmo, you find out Daeryuk
Construction's bid price.
I want to be nominated for
the next congress election.
Chairman Hwang will
support my candidacy,
since we're about to become in-laws.
You can try everything in your power,
but you won't get what you want.
Bear that in mind,
as you'll soon find out what it means.
Gangmo...
Close an eye just once.
Chairman Hong gave him
the bid agreement?
Does this guy who took the document
have something against Chairman Hwang?
He sent Chairman Hong's
housemaid to do it.
If you turn and see my face,
it will be the last thing you see.
I must see that face of yours.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com