Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 16 ~
What?! Did you follow me here?
Miju...
Oppa?
Ga...
Gangmo Oppa?
Oppa!
Miju.
Gangmo Oppa...
Miju...
Junmo?!
Yeah.
I called him Junmo.
I see.
So our youngest has
gone far away, to the US.
Still, that's a relief.
I saw you come alone,
so I was worried he might
have ended up like Mom.
I ran away from
the orphanage in Daejeon.
I worked hard to
come to Seoul right away,
but finding enough money was not easy.
I'm sorry, Miju.
Don't say that.
I'm to be blamed for that, anyway.
You told me to wait at that bakery.
Miju.
Look at me.
From here on in,
I'll make you live in luxury.
We'll find our Junmo,
and I'll make up for everything
you've been going through all this time.
I'll never separate from you again.
I'll stick right beside you.
I'm really foolish.
You haven't changed a bit.
You look just like
the last time I met you.
Same goes for me.
I couldn't even recognize you.
Any news of Big Oppa?
Still, it's nice not having
to wait for him alone.
Miju.
I...
don't think we'll find him.
- He might even...
- Be dead?
I'm not saying I never
considered the possibility,
since there is no way he wouldn't
have known where to find us.
Still, I don't believe he's dead.
Why, you do?
Nah.
See?
We must wait for him even in old age,
if that's what it takes.
Right.
Let's wait.
Until he shows up before us,
let's not give up.
KCIA agents have already been here.
Isn't that girl clever?
She even thought of hiding it
in a place like this.
By the way, Oppa.
If we do as you say,
can the chairman really be safe?
I told you.
If that account is revealed, Chairman
Hong will only end up in more trouble.
And if he asks me for it,
what do I tell him?
Just tell him the truth
and try to convince him.
I'll take care of everything.
All right, I'll count on you.
Let's go.
What happened here?
Who took this...
You hid it there?
Yeah...
Who else knows you put it here?
The chairman.
Chairman Hong?
This is my house! My house!
No trespassing!
Nobody can enter my house!
Where do you think you're going?
You bitches!
What were you trying to steal?
Don't even think about it!
It's no use!
This won't do it! Fall back!
Quick!
Seonbaenim.
What brings you here?
We were out working nearby.
Tough assignment, isn't it?
It's killing me.
I've had it with staring at him
prancing around like a fool.
It's even driving me crazy, now.
Had lunch?
Can't you see I'm even losing weight?
You go have lunch.
- I'll cover for you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Let's go, I'll buy you something nice.
Eat all you want.
What brings you...
You keep this.
Jo Pilyeon has started
suspecting your housemaid.
It will be much safer here.
When will the surveillance be eased?
Jo will soon enter the by-elections.
That will be our chance.
All right.
We'll wait until then.
Right...
I don't know if I
should ask you this favor...
Please, go ahead.
My housemaid asked me
to find her family.
I might not be able
to do anything else for her,
but I wanted to
at least do that for her.
So she's looking for someone?
Here's the names and dates of birth
of the people she's looking for.
Sorry for troubling you with this.
Don't mention it.
I'll have the boys look for them
whenever they have time.
Yes.
To Manbo Construction
and our planning team!
Cheers!
How did you manage to hide
so well the fact you were dating?
I apologize.
If you felt betrayed in any way,
try to be understanding.
I was just curious,
who was the first to propose?
I did.
So what do you find so
charming about Jeongyeon?
She's so beautiful when she smiles,
I fell in love at first sight.
And what do you like
about Chief Jo, Jeongyeon?
What can I say...
I was curious as well.
Go ahead and tell us.
Just... He's a very capable
and good looking man.
Ehh...
That's so conventional.
No, it actually doesn't sound too bad.
Chief.
Why don't you have a dance together?
No, thanks.
I can't really dance.
Ehh... You'll soon get married,
let us have a look!
What are you doing?
Men have to take the initiative!
Dance for us! Dance for us!
Let's have a dance.
I told you I can't dance!
Dance for us! Dance for us!
Blues! Blues!
Did you tell them about our marriage?
They would have found out anyway.
Why does it bother you so much?
Do you even realize the kind of stares
I get from all the female colleagues?
It's as if I forced someone
to marry me against his will,
just because I'm the chairman's daughter.
It's not completely false, is it?
What?
Nothing seems to bother you,
but when it's your colleagues, it does?
Haven't you had enough
of that sarcasm?
If you want them
to stop misunderstanding,
we'll have to at least
pretend we love each other.
How about you lean on my shoulders?
Think that would be just right?!
Wipe that look off your face.
You're dancing with the man you love.
You should smile.
Oh my... I'm so sorry!
Never really danced like this before.
Should smile, right?
Can you look like that while
dancing with the woman you love?
Drive slowly, please.
Yes.
It's okay if we're late,
so you can drive around the block again.
Yes, all right.
Agasshi.
Don't touch her.
Jeongyeon.
Get on my back.
Gangmo...
Shall we go out and have a word?
It's time you leave Jeongyeon alone.
We'll soon get married.
I can ask you that much, can't I?
Done talking?
Good night.
Think I don't know?
I will no longer tolerate...
you being in love with my future wife.
Don't ever hang around Jeongyeon
in my presence again.
Let's call it a last warning out of gratitude,
for protecting Jeongyeon all this time.
Jo Minwoo.
If you dare make my Agasshi unhappy,
then,
I will kill you with my own hands.
"My Agasshi"?!
Without you around,
she'll only be happier.
- What? You found your sister?!
- Yeah.
- Congrats, man!
- Put me down.
When all this is dealt with,
I'll ask the chairman if
he can get a house for us.
You want to leave his house?
I'll live with Miju from now on.
Then again,
after Jeongyeon gets married,
why would you continue living there?
The account?
Is your sister really keeping it?
I think Chairman Hong has it, now.
Are you telling me he has the account?
Yeah... We were one step too late.
Is that for real?
Young Master...
So Chairman Hong has that account?
You, don't even think about it.
Young Master.
I'll go get it myself,
so you forget about it.
Got it?
I will.
What?!
Make a wrong move,
and you'll risk dearly.
I will get it and later
give it to you, so...
You little... Want trouble?
What? I'll risk dearly?
Do I look so foolish to you?
- Young Master.
- You!
Hope I made myself clear
when I said get your hands off.
You know what happens
if you disobey me, right?
He's like damned pepper spray...
What now?
If he goes for it by himself,
he'll get into trouble.
Let me go!
What's wrong with you?
Where are you taking me?
Let go... Let me go!
Should we follow them?
- Return to the office.
- Yes, all right.
You remain here.
Yes.
Is there any place you can use to hide?
There's a cottage I bought
under a friend's name.
As troublesome as it might be,
hide there until I call you.
Yes, I will.
Let's go.
- Miju.
- Oppa!
What's this, did you just buy them?
Yeah... I knew you'd come.
I'll cook you a nice dinner.
- I already prepared it?!
- You did?
Yeah. You must be hungry.
Here... Let's go.
It's a TV set?!
When you're alone and
feel bored, watch that.
Must have been expensive...
Here.
What's all this?
Bought you some clothes and shoes.
They're all your size, so try them out.
Oppa, give me your wallet.
My wallet?
Do it.
Here.
Sure... Take whatever you need.
30,000 won are left.
That's your allowance for
the month. Spend it wisely.
Guess I'll be busy tomorrow.
I have to go to the bank and
open an account in your name,
and return all these clothes and shoes.
Miju.
Be careful with money.
We must save, and find our brothers.
My brother doesn't
seem to have matured yet.
It's your birthday today.
Today...
is the day you were born, Miju.
Here.
So I had a birthday like the others...
I completely forgot my birthday,
all this time.
*eaten during birthdays; symbolizes
health and gratitude towards one's mother
After Mom died,
I never had seaweed soup*.
Give me your hand.
Go ahead and eat.
Quick.
Thanks, Oppa.
Miju.
Know what my dream is?
What is it?
To erect the
tallest building in Seoul,
and on the very top,
you and I,
Hyung, and little Junmo...
All living together.
That's nice.
And what's yours?
Me?
Becoming our country's
most famous singer.
You will make it.
- Really?
- Sure.
Hey, Seoul!
Listen well!
My little sister here, Miju!
She's going to become
Korea's most famous singer!
Seoul!
Listen well!
My brother is going to build
the tallest skyscraper in Seoul!
We'll succeed for sure!
We'll succeed and live together!
Dammit, what kind of rotten scoundrel
is making all this noise at this hour?
Where did he go?
Those young twerps these days...
They don't have
any sense of community!
Ehhh! You motherless little rascals!
Oh my... I'm so sorry...
It... It's all right, don't mind me.
As if you were pretty enough
to put on those airs...
Are you Park Sotae?
Of course I am.
Who else would I be?
Sit.
You know me, right?
Yes... The son of
Manbo Construction's...
The heir.
- Yes... The heir, Hwang. Jeong. Shik.
- That's right.
Where is Chairman Hong?
If you don't mind,
why are you asking?
I was looking for something
Chairman Hong has.
If you help me out,
I'll pave your way to success.
Where is Chairman Hong?
What's wrong with these pants?
Where is Gangmo?
He said he had to go somewhere.
Give me his car keys.
Car keys?!
You have your own car.
You prick... Don't you know
my father took that away from me?
Just give me those keys.
Let's go.
Yes.
It's me.
As burdensome as it might be,
you'll have to hide there
until the elections begin.
No matter how powerful
Jo Pilyeon might be,
if that account is exposed
during his election campaign,
he will never be able to stop that.
All right.
It's here.
Should I go see if he's inside?
You stay here.
His tongue keeps
getting shorter, doesn't it?
He'll "pave my way to success"?
He calls himself
Manbo Construction's heir,
so I guess it'll be better than
waiting for Gangmo to make it.
Who are you?
You...
Chairman Hwang Taeseop's son?!
That account... Give it back!
Chairman Hong.
Give it back!
I'm trying to negotiate with you.
Negotiate?!
Yes.
Give this account to me.
Then, I'll tell my father
to help you out.
Help me?!
And how?
We'll help you avoid bankruptcy,
anyhow...
We'll do everything you ask.
Start by giving that back.
Give it back!
No way!
That's out of the question.
Chairman Hong.
So you found the account?!
Are you all right?
Hurry up and go. Quick!
Yes...
Wait... Wait.
Stop there! Stay in the car.
Don't move a finger.
Yes...
Did...
anything happen inside?
You must never
tell anyone we came here.
What?
It's between you and me,
no one else.
Got it?
Yes.
Chairman Hwang Taeseop
is looking for you.
Should I tell him you're not here?
No.
I'll meet him.
Yes.
What is the matter?
You'll pardon me for saying this,
but as you resemble so much
someone I knew...
Care for a drink?
But that can't be possible.
I've never heard of someone
coming back from the dead, not even...
So is that the reason...
you wanted to meet?
I've been buying Manbo
Construction shares, recently,
so I thought that was the reason.
You'll soon end up on top of the sector.
Those shares will bring us a nice profit.
But... That daughter of yours,
will she become your heir?
People don't usually go to private lenders
accompanied by their daughters.
Jeongyeon...
Didn't you miss her?
How did you manage to endure all this time,
without seeing your daughter?
Gyeongok.
The Gyeongok you knew is dead.
And the same goes for the mother
who gave birth to Jeongyeon.
What are you,
ruthless or just foolish?
Think blood ties can so easily be cut?
Wasn't it you who turned me
into such a ruthless, foolish woman?
You made me what I am today!
Don't tell anything
about me to Jeongyeon.
Jeongyeon will soon get married.
Her engagement is tomorrow.
It's the daughter you
so painfully gave birth to.
Thought you should know.
You're quite drunk.
You still weren't sleeping?
Be it money or people,
the more you see,
the thirstier you will become.
Did seeing your daughter
do the same thing to you?
He said my Jeongyeon...
will soon get married?!
You know how people
like us make money?
By quickly gathering
market information,
abiding by a strict negotiating formula,
showing a relentless thirst for money,
and by a neverending behind-the-scenes
struggle to achieve one's goals!
But there is something
all this know-how lacks.
A human touch.
Money and compassion
never go hand in hand.
I hope you won't let compassion
sway you enough to disappoint me.
I apologize.
You will never see me like this again.
Your engagement is tomorrow.
Drink this and go to sleep.
Play me another song.
What?
With the piano.
Are you all right?
Why do you ask?
She's getting engaged tomorrow...
If she's getting engaged, then what?
- You really...
- Do me a favor.
If you're just going to
wag your tongue, leave.
Keep acting like that
and this will kill you!
Think people would die so easily?
I saw my mother
die before my very eyes,
lost my siblings,
and even had to send away
my little brother,
but I went on living
without blinking once.
Gangmo...
From now on,
I'll only think about
making my sister's life better.
You make me go crazy, really...
You look like a fairy.
Hold it, you brat!
I'm holding it.
I hadn't been home in ages, and look...
- Is it done?
- Yes, it's ready.
Oh my! Aigoo!
Look how pretty our Agasshi looks!
Mom, know how much this dress costs?
Would be strange
if she didn't look pretty.
- Aigoo, you really...
- But she does look pretty.
I look strange, don't I?
N...No...
You look great.
Here.
It's time.
Director.
Yes.
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
Hong Gipyo is dead.
What are you saying?
Why would Hong Gipyo be dead?
I think he might have been murdered.
What?! Murdered?
Manbo Construction
~ LEE GANGMO ~
This is no laughing matter.
I'm sure it has something
to do with that account.
Start investigating this.
All right.
Jo Pilyeon!
What brings you here?
You must have heard about Hong Gipyo?!
And?
Came here to tell me the news?
I knew you were
spying on Chairman Hong.
What?
You must have been after
that account's copy?
Look, Min Honggi...
I want to believe you didn't do this.
Because a KCIA director
killing for his own means...
would ruin the name
of our entire agency.
Sure... Go on prattling all you want.
I'll pay you back for all that
when the by-elections come.
Aww... How scary.
What kind of motherless
prick could do that?
Is there anything to drink?
Why are you looking for
the bottle, all of a sudden?
We might have been rivals,
but seeing his life end so
violently was not pleasant at all.
They should just catch that despicable
killer and give him the death sentence.
Eat slowly, will you?
Chairman.
Come out, detectives are here.
- Detectives?
- Yes.
Here he comes.
What is the matter?
Lee Gangmo lives here, right?
That's right, but why?
He's suspected of the
murder of Chairman Hong Gipyo.
What are you talking about?
Gangmo is suspected of murder?!
We found clear evidence
at the murder scene.
Is he home?
He still hasn't come back?
Where is Lee Gangmo's room?
This way...
What is all this about?
Gangmo killed someone?!
See? You never know people's true colors
until things like this happen.
Aww... How horrible.
- Agasshi.
- Quick, come.
Murder?!
Who killed who?
Chairman Hong Gipyo died.
They're accusing you of his murder!
It's not you...
Right?
You would never do that.
Where are you going?
I'll have to explain to them
I'm not the killer.
They said they found clear evidence.
I didn't even meet
Chairman Hong, what evidence?
Just hide.
And then what, convince everyone
that I'm the murderer?
They said they have evidence!
What if you're really framed for murder?
You'll always have time
to turn yourself in later.
Take this.
Take it!
Don't skip your meals,
and never let the police find you.
Thank you, Agasshi.
Gangmo...
Run away.
It's him.
- Gangmo, quick!
- Lee Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Hurry up and speak.
Where is Lee Gangmo hiding?
I told you I don't know.
You were talking to each other!
I really don't know, I told you!
Young lady...
Want to do time in the can
for concealing a suspect?
She said she doesn't know, so stop it.
And who are you?
Get up.
Look.
I asked you a question.
I'm her fiance.
What?
Fiance?
If you want to detain her, talk with
Director Jo Pilyeon of the KCIA first.
He's my father.
KCIA's... Director Jo Pilyeon?!
I said stay put!
Let go.
I can walk by myself.
How much longer are you going
to keep protecting Lee Gangmo?
Think what you're doing
will change anything?
Gangmo is a murderer,
he killed a man.
Careful what you say.
Take a good look.
I'm your fiance.
We're about to get married.
Gangmo is more important to me, now.
What?
I will never let them
frame him for murder.
I'll make sure that doesn't happen.
Oppa.
Have you had dinner?
Have any leftovers?
Wait a moment, I'll warm them up.
And now a report.
The chairman of
Daeryuk Construction, Hong Gipyo,
has been murdered.
Chairman Hong's body was found
this morning in a cottage...
in Gyeonggi Province
by one of the tenants.
Citing clear evidence against him,
the police are looking...
for murder suspect Lee Gangmo.
Miju!
It's not you...
You didn't do that, right?
You didn't kill him, right?
You would never do that, right?
It's not you!
It's not me.
Trust me, Miju.
I didn't do it.
I know.
You wouldn't be capable of that.
You'd never kill the chairman.
But why are they
calling you the culprit?
Someone fabricated that evidence.
And who is that?
Why did he do that to you?
If the police can't find him,
I will.
Oppa...
Don't you worry, Miju.
Everything will go well.
Until your innocence is proven, Oppa.
Don't go anywhere, I'll hide you here.
If you stay here, nobody will know.
All right.
That Lee Gangmo must have
the account we're looking for.
We must catch him before they do.
Hello?
It's me, Shideok.
Hey... What happened to you?
Someone framed me on purpose.
Gangmo.
That day, Jeongshik went
looking for Chairman Hong.
He left with Park Sotae,
so he must know what's up.
You.
You know, right?
I really don't know
what you're referring to.
The man who murdered Chairman Hong...
is me.
Tell me about it...
I couldn't sleep all night.
Forget all my shortcomings, but when
it comes to reporting wrongdoings,
I'm second to none.
Open it.
That money...
should be more than enough to hide
until they catch Lee Gangmo.
But, you know?
Gangmo and I are really close.
And money doesn't last forever.
I told you that your life
was in my hands, right?
Take a good look.
Because I, Hwang Jeongshik,
will soon take over Manbo Construction.
You will never get
a chance like this again.
You know where
Gangmo is hiding, right?
Where is Lee Gangmo?
Around it...
Go look if there are any
eye-witnesses around the place.
All right.
How about the flyers?
They'll soon be ready.
How can I help you?
You're searching for
Lee Gangmo, right?
The man who killed
Chairman Hong Gipyo.
You know where he is?
Do you know where is Park Sotae,
the man who lived here?
Can't say.
There have been so many
people renting this place.
No contacts of note
with Lee Gangmo yet.
Continue to keep an eye
on his acquaintances.
I'm sure he'll show up.
All right.
Chairman Hong asked me for this...
You take care of it.
Seonbaenim.
My housemaid asked me
to find her family.
Father: Lee Daesu
Mother: Jeong Youngseon
Oldest Brother: Lee Seongmo
Second Brother: Lee Gangmo
Youngest Brother: Infant
Miju.
Miju!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Did you go to that cottage
on the day Chairman Hong died?
What are you going to do,
report me to the police?
Those bastards are trying to
use my brother as a scapegoat!
I have a way to get Gangmo out.
Don't get angry if who
you're waiting for doesn't come.
They'll eventually come,
if you keep waiting.
What are you,
trying to rile me up?
Is this what you were looking for?
Why do you have this?
Did you kill Chairman Hong?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com