Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 9 ~
Always on time, aren't you?
Why even bother coming...
This place is filled with the cream of
the financial and political world's crop.
Having an illegitimate daughter
can only bring embarrassment to us,
so keep quiet and don't
attract people's attention.
Here you are, Jeongyeon.
She's my daughter.
How are you?
I'm Hwang Jeongyeon.
I see your daughter took
after her mother's beauty.
Yes...
Also, our new chief
of planning, Jo Minwoo.
We already introduced each other.
Is that so?
He'll be your superior at work.
I'm not working for your company.
Shut it, you silly.
Don't mind her being my daughter,
and treat her like all the others.
Do you know where the construction
committee members are?
They're all gathered at the Royal Club.
If you can't make it into the committee,
you can forget the subway bid altogether.
That's indeed what would happen.
Since those who aren't members of the
committee are excluded from the bidding.
Chairman Hwang.
What are you, acting indifferent now?
Director.
I talked on the phone
with the members myself.
They assured me they would come,
so there must be a reason...
You still don't get it?
By now, Hong Gipyo must be
laughing at you at the Royal Club.
By now, Hwang Taeseop must
be in panic, waiting for us.
I'm sure he's all shaking, already.
Manbo Construction's tenth anniversary?!
Imagine how dreary that party will feel.
If you lose this bid,
how are you going to fund my campaign
at the next assembly elections?
The game starts now.
Why are you so impatient?
It doesn't suit you.
What?
Look, Chairman Hwang!
Hey... Hey...
What are you doing?
Chairman.
I'll head to the Royal Club.
It all depends on you now.
I will accept no mistakes.
Yes, Chairman.
You knew they were
gathered at the Royal Club?
Director.
Can I borrow some of
your time later tonight?
I'll treat you to
a really nice spectacle.
Where are you going?
Bring me home, will you?
I'm sorry.
I already have instructions
from the chairman.
Too bad, then.
Guess I'll grab a taxi.
What are those instructions?
Agasshi.
Dressing to make men believe
you're an easy woman is no fun.
Tomorrow's your first day,
so don't be late.
Have you seen how dirty that car is?
You idiot...
- Make it shine.
- Yes.
I'll bring the
committee members by myself,
so just stay here.
This is a very important matter.
What's that supposed to mean?
That it's something I shouldn't
bother with, and leave to you?
The chairman directly instructed me.
You little prick...
How dare you stare back?
Young Master, please...
Stop, please.
Don't stop him.
I'll give you three minutes.
It's all I can spare,
because of the chairman's orders.
I ought to just...
You...
I'll see you after I'm
done with the committee.
Start the car,
what are you waiting for?
Only if I go
we'll manage to bring them here.
Enough with the insolence, you prick!
I'm the son of Manbo
Construction's chairman.
The heir is going himself,
think he wouldn't manage?
Ahh... You fool...
Let's go.
So how does working here feel?
Are you managing all right?
I'm still learning the ropes.
It was an order from the director
so I was forced to take you in,
but to be honest, I don't like you.
Is it because of your personal
feelings against Director Jo Pilyeon?
Is there anyone in the KCIA who doesn't
know you're Jo Pilyeon's right-hand man?
Even a beginner knows
that no personal feelings...
should interfere with one's duties.
What are you,
suggesting I'm worse than a beginner?
Whatever your relationship is,
it doesn't concern me.
I merely work for the sake
of our country and the people.
You may leave.
Insolent bastard...
Seonbaenim.
We just got word that someone
from Manbo Construction...
is making his move towards the Royal Club,
where the committee is gathered.
- Thanks.
- Seonbaenim.
Are you going there?
What are you investigating these days?
Let's have a drink later.
Seonbaenim.
How are you?
- Ma'am.
- It's been a while.
Do you even know who I am?
I'm the son of Manbo
Construction's chairman, you fools!
Uh? Let me go, let me go!
What is the matter?
He was here to escort
the committee members out.
Don't tell them I'm here.
Yes.
I said I'm the son of
Manbo Construction's chairman!
Hey... You're embarrassing me...
Let go!
Hey... You'll ruin my clothes!
Let go! Let me go!
Seems like Hwang Taeseop
panicked, all right.
Sending here that foolish son of his...
I guess he was impatient to join
the bid for the subway construction.
I trust no one here would approve
of his entrance into the committee?!
I'm against it.
The five of us more than suffice.
Same goes for me.
All Chairman Hwang needs to gain entry
is the approval of three members.
You will find no traitor here,
so you can spare yourself the concern.
Gentlemen, have some of this.
Kiddo, tell your boss
to show up, will you?
I've been to just about
every luxury bar in town,
*slang for female owner
of bar/room saloon
but I've never seen one with
such haughty madam* before.
I'd drop the curiosity, if I were you.
There are rumors that the owner here
is Baekpa's adoptive daughter.
By Baekpa...
You mean Myeongdong's biggest
private lender, that Baekpa?
Yes. There is likely no
business in this country...
that hasn't borrowed money
from him at least once.
Wow... We'll have to be careful
what we say, this place is scary!
Let's have a drink, shall we?
Let's do that.
There is a call for
the committee members.
Is it the son of Manbo
Construction's chairman?
It's another voice.
Let him through.
- Yes.
- Is that Chairman Hong Gipyo?
That's right.
Who am I speaking to?
Could I speak with Chairman Cheon
of Gwangmyeong Construction?
Chairman Cheon.
There's a call for you.
- Me?!
- Yes.
I wasn't expecting any?!
- I'll take over for you, if I may.
- Sure.
It's me, Chairman Cheon.
I trust you remember that
Chairman Hong once gave up his bid...
because of a fire
at his company warehouse?
Ask him directly, why should I...
Is he aware that the man who set his
warehouse on fire was your secretary?
Who... Who are you?
And thanks to that,
your company won the bid.
I asked who are you!
Let me get straight to the point.
Come outside right now.
Ahh... Can I talk to Chairman Baek
of Honghae Construction?
Just a moment.
Chairman Baek, get the phone.
I'll have to get going.
Where are you going?
Something urgent at work needs
my presence, so have a good night.
Who is it?
What is this all about?!
Hello.
I'm Chairman Baek, who is it?
You're in-laws
with Chairman Cheon, right?
Why do you ask?
I hear that your daughter is hiding
a child she had before marriage...
I'm sure your in-laws
aren't aware of that?!
What do you want from me?
We need to go somewhere right now.
Will you come out and follow me?
Fine, wait just a moment.
Something came up for me as well,
so I need to go.
Chairman Jo, pick up the phone.
What call could it possibly be,
to react this way?
Yes, Chairman Jo speaking.
Let's meet right now.
But where are you taking us?
The chairman is waiting for you.
Who is this chairman?
Who ordered you to take us there
without our consent?
Didn't you give your consent,
by spontaneously entering this car?
We're late, so I'll have to speed up.
Can you really bring
the committee members here?
Chairman.
Your guests are here.
See them in.
Come on in.
Here, have a seat.
Please, sit.
Good job.
You can go.
Thank you for so kindly
accepting my invitation.
Let me make the introductions.
Here's the Director of the KCIA's
Inspection Department, Jo Pilyeon.
Is that so?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Chairman Cheon Suman
of Gwangmyeong Construction.
Gangmo... Gangmo.
Jeongshik is here.
Just stay put.
- I said don't!
- I told you I'm loaded.
And who is this?
Come here, I'll pour you a drink.
Here, have a drink.
Why, thought I'd offer drinks
to our backyard mutt?
Know who this is?
Know mutts, right? Mutts.
The chairman...
is here with the construction
committee members.
What?
Don't fool around
and let him see you here.
I won't be able to cover up for that.
Don't be so arrogant with me, you prick!
Think that just because you're
as loyal to my father as a dog,
he will save a position
in the company for you?
That's never going
to happen, and know why?
Because I will inherit
my father's company.
When that happens,
you're the first head to roll, got it?
I'll get straight to the point,
and tell you I'll have to be entrusted...
with the upcoming subway construction.
To make sure that happens, I first
need to be accepted into the committee...
As you're well aware, Chairman Hong Gipyo
presides over our committee.
You're like sworn enemies, so...
Chairman Cheon.
Isn't a majority vote
all you need to enter a committee?
All I need is for you three
to push for my acceptance.
About that...
According to the rules,
that's indeed possible.
- Director Ju?
- Yes, Chairman.
Please sign the acceptance agreement.
Chairman Hwang...
We already decided to grant
Daeryuk Construction the subway project.
Decisions can always be overturned.
Chairman Hwang.
This would put us in
a difficult position, so...
Director.
Isn't the KCIA Inspection Department
where they torture criminals?
Why... Anyone to report in particular?
No.
Is there anyone who has never
committed a crime or two before?
He's changed, we're not dealing
with the same Chairman Hwang.
- Isn't that all for the better?
- If he doesn't overstep his boundaries...
What is your name?
Lee Gangmo.
You're quite skilled.
Clean and effective.
If you'll excuse me, I'll get going.
He dug through an impenetrable fortress
like the committee in a matter of moments.
He's no ordinary underling.
Keep your eyes on him.
I will.
Come on in.
So...
Here.
You did well.
A really good job.
Thank you.
There is something I'd like to ask you.
I'd like be entrusted
the subway bid's leadership.
Want to wear necktie and suit?
Didn't you promise me?
I've already made enough experience
at the bottom of the ladder.
Allow me to do real work
for your company now.
It's still too early for you.
Chairman.
Everything has its timing and due course.
And it's not your time, yet.
I think I did enough to prove myself.
And that's just what you think.
Go out and start the car.
Chairman!
I said leave!
Yes.
Let alone what he did for us this time,
hasn't Gangmo proven himself
enough to be granted that?
The more you strike it,
the stronger iron becomes.
He needs to experience the bottom
of the ladder a little longer.
Only then we'll be able to use him
for what he's truly worth later.
Let go!
- You wench!
- What are you doing?
Even you look down on me, now?
What's wrong with you?
Enough!
Aigoo, this is too much!
Now even minions look down on me!
I can't take this anymore!
What's wrong, again?
She kept looking for the bottle.
I told her to stop, and she just...
And who the hell are you?
Did I steal your bottle or something?
How dare you try to order me around?
Give it a rest!
You may leave.
Yes...
You're drunk.
Just go to sleep.
When you die, think that
brat Jeongyeon is going to...
pour a drink at your altar
and honor your passing?
Jeongshik is our eldest son!
If she gets married,
we'll become strangers.
All right, I get it.
I got it, so now go to sleep.
And what is Jeongyeon
going to do in your company?
Are you going to let her
inherit the whole thing?
Then, what about Jeongshik...
Can't you see him always lounging
around with nothing better to do?
And who sold off raw
materials and ran away,
when I gave him the chance
to supervise a construction?
So? Are you going to keep him
out of the company forever?
Ahh... Really...
Just be honest.
Just say that you still
can't forget that wench.
Jeongyeon's mother,
that promiscuous bitch!
You're still thinking
about her, aren't you?
Why bring up the dead?
Because the living envy them, why?
Just my luck...
What did I do to deserve this?
So stop getting piss drunk
all the time, will you?
I've lost all will to live, really...
Jeongshik...
What about my poor Jeongshik...
Seems like Chairman Hwang will
gain entrance into the committee.
I'm surprised.
I thought it wouldn't be easy for him.
There's this young fella under him,
a certain Lee Gangmo.
He's responsible for this.
To succeed, you need
talented people by your side.
Using that Lee Gangmo
will benefit you for sure.
Aren't you dating anyone?
I'm not in any serious relationship,
but I'm seeing a few women.
You know, Chairman Hwang's daughter.
Was it Jeongyeon?
She sure is pretty.
The streets are filled
with women looking like her.
Show some interest in her.
Why, you don't like her?
If you need me to,
I'll show some interest.
Goddamned brat.
Does she think she can
just toy around with my hair?
She's ruined them so bad
I can't even comb them anymore.
I told you to avoid her when she's drunk.
If only your father hadn't lost his
land in Maljukgeori from gambling,
I wouldn't have had to live this way.
Why is that damned land
in Gangnam skyrocketing?
Gangmo.
Come on out.
The chairman is really angry
because of his daughter.
Come on.
Go fetch Jeongyeon at school,
and send her to work.
I will, Chairman.
Right.
Have a nice day, Honey.
And how are you going to convince
someone as stubborn as she is,
when even her father can't?
Anyhow, when Jeongyeon gets there,
report to me in detail about
what she does and who she meets.
You don't need to worry, Ma'am.
I'll be counting on you, then.
Go ahead and try me.
Think I'll let you prance around
the company all day in peace?
~ Let's Protect Our Democracy ~
~ Overthrow the Dictators! ~
Let's go to work.
I'm not going to work there.
Hey! Let...
Which faculty and year?
*peurakchi: loanword from
the Russian fraktsiya
You're a police informant*, right?
Let's hear it.
Who is this?
Someone I don't know.
Let go!
I...
am neither an informant nor a student.
Go ahead and mind your business.
I will take care of my own.
Are you out of your mind?
What do you think you're doing?
Agasshi.
We're at school.
Don't call me that.
Do you plan on wagging your tail
around my father like Jeongshik said?
Is this what you took that GED for?
There are plenty of people who
are having it much harder than you.
Think they all live like you?
Do you even know
what having it hard means?
Ever starved with
nothing to eat whatsoever?
Ever cried bitter tears for all
the unfairness surrounding you?
You can scream and
blame this world all you want,
but nobody will listen to you.
If you think your life is unfair,
just find success.
I might look pathetic in your eyes,
but this is the best for me.
Since I'll climb the ladder and succeed,
just like your father did.
Don't even try
acting like that with me.
I won't leave your side no matter what.
Here.
Let's go now, Agasshi.
Start by wiping that blood.
What is this?
It's a detailed report on the
land we're about to acquire.
I thought I asked you
for a plan for the subway bid?
Once that subway opens to the public,
the price of land in
the area will skyrocket.
The best course of action
would be buying land in the area first.
Is that so?
Daeryuk Construction already
secured a significant portion.
If we don't rush,
there will be nothing left to buy.
I'll give you carte blanche
over the entire bid.
I'll give you all the support you need,
so let's witness your skills in action.
Thank you, Chairman.
I wouldn't be so fast
to thank me, if I were you...
Because as strong
a support as I promised,
so will be the repercussions if you fail.
I will make sure you
will not be disappointed.
About Jeongyeon.
I leave that kid to your care.
I'll take that as helping her
experience what the real world means.
Jo Pilyeon raised his boy quite well.
Can't you find your way here
without Lee Gangmo's help?
Three late arrivals
will result in a pay cut,
and two absences without leave
will result in immediate termination.
Hey, Jo Minwoo!
- Who the hell are you, to...
- I...
am your direct superior.
I will no longer tolerate you
insulting your father's name this way.
Did I make myself clear?
Also.
Address your superior
with such insolence again,
and it won't just end with
a few tears down your face.
You can return to the service lobby.
The chairman ordered me
to look after Agasshi...
You still don't get it?
Your "Agasshi" is now under my care.
You will soon receive new orders.
Go wait downstairs.
From now on, if you want to meet me,
follow procedure like everyone else.
Coming here as you please
ends today, you silly.
And what is this?
An eligibility confirmation
from Daeryuk Construction.
I passed their entrance test.
You did what?
Now you know why I said
I won't work here, right?
I see...
You want to make a deal with me.
Is that what you think?
You chose business
administration on your own.
And your grades were quite good as well.
You were well aware that I wanted
you here much more than Jeongshik.
Was it just a ploy
to make me concerned?
Whatever you think,
it doesn't concern me.
Because the choice
always remains with me.
My daughter is really something.
Fine... Every deal depends on
who takes the initiative first.
All right, let's get started.
What is it that you want from me?
I can't let you join Daeryuk Construction.
You threw the first card,
so let's hear it.
Officially proclaim me as the
heir to Manbo Construction.
If you promise me
I will inherit this company,
then I'll follow your wishes.
Is that what they teach
you at school, these days?
Think that everything should be
given to you on a silver platter?
I didn't come here to hear your lectures.
Just make your decision.
Prove your skills
to everyone in this company.
Then, I'll announce you as my heir.
Without first proving yourself,
I'm not giving you a thing.
Fine.
You promised you will
do so if I prove myself.
Jeongyeon.
Do you covet this company that bad?
I don't want to be
abandoned like my mother.
She was kicked out
because she was powerless.
If I ever leave, it'll be on my terms.
I'm never going to end up like her.
That little...
Yes, we completed our
report on the area already.
- Didn't I tell you already last week?
- Chief.
Can I help you with anything?
I'm fine.
Seems like you didn't
understand what I told you,
but just start acquiring
equipment and materials.
Should I bring you a cup of coffee?
I'm good at making that.
You want coffee?
Have a seat, I'll go get it.
No...
Never mind.
Let me do that, I'm good at copying.
There's no need, Agasshi, let me do it.
Chief, please sign these.
Is Hwang Jeongyeon managing well?
We're busy enough as it is,
and she just seems to interfere...
I think not entrusting her anything
for the time being would be wiser.
- You may go.
- Yes.
Everyone's gone home,
you still have work left to do?
My superior is still here,
can a bottom feeder like me leave early?
Isn't giving me no work
on purpose a little crude?
I can't entrust anything to
people who aren't prepared.
This is all the data
regarding our upcoming bid.
Start by studying these, and then
I'll decide what your duties will be.
He's so annoying, that Jo Minwoo...
But he sure knows
how to push your buttons.
Fine, you just wait and see.
I'll wipe off that
pompous smirk off your face.
You can bet on that.
I'd prefer if you didn't
talk about Jo Minwoo with me.
I know, that you dislike
him as much as I do.
You're right, let's just stop.
He's just going to ruin the mood.
Ajumma, another bottle of soju.
Yes.
Here...
Why aren't you drinking at all?
Awww... Bitter.
It's so bitter...
Should I let you down now?
No way.
I'm so drunk I can't walk straight.
Remember?
When we were kids,
the first time we met in Daejeon.
You carried me on
your back that day, too.
Your back is so comfortable.
You don't know that, do you?
I wish time could just stop right now.
If you're tired, just sleep.
Gangmo.
Sleep.
Lee Gangmo.
Don't call me and just sleep.
Don't you ever abandon me.
Don't abandon me like my mother did.
Ma'am, it's time to head to the stage.
It's the bid presentation
I'll show to the other members.
So with this you'll keep
the other members at bay,
and Daeryuk Construction
will end up winning the bid?
Yes, Director.
They're waiting for me next door.
Jo Pilyeon is eyeing a political career.
If Manbo Construction
fails to win this bid,
I'm sure the shock
will be hard to cope with.
You don't need to worry about
Jo Pilyeon or Hwang Taeseop now.
These days, the KCIA seems
to have lost its charm.
The Blue House's escorts
treat us like dirt.
I can understand.
I'll make sure you become a
congressman at the next elections.
So all you need to do is make
a few contacts among politicians.
- Thank you, Chairman Hong.
- Yes.
You must take good care of the director.
Yes, Chairman.
Wait here, I'll bring you
the good news later.
All right.
Have a seat.
You're cute.
What's your name?
Lola.
Not what you use here,
the one your parents gave you.
Gyeongja.
Yeom Gyeongja.
~ Bae Insook's "Like Everyone Else Would" ~
(Cover of Alain Barriere's Un Poete)
"Like everyone else would,"
"They come back to mind
when I cross the street."
"The faces of yesteryear,
who whispered in my ears,"
"Caressing the way like falling petals."
"Like pouring rainwater, I'm drenched
by those precious memories,"
"I turn back as nostalgia haunts me,"
"Past those rivers of tears."
"Like everyone else would,"
"A glance at the mirror and I recall,"
"The streets and alleys
my childhood memories were made of."
"The white dreams
which made my heart throb..."
"Suddenly vanish out of the blue."
"As sadness surrounds me, I look back,"
"Past those rivers of tears."
What are you waiting for?
There's no way a dead
woman could be alive.
But they sure look alike...
"When I close my eyes,
they come back to mind."
"Not the woes of breaking up,
but the very first moments we shared,"
"Placid waves of warmth
gently caressing me."
Chairman Hwang, what brings you here?
What are you doing here?
I suppose you haven't heard the news.
Starting today, I've become an official
member of the construction committee.
What's that supposed to mean?
Listen, Chairman Hwang.
Think you can just
barge in as you please?
Those are agreements approving
my entrance into the committee.
They're what?!
How do you explain this?
Uh?
From what I hear,
you enjoy playing mahjong here?!
Let's use cards next time.
Mahjong just gives me a headache.
Get out of my face.
I'm never going to allow you in!
And who the hell are you?
Can you decide that on your own?
These three gentlemen...
already agreed to it.
If you don't approve their decision,
you can just leave,
or break up the committee altogether.
Do as you wish!
According to committee rules,
those not present at our meetings
give up all their voting rights.
Chairman Hong.
As you wish.
One mouth less to share the pie with.
And with that, let's get this meeting
for the subway bidding rights started.
I was going to propose
doing it via secret voting...
I'm sure there would be no objections?!
Who will take care of counting votes?
Care to help me with that,
Chairman Cheon?
Manbo Construction.
Daeryuk Construction.
Accordingly, Manbo Construction
will be entrusted the subway construction.
That is all.
All these are about open bids
in the construction sector.
Is it going well?
Afraid not.
I can't really get my head around it.
We have an expert on the matter, though.
Should I introduce you to him?
I'd appreciate it.
At last, Chairman Hwang won the
subway bidding rights at the meeting.
That's good to hear.
~ Demonstrations in Busan, Masan ~
The situation in Busan
and Masan is quite serious.
They need to get it over with
before things escalate.
Until the construction is
officially assigned to Manbo,
we must never let our guard down.
Keep an eye on Min Honggi until then,
because if he makes a move,
you never know what might happen.
I will.
We will finally get the chance
to leave this gloomy rat-hole,
and finally enter the political arena.
As hard as it might be to wait,
endure it until then.
Jo Pilyeon, Hwang Taeseop...
It's not going to go as you plan.
I'll never allow it.
So he gained control of
the committee in one strike?
Seems like that Hwang Taeseop
is not your ordinary fella?
~ Euiinmulyong. Yonginmuleui. ~
Baekpa
You said you had
some kind of past together?
Is he the only particular
relationship my past was made of?!
You experience
many relationships in life,
but the traces they leave
behind are always different.
Seems like it'll rain.
It's cold, so don't touch it.
To me, it's the warmest of them all.
I still don't understand.
Why you gave such an opportunity
to someone as insignificant as me.
Know what these characters stand for?
Euiinmulyong. Yonginmuleui.
If haunted by suspicion,
do not use that person.
But if you already are,
don't ever bear suspicions.
You're working for me,
so I will never suspect you.
That's all you need to know.
Yes.
Chairman Hong will not so easily give up.
A cloud of dust is about
to assault those sand dunes.
What is this?
Let's wake up!
All right.
Today was the day you
always go to 31 Building, right?
Just let us handle this for today.
Forget it.
Hey... Miju and your brother could come!
I gave up.
Seeing as they never came all these years,
I won't be able to find them this way.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Will they be enough?
The others are waiting outside.
We're at war with Daeryuk Construction.
We must gain control
of the subway lot at all cost.
Spare no effort.
Yes.
*lit. grandmother,
used to address elder women
Halmeoni*.
Some rice cakes, please.
It's good.
Waiting for someone here?
Yes.
Who?
Your boyfriend?
Yes, both of them.
Both?!
You have that many?
Actually, I'm waiting for my brothers.
We separated when we were kids.
This tastes great.
Long time no see.
It's me, Sotae.
Park Sotae.
The one who used to shine shoes
with you in Myeongdong.
I've heard you were released from prison.
Really?
You disappoint me.
Not even a visit all this time...
Take your boys and pull out
of the neighborhood.
Never been in the can, have you?
Think it's easy to find
a job with a conviction?
Thanks to Chairman Hong Gipyo
my title now is "chief."
Chief Park.
Where else would I hear that?
Then, let's make the rules clear.
Those who lose will
give up this place for good.
Nah...
Let's just do it my way.
We fight to our deaths.
Fine with me.
"Here comes the water cock,
quacking on the paddy field."
"Here comes the cuckoo,
echoing in the forest."
Wow... They fit just right.
They're so pretty!
Thanks, Oppa.
"When my Oppa will ride
to Seoul with his horse,"
"He said he will bring me silken shoes."
You said so yourself.
Let's fight to our deaths.
I sure did.
I'm on the edge of a cliff already.
This is the kind of life
that suits people like us.
Come.
Come get some!
Run, you pricks!
That way!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I didn't demonstrate.
You were found with demonstrators.
I was waiting outside 31 Building,
and they just arrested me.
Shut it.
Which college and year?
The name of your school!
I'm not a college student.
Then, what are you?
I...
am a housemaid.
Uh?!
Housemaid.
Housemaid?!
The ones cooking,
doing the laundry and stuff?
Yes.
Are you telling the truth?
Can't you call and find out?
- Enough!
- Just go!
You're hurting me!
Yes, I understand.
See?
What did I tell you?
Next time don't even pass
where they're demonstrating.
Just go, go...
Ahh, my shoes.
Are these your sister's?
No, they're mine.
My brother bought them.
They're really pretty, aren't they?
Aww... Just go!
You're hurting me!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
I'm sorry, Miju.
Nobody ever lasted
past ten days with her.
Until you tell me to leave,
I'll stay here.
Become in-laws?!
Why? Did it upset you that much?
The hell does he think he's dealing with?
Hwang Taeseop...
Was this the only thing you used
to get them into your pocket?
Are you dating Jeongyeon?
You're not, right?
Don't even joke about that.
We failed at the bid.
The committee members
stabbed us in the back.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com