Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 28 -
Gangmo!
Jeongyeon is here!
What's wrong with you?
Why, do you know these people?
I'd like to meet with the president.
Our president still isn't back
from his business trip abroad?!
Then, there must be someone
responsible on his behalf.
I'd be the man responsible here.
Why, did you come here
to sign a contract?
But what can we do now? Only the
president takes care of contracts?!
Let's go talk inside, for starters.
Ehh Ehh!
How dare you boss your way around...
So these folks are
from Manbo Construction?
Likely?!
You know, our president?
He said he's not going to deal with
Manbo Construction no matter what.
So don't try to get us into trouble,
and go before I forget
I ever had manners.
Shideok!
Director!
Why did you come here yourself?
Hangang Construction's
president still isn't back.
I'd like to know why he
refuses to do business with us?
Because they already signed an exclusive
deal with Gwangmyeong Construction,
they can't sign with anyone else.
I suggest we just go back.
What would have Gangmo done
in this situation?
I really wanted to make a
good impression with this project...
If only Gangmo could be by my side,
things would have
never gotten to this point.
Listen to you... Lee Gangmo!
Do you know why Jeongyeon
has been living that way?
It was only to avenge you!
To make Minwoo and Jeongshik
pay for what they did to you.
She even caught aphasia,
shocked about your death.
Seeing her struggle so much by
herself on that construction site...
It's so hard to bear,
it brings me to tears.
What?!
Park Sotae works for
Hangang Construction?!
How did he manage to survive,
not to mention end up there?
The man who now owns Lee Gangmo's
Gaepo-Dong mudflats...
is James Lee.
Yeah... I know that.
And turns out that the president
of Hangang Construction...
is exactly that James fella.
Really?
But... Never seen two people
with the same name before?
I've even heard James is the
most common name in the States.
Park Sotae is the man we sent
to prison to kill Lee Gangmo.
Hey... Then, by any chance...
And Shideok was acting strange as well.
Maybe that James...
could in fact be Lee Gangmo.
Hey... No matter how you put it,
there's no way.
Gangmo died.
We even got his death notice.
My father spread his ashes into
the river, what are you saying?
I agree that Park Sotae's
involvement is a little suspicious,
but it can't be Lee Gangmo, no way.
How can you come back from the dead?
It makes no sense.
I wanted to talk with
you myself, Chairman Hwang.
Commissioner.
Why are you doing this to us?
You can't allow any
additional budget resources?!
As you're well aware, there will soon
be a probe into congress spending, and...
Do I look like the kind of man who
would take those excuses at face value?
If you refuse to believe me,
then that's your prerogative.
We go such a long way back,
you of all people can't do this to me.
That's exactly what I'd like
to tell you, on the contrary.
What?
Didn't I warn you more than once to
cut your ties with Candidate Jo Pilyeon?
Because I support Min Honggi,
Jo Pilyeon bears ill will against me.
If you really thought of me as an ally,
you would have renounced further dealings
with Jo Pilyeon while you still could.
So was that the real
reason behind all this?
- That's the reason you're trying to bring us...
- I see we're done talking,
so I'll have to ask you to leave.
It won't go as you think!
Seems like you're looking
down on me just because...
I've always treated you
with meek obedience,
but you'll never take that
highway project away from me!
Is that so?
Shall I give it a try, then?
You won't keep this post forever.
What?
So you're going to mess with me?
Be my guest, then!
Think I can't get you fired
if I really want to?
- Dad...
- Listen, Chairman Hwang!
I apologize, Commissioner.
Let's just go, Dad.
You've gone too far, Dad.
He was the first to betray me.
Still, we're dealing with
the head of the City Council.
So what was I supposed to do,
hold his trousers like a miserable
lackey and beg my way out of it?
- Dad...
- Do you even realize...
why I spent so much money on
those big shots all these years?
It was to avoid facing
such embarrassments.
So that I wouldn't have to
hang from those sharks' lips.
Even business is all about politics.
Once Jo Pilyeon wins the elections,
you'll see how quickly he'll be tamed.
What?!
You will get me fired?
Yes.
It's me, Sir.
- Hangang Construction's...
- Ohh... President Lee.
Have you made up your mind?
If you really wish for me to
help Manbo Construction...
No.
There's no need to do that.
Manbo Construction will soon have
to deal with an on-site supervision.
We can reopen negotiations
on the highway project...
once the supervision results are out.
I understand.
He refuses to speak to the very end.
Is he just afraid of Jo Pilyeon?
That's part of the problem,
but he also likely believes
Jo might come to his rescue.
To derail Jo Pilyeon's campaign,
we must make him confess at all cost.
Considering the situation,
it would be wiser to just
make him join forces with us.
Join forces?!
Is there such a way?
- Days Before the Elections -
All sample surveys put us
well ahead of Min Honggi.
And also, Honey... Take a look at the
polls we ran ourselves, you're first.
Good job, everyone.
Now we can just relax
and wait for the counting.
What brings you here?
Let's have a word next door,
if you don't mind.
By any chance, is that Choi Taewook
in Seoul, at the moment?
And how do you know that?
Intel from the ANSP.
Jaechun, hurry up
and get him into hiding.
Actually, I've lost contact
with him these last few days.
What's that supposed to mean?
It does look like he left Cheongju,
but I have never seen him in Seoul.
You foolish idiot!
How can you not be
aware of his whereabouts?
It can't be helped.
Before any other agent
gets his hands on him,
I'll be forced to catch him myself.
Can you do that for me?
What else can we do?!
All right...
I owe you one, Seongmo.
But even if we do catch him,
that doesn't solve anything.
What do you plan to do
with that Choi Taewook?
We must get rid of him.
I can't forfeit my seat in congress
because of that useless minion.
Killing him is the only way
to avoid any future complications.
How did it go?
Seonbaenim.
Let's go.
Tiger hunting begins now.
Why don't you just go by the book?
And also, just because I
beat up a few displaced fools,
can you reduce people to this state?
All we need from you is the truth.
Who instigated you?
Have no idea.
- I don't know.
- Choi Taewook!
Do you really believe Jo Pilyeon
will do everything to protect you?
How many times do I have to tell you
I've got nothing to do with...
What do you plan to do
with that Choi Taewook?
We must get rid of him.
I can't forfeit my seat in congress
because of that useless minion.
Killing him is the only way
to avoid any future complications.
Shall we go down
the list of your charges?
Breaking election law,
and considering you used a
lead pipe during your assault,
that will mean attempted murder.
What else... Escape and formation
of organized crime society,
instigation to violence, blackmail,
intimidation, racketeering,
attempted murder by contract,
perjury and so on,
for a grand total of forty-eight counts.
It's your last chance.
Confess that Jo Pilyeon instigated
your assault on that clearance area.
Then, of those forty-eight counts,
you'll only be charged for one,
simple assault.
Looks like the chief
is not coming today?!
I'm sorry.
I'll never make you cry again.
Aww... It's so embarrassing...
How can I look him in the face again?
I was insane...
He tries to kiss me
and I just stand there...
Chief...
Why?
You regret kissing me?
Uh?! No...
I didn't mean that...
I mean... It's not like I didn't...
So...
Like...
It's late.
I'll drive you home.
Chief.
"Minwoo."
Uh?
Hearing you call me Chief just feels like
you're keeping your distance, I don't like it.
Call my name.
Mi...
Min... Woo...
Forgot how to spell it?
Want me to write it down for you?
I can't call your name...
It makes me feel embarrassed.
I'll get going, then.
I'll call you.
Ahh... Right.
I had something to give you yesterday.
Might be a day late,
but Happy Birthday.
Birthday?!
Do you know what giving a man
a necktie pin really means?
The way I've heard it,
it's what women give to men
when they confess to them?!
Really?
I just bought it without knowing?!
But what now?
Yesterday wasn't even my birthday.
What?
I'm sure I read right
on that library card?
We use the lunar
calendar in my family.
Give it back, then.
Hey... If you gave it to me,
it's mine... How nasty...
I'll give it to you again
on your real birthday.
Nope.
I don't have money
to buy you another one!
Give it back, come on...
I said no.
Give it here!
Hey... How can you...
In the heat of the moment,
I didn't do anything last time,
but you can forget about it
unless I give you permission.
Hey...
Ever seen anyone
ask permission to kiss?
You thief...
What?
You took my first kiss away...
Hey...
Hey! You...
Have a good night, Chief.
No...
Min...woo...
First kiss?!
- 4 - Independent JO Pilyeon -
- Vote Counting Inspector -
Next are the counting results
from the Gangnam district.
Beating second-placed Min Honggi
by a landslide margin,
independent candidate Jo Pilyeon
has won the congressional elections.
Congratulations...
Congressman Jo Pilyeon!
Thanks, Chairman Hwang!
Congratulations!
- Congratulations, Sir.
- Thanks, Seongmo.
I won!
Jo Pilyeon finally made it!
Applause!
Jo Pilyeon! Jo Pilyeon!
What did you say?
What is the matter?
We're the City Council's
Supervision Team.
We'll take all your data
regarding the highway project.
Wait a moment...
Hello?
It's the construction site.
We have inspectors here, it's a mess!
Come on in.
He was the main culprit in the
assault at the clearance area.
I was contacted.
Detective Lee. Escort him.
Yes.
Here are all our notes
from the investigation.
You can consult them.
Thank you.
Didn't you file another one of these?
Can you publish this in
tomorrow's morning edition?
I'll just have to call all my colleagues
from the evening edition, I guess.
I'll have to get busy.
So in the end Jo Pilyeon triumphed.
Makes you feel like we
supported Candidate Min in vain.
There's no way Jo Pilyeon wouldn't
be aware that you supported Min.
So?
I'm sure he'll attempt
some kind of retaliation.
And you were so vocal and
confident about winning this...
What is all this about?
First, allow me to
apologize for this defeat.
That's fine with me, but even
getting on your knees and begging...
before Baekpa won't be enough.
I have no use for apologies.
We'll just avoid
each other from now on.
Give this a read first.
It's tomorrow's morning edition.
- Candidate Jo Pilyeon, Victory Might be Overturned -
Clearance Area Assault Exposed as a Ruse
- Jo Pilyeon Personally Instigated Violence -
This...
What could it possibly be about?
What is this?
Jo Pilyeon's victory
could be overturned?!
Cheers!
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
This victory wouldn't have been
possible without your help.
Thank you, Chairman Hwang.
I'd like a word with you, Congressman.
Go ahead and tell me.
Actually, I've been put in
a slightly difficult position.
Ahh... I've heard from Minwoo already.
So inspectors from the
Supervision Team showed up?
That is all a trick by
Commissioner Han Myeongseok.
What are you trying to say?
A trick by Commissioner Han?!
Commissioner Han supports Min Honggi.
Just because I support you,
he attempted to take the
highway project away from me.
Han Myeongseok, that fella
needs to be taught a lesson.
Don't you worry, Chairman Hwang.
I'll meet with him firsthand and
tell him to halt the supervision.
Will you do that for me?
Hell, by the next personnel changes,
I'll have to push some buttons and
get him sacked from his position.
If you could only do that for me,
there is nothing else I would ask for.
Let's drink.
We weren't expecting
anyone at this hour?
I'm sure it's Seongmo.
Go open the door.
I'm coming.
Thank you again, Congressman.
Who are you people?
Police.
Mister Jo Pilyeon, right?
And?
You're under arrest for instigation to
violence and breaking the election law.
What?!
Arrest?!
Do you people even realize
who you're dealing with?
Let's not resist the arrest,
or you'll force us to escort you
to the station one way or another.
Listen.
Which station are you people from?
Who the hell is your superior?
Escort him out!
Congressman!
You son of a bitch!
And you must be Go Jaechun, right?
Take him as well!
Let go...
Let me go, you bastard!
I'll remember all you people.
- Dad... Dad!
- Honey!
Minwoo! Honey!
What is going on here?
Jo Pilyeon is arrested?!
Then, what will happen
to the highway project?
I'll just confess
I was behind the assault.
Don't worry about me,
get out of here and fulfill your term.
Subjecting you to this
really makes me feel ashamed.
Ohh... Seongmo!
How did it go?
I think the higher-ups got involved.
If it's the higher-ups,
they're all people I know.
Who was behind this?
Min Honggi has his connections as well.
Not to mention that having the
ruling party's support gives him an edge.
I was much too careless.
Despite the fact I know who I was
dealing with better than anyone.
It was foolish of me.
If you're sentenced, you'll be
deprived of your seat in congress.
Don't you worry.
I'll take all the blame for this.
Choi Taewook already testified.
Are you telling me the
investigation is already over?
It's already all written in this
investigation report by the ANSP.
Go Jaechun keeps claiming
he alone was behind this,
but we have both a witness
and enough evidence in our hands.
Even if you keep denying
those charges, it'll be useless.
Leave Go Jaechun out of this.
Not just him,
but also everyone else from my
camp who was involved with this.
Then, are you going to plead guilty?
I have more experience
than you in this circle.
After I've met with my lawyer,
I'll follow your wishes.
The trade meeting at
City Hall will soon begin.
And Chief Jo?
He went to the trial.
At the meeting today, they're going
to publish the supervision results.
Go there for me.
Wrap it up on my behalf,
and then come back.
All right, Dad.
Jo Pilyeon's election trial
just concluded.
How did it go?
He was sentenced.
As he got a one-year sentence, he will
be deprived of his congress seat as well.
Leave me alone, will you?
- 14th Highway Construction Trade Meeting -
How is everyone?
Didn't Chairman Hwang Taeseop come?
I came here on his behalf.
Then, we'll begin with the results of
Manbo Construction's on-site supervision.
Basing their decision
upon four distinct criteria,
the team concludes
that Manbo Construction...
is not suited to complete this project.
Consequentially, as the City Council was
impressed by their reasonable estimates...
and their revolutionary
construction method,
we decided to entrust the rest of
this project to Gwangmyeong Construction.
We did it!
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, Chairman.
I'd like the representatives of
both companies to come forward,
and sign this
memorandum of understanding.
Go ahead and seal it.
What's the matter?
I'm sure...
I'm sure that was Gangmo.
What?
I have no doubt it was him.
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
You just saw things.
Let's go.
Gangmo.
Gangmo!
Honey.
Congressman.
Are you all right, Honey?
Are they making it hard
for you in any way?
I'm perfectly fine.
How can a man have that expression?
Now that I think about it, my life
was in need of a little incitement.
I've been winning for so long,
I lost sight of the big picture.
Nothing can incite you
like a little suffering.
Dad...
And one day this same suffering will
become the medal heralding my triumph.
You just wait, Minwoo.
The day that medal pierces this chest,
it will bring forth indescribable
suffering upon those...
who are now screaming in joy,
believing they've defeated me.
Honey...
Don't show weakness to anyone.
Jo Pilyeon's wife should be
able to control her emotions.
All right.
All right, I'll do that.
You can leave now.
Honey...
Honey!
What did we do to deserve this?
Your father in prison...
What now... Honey!
Take her home.
All right.
- Yoon Seunghee's Like a Swallow -
When the spring comes,
he said he would come back by my side.
Like a singing swallow.
How can you try to sneak in
and touch my hands?
Can't even hold your hands?
That's right.
Why do you keep acting so precious?
How nasty...
You were the first to
hold my hands, remember?
She barges in and just
grabs your hands, and then...
I only did that to
console you, that's all.
I need your consolation today.
Uh?
So just give me your hand.
Hold my hand and comfort me, will you?
Liar...
Hey... Do I really
need to spell it out?
I really had a terrible day.
Is there anything wrong, really?
Hey... Forget it, then!
Forget I ever mentioned it!
Even holding hands can be this hard...
So something bad happened to you?
Can't you tell me what's wrong?
I'll lie down a moment.
What's with the sigh?
As if the sky was about to fall.
I've just had it, that's all.
I just wanted to shake off everything,
and go somewhere quiet, that's all.
I'll cover your ears,
so just close your eyes.
Then, you'll suddenly feel at peace.
So what did you want to see me for?
I hear Manbo Construction's highway
project went to Gwangmyeong Construction?!
I'm well aware.
You said you would join forces
with corporations, right?
- Then, by any chance...
- Yes.
It's Gwangmyeong Construction.
So it was you.
The one responsible for convincing Chairman
Cheon to oust Manbo Construction...
Didn't I tell you I would
defeat Manbo Construction?
Manbo Construction is not going to collapse
just because of a highway project.
I'm well aware that
this is only the beginning.
By any chance,
have we ever met before?
It's just that you look familiar...
Do you know me, by any chance?
Sorry to disappoint you.
Before you met him, what did you do?
Now that I think about it,
we know far too little about you.
Isn't what I'll do from now on
what really matters?
Still, he invested in your company...
Private lenders like us only need
to know the strict necessary.
You may leave.
Yes.
I'll visit you again soon.
So he joins forces
with Chairman Cheon,
and scores one against
Manbo Construction?!
That fella is defying
all my expectations.
Thank you.
This next song always brings up
really precious memories.
- Baek Seolhee's Spring is Coming to an End -
As the spring breeze
caressed my pink skirt,
Heat dwelling on my coat strings,
the air swarming with swallows.
Back when flowers bloomed by the
sacred tree, as we together smiled,
Or when we together cried by those
withered roses, pledging to each other.
Spring is coming to an end.
Wow... Gyeongok, when it comes
to singing, you really are great.
You're the best!
Really?
You know what? Working at the
construction site might kill me,
but I live for this.
This is it.
Then...
Shall we live together?
What?
Why don't you ever mention marriage?
You're not already married, are you?
What are you saying?
Of... course not...
I can barely take care
of myself, you silly.
I don't need anything else,
just for you to love me.
To only have eyes for me,
and only treat me with kindness.
To only think about me.
You can do that for me, right?
Are your standards really that low?
With all the fine men you
could find out there, why me?
You'll only end up struggling
if you live with me.
I've long gotten used to struggling.
*archaic for partner, husband
Let me pour you a drink, Seobangnim*.
Fresh weeds carried away by the current.
I sent another letter again,
leaving along with that last train's hopes.
Back when we together
laughed under the starry sky,
and we shared tears
under those falling stars.
Carried away by such hollow memories,
Spring is coming to an end.
What are you going to accomplish by
going to the Royal Club at this hour?
What do you think?
It was that wench who owns the place who
convinced everyone to push for Jeongyeon.
Am I supposed to
just take it lying down?
Mom, after we lost the highway project
and Minwoo's father went to prison,
- is this the time to be...
- What does that have to do with anything?
Aren't you even angry that they took
away your heir status under your nose?
Of course I am!
I'm sure there's
something fishy going on.
Or else, how would someone running a
business have the time to scheme that?
Whatever.
You go there by yourself.
I'll be waiting outside.
Back in the day,
when I had nothing to my name,
all I needed to endure days like this
was thinking about success.
But now that I've made it,
these headaches never seem to go away.
I've heard Gwangmyeong Construction
took over the highway project.
It's only going to spoil the mood,
so let's not go there.
Do you know who's behind that?
It was Han Myeongseok.
He betrayed me.
It wasn't Commissioner Han.
What's that supposed to mean?
Someone else plotted all this.
And who is that?
It's Hangang Construction's
president, a certain James Lee.
J...James?!
Then, are you telling me
he and Chairman Cheon were in cahoots?
How can I help you?
Where's your boss?
If you don't have an appointment,
you can't meet her.
Say what?
What's so great about a damned club,
to need appointments?
Ma'am...
And what are you doing here?
Are you here with the chairman?
I'm sure Commissioner Han
fell into their trap as well.
How could this happen...
That James... What kind of man
could we possibly be dealing with?
He did look familiar,
but I really can't
figure out who he is.
Thanks, Gyeongok.
If it weren't for you,
I would almost have let them
fool me without knowing a thing.
What are you doing here?
What do I see...
Was it just this?
So you two fell for each other,
pushed out my Jeongshik...
I can't believe it.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- And you!
Don't even say a word.
Tell me.
How long has this affair
between you two been going on?
I can forgive all the rest,
but you better take that back.
Say what?
We're not what you think...
What? "We"?!
When did it start becoming "we"?
Was it all so that, after taking away
Jeongshik's status, it'd be my turn,
and then you'd finally be
able to go live with him?
Just because you made
a few pennies selling drinks,
think you can prance around
acting like a queen?
Even a lowly mistress
should know her place,
how dare you barge in without...
Go act like a vulgar tramp at home,
how dare you treat me like this?
What?
Do I look like the kind of woman
who deserves your contempt?
You've barked up the wrong tree,
so unless you want to be really
embarrassed, get the hell out of my sight!
That... That wench!
What do you think you're doing?
You tell me.
What were you scheming with her?
Hurry up and tell me!
Ahh... Really...
You woman...
I won't let you two get away with this.
This Oh Namsuk
is not to be taken lightly.
- Cheers!
- Cheers...
Aww... That's refreshing.
- Hey!
- Wait... Wait.
You... Nah...
Let's just put this away.
Look at you.
Do you know how much
you've had already?
So, what?
Since you're with me,
I'm drinking a little bit.
So that's how it tastes like...
Hey!
Forget that,
and have something to eat.
Here you go.
Big Oppa!
Little Oppa!
Yeah, Miju. Tell me.
Seeing you two makes me so happy...
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Looks like she's happy you came.
Every time I think of her,
I feel sorry.
Have a drink.
Good job.
I never imagined you'd take the highway
project away from them so quickly.
It's just the first step.
I should say the same about you.
Sending Jo Pilyeon to prison...
It will be hard for him to
get back on his feet this time.
I think I might now be
able to help you for real,
what are your plans from now on?
Chairman Hwang will likely point
his blade at Chairman Cheon.
I'll have to take a step forward
and enter the fight firsthand.
Chief...
She even talks in her sleep?!
"Chief..."
Chairman, I'm afraid
I'll have to take this?
Ahh... I lost again!
See? Told you I'm not
cut out for mahjong.
Seems like today
is not your day, Chairman.
Did I ever witness a
good one at the table?
Luck only graces those
good enough for it.
Still, you've gotten much better.
- Is that so?
- That's right.
So how much do I have to fork out
before I start improving?
We've had our fun playing,
so shall we get to the point now?
But, Chairman Hwang.
Why didn't Chairman Cheon show up?
Maybe he didn't know we came here
instead of the Royal Club?
I didn't invite him on purpose.
You didn't invite him?!
Is it because of the
highway project thing?
That's Commissioner
Han Myeongseok's doing...
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
Chairman Cheon conspired with that man
running Hangang Construction...
to take the highway project away from us.
They planned this
from the very beginning.
That's not possible...
Chairman Cheon broke committee rules.
As the chairman of this committee,
I'd like to motion for
his permanent exclusion.
Does anyone here oppose my wishes?
Hello?
That's right.
Yes, just a moment.
It's a call for Chairman Baek.
For me?!
Yes.
And who would call me here...
It's me, Chairman Baek.
Do you know who killed
Chairman Hong Gipyo?
What are you saying?
It was Chairman Hwang
Taeseop's son, Hwang Jeongshik.
And of course Chairman Hwang
covered up the truth.
Listen.
Who are you?
Cheon Suman here.
What this fella said is right.
I can swear on my own ancestors.
If you'd like to know more,
please come out.
Of course, you must not tell
anything to Chairman Hwang.
Yes.
I understand.
Chairman Jo?
Come pick up the phone.
- Me?!
- Yes.
Yes, Chairman Jo speaking.
When are you going to show up?
What call could it possibly have been,
to suddenly ask for your attention?
It's nothing.
It was from the golf club,
and... Right!
Chairman Hwang
doesn't like golf, isn't it?
Anyhow, let's wrap up
Chairman Cheon's expulsion here.
But we still are a committee,
so shouldn't we first invite the interested
party and announce our decision to him?
If that is your wish,
let's gather again
tonight at the Royal Club.
Anyhow, I'll consider this a unanimous
vote in favor of his exclusion.
Are we really supposed to believe that?
I'll speed up a little,
if you don't mind.
Ahh... Yes, go ahead.
What's that supposed to mean?
Let's be honest, don't you remember
how much better things were...
when Chairman Hong was
presiding over the committee?
But it was Hwang Taeseop's
son who killed him.
And how can you prove that?
There is someone here who can prove it.
They're all waiting inside.
The order of the day...
concerns the expulsion of Chairman
Cheon of Gwangmyeong Construction.
Aren't you being excessive?
- I merely did what Commissioner Han...
- We'll decide via secret voting.
I'm sure you know you must
abide by our decision, Chairman?
Here... Let's begin.
I will now announce the results of the
voting on Chairman Cheon's expulsion.
One vote against.
For.
Against.
And with that, the motion to expel
Chairman Cheon from the committee...
has been rejected.
Dammit!
How do you explain this?
Are you deaf?
Let's hear it!
Since we're all gathered here tonight,
I'll take this opportunity
to introduce a new member.
And what is that supposed to mean?
A new member?!
Come on in.
Sir,
how have you been?
You...
You!
I'm president of Hangang Construction,
Lee Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Gangmo?!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Why are you trying to
strangle Manbo Construction?
And how about paying the price
for taking my father's life?
Why don't you go wear a pair of pants?
Why should I wear pants
at home, when it's so hot?
Seems like Jo Pilyeon
might be released earlier.
You better be on your toes.
He's not the kind of man
who'll forgive and forget.
So you want to create a rift between
Jo Pilyeon and Hwang Taeseop?
If Hwang Taeseop is involved,
all the better.
Jo Pilyeon knows I'm alive.
Then, what now?
I'll have to meet him.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com