Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 15 ~
Yes.
Shideok...
Gangmo!
What's wrong with your voice?
Listen well.
Don't tell this to anyone,
and come here alone.
Quick.
Jeongyeon.
How hurt was he?
He sounded like he was about to die.
Shideok, speed up, will you?
Yes.
Gangmo!
Gangmo, where are you?
- Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
Gangmo.
What happened to you?
I told you to come alone...
Are you all right?
What is all this about?
Don't worry, Agasshi.
I'm all r...
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
Gangmo... Wake up.
We're here.
Gangmo.
Doctor... Doctor!
This will hurt.
There... It's done.
Here it is.
Hello?
Jeongshik.
It's me, Minwoo.
Has Jeongyeon come home?
She's not here?
She's not?
She went out to meet Gangmo,
and still hasn't come back.
Lee Gangmo?!
Don't you know
where she was headed?
No idea.
I'm tired, so let's hang up.
Gangmo.
How are you feeling?
Agasshi.
We're at a hospital.
For gunfire wounds,
they'll surely notify the police.
The director is friends with my father.
There's no need to worry.
Still not curfew, right?
Just lie down.
I'll sleep here tonight.
Agasshi...
You can't sleep outside.
You fool.
Is it time to be worrying about me?
You were shot, and risked death!
Why are you always
so foolish and reckless?
I told you I would
take care of my father.
And how?
By marrying Jo Minwoo?
Just wait a little longer.
- I'll find that account, and...
- My father's being released tomorrow.
It's all been taken care of, now.
Jeongyeon... No.
Where is Lee Gangmo?
Why, they told you he was with her?
I know everything already.
Where is Lee Gangmo?
I said I don't know!
Why are you doing this to me?
Gangmo.
Are you sleeping?
You are...
Gangmo.
Thanks.
For making it alive.
Also...
for protecting me all this time.
I wish things could be
a little easier for you.
Wish I could see you
live in a nice house,
your kids playing all around the yard,
as your pretty wife is
preparing a tasty dinner for you,
waiting for you to come home.
You'd then arrive, your hands filled
with candies for your children,
as your laughter of joy
echoes all around.
I...
want to see that kind of
happiness stamped on your face.
That's why...
I will no longer try
to keep you all for myself.
I'll no longer bother you,
asking you to remain by my side.
Why are you fantasizing
all on your own?
You weren't sleeping?
I'm not the kind of man...
who will just leave or
stay by your side as you wish.
Gangmo...
Ever since I turned thirteen,
you've been like family to me.
After I lost my siblings and parents,
do you know how much happiness...
having a family to protect brought me?
Don't take that happiness
away from me.
Go ahead and sleep.
I'm the patient tonight,
so you'll have to
make do with the sofa.
Same clothes you wore yesterday, I see.
I'd prefer if you didn't concern
yourself with my fashion choices.
We're about to get married.
It's not like we're
doing that out of love.
So, what...
Let's not care about
whatever the other is doing?
Will be much less trouble
for the both of us.
If that's your wish, fine with me.
Dad.
Are you feeling okay?
No injuries at all?
Mom is waiting for you with
all your favorite dishes.
Let's hurry up home, Dad.
So you're going to
get married with Minwoo?
I also promised them we'd
support his father's candidacy.
It wasn't for me to decide,
but I had no other choice.
Are you confident
you'll be happy with him?
That you won't regret marrying him,
and you will lead a happy life?
I really don't know.
What "leading a happy life" means.
Don't answer your father
that way, you silly.
When it comes to business,
I never had any scruples.
But with one's children,
that's another story.
This marriage is nothing but business.
That's what led me to that decision.
I'm happy you got out safe.
If your mother were here,
she'd have been against this marriage.
I wonder how angry she will be,
when we meet again in the afterlife.
I won't regret this.
I'll marry Jo Minwoo,
and live a happy life.
If I think of marriage as
just another business venture,
then I'm confident I can do well.
So what do I owe the occasion to?
Are the committee members
still under investigation?
One was released,
and as for the rest
of the suspected, not yet.
Release them all,
and wrap up the investigations.
Congressman.
I released Hong Gipyo and
cleared him of all accusations.
What are you saying?
You released Hong Gipyo?!
We found his account.
If we only get rid of that account,
all the obstacles threatening Gangnam's
redevelopment will go away with it.
And how are you going
to deal with the opposition?
They have no evidence,
what could they possibly do?
The press already
has set its eyes on this.
- If we wrap up investigations...
- As for the press, no need to worry.
Manipulate things a little, and it will
fly out of people's radar in no time.
Right... That's your specialty, isn't it?
I've had it with this damned account,
so burn it to ashes.
What the hell have you been doing?
What were you doing while
Min Honggi got hold of that account?
I apologize. I couldn't
catch wind of the situation.
How did he manage
to find that account?
In exchange for his release,
it seems like Hong Gipyo confessed.
Where is Hong Gipyo?
They transferred him
straight to the hospital.
Stick a few of our boys
outside his room, day and night.
By now, Director Min must have
already gotten rid of the account.
He even survived electroshock.
Why do you think someone like him
would confess only now?
Then...
I'm sure he made a copy of it.
Trail him thoroughly.
Yes, Director.
Honey.
Can you hear me?
Chairman!
Honey!
What's the matter, Chairman?
There... Take a look at that clock.
Look at that fool.
What's wrong, Honey?
Get a hold of yourself!
Chairman...
You have some visitors...
Chairman Hong.
How are you feeling?
I apologize.
Help me out.
Chairman Hong, what's wrong with you?
It's us, Chairman Hong.
I didn't do it.
I apologize.
Help me out.
I beg you, help me out!
Help me... Help me!
- Help... Help...
- Chairman Hong!
Chairman Hong!
This is serious.
What's the matter, all of a sudden?
The patient is acting strange?!
Seems like he suffered
some kind of head trauma.
So are the rumors that
Hong Gipyo has gone mad true?
That's what I've heard.
Thank you, Director.
My father getting out safely
is all thanks to you.
There are also instances of
imaginary maladies, from time to time.
Imaginary?!
Be it because of fear
of being investigated again,
or as a result of ulterior purposes.
Wasn't all this case wrapped up?
Hong Gipyo might
still have that account.
Because he's more than capable
of having made a copy.
With the kids' engagement
and the subway construction,
you have a lot on
your plate, these days.
Don't worry about a thing,
and take good care of yourself.
Here, let me pour you one.
Let's drink the night away.
Hey... Hey... Jeongshik!
Get a hold of yourself.
I said I'm all right...
Dad. Are you just going?
Don't you want another few drinks?
You fool.
Who the hell are you,
to accept drinks from anyone?
Ahh... Really, Dad.
My sister is getting married,
can't I even accept drinks from my in-laws...
I've had it with this fool.
- Send him home right away.
- Let's get going.
Ahh... I'm not drunk at all...
Dad. Wonder if
Myeongwol is doing fine?!
I'll get going!
Ohh... Gangmo.
Let's have a word.
Are you telling me Chairman Hong
might have another account?
We might be about to become in-laws,
but I don't trust Director Jo.
We can't allow him to get
his hands on that account.
I'll find it.
Don't you worry, Chairman.
I've heard you risked your life.
I know how much you go
through every day for my sake.
I will make up for that,
whatever it takes.
Chairman.
You're like a father to me.
That's what has guided me
all this time.
And it's something
that will never change.
Right...
Thank you for
seeing it that way, Gangmo.
Ehh... Look at this,
what is happening to this world...
Where is his guardian?
She's not feeling well,
so she went home.
We will either have to discharge him,
or transfer him to a mental institution.
I'll discuss it with his wife.
Then...
You're reading it upside down.
Where's the account?
That copy I gave you.
Where did you put it?
Chairman...
There are still people spying on me.
Then, are you just
acting like this on purpose?
Miju.
Can you help me out one more time?
First, have them discharge me.
After that, bring me the account.
Got it?
I'll go file all the documents
for your discharge right away.
Even if you get out of here,
it won't be easy to stop
Director Jo from suspecting you.
Don't you worry.
I have a plan.
You just wait.
How my revenge will taste like.
Have a drink.
Minwoo, you too.
We are family now.
Minwoo, what are you waiting for?
Pour your father-in-law a drink.
Yes.
Let's set the engagement
ceremony for next Saturday.
Aren't we going a little too fast?
If it were up to me,
I'd just get them married that day.
How about you, Jeongyeon?
It makes no difference to me.
All the complicated talk is dealt with,
so Minwoo,
take Jeongyeon and go have fun.
You're already wrapping things up?
I haven't even talked once
with Jeongyeon.
You'll get plenty of chances
to do so, from now on.
What are you doing?
You can go.
Yes.
Then, if you'll excuse me...
Have fun.
- Here... Let's have a drink.
- Yes.
I have other plans, so I need to go.
You didn't want to go out
on a date with me, did you?
You'll tell the director we had
the best of times on our date, right?
Gangmo, can you give me a lift?
I want to take a walk.
Is there any place
you could take me to?
I need to do something
for the chairman.
Just go back to work.
What is it?
What did my father tell you to do?
Company work.
What company work?
If it has anything to do with Chairman Hong,
don't even think about it.
Don't worry about me
and do your work.
Lee Gangmo...
Honey.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You've had it hard, right?
What happened?
It's a long story.
But forget that.
You'll have to go down to Jeju.
Jeju?!
I found a nice nursing home there.
And you?
I'll have to wrap up things at work...
I'll be busy.
Can't I wait here
and leave with you later?
We'll spend the rest
of our days together,
what are you worrying for?
I want to quit being a businessman.
Let's just raise stock
in the countryside,
and spend the rest
of our days in peace.
Honey...
I'll leave her to you until Jeju Island.
Don't you worry, Chairman.
You must remain healthy, Ma'am.
I bet you're happy that you won't
have to listen to my bell anymore?
I thought I would,
but I'm sad.
Take this.
What's this?
It's a savings account in your name
I've been keeping all this time.
Ma'am...
I wanted to give you this
when you got married.
In your mother's place.
When you find your brothers,
you'll come to Jeju, right?
Yes, Ma'am.
Let's meet again.
Here... You'll be late.
Get going.
Are you done packing?
Look.
Can you see your face shine in there?
Wow... Ajeosshi, you're really great.
You little scoundrel,
that's how you shine shoes.
Go! Out of the way.
And my money?
You little...
What do you take your seonbae for?
After teaching you the tricks
of the trade, you should pay me.
Still, pay me!
Look at him, staring straight!
Ohhh... Fine.
I'll pay you.
How much should I give him...
Dream on, you little twerp.
Before I get my shoes dirty again,
out of my sight!
Little rascals...
Never listening to adults...
Ajeosshi.
You still haven't left?
You little... How dare you...
Come here! You!
Aigoo... Really...
You're here?
Have a seat.
What were you talking about?
His housemaid quit?
Don't even get me started.
The whole family split up.
Any idea where that housemaid went?
Where she moved to.
I'd like to know, too.
Ahh... Should have dated her once...
Find out where she is right away.
The chairman has gone batty,
how the hell am I supposed to do that?
If I tell you something, just do it!
Miju.
What?
You keep this account.
Even using a safe box at
the bank makes me nervous.
When the time comes,
I'll come looking for it.
What are you trying to do?
Chairman.
I feel like I'm putting too heavy
a burden on your shoulders,
so forgive me.
Where do I hide this?
Hey... What's wrong with you?
Let me ask you something.
Does Jeongyeon like Gangmo?
What?! Hey...
Are you telling me you're
jealous of someone like Gangmo?
I asked you a question!
Gangmo is nothing but a servant,
and Jeongyeon is his keeper.
And I thought
something serious was up...
And how would you possibly know...
Give it a rest, Minwoo.
But I'm sure Gangmo likes Jeongyeon.
Isn't it laughable?
He should know his place.
Jeongshik Oppa!
Ohh... Myeongwol!
Why do you show up
so rarely these days?
I'm busy at work, what else?
He's about to get married.
Pour him a drink.
Congratulations.
Ahh... You little...
Myeongwol.
I'm staying here for the night.
Really?
Are you going to spend it with me?
Pour me another.
Oppa... Slow down.
Myeongwol...
What's this?
Those two...
Where have they gone,
while I was in the men's room?
Get out of the way.
What's the matter?
What's wrong with you?
Get the hell out.
What got into you?!
It's quite late.
And Gangmo?
Gangmo?! He's still not back.
I told you to take it easy at the table.
Shideok.
What is Gangmo doing, these days?
What did the chairman entrust to him?
I... Agasshi.
I'm well aware that
I shouldn't even say this,
but leave Gangmo alone.
What are you trying to say?
Because of you, Gangmo is always...
Never mind.
Go ahead.
Because of me, Gangmo what?
You don't know?
Hwang Jeongyeon!
Hwang Jeongyeon, come out!
Come here!
I said come out, Hwang Jeongyeon!
Minwoo.
I had something to tell you.
Do you even realize what time it is?
I said I had something to tell you!
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Go back in, I'll drive him home.
Let go!
Hey... Hwang Jeongyeon.
So what did you want to talk about?
After making all this mess,
at least let's listen to it.
I really hate you, Hwang Jeongyeon...
I really do.
So much it's suffocating me.
I know.
No...
You don't.
What would you know?
Do you know anything about me?
Anything at all?
Is there anything more we
need to know about each other?
We both gained what we wanted,
so that's it.
Let's not complicate things for nothing.
I think I'm falling in love with you.
I mean it.
Did Jo Minwoo leave?
Let's have a word.
If everything's all right,
then forget it.
Go to sleep.
Gangmo.
Aigoo... Aigoo!!
You wretched fool.
Think this will bring you any benefit?
Did you find out where
that housemaid is living?
Still couldn't find that,
and it seems like she's
working as a bus conductor now.
Bus conductor?
Which company's buses?
Hurry up.
Hurry up, come on.
The ticket.
Here... Let's hurry up.
Those in front,
please move and let them pass.
Here... Let's hurry up.
All right!
Stop... Stop!
Thank you.
One of our men is
spying on his wife in Jeju.
Go search Hong Gipyo's house
when he's not home.
All right.
Right...
He also had a housemaid, didn't he?
I think she quit.
She looked suspicious,
for some reason.
I will take care of finding her.
Shouldn't I come back by your side?
You do that.
What are you doing?
You... moved?!
Why are you following me
around all day?
Ahh... Bought some
candles and matches.
Looks like there'll be plenty of
blackouts in this neighborhood?!
Here.
Can I...
come in a moment?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would you enter
a single woman's room?
I had something to ask you.
I have nothing to listen to.
Ehh... He's such a nuisance.
Did he find out I have the account?
So how about this quarter's donations?
We'll have to continue, obviously.
First they complain of
sponsor this and that,
and now they're still
after that money?
From now on, Director
Jo Pilyeon will be in charge.
Jo Pilyeon?!
That wicked tyrant
who sent Chairman Hong crazy?
What are you doing here?
Are you feeling any better?
What...
What are you...
Help me. Save my life!
What's wrong with you?
Considering all
the money you give them,
you could certainly
help me out this once.
Ohh Ohh... Careful what you say!
I'll beg, if necessary.
Don't abandon me!
- Chairman...
- This won't do, let's just...
Stop... Fellas!
I'll do whatever you ask me.
Should I take off
my clothes and dance for you?
Or want me to bark like a mutt?
Chairman Hong...
Look, Chairman Hong.
In case you really haven't gone crazy,
listen well to my very last offer.
Do you at least have
a copy of that account?
Give it to me.
Then, I can certainly give you
enough for you and your wife...
to go live overseas.
How about it?
Will you give it to me?
Chairman Hong!
You son of a bitch...
Out of the way!
It's me.
Seems like KCIA agents
came here today.
Jo Pilyeon started
suspecting your housemaid.
Thankfully, I was able to volunteer
to spy on her, so don't worry too much.
How much longer do I
have to pretend like this?
Let's not rush things.
The right opportunity will soon come.
The moment Jo Pilyeon
stops suspecting you...
is when we'll reveal
that account to the world.
It's trouble.
Jo Pilyeon sent his men
to search that maid's house.
I don't think it's here.
Search the kitchen and
then start from scratch!
Yes.
How did it go?
Did you find it?
It's not there.
It's not?!
No.
I don't think that maid is involved.
Then, who could possibly have it?
Isn't there a chance there
might be no copy to begin with?
Nah.
There is no way.
Thank you.
Go.
All right!
- See you tomorrow.
- See you.
Last stop.
Aren't you leaving?
Last stop!
What is this...
Give me the ticket and leave.
Ahh... Where did the ticket go?!
You ride the bus all day,
and don't even have a ticket?
Did I throw it away earlier on?
I can bring it tomorrow, right?
Tomorrow.
Look.
Are you going to keep this up?
Let's just have a talk for an hour.
I said I have nothing to talk about.
Then, I'm not giving up, either.
Do as you wish, then.
Also, try to freeload again,
and I'll report you to the police.
What's the matter?
It must have been a thief.
I shouldn't just stay here...
Where are you going?
I'll call the police.
This was no thief.
What?
Look at these footsteps.
There were at least two of them.
The account.
You have it, right?
Look if it's still there.
What are you waiting for?
Look for it.
There is no such thing here.
Look, young lady.
I said there's none,
so hurry up and leave.
Chairman Hong is trying to
reveal that account.
If he does, he won't survive.
Do you understand?
If you really care about him,
give me that account.
I said I don't know.
Leave.
Before I start screaming,
get out of here!
My shoes...
Chief Jo, I suppose?
Your mother called me.
She told me to prepare a
special ring for your engagement.
Yes.
We have a unique model
from an Italian designer.
I'll show you that.
Just give me anything you have.
As long as it fits my finger, that'll do.
This would be fine.
Still, wouldn't you like
to look at what I prepared?
Let's have this.
How does she look?
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yes. I like it.
I'll choose this one.
Show me another model.
But seems like the groom likes it...
But I don't.
I'll choose something else.
He looks great.
If you want to try out other models,
I can leave, can't I?
People here know me.
Walked all day long, so my feet hurt.
Why?
Am I embarrassing you?
Sit somewhere else, then.
What are you doing?
Just stay put.
All the fatigue
will go away in a moment.
People are looking!
Not doing this to be nice.
Our circle, it's a small world.
Want to advertise to everyone that
it's just a loveless contract marriage?
It will be hard for us, from now on,
since we'll have to pretend we're
the happiest people in the world.
If acting as if
you love me is too hard,
just accept the love
that I show for you.
Will be much easier that way.
I couldn't care less
about what other people think.
You're quite busy these days.
Looking for Chairman Hong's
account, right?
I'll have to do that myself.
What?
Get my hands on that account.
Just leave it to me.
And why?
So you can continue
receiving all the praise?
- It's not that...
- If it's not, then what is it?
I'm, what, in the way?
While Jeongyeon and Minwoo
are talking about engagement,
shouldn't I attract my father's
attention with something?
- Listen...
- Spare me the excuses,
and if you find any good lead,
report to me immediately.
I'll come get it myself.
Got it?
Aww... That little...
Why don't you just leave it to him?
So he can go out there and get shot.
Are you just going to keep
following that housemaid?
That's the only option we have now.
You're not even sure she has it.
~ Little Women by Kwon Taesu & Kim Sehwa ~
When did we meet each other,
And when did we break up?
Both loving each other and breaking up
was nothing but suffering...
Wow... I envy her...
Should have become a singer.
Hey, what are you doing?
Bring the drinks.
Yes...
Hey... My bottle.
My bottle!
Currently, Hwang Taeseop holds
sixty percent of the company's shares...
either firsthand or through his family.
Buy all the Manbo Construction
shares you can find.
All right.
I'm Manbo Construction's
Hwang Taeseop.
I've heard a lot about you.
Is she your daughter?
Yes.
Introduce yourself.
Nice to meet you,
my name is Hwang Jeongyeon.
I'm in charge of
the subway construction.
I'd need some financial
help to cover expenses...
If it's Manbo Construction,
I certainly should help you out.
But I trust you know our conditions?
Yes.
I know.
- It's me.
- Ohh... Come on in.
The contract?
Here it is.
Dad.
Read it thoroughly, and then sign it.
Yes.
You own the Royal Club, right?
Remember me?
We met at the club, a while ago.
Really? I'm sorry.
I can't remember all my customers.
I see.
The more I think about it,
they look too much alike.
How could she look so much
like Jeongyeon's late mother...
Do you know her?
Is she dead?
I think it'll be hard
for her to survive the night.
Dad.
Nah... It's impossible.
I saw her dead.
What did you just say?
- What?
- You said something.
I did?! And when?
Is anything the matter?
Nah, I'm fine.
I'm perfectly fine...
Oppa... You'll come today, right?
Halmeoni!
Ohh... You're here?
Want some cakes?
I had breakfast already.
Ohh... You did?
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
- It's hot, isn't it?
- It sure is.
What day is it again?
Newspapers!
~ Saturday - June 30, 1979 ~
Right... I met that fella
looking for you, the other day.
What?!
I'm sure he'll come today.
I told him you come here
every last day of the month.
Must be happy...
You'll finally meet your brothers.
Oppa...
They're shoes!
Put them on.
Miju.
Will you sing Oppa a song?
Want to hear one?
Yeah.
Fine, since you
even bought me shoes.
"Here comes the water cock,
quacking on the paddy field."
"Here comes the cuckoo,
echoing in the forest."
"When my Oppa will ride
to Seoul with his horse,"
"He said he will
bring me silken shoes."
"Hear the sound of wild geese,
coming from the north."
"The cricket chirps away
in sad melancholy,"
"But still no news of
my Oppa from Seoul,"
"As the leaves keep falling."
Oppa!
What?! Did you follow me here?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Time to leave Jeongyeon alone.
I can't tolerate you
loving my wife anymore.
Chairman Hong has that account?
He has it?
I'll go get it myself,
so stay out of this.
Didn't you miss Jeongyeon?
She'll soon get married.
She's getting engaged tomorrow.
Director. Seems like
Hong Gipyo was murdered.
Murdered?!
Oppa, you didn't do it... right?
Someone was trying to frame me.
My housemaid asked me for this.
Miju!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com