Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 43 -
So it was you?
I'm sure they treated you well enough?!
Who did you do this for?
That's none of your business.
Just stay here quietly,
and be glad if you're sold to a brothel...
I knew it the moment
I saw you punch that sandbag,
but you sure can hit?
If you don't set me free
right this moment,
you will all...
You insolent little bitch...
Director Yoo Gyeongok?
That'd be me.
We have your daughter.
Who are you people?
I asked you a question!
What are you asking?
Hello?
Hello?!
Listen well.
Whomever you are,
and whatever you're asking,
it doesn't matter.
Because I...
will kill you all.
You will regret abducting Jeongyeon...
even from six feet under.
Because I'll follow you into
the pits of hell if I have to,
and tear you apart limb from limb!
The moment you
report this to the police,
you know that
Hwang Jeongyeon will die, right?
Wait quietly until we call you back.
Those people know that
Jeongyeon is my daughter.
Tell me everything
that happened earlier on.
This guy came asking for a loan.
Looked like she knew him really well...
His name was... Hwang Jeong...
Hwang Jeongshik?
Yes! That's the one.
Hwang Jeongshik.
If it was Hwang Jeongshik...
This has something
to do with Cha Bucheol.
What's that supposed to mean?
Those two have been
hanging out together for a while.
Director...
They'll soon tell you their conditions.
But never let them get any leverage.
You know what I mean?
Are you telling me
to ignore their requests?
If you do, Jeongyeon could be in danger.
If only to buy time,
we must play hardball with them.
But what if something
happens to Jeongyeon...
Before that can happen,
I'll find Jeongyeon and rescue her.
You can bet on it.
To people like us, intel means money.
If we only wanted to,
we could hear the whispers people
in the slums make under their bedcovers.
Is that so?
I bet.
And we're also perfectly aware
that you launched this tax investigation.
Please overturn that order.
Sounds like a favor to me?!
But the way you're asking it
seems a little coarse.
If that is the case,
I can only apologize,
but honestly, that is
how I feel at the moment.
When it comes to taxes,
I can open the dances,
but I can't change the tune on my own.
Congressman Jo.
So I hear you'll be forced to give back
all the principal that Baekpa lent you?
Intel is money on this side
of the pond as well.
And once that principal is retrieved,
I'm sure the balance of power
will go through significant changes?
Will Yoo Gyeongok
become your new kingpin?
I better get up.
I'm not done talking.
We will devote our most earnest efforts
to pay the taxes you so cordially asked.
Just sit.
He's going to fight with Yoo Gyeongok
over the underground market.
Still, how dare he...
In the end,
he'll be groveling at my feet.
Although it will be easier
said than done,
we need to make that happen.
Hey... That way!
Shoot!
Gangmo.
How did it go?
How about Hwang Jeongshik?
He didn't show up at home and
not even at the gambling house.
Looks like he fled already.
That rat bastard...
First he gets obsessed with gambling,
and now he even gets his sister involved?!
How are things proceeding
with our boiler issues?
Youngchul Hyungnim is trying to
find out the accident's causes,
so you just focus on Jeongyeon.
We can't take it anymore. And it's not
like we can always leave the doors open.
Please find a solution.
Yes, yes. Don't you worry.
We will deal with it right away.
Go back in.
See you.
So there were no problems
with the boiler?
None.
It's not a technical defect for sure.
I'll be damned...
I could smell gas from a mile away...
Were you looking for me, Chairman?
So I hear Hangang Construction
is checking boilers door by door?
Yes.
And did they find what the problem was?
Even the Beaute engineers
haven't been able to find the answer.
Maybe it's exactly because they're
engineers that they can't find it.
What?
This is not a defect.
What are you trying to say?
I've examined that data all night,
and there was only one difference between
the European boiler system and Korea's.
And what is that, Chairman?
Gas.
What?! Gas?
The gas we use is different
from the Europeans'.
Contact the research lab.
If my guess is right,
we will able to make new inroads into
the development of our ondol-styled boiler.
All right, Chairman.
Ahh...
How did it go with the ads about Lee Miju?
We started with the evening
edition of the four major dailies,
and leaflets will be distributed as well.
- Kang Wooju -
Aren't you playing with your buddies?
What is this called?
So you don't know.
- Lion.
- Ohh!
You know the lion!
Let's see what's next...
So what is this one?
Elephant.
Wow... Even the elephant?!
You're good.
Then...
Should your uncl... No.
Should this ajeosshi buy you ice cream?
Wooju doesn't like ice cream.
You don't...
How about chocolate?
You like it?
Wooju...
Wooju.
Let's stop reading and go back in, uh?
Lee Miju.
Big Oppa...
Thanks for the invites.
I just couldn't wait until the concert.
Missed you too much.
Seongmo Oppa...
Had lunch?
Here.
It's been hard practicing, uh?
Here...
Why aren't you asking me anything?
I got rid of the baby.
- The reason I haven't come looking for you...
- I know.
That you wanted to show us
that you could succeed.
Sorry, Oppa.
You were worried, weren't you?
Nah.
We felt sorry, on the contrary.
And Gangmo Oppa?
Gangmo really misses you.
Actually, we planned to meet you
after your performance.
But I missed you so much...
Guess I cheated a little.
I know that Little Oppa's
business is doing well.
I've heard the news.
But, Miju.
Minwoo is still looking for you.
If you get more popular
after that concert,
you will no longer be able to avoid him.
That man is no longer part of my life.
I can't do anything about the past,
but he and I are through for good.
I won't ever meet Minwoo again.
Stop worrying, Big Oppa.
From now on,
I'll only focus on succeeding.
Come on in.
Are you out of your mind?
Didn't I tell you to keep a low profile?
Hey, Cha Bucheol.
Looks like you underestimated me.
What?!
So while I was "keeping a low profile,"
you'd frame me for abduction?
I see we've got some brains up there.
Let's renegotiate.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm afraid a few months'
worth of interests won't do.
So?
Cancel all my debts.
Hey... Hwang Jeongshik!
I could also get rid of you?!
Go ahead.
I've got nothing to lose anyway.
- You little son of a...
- If you lay a finger on me,
you'll be reported
to the police right away.
So you said that Yoo Gyeongok
is Jeongyeon's mother?
She might not report you, but I can?!
Should I try?
Shall we see whether I die first,
or the report gets to them faster?
I guess negotiations are over?!
Stop trying to use my
gambling debts to blackmail me.
- Congressman Oh Byeongtak -
Autobiography Publication Party
- On The Path to History -
I should thank you
for this publication party.
I'm glad you liked it.
I hear there's no ruling party member
who doesn't owe you big time?!
I really haven't done anything special.
Director Hwang.
You wanted to meet him, right?
Here's Congressman Park.
Congressman, I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Hwang Taeseop.
These days, that Hwang Taeseop
is making his ambitions pretty clear.
I've heard that not only Congressman Oh,
but just about every congressman
capable of recommending him is being helped.
I really don't know where he would find
the money to help all those congressmen.
There's no way the money would be his,
so I guess Yoo Gyeongok is
backing him from behind the curtains.
If you'll excuse me a moment,
I will be right back.
That way.
What is that supposed to mean?
Jeongyeon was abducted?!
So I hear Director
Yoo Gyeongok is her mother?
What...
Where did you hear that?
I've heard it from the
people who abducted her.
And who are they?
Who abducted my daughter?
I don't know them, either.
But after being with Jeongyeon,
they suddenly showed up...
Shouldn't we report this to the police?
It looked like they'd kill her
right away, in case we did.
Gyeongok...
I'll have to head to the Royal Club.
Yoo Gyeongok is her mother?
So you abandoned Mom just as she said?!
What?
Hwang Jeongyeon was abducted?
Yes.
Who's behind this?
I don't think they had any idea.
Did they report it to the police?
They're holding back,
fearing for her life.
Something is up for sure.
There must be some internal struggle
within the private lending organization.
Doesn't this benefit you?
I don't think turning that
organization against us would be wise.
We could actually gain control of the
whole operation, if things go our way.
Is that so? I see...
- Find out what's going on in detail.
- Yes, Congressman.
Jeongshik is still outside, right?
If you hurry up,
you might be able to meet him.
Just like Minwoo said, if we play
our cards well, the whole pot is ours.
Aigoo... Congressman Jo.
I really enjoyed your book.
It was truly touching.
Gangmo!
Hwang Jeongshik has shown up!
Where is he now?
He went to a saloon with Jo Minwoo.
Sotae went after him.
What's that?
I hear Jeongyeon was abducted.
It has something to do with you, right?
Doesn't it?
And why would you
show any interest in this?
Ahh...
By any chance,
were you aware of it as well?
That Jeongyeon was
Yoo Gyeongok's daughter.
This whole thing was
orchestrated by Cha Bucheol, right?
Wh...What?!
The only one who knew Yoo Gyeongok
was Jeongyeon's mother is him.
G...G...Gangmo...
What's with you?
Get the hell out!
Are you involved
with Jeongyeon's abduction?
What's that bullshit supposed to mean?
If that's not the case,
stay put and don't get in the way.
Take him out.
- Come...
- Let go.
Director Moon.
You have Cha Bucheol's number, right?
I wonder if he's moved his office or
something, but I can't reach him as of late.
Cha Bucheol, that third-rate thug...
How can he handle it this way...
I do remember his car phone number.
I'm sure he hasn't changed that.
Gangmo... I don't know.
Speak! I said speak!
Where is Jeongyeon?
Where is that bastard Cha Bucheol?
I don't know... I really don't!
And I told you it wasn't Bucheol!
You piece of shit!
And you call yourself a man?
Do you?!
Stop him or he'll kill him!
Don't kill me, Gangmo.
I was just talking with her,
and suddenly...
Spare that bullshit
for who will believe it!
Believe me or not...
I don't know a thing, so just kill me!
Hey... Gangmo!
Looks like he really doesn't know!
Fine... Kill me!
Let's see you become a murderer!
Hey...
If anything happens to Jeongyeon,
then we won't even try
to stop Gangmo! Is that clear?
I don't know...
I don't know a damned thing!
Sorry-ass son of a cunt.
Even in my prime,
I never stooped this low.
Pathetic asswipe... Ehh...
You better stop looking down on me.
Because you will soon regret
everything you did to me.
You look so quiet and
obedient when you sleep...
So let's start doing as I say, shall we?
It's precious goods we're dealing with.
I'm doing my best
to handle them with care...
What's with the surprise?
Afraid I'll bite you?
You rat bastard...
- You crazy...
- Hyungnim.
What is it?
Chairman Jo Minwoo
wants to meet you urgently.
Who the hell does he think he is?
Always bossing me around.
Gangmo...
How have you been, Congressman?
Is Noh Gapsoo behind this?
Hwang Jeongyeon's abduction.
I really don't know
what you're talking about...
I'm sure President Noh would have asked
for a pledge giving up on that principal.
Or maybe that IOU list.
I'm afraid I have no idea
what you're telling me.
You really don't know anything about this?
How could I ever try to deceive you?
You mean it?
I swear to God.
Please believe me, Congressman.
All right. You can go.
Are you just letting him go?
Jaechun, you go after him.
Find where their hideout is.
All right.
It's President Noh, all right.
I'll have to get my hands
on that pledge and the IOU list.
Just because I wag my tail around you,
you bastards seem to think
I'm just your little pet.
Let's go.
They said it brings good luck,
so I even wore my wife's panties...
Keeps bothering me...
The hell is this?
I told her to give me
those with flower patterns,
what is with the damned little drums?
Today's not my day, all right.
Hurry up and just give us the cards.
May I join in?
Why the hell not?
Aren't we all here to play?
Have a seat.
But, who introduced you to...
If you tell Director Cha that I
come from Myeong-Dong, he should know.
Ahh... Is that so?
But Director Cha left
the business to us and quit?
Really?
What's this, a neighborhood meeting?
Let's see the cards.
Here... Let's up the ante a little.
Looks like that Bucheol
really got out of this?
- Should we just look elsewhere?
- That guy is Cha Bucheol's underling.
Judging by how he kept staring at me
throughout the entire game.
Yes, Hyungnim.
Looks like he came from
the Myeong-Dong lending market.
Yes.
Never really seen him before.
It's obvious.
Must be one of their minions.
If he asks for money, refuse.
Yes, Hyungnim.
All right.
Must be hungry?
Help yourself.
Ahh... So here you were!
Lend me some money, will you?
Looks like it's really not my day.
Just call it a night.
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know me?
I've been a regular ever
since Director Cha's days.
Ahh... You really...
- Redial Last Number -
Just try me!
Try to get any closer!
Do you really have a death wish?
Put that down!
What is it that you want?
Why did you abduct me?
Answer the goddamned phone!
What is it?
Catch that brat. Do it!
Let go... Let me go!
- Let go!
- Speak!
The hell are you?
- Is that the dry cleaner's?
- What?
Dry cleaner's?!
You really... I better not
meet you on the street!
I am sorry.
Looks like I dialed the wrong number.
Don't ever do anything you'll
have to feel sorry about again.
You... What are you doing here?
Where is Cha Bucheol?
Tell me!
Where is Cha Bucheol now?
- I don't know...
- You don't?!
Should I encourage you to tell me?
My boys...
are waiting out there.
Speak!
Where is Cha Bucheol?
Hyungnim! It's me.
Go tell Bucheol.
If he doesn't set Jeongyeon
free before I find her,
I will kill him with my own hands.
Ahh... You people.
Can't even lend us some money...
Hyungnim!
Turn it off.
Did you close up shop
and send out all the boys?
Yes, Hyungnim.
Hey.
What is going on
between you and Lee Gangmo?
What the hell do you mean to him,
to frantically prance around
looking for you like a rabid dog?
Are you lovers?
I suggest you shut your mouth,
and let me go while you still can.
Or else...
Or else?
Gangmo will beat you to a pulp.
Hey.
Acting all tough
just because of Lee Gangmo?
You've been abducted.
You might die.
Know that?
What the hell is all this about?
Jeongyeon was abducted?!
Yes?
How have you been?
What do I owe this call to, Director Cha?
Make a wild guess... I'm sure
you already have a vague idea?!
I know that Lee Gangmo is listening.
What are your conditions?
Tell us what you want.
Hey, Lee Gangmo.
Will you please
stay the hell out of this?
This is between me and Director Yoo.
Why are you always getting in the way?
I can see a reservoir from here!
A three-hour drive from Seoul...
Jeongyeon! Jeongyeon!!
Gangmo!
Jeongyeon... What's going on?
Hwang Jeongyeon!
- You dare bite me?
- Get her out of here, you idiot!
I'll make things simple, so listen well.
You know the principal which
was supposed to be retrieved?
Write a pledge renouncing it.
Give us the IOU list you're carrying,
or else your daughter is dead.
Are we listening, Director Yoo?
And who said Hwang Jeongyeon
is my daughter?
What?
I don't know where
you heard that nonsense,
but I'm afraid you're wrong.
If she was my daughter,
why would I hide it?
Don't you think?
I've heard what you and
Baekpa said loud and clear!
Hwang Jeongyeon is your daughter!!
To me, Hwang Jeongyeon is not
as important as Baekpa's last wishes.
You made a wrong guess.
Check your sources and call us again.
Gyeongok. What are you...
Well done.
But will anything happen to Jeongyeon?
We at least bought some time,
so the key is how long it
will take for us to find her.
Just as I thought,
the organization was behind this.
Any idea who might
have orchestrated this all?
I do have someone in mind,
but I can't let
speculations cloud my judgment.
Gyeongok...
Are you all right?
This all happened because of me.
I even thought that,
when the time would come,
I'd give her everything I have.
Because that was the only way...
to make it up to her.
That was the only thing that helped me
endure all this over the years...
Yeah... I know what you're feeling.
I know.
But it's exactly in times like these
that we need to get a hold of ourselves.
It's the only way to save Jeongyeon.
First, let's do what Gangmo suggested.
I'm sure he'll be able to rescue her.
Why?
Raise a ruckus again, will you?
How about...
you set me free and we see if
you can really handle me in a fight?
What?
A fight?!
Ahh... Look at this crazy brat...
You never fail to amaze me.
You act just like your moth...
What?
Forget it.
Even that info means money to me.
Can't let it out of the oven so easily.
What are you trying to say?
All you need to do is follow my orders.
Are we clear?
Spare me all that bullshit.
Think Director Yoo will do as you say?
Dream on.
She has no reason
to exchange me with money.
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon...
There is something you don't...
No, something you shouldn't know.
And what the hell is that?
You really...
Who are you screaming at?
Hey.
I'm much scarier than you think.
If I sell you off to Japan, you'll be rotting
in a room saloon for the rest of your life.
Think I couldn't?
I'll go get the phone,
so don't make another scene,
and just beg them to save you.
Think that it's the only way
you'll get out of here alive,
and give it your best.
You fuc...
A reservoir three hours from Seoul.
A reservoir three hours from Seoul...
Jeongyeon.
Hang in there a little longer.
Whatever it takes,
I'll come get you.
Gangmo...
Are you asking me to arrest Cha Bucheol?
He abducted Hwang Jeongyeon.
He'll soon get a pledge and
that IOU list from Yoo Gyeongok.
You just need to get your hands on that.
What would you do with
that pledge and the IOU list?
There's this private lender
called Noh Gapsoo.
With Baekpa out of the picture,
he's virtually fighting Yoo Gyeongok
with the entire organization at stake.
I'm just trying to tread in his path.
So you'll try to gain control
of the private lending...
That's exactly it.
The more you learn about the underground
market, the more alluring it becomes.
It's even a little intimidating.
And if we lose this opportunity,
it will be hard to get another one.
I understand what you mean.
But there's a problem.
Lee Gangmo is on a rampage
trying to find Cha Bucheol.
We can't allow him to
rescue Hwang Jeongyeon.
Is that clear?
You must find Cha Bucheol first,
and bring him to me.
All right.
Jaechun will help you.
I can handle it by myself.
I know how busy you are these days.
If you join forces with Jaechun,
it'll be much easier.
Let's join forces like
back in the KCIA days, Seongmo.
So this heat exchanger helps the
gas combustion, and turns it into heat?
Didn't I explain it to you already?
Ahh... How could telling me
only once do it?
So let's hear it in detail,
while you're at it.
Let's just forget it.
It's not like it'd help us find
the cause of those accidents.
Wait... What...
Ahh... Look at him.
It's just his temper...
He's not a bad person.
I'll explain it to you one more time.
Aigoo... Like I don't have a temper?
But, where is everyone?
- Where did the president go?
- Don't even get me started.
Those boilers aren't the only
thing that's about to explode.
And what is that supposed to mean?
We got a call from the research lab,
and right as you suggested,
gas was the problem.
When will you be able to get your
hands on Beaute's core technology?
He said it would take until
about the end of next week.
Tell him to hurry up.
Now that they're running around aimlessly,
it's the perfect opportunity to beat
them to it and develop our own boilers.
Generously fund the boiler
research team from Hanguk University.
All right, Chairman.
Yes.
Your mother is in the hospital,
and you don't even pay her a visit?
Of all places, why that hospital?
Uh?!
Because I heard this place
is best when it comes to joints.
You can do whatever you want,
but I won't marry that woman.
And who ever asked you to marry her?
I just want to see you, that's all.
Mom.
Ehh... No excuses.
Just come visit me.
Always talking so much...
Aigoo... Come on in, Doctor Yoo.
So how about that meeting,
was my Minwoo all right?
While I'm hospitalized here,
I'll tell Minwoo to come,
so give it a try.
Thank you.
Ahh... Right. Mother.
I told my father to entrust his new
heart center to Manbo Construction.
Aigoo... How considerate of you.
It's just that Minwoo is
not too interested in women,
but right after you had that meeting,
he seemed to like you.
Are you all right?
Be careful.
Wooju's mother will soon be here.
Why bother her when she's so busy?
It's not like I'm not used
to joint inflammation by now...
Grandma.
Where have you been?
Grandma, here...
Are you helping Grandma get better?
Aigoo, my boy...
Don't you worry.
Grandma is all right.
What?
Help me up, please.
I need to wash my hands.
Please...
Done?
Mom...
You're so busy, why bother...
Again with the inflammation?
They said it's nothing serious.
A little treatment and
I'll get better in no time.
Where is Wooju?
The men's room.
He said he's a man, so there's no way
he's coming to the ladies' room with me.
Hey... Kiddo.
You should thank me.
Thank you.
Hi.
Is my mother all right?
Yes, she's fine.
I was about to get off...
What?
If you're not busy,
would you have dinner...
- Then, I'll go see my mother, and...
- Chairman.
We found someone who saw Miju.
I'm sorry.
Let's save it for another day.
Wooju...
Wooju. Kang Wooju!
Wooju?
- Chowon Coffeehouse -
I'll be shooting,
so let's do it in one take.
Are we clear?
Hey... Tie her up again.
Let go... I'll do as he said!
Happy now?
Do you mean it?
I can't allow you
to sell me off like that.
So we finally start to get it?!
So you'll be shooting a video?
Just do as I say. Sit there.
- Chowon Coffeehouse -
Hey... Go get a pen and some paper.
Yes.
Since you said you'd cooperate,
go ahead and read this.
Here... Let's begin.
Before that, will you give me a cigarette?
You smoke?!
Before I change my mind, do it.
Aigoo...
Hey... Hey.
It's upside down.
You're here, Hyung?
Why didn't you tell me?
If I knew you were going
after those abductors,
I would have helped you.
Bucheol knows your face, so I couldn't.
It would get you in danger as well.
I need to catch him as well from now on.
Jo Pilyeon told me.
To catch Cha Bucheol
before you find Hwang Jeongyeon.
What is he scheming?
He wants to gain control
of the private lending market.
In other words, stop Yoo Gyeongok
and Hwang Jeongyeon...
from gaining any more influence.
Then, can I rest assured
and work with you on this now?
Go Jaechun will be with me.
He could find out we're brothers,
if things go wrong.
Jo Pilyeon...
He sure is tenacious.
I'll lead Jaechun astray,
so take the opportunity
to save Hwang Jeongyeon.
He still hasn't made his move.
He will soon.
That's how abductions work.
In the end, they'll be the ones
to make the first move.
Miju's live performance is this weekend.
You'll come, right?
Of course.
We'll need to cheer her on.
Don't you worry about this.
Until he gains what he wants,
he won't touch Jeongyeon.
Gangmo.
Gangmo...
They...
sent us a tape with Jeongyeon in it.
If you don't listen to these people,
they might kill me.
Please help me.
Give them what they ask.
You have three days.
If you don't send them that pledge
and the IOU list within three days,
I might die.
Jeongyeon doesn't smoke.
She tried to send us some kind of signal.
Rewind the tape.
Stop!
That matchbox.
Chowon... Coffeehouse. Right?
Ohh... Yeah... Looks like it.
How about the phone number?
I can only see the area code?
What's the area code?
Starts with 0443.
*national phone directory
Yes, 114* speaking.
How may I help you?
Yes... Could you please tell me
the number for Chowon Coffeehouse?
Just a moment, please.
You will meet an important
person coming from the east,
but the sun will set
and the path is still long.
Hey... Must be east, then.
That reservoir is there.
East or west, let's first check
the reservoir nearby.
There must be some
kind of villa around here.
If we react carelessly,
they could spot us.
And we don't even know how
many people we'll be dealing with.
So, what, are we just going to sit here?
They'll come here for sure.
Even if they do,
how will we recognize them?
We only know Bucheol's face.
Coffee for three.
Gangmo!
You dare bite me?
Listen.
Are those people regulars?
They come pretty often these days.
What kind of people are they?
Gangsters.
You can't imagine how annoying they are.
Wait here just a moment.
Ahh... I'm sorry.
Hey... Did you leave your eyes at home?
I apologize.
I should have been more careful.
- I ought to...
- Hey.
Stop.
Pay for the dry cleaner's,
and get the fuck out.
Don't ever do anything you'll
have to feel sorry about again.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
If you don't tell me by the
count of three, you're all dead.
- One...
- Are you crazy?
Two!
But you don't even cry?
I was told that men shouldn't cry.
You can, since you're still a kid.
Who got you this gig?
Did you sell something else
other than your albums?
I found her...
Cha Soojeong is Lee Miju.
He either must be really crazy
about you, or think I'm an idiot.
When you get what you want, let us go.
And you think I'd just let him go?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com