Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 18 -
Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo!
Is this the tallest building in Seoul?
I thought you had died.
How foolish of me.
My brother was right in front of me,
and I didn't even recognize him.
Hyung...
Seongmo Hyung!
I'm your wretched brother.
Hyung!
Hyung... Hyung!
Hyung...
Hyung, you haven't
seen Miju yet, right?
I met her.
Hyung, I'm sorry.
Mom passed away.
Don't talk about it, Gangmo.
And our youngest, Junmo,
was adopted overseas.
And after we all
got separated, even Miju...
She had to grow up in an orphanage.
I know...
And that's why it's so painful to bear.
I was so foolish...
The fact I couldn't protect
my family makes me so angry...
It's so painful to bear, Gangmo.
Hyung...
Hyung! Hyung...
Hyung!
How did you end up
working for Chairman Hwang?
He's like a father to me.
In my darkest hour,
right when I lost Miju,
he took me under his wings.
Gangmo.
He's an orphan just like me.
And just like him,
one day I will succeed.
So how did you enter the KCIA?
Must be really difficult
to be accepted there?!
Seems like Director Jo Pilyeon
has full confidence in you,
so were you helped by him?
Let's talk about that another day.
Inside you'll find a forged ID,
and I added a few things
you might need.
Here's where you'll be hiding.
For the time being, stay there.
I don't want to spend
the rest of my life hiding.
I'll never let that happen.
I'll soon send you overseas.
Trust me. Got it?
Take good care of Miju, Hyung.
Don't you worry.
I'm the eldest, remember?
From here on in,
I'll take care of my family.
How do you explain this?
Lee Gangmo escaped?!
Someone helped him get out.
Are you saying he had an accomplice?
Seeing how he dealt
with those detectives,
we're likely dealing with a pro.
There's good reason
to suspect Director Min's side.
Stick to his underlings day and night.
If they're hiding Lee Gangmo anywhere,
they'll try to establish contact
before the elections.
- Yes.
- Consider it done, Director.
Let me ask you just one thing.
Why didn't you tell your brother
that Jo Pilyeon and Hwang Taeseop...
were responsible
for your father's death?
He still acts as if he owes
Chairman Hwang his life.
I can keep the burden
of revenge all to myself.
Gangmo has always been
full of dreams.
I don't want to see that
filthy blood stain his hands.
So what you're saying is that you'll
bear that burden all by yourself.
Gangmo...
has already endured enough
difficulties because of me.
From now on,
I'll only live for my siblings' sake.
I told you I know nothing!
Young lady, isn't he your brother?
I told you I haven't seen
him once after that day.
We'll have to take
her down to the station.
This won't do it.
The station?!
- Why would you take me...
- Detectives.
Is she Lee Gangmo's sister?
Yes, that's right.
And you are?
We'll take care of investigating her.
What?
Yes... Yes, certainly.
Let's go.
How about Little Oppa?
He's hiding in a safe place,
so you don't need to worry.
Big Oppa...
Ahh... Miju.
Detectives will start trailing you.
Don't try looking for me
before I get in contact first.
All right, Oppa.
But, what will happen to
Gangmo Oppa from now on?
First, he'll have to go overseas.
After that, we'll catch the
culprit and prove his innocence.
Then, when can we start
living all together again?
Let's endure it a little longer.
There's nothing else we can do now.
If Gangmo Oppa goes abroad,
I'll follow him there.
I'll cook for him, do his laundry,
and take care of him.
Miju.
Leave Gangmo to me,
and worry about having fun
doing what you really want.
That's what Gangmo
would like you to do.
First, let's move to a nicer place.
Stop working as a bus conductor.
From now on, I'll provide for you.
No, Oppa.
That would only make
the police suspect us.
As you say, all I need to do
is to work hard and live happily.
Worry about Gangmo Oppa instead.
Will you be staying for long?
Just a few days.
If you need anything,
feel free to call me, uh?
Yes.
Jeongyeon.
When will we meet again?
Will that day even come?
Everything is in order,
including your heart.
Really?
There's nothing wrong with you,
but you feel chest pains all day long.
What else... Insomnia, shortness
of breath, lack of appetite.
Did you break up with your partner?
What?
Those are the kind of symptoms
people who break up sometimes show.
It must be because I'm concerned
about a friend, I suppose.
Sometimes your mind can be deceitful.
But your body never lies.
The way I see it, I think you must be
in love with that friend of yours?!
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Here.
Write it from scratch.
Let's meet on Sunday at noon,
in front of the Hangang Hotel.
I'm asking you out on a date.
Don't worry about Gangmo.
I'm trying to help him
one way or another.
Can't you look where you're going?
Do you even know who I am?
Everything going well, I hope?
What are you, out of your mind?
How can you come here?
Then, what else could I do?
I ran out of money.
You really...
Here... In the car.
So you've already spent
all that money I gave you?
Think hiding is that easy?
You could just get it over with
and go for a big payoff.
I ought to just...
Why, no money left to give me?
If that's the case, someone will have
to hear a few words from me, I guess.
Is there any position available here
at Manbo Construction? I wonder...
You...
This is the last time.
Pop up before me
without my consent again,
and they won't even find your
dead body when I'm done with you.
Is that clear?
So who's blackmailing who?
Hey... Hey...
Couldn't you add an egg yolk
or two in this herbal tea?
Aww... Oppa.
That's for morning coffee.
Didn't seem that way to me...
Hey... Hey!
- Come on in...
- Come on in where...
Park Sotae. Right?
And who do I have the pleasure
to meet, calling my name and all?
I'm Jeongyeon.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
I'm sure that name should ring a bell?
Let's go together
to the police station.
What's wrong with you?
You went to meet Chairman Hong
with Jeongshik that day.
Let's go to the station,
and confess the truth!
Why, did... anyone witness us?
Witness or not,
let's go and confess everything.
We never went there?!
And what's with the attitude?
- You didn't?
- That's right. We went back on the way, why?
And what are you
meeting Jeongshik for?
Why have you
been hiding as of late?
Ahh... You're driving me crazy.
Let's go.
Go ahead, I have nothing to hide.
Here... Let's go.
- How much is it?
- 500 won.
What are you waiting for?
Bill is yours.
Stop there!
I have something to tell you.
Is it urgent?
Yes. Very urgent.
Head to the station alone.
Have them explain to you
what happened with Gangmo.
All right, Chairman.
What else happened to Gangmo?
I was told he escaped from prison.
What?!
Here... Let's go up.
So, what was this
urgent matter to discuss?
I struggled long and hard
on whether I should tell you.
But I just thought
you had the right to know.
Just say it.
On the day Chairman Hong
was murdered,
Jeongshik went to that cottage.
Wh...What did you just say?
Shideok gave the keys
of Gangmo's car to Jeongshik.
And Gangmo's work uniform
was inside the trunk.
Jeongyeon...
What are you trying to say?
A man called Park Sotae
went there with Jeongshik.
I just saw him meet with Jeongshik.
Nah... There must be
a misunderstanding of sorts.
Why would Jeongshik meet Hong Gipyo?
According to Shideok,
he was looking for an account.
To win your praise.
What?!
Dad... Are you all right?
It's all right. I'm fine.
Jeongyeon.
You didn't tell this to anyone, did you?
You're the first one I told this to.
Gangmo would even pretend
to die if you asked him to.
You're the only one
who can prove his innocence.
It's not Jeongshik.
Dad!
Might be a wretched punk,
but he's still my son.
Think I wouldn't know
my own flesh and blood?
He's not the kind of man
who can kill.
Jeongyeon...
It wasn't Jeongshik.
Then, how about Gangmo?
Think he's the kind of man
who could commit murder?
I'm sure Jeongshik has that account.
Verify that yourself.
There's no need.
There is no way
Jeongshik is responsible!
I believe in you.
Believe that you're not the kind
of coward who would ignore Gangmo.
I do.
Ahh... Really...
Jeongshik killed a man?!
No way.
Jeongshik would never do that!
No.
He wouldn't be capable of that!
Here... Let me pour you one.
Yes, Dad.
But, tell me.
What's the occasion?
We generally don't get
to share these moments.
Why, what's wrong with
father and son having a drink?
Here, have one yourself.
Fine, let's see if I still remember what
a drink poured by my son tastes like.
Things are hectic these days, I bet?
I know how things
are going in the company.
We have the subway construction,
and with the upcoming by-elections,
there's Director Jo's campaign to fund.
Not to mention falling
estate prices... Ehh...
So I was wondering.
Jeongshik.
Yes, Dad?
By any chance,
are you in possession of
Chairman Hong Gipyo's account?
What?
What is that supposed to mean?
I mean... Why would I have it?
Listen to you...
Chairman Hong is dead, anyhow.
And Gangmo is being
accused of his murder.
And?
If you do have that account,
give it to me.
With that in our hands, there's no
need to worry about campaign funding.
Dad...
What on earth are you talking about?
If you don't have it, then too bad.
But if you really do,
we must make the best use of it.
Only then we can save our company.
Jeongshik.
Why do you think
I would even ask you this?
In due time, when you
find yourself in my shoes,
you'll understand my concerns.
I'll head home, so take
your time and enjoy the night.
Jeongshik...
It's not you...
Right?
You didn't kill him, right?
You fool.
Please... I beg you,
don't ever bring me that account.
Uh? Jeongshik.
*archaic for partner, husband
What's capturing
your thoughts, Seobangnim*?
Seeing how far Dad went with this,
it really must be
a golden opportunity.
Opportunity? To do what?
"Make a nice showing
once and for all,"
"and capture your place as my heir?"
Right... Oppa!
Inherit the company,
and get me out of here, will you?
Do what?
Aigoo... You sly fox!
Come here!
Smuggle me out?!
What's the destination?
I'm looking into it, so hang in there.
The moment I get you a spot there,
you'll be able to go abroad.
Miju is doing okay, I hope?
Yeah.
Strong and cheerful as always.
But I worry about you as well.
I fear something might
happen to you because of me.
If anything happens to you,
I don't think I want to go on anymore.
Don't even joke about that, Hyung.
So you must keep yourself
out of trouble.
If you don't, I...
I will never be able to face
our parents in the afterlife.
I'm sorry, Hyung.
I've put you through so much trouble...
What happened to you is all my fault.
Hyung.
Let's talk again soon.
Right.
Seonbaenim.
Did you look into it?
There's a boat headed
for Hong Kong in Incheon.
Do they allow smuggling?
That's what they do for a living.
There's no time to waste.
Get in contact with them,
and get a spot on that boat.
Yes, Seonbaenim.
You must never reveal our identities.
Don't worry.
If you don't have it, then too bad.
But if you really do,
we must make the best use of it.
Only then we can save our company.
Fine...
I even killed someone for this.
I can't just get rid of it.
Come in.
Go ahead and open it.
What you were so anxiously
looking for is inside here.
Take a look.
It's Chairman Hong's account, right?
And why do you have this?
What?
Did you kill Chairman Hong?
Are you the one who killed him?
And why would that matter now?
You said that with this in our hands...
You idiot!
Dad...
What...
What the hell happened to you?
My son kills a man?!
You pathetic fool...
I just wanted to make you happy, Dad.
You useless fool...
I wanted to make a good impression,
and at least give you
a little help, that's all.
You're right...
It's not your fault.
When someone ends in this state,
his parents are always to blame.
I didn't raise you properly.
It's all my fault.
Right... I'm the pathetic fool here.
And what did I do wrong?
I just was unlucky, that's all!
All I wanted was to be
acknowledged by you!
Yeah... I know.
Of course I know, you silly.
The hell do you know?
Do you even realize how I feel?
First Jeongyeon upstages me,
then Gangmo takes my place...
Do you know how it really feels like to
be considered a nuisance no matter what?
Jeongshik...
Stay away...
If you could only accept me,
I would enter a prison cell
right away with no regrets.
But what is this?
What the hell is all this?
Why don't you get up now?
Jeongyeon.
You... You...
Can't you close an eye
just this once?
For your father's sake,
can't you feign ignorance
just for once?
And what about Gangmo?
He's like a son to you!
I will do everything I can for him.
Dad...
Dad.
You can't do this.
Don't do it, Dad.
Jeongyeon.
You can't realize
what I'm going through.
When you get children of your own,
you'll understand.
I can make it up for all
Gangmo is going through anytime.
But when a parent
ruins his child's life,
there's nothing
that can make up for that.
Dad...
I'm sorry, Jeongyeon.
Hello?
Gangmo?
Shideok.
Where on earth are you?
It's an islet in the
outskirts of Incheon.
Incheon where?
Shouldn't you at least
tell me where you are?
Wait.
Agasshi?
Is she doing well?
She's getting married soon.
My mother told me.
That Jo Minwoo's family seems to be
rushing to get them married.
Gangmo.
Are you listening?
Take good care of her.
Is Jeongyeon the problem now?
She can do nothing by herself.
So you at least look after her.
Aigoo... You silly fool.
Also, should she ever worry about me,
tell her I'm all right,
to live happily with Jo Minwoo.
Just say that.
Hey... Lee Gangmo!
Shideok.
Didn't Gangmo call you?
You still haven't
heard a thing from him?
Nothing.
~ West Sea Lodge ~
Ganghwa-Gun, Gyeonggi Province
Looking for this?
This is where Gangmo is staying, right?
Give it back.
Gangmo is hiding here, right?
I said give it to me!
For whose sake did Gangmo
end up in this mess?
It's all because of you!
What are you trying to say?
Because of me?!
Why do you think he's always been
so stupidly loyal to the chairman?
So that one day, whenever
it might be, you'll be his,
because of love or whatever that
nonsense is called... That's what!
You can just get married with
Jo Minwoo and it'll be all over,
but what is going
to happen to Gangmo?
Stop making that
poor fool suffer so much.
Gangmo...
If that's the kind of marriage
you'll get into, just don't!
I'll help the chairman get out.
There's no need to bow down to people
like them, or let them trample on you!
You just...
Just have faith in me.
Aren't you tired of that?
All you ever do to me is giving.
You never received anything in return.
All I am to you is a burden.
Haven't you had enough of that?
I sure have.
But marrying Jo Minwoo... No way.
Why?
Because I...
don't want you to marry.
If you do it this way it's 10, 35, 45.
The answer is right there
under your eyes if you do.
Got it?
Lee Gangmo.
Do you like me or something?
Hey...
Think you're that pretty?
I only like girls with pretty faces.
Gangmo...
What can we do now?
What can I do?
The morning air sure
feels tense around here...
Jeongshik. Did you do something
to upset your father again?
Honey.
What did he do this time?
Just eat your breakfast.
Chairman.
Chairman, this is serious.
Your daughter...
Aigoo... What now...
Jeongyeon what?
She's not in her room.
Did she ever have breakfast
together with us?
That's not what I mean.
Go look for yourself.
Her wardrobe is all over the place,
so she... must have run away.
What?
Jeongyeon ran away?!
~ West Sea Lodge ~
Ganghwa-Gun, Gyeonggi Province
It's pretty.
I like it.
But didn't you already get engaged?
One thing led to another, and I still
didn't get the chance to propose properly.
I'll make it official today.
Hangang Hotel, come on out, quick!
Thank you. Quick.
Hurry up.
Quick.
That guy... He looks familiar?!
All right!
~ West Sea Lodge ~
The sea smells nice.
Hey... Did you want to
keep all this for yourself?
What's with that look?
Do you know how hard
finding you has been?
Agasshi.
Don't call me that.
I don't ever want
to hear you call me that.
There still must be a bus going back.
Let go!
I'm not going back.
Hey... Hwang Jeongyeon.
The room is larger than I thought?!
- And the owner seems really nice...
- Why are you so immature?
I'm wanted by the police.
Stay with me and you'll be
in danger as well, can't you get it?
And so what?
As if you didn't go
through hell because of me.
Why can't I do the same?
Just go back.
Forget it.
I expected you to react this way.
You must go back.
- I'm not going home!
- You really!
I missed you, Gangmo.
I missed you.
So much I couldn't take it anymore.
I really missed you.
Ohh... You're back?
Have a seat. You must be hungry.
Must be because we're right next
to the sea, but fish is really cheap.
Don't really know what it'll taste like.
Take the first bus
back to Seoul in the morning.
The owner gave us some kimchi as well.
Go ahead and taste it.
How is it?
Any good?
It is?! It's got to be.
Might have only learned
over the maid's shoulders,
but I've got an eye for this.
Consider this an honor, it's the
first time I personally cook something.
Take it easy!
You'll get indigestion.
Aww... Salty...
Stop eating it, it's too salty.
I said stop it.
Isn't it salty to you?
Who made this for me?
If I add some water and heat it again,
will it get any better?
It's fine.
Aww... So annoying.
Why is it so salty here?
Take a look.
This way.
Hey... Lee Gangmo!
He's still there?!
Who could he be waiting for,
for so long?
That's so sad...
Wipe it.
Ehh... Really...
You made it worse!
Ahh... Right!
The laundry bill.
Excuse me.
For the laundry bill.
Don't you remember last time,
at the police station?
Will you get out of my sight?
Don't be too angry if who
you're waiting for is not coming.
What?
I know from personal experience.
Even those who can't come
will feel anxious.
What are you, trying to rile me up?
What?
You've come...
Let me do it.
Hwang Taeseop, that fella
defied my expectations.
Take good care of him.
But you must never forget that,
the more important the customer,
the more dangerous any
personal attachment will become.
I feel no such sentiment for him.
Same goes for your daughter.
If she will one day inherit the company,
she must remain nothing but a customer.
I will keep it in mind.
Are you sleeping?
No.
You don't have enough blankets, I bet?
Use these.
We were just fine...
It will be too hard on your backs.
Aigoo... She sure is pretty.
It's good to be young...
Aren't you going to sleep?
You go ahead.
Gangmo.
Hurry up and sleep.
You need to catch
the first bus tomorrow.
I can't forgive my family
for what they did to you.
So what are you going to do?
I'll spend the
rest of my life with you.
Whichever path you take.
Wake up, Hwang Jeongyeon!
You're about to get married.
No... I'm not marrying Jo Minwoo.
I couldn't possibly do that now.
And that's because of you, Gangmo.
What are you, pitying me?
Just because I was accused
of murder instead of Jeongshik?
I have no use for your compassion,
so take the first bus in the morning.
Must have been when I was little.
When I realized that
everyone had a mother,
except me.
It was then that I started
looking over my shoulders.
Thinking that,
if I did so, my mother
could be looking at me.
But...
You know that I've picked up
that habit once again?
When I turn back,
you should be there looking at me.
When I call your name,
you should appear right away.
But I can't find you
no matter where I look.
I just thought...
I thought it was just making me
uncomfortable, or something.
But that wasn't the reason.
Just like when I realized
I didn't have a mother,
it was as if...
my entire heart was
suddenly taken away from me.
Hey... Hwang Jeongyeon...
You like me, too.
You're in love with me too, you silly!
No.
I have never been attracted
to you, not even once.
Gangmo...
I merely wanted to
impress the chairman!
Because you and I are just friends.
This is the very first time...
you lie to me.
Stop fooling yourself!
So you think I was in love with you?!
Why, don't you know that such sentiments
are nothing but a luxury to me?
I just wanted to succeed.
That is all.
Are we clear?
I will soon leave this country.
So, from here on in,
stop bothering me.
You idiot!
What am I supposed to do?
Stop making me suffer so much!
It's driving me crazy...
I can't take it anymore!
You fool...
Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon...
I will get going.
Listen.
Tell Jeongyeon we need to meet today.
There are so many
preparations for the wedding,
how could she just ignore it all
without showing up once?
Think bringing in a working daughter-in-law
would be that easy to deal with?
Don't get me started.
Jeongyeon...
I just feel like she's looking
down on us, that's why I'm upset.
It's not that.
Look at him.
Aigoo... Already taking her side...
Let me handle it.
Did you find her?
I even asked all her school friends,
but nobody had a clue.
Even if you get your
entire team on it, find her,
and file a missing report
with the police.
The police?!
I get goosebumps
just hearing that name,
why would you bother with them?
What if Jeongyeon went
looking for Lee Gangmo?
What?
Hey...
Aren't we losing ourselves
in wild conjecture?
If my father learns of this,
it's all over.
Call them right now... Do it!
Ehh... You really...
That temper...
All right.
Is it true you'll join the
by-election race as an independent?
Is there anything wrong with that?
The opposition candidate
is no pushover.
With majority in Congress
depending on a handful of votes,
why would you enter the race and
hog votes, messing up the whole thing?
I'm not merely joining this race
to disturb opponents, but to win it.
Will you really keep this up?
Didn't you hear me asking you for a little
patience until the next recommendation?
You were the first not to live up
to your end of the bargain.
Look, Director Jo!
Seems like you're banking
on Chairman Hwang Taeseop,
but he can't go on much longer
funding you every step of the way.
As you're well aware, the estate
market is scraping the bottom.
Not to mention the expenses
for their subway construction,
so he'll soon run out of options.
That's not for you to be worried about.
I didn't say I'm worried,
but merely pointing out
how things really stand.
If you'll excuse me, I'll get going.
Director Min will soon be here.
Let's deal with this here and now!
That fella...
He really refuses to listen.
Don't tell me you're leaving already?
Where are you hiding Lee Gangmo?
Those who helped
him escape were pros.
Think I don't know
you were behind this?
Listen...
Forget all the rest, how about letting
fair play dominate these elections?
Hearing that from you
makes me even more suspicious.
We must get our hands on
Lee Gangmo before the elections.
We're using everything
at our disposal to find him.
Look at every port in the country.
What?
If what I suspect is true,
he will try to smuggle
himself out of the country.
Sm...Smuggle?!
Discreetly open a cooperative
investigation with the police.
Once you find smuggling brokers,
you will surely get
to the bottom of this.
All right, Director.
- Hello?
- It's me, Hyung.
How did it go?
Hong Kong?!
There is a boat
headed for Hong Kong.
I'll soon get you
a spot there, so get ready.
All right, Hyung.
Will you marry me?
All right.
Stop!
Ehh... You silly fool.
If we were going to break up anyway,
should at least have not hurt her.
Ahh... You idiot.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
On The Next Episode of
~ GIANT ~
- Where is Seongmo?
- He went to Incheon Port.
Jeongyeon can't come with you.
Hwang Taeseop and
Jo Pilyeon were responsible...
for our father's death.
Find from which port a boat
headed for Hong Kong is leaving.
So you're suggesting
he's smuggling himself out?
It's foolproof evidence.
Did you know Lee Gangmo
had land in his name?
We must get our hands on that land.
Kill Lee Gangmo.
Leave revenge to me.
There's no need
for you to get involved.
I'll avenge what they did my own way.
By destroying Manbo Construction.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com