This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
- Episode 36 -
Dad.
You did it.
We can protect our company now.
Chairman Hwang.
Mom...
I'm fine.
Everything is fine.
I'm all right.
Who is Oh Namsuk?
You're under investigation for fraud
and forgery of private documents.
Mom... Mom!
Mom!
Ahh... Let go! Mom!
What?
Hwang Taeseop showed up
at the shareholders' meeting?!
Yes.
Mister Kim just called me.
He said all our plans failed.
Who's behind this...
Who brought Hwang Taeseop there?
There's no time to wait.
Minwoo, that fool...
As if things weren't bad enough...
- Go get Minwoo right away.
- Calm down, Sir.
Just because of a damned woman,
he ruins all the work we put into this?
I'm not going to let him
get away with this.
If Chairman Hwang has recovered,
then the land we sold
could get us in trouble.
Chief Moon, you leave the
company and lie low for a while.
Once I become chairman,
then you can come back.
So I hear Chairman
Hwang Taeseop has come back?!
Are we finally waking up?
It's all thanks to you.
With his return, he made
all our efforts useless.
Even the secret fund we
gathered will do us no good.
You don't need to worry.
I'll become chairman of
Manbo Construction as planned.
Do you have any plan?
It's really a relief that you were
handling the president's secret fund.
If you need any help, just tell me.
Manbo Construction's
term drafts will soon be up.
Help me make sure
their checks start bouncing.
Want to force them
to file for bankruptcy?
If we resume construction on those
Songpa apartments when I become chairman,
we'll easily deal with
that amount of bad debt.
All right.
You should have gotten
a hold of yourself a lot earlier.
Don't get any illusions.
Because it's not for you,
but all for my sake.
And...
for Miju as well.
You still have feelings for that...
I'll find her.
Even if I have to search
the entire world to do so,
I will find her.
Fine.
I'll be waiting for good news.
If you hadn't done that at the end,
we wouldn't be here.
You should have been more careful...
I did all I could...
Forget it, forget it.
What shall we do when we're out?
- I know this nice place...
- Can't you keep quiet?
- What's with her?
- What?!
What did this old broad just say?
Shut your mouth.
Did you rent the damned place?
Ignorant brats...
Ignorant?!
Should I give you a taste
of how ignorant my fists are?
Ahh... What...
What is wrong with you?
I mean...
Let's be honest...
You should show some etiquette
and respect public morality.
Etiquette?!
Why, was respecting etiquette
what got you here?
Enough with all this commotion!
Oh Namsuk, come out.
You have a visit.
Uh?
You...
I fell for your tricks
hook, line and sinker, didn't I?
You brought all this upon yourself.
You still refuse to admit your faults?
I got myself a lawyer.
And once the investigation
is over, I'll be out.
He says the worst they can give me
for forging that document is a fine?!
It's a divorce application.
What?
Divorce?!
Dad says he wants to
break off this marriage.
Fine.
What will he give me as alimony?
The house in your name,
and the company shares you still have.
If this were up to me, I would
have even gone through a lawsuit...
to take away everything you have
down to the last penny,
but looks like my father
thought otherwise.
Once you're out,
divorce procedures will begin.
I've already lost all interest myself.
So he's asking for a divorce?
It's exactly what I wanted.
Thank you for settling it so quickly.
Fine...
All the better.
It's much better this way.
Thank... you.
Gyeongok.
Thanks.
Dad!
They told us a hospital in the
States could help you fully recover.
Is that really true?
Yes.
The doctor says he'll recommend
him to a specialist clinic.
I will escort you there.
Let me come with you, Chairman.
- Yangsuri Public... -
- Yangsuri Public
Cemetery, Lee Daesoo -
Jeongyeon.
Gangmo...
What?
Lee Gangmo...
Building the foundations was
more problematic than I expected,
but now that I got it all settled,
everything will go smoothly from now on.
Solid foundations are the key
behind a strong and reliable building.
Don't worry too much about
deadlines and focus on quality first.
Yes.
Quick... Get moving.
Aigoo... You!
You'll end up falling again!
Why can't you lift this?
Aigoo... Really...
I'll help you out with it.
Wh...What?!
But... P...President...
It's all right...
Here, quick...
What...
President.
What are you waiting for?
Even the president is doing it...
Ahh... I'm wearing a suit today...
Director Park,
what are you doing? Come.
Director, my ass.
I'll get all filthy this way.
Give me the cleanest one...
Not this! That one over there.
I've heard...
the chairman's rehab is going well.
And how did you find out?
I myself was told of my father's
rehab only recently.
Anyhow, congrats.
For protecting his post
and Manbo Construction as well.
I need to go back to the site.
What did you want to talk about?
My father...
told me to give you this.
- Yangsuri Public Cemetery, Lee Daesoo -
Can I ask who this Lee Daesoo is?
No... No need to know.
Dad will soon leave for the States.
He's going to get treatment there.
I just...
thought you should know.
Where are we going?
What's this?
We'll only know when we get there.
- Lee Daesoo -
It's Dad.
We found him, Hyung.
Dad...
Dad!
You were here?
I'm...
your favorite pest, Gangmo.
Dad...
Dad.
Remember what you told me,
right before you died?
You said that to protect one's family,
the most important thing is courage.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I...
couldn't protect Mom.
And I had to send our
youngest Junmo to a foster family.
I deserve all the blame.
Scold me for it, Dad!
It wasn't Gangmo's fault, Dad.
I'm the only one to blame.
It was all because of me, Dad...
I apologize, Dad...
It's all my fault...
Dad...
I wish Miju could have learned of this.
We'll have to take her along next time.
Dad will love to see her.
So Chairman Hwang took care of
Dad's graveyard all this time?
On the day he was assaulted,
I got a call from him.
He said I'd get to meet
a very welcome person.
There is nothing that will
earn him my forgiveness,
after what he did to our father.
For my sake, Jeongyeon
put everything on the line.
She gave up her family,
her ambitions and everything else.
Just to be together, she was
following me into the pits of hell.
- Gangmo...
- And the same person,
is now being devoured by her
desire to get revenge against me.
The one responsible for that...
is none other than me.
I know we must
avenge our father, Hyung.
But I... I...
No need to say it.
You just forget about revenge.
Just focus on making
Hangang Construction succeed.
You have every right to do so, Gangmo.
Dad...
Let me ask you just one thing.
Was Gangmo the one
who's been looking after you?
All this time, was he
the one who took care of you?
Jeongyeon.
You... misunderstood.
Gangmo saved my life.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you telling me that...
he wasn't the one who assaulted you?
And the only reason we were
able to protect our company...
was thanks to Gangmo's help.
Before I leave for the States,
I want to see Gangmo.
The man who did that to my father...
Lee Gangmo, I know it was you.
You're free to think whatever you want.
Since my goal is and will always be
defeating Manbo Construction.
Hand Hangang Construction to me.
Do you know what my dream is?
And you want to trample on that?
Because...
the sole fact that someone
like you shares my same dream...
is too hard to bear.
Gangmo...
How could we end up like this?
It's so foolish.
Why didn't you...
just hate me all the way?
Then, at least,
I could have pretended
to hate you as well.
I'm sorry, Gangmo...
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
What can we do, Gangmo?
Eonni!
Ahh... I'm so hungry!
Let's go have lunch, shall we?
- Get moving!
- Why? Can't we stay here?
Dad wants to see you.
I have no reason to see him.
I've heard everything from him.
I'll neither say thank you,
nor that I'm sorry.
Because it would only
make it worse for you.
- I don't know what he told you, but...
- Don't you worry.
I'll never let Jo Pilyeon and his son...
take Manbo Construction away from me.
Isn't that what you wish for?
For me to get the
company back on its feet,
and compete with you fair and square.
Dad... Gangmo is here.
Gangmo.
I...
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Can you forgive me for what I did?
Your father...
Daesoo.
That fool...
was like a brother to me.
I let Jo Pilyeon deceive me,
and just stared while he
was killing my dearest friend.
If to pay for what I did...
I'll have to spend the
rest of my days in this state,
I will have no complaints.
Gangmo.
If you don't... No.
If I don't earn your forgiveness,
my life will no
longer have any meaning.
Please...
Please forgive me,
Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Go to the States...
and come back fully recovered.
Thanks...
Thank you!
It's all over for me now.
I'm done.
Jeongshik.
You don't know how things are
going on in the company, right?
Couldn't care less about that anymore.
Manbo Construction...
will soon file for
preliminary bankruptcy.
What?!
Bankruptcy?!
Their main bank will
soon turn its back on them.
In no time, our company shares
will be worth nothing.
Minwoo...
Then...
What should we do?
Before stock prices get any worse,
sell all the shares
you and your mother have left.
Sell our shares?!
Not long ago, I had
a meeting with the boys.
Geosan Auto, Daeyang Trading,
Hanguk Group, Dongguk Bank.
They're all sons of tycoons.
Why, did they promise
they'd buy our shares?
They told me they'll invest in us.
I'll buy those shares for them.
You... You're not telling me...
this is all to get your hands on
Manbo Construction, are you?
Haven't you just heard the
company is about to go belly up?
I'm putting everything on the line here!
And they merely got fooled
into investing thanks to me.
Ever since I joined the company,
I've given my all for its sake.
It's my last resort to make sure...
Manbo Construction doesn't disintegrate.
After preliminary bankruptcy,
there will be a second and third filing...
By then, there will be no hope.
So before things get worse,
talk with your mother,
and I really suggest
you sell those shares.
Chairman.
I wish you a full recovery, Sir.
Thank you.
Get back to us as
strong as ever, Chairman.
Chairman Hwang... Fighting.
All right.
We'll be waiting for you, Chairman.
No need to come to the airport.
No... I'll see Dad out.
Director!
Director.
What's the matter?
What is it about?
It's nothing...
Just like you said,
I'd better let you two go.
I'll leave Dad to your care.
Don't you worry, Jeongyeon.
Dad.
Don't worry about the company,
and come back to us fully recovered.
All right.
We wish you the best, Chairman.
What do you mean...
Our checks are bouncing?!
Our main lender Goryeo Bank
has refused any loan extensions.
And why, all of a sudden?
We don't know the details yet,
but we suspect it might be
because the construction was halted.
Get the car.
I must meet the
bank president right away.
Yes, Director.
Before that,
deal with today's drafts.
All right, Director.
President!
What is going on?
Why are our checks bouncing?
Don't you know what's happening with
your company better than anyone?
- President!
- I'm busy now.
President...
President! Just a moment...
Give me just a moment...
Once they learned their main
bank turned its back on them,
everyone else started
bouncing their checks.
If this keeps up,
they'll soon be filing
for preliminary bankruptcy.
And Manbo Construction's
stocks will continue to crash.
Jo Minwoo is not going
to lose this opportunity.
Keep any buying trends in check.
All right.
I apologize, I'm a little late.
Don't even mention it, President.
Ahh... Let me introduce them.
These are my investors.
Is Chairman Lee doing well?
Yes.
You already knew each other?
We sure do.
Here's the second heir of Geosan Auto.
And here is Daeyang Trading's.
I see you've chosen quite the investors.
Then, I'll get straight to the point.
We'd like some tips regarding
a takeover of Manbo Construction.
Are you planning to
take over the company?
Of course.
Sir...
- Hwang Jeongyeon...
- Is she still here?
Please give me your help, Sir.
I'm not engaging in charity.
You may leave.
Once the construction resumes,
everything will go back to normal.
- If you could only help us until...
- Gyeongok.
Our guest is leaving.
But, Sir...
Are you deaf as well?
I'll try to convince him.
I'm counting on you.
Someone must be behind all this.
Are you saying that someone
might be orchestrating this?
If such weren't the case,
things wouldn't escalate so quickly.
If only to safeguard our
investment in Manbo Construction,
we can't just sit and stare
while this happens, Sir.
I've already sold them all.
What?
A few days ago,
I got a call from the bank.
Knowing this would happen,
I already sold all our shares.
Sir...
If only for my sake and
everything I've done for you,
help me out just this once.
The reason I could endure
all this time under you...
was the hope that I could
one day help my daughter.
If you really have your
daughter's future at heart,
give up on Manbo Construction.
If what you want is
for your daughter to succeed,
throw her into the pits of hell,
and let her escape from
those flames on her own.
Sir...
Think that helping her out this time
would make things any better for her?
You shouldn't catch fish for her,
but just teach her how to fish!
If I'm not mistaken about her,
that Jeongyeon will only get
stronger when put under pressure.
I have no intention of
helping Manbo Construction.
And I'm not sure I like that cheap
compassion you're throwing at her feet...
just because you're her mother!
If I made myself clear,
then you may leave.
Yes.
It's me, Jeongshik.
Have you talked it out
with your mother?
All right.
You made the right decision.
Let's meet at the Hangang
Hotel coffeehouse tomorrow.
Don't forget your seal.
Chief Moon.
Looks like we might need to
use our secret fund very soon.
Get the money ready.
Yes, all right.
Here... Let's have a drink.
But, tell me.
Work must be killing you these days,
I'm sure you didn't gather us all
here just for a few tasty bites?
Actually, I have a
favor to ask you all.
See, what did I tell you?
Personal favors, all right!
Help Manbo Construction
resume its apartment project.
Ahh... President Lee,
again with that favor?
I see witnessing Chairman Hwang
being assaulted made you weak.
Manbo Construction's collapse
would damage the entire sector.
I'll be counting on you.
Aigoo... Looks like you
haven't heard the news.
Manbo Construction filed for
preliminary bankruptcy today.
According to the news
coming from the bank,
it looks like Chief Jo Minwoo
will soon begin a takeover.
Then, what?
Jo Pilyeon interfered with the construction
to put his son in charge of the company?
That's the only plausible explanation.
Hey... The meat will burn.
There are people willing to
invest in Manbo Construction.
What?!
They came here with me,
would you like to meet them?
Tell them to come in.
You've met them before, right?
They're my investors.
That'll be enough to
cover tomorrow's drafts.
What they're asking for is Chairman
Hwang's unconditional resignation,
including forfeiting all the
company shares in his possession.
Of course,
the vacant post of chairman...
will be entrusted to me,
considering my 30-percent holdings.
It's one of their conditions as well.
Thirty percent?!
You're telling me you had almost
one-third of all company shares?
Just a check and
you'll find out for yourself.
Will you accept our conditions?
Take until tomorrow to
decide, and let us know.
We'll be waiting.
Jo Minwoo!
Go ahead first.
I thought there wasn't
anything left to say?!
I am well aware...
that the ones stopping our
apartment construction...
are you and your father.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
This is all you can do.
What?
You can neither
beat me nor Lee Gangmo.
Before you resent us for that,
blame your own capabilities.
It's not...
It's not over yet.
Can you find
five billion won by tomorrow?
Ahh...
4.5 billion the day after,
and after that...
End of the line, I'm afraid.
The only thing left is for you
to get out of the picture.
No...
No way...
I'm not done yet.
You won't take it from me.
I won't let you.
I'm not losing to you.
By tomorrow, Manbo Construction
will fall into Jo Minwoo's hands.
Are you just going to take it lying down?
You're the only one
who can save Jeongyeon.
You know that.
Baekpa opposes it.
You gave birth to Jeongyeon!
You're...
the mother she spent
all that time looking for.
Is that...
Is that not enough for you?
If he opposes it,
there is nothing I can do!
I'll pledge Hangang Construction
to him as collateral.
Use that to save Jeongyeon.
Go tell him yourself.
He'll probably kick you out
without blinking once!
I'll take care of Jeongyeon.
Lee Gangmo.
You have no right or need to do this!
Yes, you're right.
To Jeongyeon, I mean nothing.
What's this...
Did you come here looking for me?
So the company is going bankrupt?
Is there anything
you don't know about me?
Don't know if I like that?
I'll only have
three of these and leave.
Should I explain to you the reason,
or tell you a way to get out of it?
All right.
The both of them would be better.
You used to play in the dirt
back when you were little, right?
And?
The stronger your grip on that mud,
the easier that desire will make
all the mud fall out of your hands.
That's the reason you failed.
From the very start,
you had a far too strong grip
on things which weren't yours,
things which never suited you.
You should just let go
of all that instead.
You want me...
to give up on Manbo Construction?
That's right.
If you get hold of something else,
you'll make something much bigger out of it.
So never look back.
Only one left.
Shall I let you in
on what you could do?
Grow stronger.
They won't steal it from you,
you will let them have it.
Let those greedy beasts have it.
Keep your chin up, and look
at them straight in the eyes.
And...
proudly bid them farewell.
Just like someone who
rid herself of all her burdens.
Now matter how wronged
or angry you feel,
don't give them the
pleasure of a single tear.
I know how all that feels.
How some things
are taken away from you,
but others are just given away.
I've had my three shots,
so I guess it's time to go?!
It's not the end for you,
you're starting anew.
Ours...
Ours is an ill-fated relationship.
Just thought you were
forgetting that for a minute.
How are you?
Good morning.
- Manbo Construction Takeover Ceremony -
Without further ado,
I ask Hwang Jeongyeon and Jo Minwoo
to sign the takeover agreement.
First, Miss Hwang Jeongyeon.
Mister Jo Minwoo as well.
With company shareholders
bearing witness,
both sides have signed
the takeover agreement.
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon will
now give her farewell speech.
I...
pride myself on having done my very best
for Manbo Construction's development.
I might be leaving this company,
but on behalf of my father,
former chairman Hwang Taeseop...
I believe this place he devoted
his passion and youth for...
will be protected by the new chairman
and you shareholders to the very end.
I enjoyed this experience.
Our Manbo Construction has had to
suffer plenty of difficulties over time.
You have my word.
Not only we will become
top of the sector at home,
but to truly make
this a global corporation,
I will spare no effort.
Enjoy this ovation
while it lasts, Jo Minwoo.
As in the end, it will turn into the most
painful grief you'll ever experience.
Congratulations!
This is just the beginning.
This Hwang Taeseop
and his Manbo Construction...
are going to reach the very top
of the construction business.
Dad...
I'm sorry.
I lost Manbo Construction.
Your dream of a lifetime...
was ruined because of me.
I'm sorry, Dad...
You really looked great
at the farewell speech today.
What do you plan to do from now on?
I don't know.
Nothing really comes to mind.
What do you think
a 100-won bill could buy you?
Know how much a bus token costs?
Never bought fish at
the market before, have you?
People who dealt with
tens of billions at once...
would never understand how scary
ten, a hundred won can be.
They might make ten billion
through a corporation,
but couldn't possibly earn even
a thousand won on their own.
You know what they call a mountain of
coins devouring those ten billions?
That's private lending.
- Private...
- If you're interested, come look for me.
But there is something
you must bear in mind first.
The fact that you must completely abandon
your past life as a chairman's daughter...
from head to toe.
Stand at the very bottom,
and a cloud of dust will assault you.
Once you've gone through all that,
that's when you'll finally
earn your first coin.
If you're not prepared
to go through that,
don't even bother looking for me.
- Gaepo Apartment Completion Ceremony -
1... 2... 3!
- Manbo Construction -
Saudi Arabia Highway Project
- Democratic Justice Party's Jo Pilyeon -
Wins Gangnam Congress Race
Who are they? Stop them!
Gangmo...
- 1986 -
Eonni!
Eonni!!
It's a letter from the States!
My beloved daughter, Jeongyeon.
The Yankee doctor here...
told me that I'm just fine now,
so I can finally stop pestering him.
It's been hard for you, hasn't it?
Who cares if all we lost is a company?!
Jeongyeon.
Don't you worry about a thing.
Dad.
Forget everything else,
but if I forgot even for a
second how much I owe you,
I'd be no better than a dog.
I'll make it up to you.
All the sins I committed against you,
and everything you did for me.
It's to make up for those things
that I didn't die and recovered.
Gyeongok.
Congrats on your promotion, Hyung.
That's that,
but I'm worried about Miju.
We should have
stopped her when we could.
If I only think of all the hardships
she must be going through with that baby...
Our Miju is smart,
so everything will be fine.
We'll soon find her, Gangmo.
It's been four years already, four!
Manbo Construction's chairman
is searching for someone,
do I really need to wait all this long?
I apologize, Chairman.
Even asking for
the police's cooperation...
If it doesn't work,
get me the damned Chief of Police.
Even if they have to search all over
this country, they must find her!
All right, Chairman.
Lee Miju...
You really...
Miju...
Please, show up before me.
- Come on in, Deputy.
- Long time no see.
Ahh... That's nice.
When did you take over this place?
Looks like you were the
only one who didn't know?
Let's have a seat.
Aigoo... Girls, there's no time.
Hey... She's still not here?
N...No... Not yet.
How can a replacement be so late?
Who introduced her to us?
She's here!
Our replacement is here.
Really? There's no time,
so get her changed right away.
- Hurry and send her up!
- Yes!
We thank all our esteemed guests for
gracing our Bagdad with their presence.
Tonight's opening act...
is famous star...
Nabi!
Or at least that was the case until
something came up, and she couldn't come.
But let me introduce a great newcomer
who will stir up the scene like no other!
Give her an applause!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I think it's time to make
her go through a little test.
About that new singer
we saw last time...
She really left an impression.
Isn't the area full of rocky mountains?
And who's going to do it?
Let's just throw
everything we have at it.
If we go for it to the end,
we'll find a way.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com