Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 51
Wooju, are you back?
Wooju, see you tomorrow.
Chairman.
It's that kid.
Establish a support fund for the
kindergarten that kid is frequenting.
You want to help his kindergarten?
I'll have to take a closer look at that boy.
I understand what you mean, Chairman.
Yes.
Ahh... Yes.
What can I do for you, Reporter Kim?
Cha Soojeong's real name is Lee Miju.
That kid named Wooju is her son for sure.
Let's talk face to face.
I'll call you again.
This is serious, Chairman.
Reporter Kim from Celeb Daily has
learned that Lee Miju is that kid's mother.
How shall we proceed?
Tell him to come to our offices.
I will meet him firsthand.
But Chairman, if he begins suspecting
any possible connection between you two...
If Miju's kid turns out to be...
I must settle this on my own.
Do as instructed.
All right, Chairman.
You still haven't dealt with that reporter?
I did try to get in touch a few times,
but he refuses to meet, so...
And you even try to make excuses now?
I apologize.... Director.
Keep calling him until he agrees
to meet tonight at the Royal Club.
Yes. I will.
I see you've got yourself quite a scoop.
How do you plan to proceed?
I'll keep digging into it a
little deeper, and then publish it.
Director Moon.
How much money did we invest in
the apartments Miss Cha is advertising?
If we add the New City apartments
which are under development,
I'd say over ten billion won in total.
You know that Celeb
Daily's president Jo Cheolyeon...
is a distant relative of my father, right?
Ahh... Is that so?
So go ahead and write that
article about Cha Soojeong.
Instead, any damages
we might incur in the process...
will have to be dealt
with by President Jo himself.
What?
Then, why don't you
just change your model...
Are you suggesting we change our
marketing strategy based on groundless rumors?
That is not what I meant...
I leave the judgment to you.
It's time for our meeting.
What's wrong with Chairman Jo?
Why obsess over someone with such
a troubled background like Cha Soojeong...
I'm just telling you
this for your own sake,
but I suggest you leave it at that.
I've heard from Manager Park.
So there appear to be strange
rumors spreading about Soojeong?
The reason I invited you here....
You don't need to worry.
Since I no longer plan to write that article.
You've made the right decision.
- Because if you wrote about such groundless rumors...
- Miss Cha?
You've found yourself
quite the remarkable sponsor.
What are you trying to say?
Thank you for the drinks.
What's that supposed to mean?
Sponsor?!
I have no idea.
He's officially registered as son
of a certain Kang Jeongja,
but she is way too old to have children.
- Kang Wooju -
Seongmo.
What brings you here, Congressman?
I had an appointment with Director Kim.
Everything is fine, I hope?
I might have lost a
little attachment for the force,
but I'm trying to patch up the wounds.
If you have the time,
go pay Minwoo a visit.
I can't get in touch with him,
and I get the feeling
he's trying to avoid me.
Isn't he past that age already?
It's because of that Lee Miju.
We should have cut
her off for good back then...
I know how busy you are, but
keep Minwoo in check for me.
What will he meet the director for?
The director went
to Busan in the morning.
What?
I'm sure he came to meet Chief Oh.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes, Chief.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm new recruit Ji Yeonsoo.
I've been assigned under your
command for the next five months.
Ohh... So it was you.
Starting with this round,
every agent ranked section chief and
above will be assigned recruits for training.
So you take care of her, Chanseong.
I'm well aware of your reputation, Chief.
I hope I can count on your help, Sir!
Start by fixing
the way you address me.
Are we in the army?
Yes! S...ir...
One more thing.
Don't talk too much.
I can't stand that.
Yes, Chief...
As you've seen,
we couldn't really find anything suspicious.
The way I see it,
all this feels unnatural.
That entire event is suspicious in itself.
Explain yourself.
The host of that event
was this Hwang Jeongyeon.
She's the daughter of Hwang
Taeseop, who's eying an entrance into politics.
They never planned
to invite politicians there.
But for some unknown reason,
the situation suddenly changed.
And something else which doesn't compute...
is those opposition party members.
These are the same people who called the
Olympics an excuse to prolong the regime's lifespan,
and now they just participate
in an event in support of it?!
Of course, Hwang
Jeongyeon convinced them.
All those opposition party members
were actually supposed to be in Busan,
for a major demonstration which
would take place the day after.
So all that those CCTV
cameras caught on tape...
Was a show someone
orchestrated from behind the scenes.
And you were the
ones who fell into their trap.
And you're suggesting that
Hwang Jeongyeon is behind all this.
Can't say... It's still too
early to jump to conclusions.
Then, who? Hwang Taeseop?
Here's Lee Gangmo.
He's the president
of Hangang Construction.
He is extremely tenacious
and quick on his feet.
Not to mention daring.
And what would a businessman
gain from getting involved in all this?
He bears a grudge against me.
Of course that alone can't prove anything,
but if anyone is capable of
orchestrating all this from behind the scenes,
he's without a doubt our best bet.
So dig into him.
Since you're there, add Hwang Jeongyeon.
You'll be surprised to see the results.
I'll give that a try.
And I'm sure you'll also handle
Lee Seongmo as discussed?
Don't worry about that.
I've already proceeded in that direction.
How is Miju?
Why?
You know, last time at the
Royal Club with Jo Minwoo...
It really felt like they loved each other.
Miju knows that our father
died because of Jo Pilyeon.
- It's getting late.
- Gangmo.
- Sorry for being late.
- No worries.
Jeongyeon, let me introduce the daughter of
Chairman Cheon of Gwangmyeong Construction.
I'm Cheon Suyeon.
I'm Hwang Jeongyeon.
I've heard a lot about
you from President Lee.
So you're good friends?
Yes.
You must be busy, so should
I get straight to the point?
I'd like to invest two hundred million.
Here's the contract.
Give it a read.
I'll just trust Gangmo and
invest without any questions.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll have to take responsibility.
Fine with me.
I guarantee you this
investment won't disappoint you.
Really?
But... I guess you just
came from the boiler factory?
What?
There...
Use this to wipe it.
It's all right, later.
Let me do it.
How can a president go
around with that on his shirt?
Miju knows that our father
died because of Jo Pilyeon.
My father is really interested in
this boiler development, too.
If you're successful with your project,
he plans to use those boilers in his apartments.
I'll have to give him a call, then?
Excuse me.
Please tell President Lee Gangmo that I
had to leave because of another appointment.
Yes, I will.
Water has started boiling here,
is it still all right on your side?
Don't you worry about me,
and focus on your side.
Yes.
Director Yang!
Director Yang, are you all right?
Is anyone out there?
Come help us!
Director Yang... Director Yang!
Anyone?
Come on in.
How did it happen?
It was an accident.
Suddenly the valve's lid just...
What did the doctors say?
Thankfully it's not life-threatening,
but what now?
Now we'll suffer delays in our development.
The important thing now is
for Director Yang to fully recover.
Then we can forget about
completing development on time?
For the time being, you take
over the construction site, Shideok.
Gangmo, and you?
Him and I will focus on the boiler.
It's no use.
Even a technician like him can't
solve it, how are we supposed to do it?
We'll just have to keep trying.
We can't just keep lying idle.
Ahh... Told you we should have had a ceremony
when we first acquired the company.
It's not only innovative for our
domestic market, but worldwide.
It was completed a lot
earlier than I imagined.
A lot of the merit
should go to Mister Kim here.
I have high expectations for the future.
Right... We learned that there
was an accident at the Beaute factory.
Really?
Their technical director was seriously injured,
so they'll suffer substantial delays as a result.
It seems that it'll be virtually impossible
for them to develop their boiler on time.
We will begin a huge advertising campaign
in concomitance with the apartment sale.
Pay special attention to avoid any leaks.
All right, Chairman.
Chairman, I think we should go.
Here's our section manager.
I already heard the details.
So you'll fix our playground free of charge?
Our chairman has a vested
interest in marketing for children.
Thank you, Manager.
Can I take a look around?
Certainly.
What?
Help me up, please.
I need to wash my hands.
What's the matter, Chairman?
- Kang Wooju -
You remember me?
I helped you get your
airplane back at the hospital.
And helped you wash your hands.
Tell me...
Where is your father?
Is your father home?
In heaven.
Heaven?!
My Daddy is in heaven.
Ever tried that?
Want me to do that for you?
No.
No?
Only my Daddy can do that.
- Chairman.
- Wow...
Wow... Wooju is the tallest now.
Ahh... Let's go finish what
we were discussing inside.
- Here... Let's go.
- Yes...
Want to ride a plane?
Let's do that.
Really?
- Yes.
- All right.
Is it fun?
We will soon send our employees.
We'll finalize all the details then.
Thank you.
Manager.
Manager?
You must really like children.
Yes.
He's cute.
You only were able to
retrieve 40 percent of the funds this month?
Seems like a significant portion of our
capital has moved towards Noh Gapsoo.
Jong-Ro in particular.
If this keeps up, it's only a matter
of time before we lose all clients there.
Send some of the boys
and check the situation there.
Yes, Director.
What is it?
A guest is waiting for you.
A guest?
Who is that?
How have you been, Director Yoo?
What brings you here?
President Noh Gapsoo sent me here.
He voiced his concerns about you,
saying you might be facing
severe cash flow problems.
And?
If you give up Jong-Ro,
he said he's prepared to help
you with those cash flow issues.
Go tell President Noh.
That if he truly wishes to see my downfall,
he better stop kidding with me
and start fighting for real.
I might not be able to guarantee victory,
but I am pretty confident
that I could cripple him for life.
You know that Madam Oh Namsuk...
died because of you, right?
On her way to meet you,
my mother had a car accident and died.
You and your husband,
along with your daughter, Hwang Jeongyeon.
I'm sure she would have had a
lot to talk about with you all.
But she wasn't able to say a single thing,
and suffered a violent death.
So?
Did you come here to express
your indignation about that?
Not at all.
I actually came here to thank you.
Thank you for finally making a decent
man out of this miserable prick,
Director Yoo Gyeongok.
I never imagined you'd have the
guts to make that report to him.
I said nothing wrong.
How can you be sure that there are no
ruling party members supporting the amendment?
Then, you could have offered a rebuttal.
I don't like your political philosophy.
And what would that be?
Is it not to avoid all
obstacles and go the distance?
You forgot something.
The fact that I never
swim against the tide.
And that "tide" would be made of all the
propaganda bandied about on the street?
That is subjective.
Whether it is right or wrong,
that is up to history to judge.
We're still a long way from reaching
the quorum necessary for the amendment.
Things are proceeding
a lot faster than I imagined.
Have you met with the
opposition party members?
After they verified the account that
day, their attitude completely changed.
If the ruling party does its part,
I think we might succeed.
Now that we got to this point, we must
push ahead and bring it to fruition.
Or else we will all die for it.
So I was wondering...
How about I take care of dealing with the
opposition party from now on?
I think that it will be a
much safer way to proceed.
Why, are you looking to be
recommended by the opposition party,
should you decide to enter politics?
If your target is Jo Pilyeon,
I suppose it would be easier to
go at him from the opposition party.
There is still a lot of work to do,
so I'll refrain from making any
proclamations, if you'll forgive me.
You start drinking without me...
Would it taste as good?
Come on in, Congressman.
I've just heard the
news from Chairman Hwang.
With someone of your
political acumen helping us,
I suddenly feel empowered.
I've been to the Blue House today.
The president seems to be nervous
to an unprecedented extent.
And what I mean is that it could
suddenly lead him to take drastic measures.
So act with the utmost prudence.
This month alone, sales
have increased 140 percent.
140 percent?!
My... What is this...
Come on in.
Is there any particular
model you were looking for?
Yes... I'd like to see these.
Have a seat.
How do they feel?
They're quite comfortable,
and I like the design.
Director Moon.
Yes, Chairman.
Buy all shoes of this size on display.
All right, Chairman.
Right away.
Seonhwa, aren't you hungry?
Right... Let's go eat something.
- Let's go have lunch, then.
- Yes.
What's with him?
He gets on my nerves.
I'll go to the lady's room a moment.
What's wrong with you?
This will not make any difference.
Don't you realize it'll only
make us more uncomfortable?
I found a thing called hope these days.
An ardent wish.
I wanted to tell you that.
Yes...
Ohh... Jeongyeon!
Nah, go ahead.
Really?
Where?
Did you find the
cause of those gas leaks?
Not yet.
How about Jo Minwoo's side?
They stole our core
technology to develop theirs.
But we can catch up to them.
You still have that?
The secret fund account.
Why are you asking?
Honestly, it worries me a little.
If anything had gone wrong at the event...
Sorry, Jeongyeon.
I still feel bad for getting
you involved in all that.
That's not what I meant!
Aren't you finishing it?
I'm done.
You know that I don't eat that much.
I'm full.
Eat...
Have I ever complained
that you eat too much?
Come on.
Would be a waste, wouldn't it?
I think I might have to
go back to the hospital, what do we do?
I can't really drive you home.
What am I, a little girl?
Don't worry about me and
finish developing those boilers.
I'm going.
Who are you?
Answer me!
Look...
Wake up.
Can... Can you...
President Lee!
What now...
President Lee, get a hold of yourself!
The hell is this?
I guess it's data about boilers.
You fool.
What were you doing out there?
I apologize.
He didn't find out who you were, right?
The ANSP?
The way I see it, those
weren't just thieves.
I'm sure it was them.
Then, are you telling me
they already got a hold of this?
I guess they got suspicious after
finding some clues at the event.
All the more reason why
we must remain calm.
For the time being, you two
should remain together at all times.
Yes, President.
You be careful as well.
Yeah.
I'll focus my efforts
on our boiler development.
If they don't find any solid clue,
even the ANSP won't be able to do much.
- Don't get up.
- You're here, President...
How are you feeling?
I'm fine,
but I really have no excuses.
As long as you're alive and well,
we'll always find the time to
complete our boiler development.
But if there are any more
delays, you'll incur heavy losses.
Don't you worry about that,
and focus on recovering.
If the factory manager could still be with us...
It's hair from that kid named Kang Wooju.
How long will it take for those DNA tests?
The research center in Chicago....
said we'd have the
results in about two weeks.
If possible, I'd like it done
in no more than ten days.
I will try to press them.
But if he does turn out to be your son,
how do you plan to proceed?
I'll have to go get him, of course.
- But, Miss Lee Miju...
- I will bring her as well.
What?
If she's indeed the mother of my child,
then be it my father or Lee Gangmo,
nobody will be able to stop me.
I'll protect my family.
So I finally find you.
I had something to give you.
- Boiler Development Daily Report -
It's Beaute Boilers' daily report.
I took it from Lee Gangmo.
I'm sure that it will be
of help, upon closer look.
I see you wasted your time
with something I have no use for.
You have no use for it?!
According to rumors, you're ignoring
business to focus on something else...
Since you're here,
I'll go ahead and tell you.
From here on in, don't
get involved in my business.
What?
Whatever the case,
I will decide and act upon it.
You just focus on your political career.
Minwoo, you...
I'm busy, so if you'll excuse me...
So Minwoo these days is fixing some...
what was it, a kindergarten?
Yes.
That's what his secretaries told me.
The hell got into him?
Come on in.
Have you already talked
with our representatives?
Yes. Please come in.
Yes.
Ajeosshi...
What?
Again with the wooden horse?
No way.
Come on...
I said no.
Happy now?
- Yes.
- All right... Ready...
What on earth is he doing?
Find out who that kid is.
Whose son he is, and why
he's turning him into a raging fool.
Dig up everything you can find.
All right, Congressman.
That boy can't possibly be...
Nah.
There is no way.
Seongmo said Lee Miju got an abortion.
I'm back.
Who is he?
Who the hell is that boy?
Cha Soojeong's.... No.
Lee Miju's son.
Seems that Minwoo stopped
this celeb tabloid writer from...
publishing a scoop about her.
Then... Are you telling
me that he's Minwoo's son?
We still have no research labs
able to verify whether their DNA matches.
Minwoo will surely try to find that out.
Look into it.
Yes, Congressman.
No!
I'll have to first see that kid.
Give it here... It's mine!
Try to get it if you can.
I said it's mine!
You couldn't get it
back, so now it's mine.
Don't cry.
They say crying is like admitting defeat.
All you need to do
is getting it back later.
What are you trying to say, Mom?
Wooju disappeared?!
Mom... Stop crying...
Just call the police station.
I'll head there right away.
How is this one?
If you want anything else, just choose it.
Not stuff for girls like this.
- Follow him.
- Yes.
Wooju!
Kang Wooju!
Wooju.
- Wooju.
- Mommy.
Wooju!
Where have you been?
I told you not to
leave by yourself, didn't I?
You'll have to get scolded.
Will you do that again?
I won't.
Don't you ever do that again, Wooju.
Got it?
Where did you get all this?
Some ajeosshi bought them for me.
Who?
Grandma is worried,
so let's go back home.
But we don't really know whether
that's really Minwoo's son.
It's his.
What?
I'm sure of it.
He looks just like
Minwoo when he was his age.
Then...
That brat gave birth to a child
that should have never been born.
Nobody can find out about him.
The secretary called me, saying Minwoo
contacted a research lab in the US for a DNA test.
Have you found out which research lab it was?
Yes.
I wrote it here.
Seonbaenim, this...
Did you check your brain at the door?
I apologize.
Chanseong.
Yes, Chief.
Take her to the gym.
Yes.
Follow me...
Only ever hold two targets at gunpoint.
The one down at the shooting range,
and your assaulter's chest.
But you dared to point that
gun at a colleague of yours.
If we measured our agents'
aptitude based on points,
that would be grounds for immediate elimination.
I... I will take steps to correct that.
You have ten minutes.
If you manage to take me down
in ten minutes, you'll be forgiven.
Or else, you will voluntarily
leave your current post.
Keep track.
All right.
Ten minutes.
Come get some.
How much time left?
Three minutes.
Heard that?
You only have three minutes to take me down.
Are you giving up?
I don't even know why
you bothered coming here.
But what I'm sure of is that
you're not cut out to be an agent.
Is that clear?
Find yourself another post.
You're out of my office starting now.
I still have time, right?
Y...eah...
So I don't need to leave
your office now, right?
You only told me to take
you down in ten minutes,
you never said anything
about how I should do it.
I'm hungry... Let's go eat.
Chief Lee.
Outside the office, no titles.
Seonbaenim...
And I can tolerate that even less.
Then, what else should I call you?
Don't call me.
I'll settle for "ajeosshi," then.
What?
I'm really sorry for hitting you down there.
If you ever have trouble getting
married because of it, give me a call.
This is good.
Let's call it a day, Chanseong.
Yes.
Hey, newcomer.
Aren't you leaving?
I'll have to turn in this report
and wait for them to examine it.
Good job today, everyone.
Thought she was just a blockhead,
but turns out she's not your ordinary gal?
From the very moment she came here,
I started getting these headaches...
I'll have to meet Gangmo tonight.
For the time being, I suggest you
refrain from visiting your brother.
What do you mean?
The ANSP has been trailing
President Lee for a few days.
Who ordered that?
It comes straight from Chief Oh,
so Jo Pilyeon must be behind it.
Is Gangmo aware of that?
I actually found out from him.
If we claim we completed development
without finding the cause of our leaks,
there's a good possibility they'll
leave us out of the New City project.
It's all because I don't have a clue.
I tried assembling it from scratch a
thousand times, but it is no use.
- Stop stuffing yourself, will you?
- Just checking how they taste.
What's this?
Is it someone's birthday?
Gyeongja prepared all this for us.
See? If it weren't for my Gyeongja,
who would ever worry about me?
Look at your face, President...
Eat all this by yourself and
regain your strength, President.
What the hell...
Then, how about me?
You have hands, so help
yourself or starve.
- Have a seat, President.
- All right, thanks.
Come on, let's all have a seat and eat.
- By the way, Gyeongja.
- Uh?
What's wrong with your face?
It's all because of that damn Park Sotae.
Wh.... What?! Pa... Park Sotae?!
So, what, you like him so much
that all those pimples started popping up?
He only brings me cheap-ass
counterfeit cosmetics...
And because of that, look at my face.
Hey... Look at him. Doesn't all this
look like defective merchandise?
Ehh... Really, I ought to just
throw that goddamned wig...
Think I knew it was all counterfeit stuff?
That sorry-ass son of a
cunt said it was Made in USA,
so I paid him all he asked.
You still have those cosmetics?
Sure! Wanted to try this crap out
on his damned mug, so I kept them.
Here you go.
This is original?!
Right?!
Isn't it? See?
I guess it's too refined for someone's face...
What?
Are you done talking?
Like I said anything wrong.
- I guess your face is not good enough for it.
- You little rat...
What's wrong with him?
That was the reason
behind those gas leaks.
And what would that be?
Gas.
Gas?!
The gas Beaute Boilers used in Europe...
and gas used in Korea are different.
So...
If this is a boiler,
then this would be gas?
Everyone, gather at the factory.
Gangmo! Let's finish this first!
- Gangmo!
- Aigoo, see? He works too damn hard.
Hey! Stop eating, will you?
Move your ass. You still can eat after that?
Ahh... That bowling ball...
Wait... Forgot.
See you.
Your guest is here.
Send him in.
How have you been?
So the man President
Noh sent was you?
Yes, Congressman.
Have a seat.
According to President Noh,
you bear a grudge against Chairman
Hwang, his daughter and Yoo Gyeongok?
Does my bearing a grudge
against them look strange to you?
Nah... That's not what I meant.
At times, blood ties can be a lot
more intense than people can imagine.
I've heard from President
Noh what you're looking for.
So? Would you be able to do that for me?
What you want is something I desire as well.
If you do it, things
might be easier for us all.
I like it.
Instead, I have a request as well.
Tell me.
If you like the way I work,
give me info on all construction
projects around Gangnam,
including the New City one.
You've changed a lot over the years.
I left my soul back in hell.
People can always change.
These days, Chairman Hwang is
meeting with opposition party members.
I'm sure it has to do with
the constitutional amendment.
And if you dig deeper, you'll also
hear of a secret fund account.
I know that Yoo Gyeongok is backing
him, and Hwang Jeongyeon is helping her.
Find out everything regarding that account.
Is that clear?
I understand.
Here... Let's have a drink.
When did you say the conference was?
In three days.
So if we can't finish the boiler by then,
will they exclude us from the selection?
Let's just go at it until the end, uh?
Let's just reassemble it from scratch.
All right.
We can't let them exclude us this way.
We spent so much acquiring this company...
I'll go take a little breather.
He's had it as well, I guess...
No matter what Gangmo says,
this is not going to work.
Is reading a few books
going to help us develop a boiler?
Ahh... If that sorry-ass factory
manager hadn't stolen our technology...
Who's there?
Who are you?
You...
What else are you here
to steal this time?
Here are the schematics for Manbo
Construction's new boiler.
I came in to leave this here in secret...
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Wooju.
Whenever we meet, just call me Daddy.
Promise.
The hell are you looking at, you losers?
I apologize.
You can find your way back home, right?
I can do that.
They're the DNA test results.
Wooju is not your son?!
Hangang Construction will be
added to the list of companies to oust.
Start by stopping his boiler development.
How about you just
set his factory on fire instead?
Whatever I end up
doing, don't resent me.
Because Lee Miju, you
brought this upon yourself.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com