Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 22 -
What are you trying to tell me?
Get rid of Lee Gangmo.
Kill him.
Do it quietly, without
attracting anyone's attention.
With this money, start by
bribing the camp instructor.
I'm sure you know already,
but there are plenty of dead bodies
coming out of the Samcheong camp.
- So getting rid of Lee Gangmo...
- Is a walk in the park.
Leave it to me.
I think leaving you at the ANSP
was the right choice.
So did you find an informer
willing to reveal Min Honggi's past?
We'll soon find a solution to that.
You just worry about Lee Gangmo.
I already have other plans
for our campaign issues.
Shouldn't you at least tell me
where you're taking me?
Aren't you listening to me?
What's wrong with you?
If you don't stop the car,
I'll just step out right now!
Keep quiet, will you?
Careful about Jeongshik.
I said be careful about him.
Didn't you say you're not the
kind of woman I think you are?!
And neither am I a child.
I can protect myself.
You can?
Wh...What are you doing?
If Jeongshik starts acting
like this, what will you do?
I could just do this, for instance?!
Is your nose bleeding?
Let me see.
It's just fine.
You laugh?!
Is this funny?
Ehh... I ought to...
Chief, you seem nicer than I thought.
What?
You'll also withdraw the lawsuit, right?
Hey...
You...
- Ajumma, another serving here.
- Yes, just a moment.
- More water here, please.
- Yes.
Hey...
Told you we should have
gone to a better place.
It'll stink up all my clothes!
So hurry up and turn the meat.
Don't know how.
You can't even hold chopsticks?
I never tried
cooking meat myself before.
You sure have it easy...
So go ahead and eat.
I don't like overcooked meat.
Let's just forget it.
I'll just have it all for myself.
Don't show up before me again.
So you're going
to withdraw the lawsuit?
Stop wasting your time and
just give it up, that's all.
I'm not giving up.
I'll toughen it up with meat and keep
pestering you until you withdraw it,
so consider yourself warned.
No... This makes no sense.
Why would I...
Hey. Why did they take me here
and force all this on me?
See? Something's wrong here...
Either a document mishap or...
Still don't get it?
What... Get what?
We were sent here by
Jo Minwoo and Hwang Jeongshik.
They could have just sent you,
why involve me...
Because you didn't get rid of me.
What?
Thought they'd treat a powerless and
ignorant fool like you with respect?
You lousy ass sons of a
motherless bitch with rabies...
Enough!
TV reporters are waiting outside.
Other than anything
dealing with your re-education,
all unnecessary remarks
are strictly prohibited.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, Sir!
Any volunteers for
the self-criticism speech?
Whoever comes forward,
make a good showing and we'll
promote you to Chief Inmate.
I volunteer!
Good.
Everyone report to the parade ground.
If I wasn't blessed by the
purifying Samcheong re-education,
I would have spent the rest
of my days living like a beast!
It was thanks to the precious
re-education I was given here...
that I was able to be
reborn as a decent person!
For giving such a golden opportunity
to a miserable fool like me,
I can only extend President
Jeon Duhwan my sincerest gratitude,
and promise I will spend the rest of
my days sacrificing for the sake...
of our beloved nation!
We're from Daehan Television.
Share with us your thoughts on the
re-education process you've experienced.
Don't be nervous,
and just speak your mind.
Let's start from scratch.
Share your thoughts with our viewers.
This is not a re-education camp,
but a human slaughterhouse,
where undiscriminating violence...
is perpetrated on a daily basis.
Think everyone taken here
was a gangster or a thief?
Just to fill their quota, every police
station forced innocent people here!
You'll get us into trouble this way...
Take a good look, fellow citizens!
Just yesterday,
one of us was beaten to death!
Your fathers, sons and brothers
are being taken here for no reason,
and killed indiscriminately!
Hey... Stop him!
You are being deceived!
This place is pure hell!
There is no re-education, just cruel
assaults against innocent people!
Seonsaengnim!
You people!
Give us back that camera!
This interview is over.
Still, give us back that camera.
For reasons of military security,
today's interview cannot be broadcast.
Take away those fools.
- Hey...
- Yes.
Can't you read what's written here?
- Yes, Sir...
- I'm the Chief Inmate here.
Everyone stop!
Red hunt!
- Everyone stand.
- Everyone stand!
The collective will be held
responsible for today's actions.
Therefore, you will spend all
day and night in this position.
Should anyone fall down before
tomorrow morning's bugle call,
you will all miss breakfast.
Is that clear?
Yes, Sir!
Red hunt!
Yes! No. 534!
You little bastards...
Let's do it right!
Hang in there, Seonsaengnim.
This will not be the end of it.
Maybe...
dying will be much less painful.
I can't die here.
I will survive and get out of here.
Don't you die either, Seonsaengnim.
That'd be what a coward would do.
If only to tell the world what
you felt, saw and went through here,
only think about surviving
and getting out of here.
That is what smart people
like you should do.
I told you, if you tell him his
friend Shideok is here, he'll come.
Ahh... You really don't
want to listen, do you?
Lee Gangmo is not here.
How can you visit
someone who's not here?!
What are you trying to say?
Gangmo is not here?!
Did they transfer him to another prison?
He wasn't transferred...
They took him to the Samcheong camp.
The Samcheong camp?!
They took Gangmo there?!
Anyhow, now you know,
so don't come again looking for him.
- Wait...
- Where is that?
Where is this place
they took Gangmo to?
Ahh... Really...
Wait! Warden!
About those mudflats in Gaepo,
they're quite vast.
I'm sure I told you that
Lee Gangmo owns that land?!
Turns out that it
falls right into my area.
If it's a business matter, I'd like you to
refrain from talking about it in my presence.
But I believe I
have the right to do that?
Don't I?
If I get elected,
I'll let you build anything
you want on that land.
Think about it.
If my political influence and your
business smarts are put together,
those mudflats can become
the cream of Gangnam's crop.
First worry about winning the elections,
and when Lee Gangmo is released,
then we can discuss the matter again.
Dad, Gangmo was...
Long time no see, Jeongyeon.
You're here.
So I hear these days you're
working particularly hard?!
No matter how busy you are,
I'm disappointed you never pay us a visit.
Dad.
Why don't you go?
I certainly understand you,
- but your future mother-in-law...
- I guess...
he hasn't told you yet?
Told me what?
Are you hiding something from me?
Just go back for now.
I'll explain everything at home.
No.
If you still don't know,
I'll tell you.
- Jeongyeon...
- They've...
broken off the engagement.
I did try everything I could to stop it,
but seems like they
weren't made for each other.
Who is behind this?
I asked him to do it.
Because I thought I wouldn't be
able to endure a loveless marriage.
So?
You gave your consent?
Yes.
With pleasure.
Dad.
Have you heard about Gangmo?
Heard what?
He was taken to the
Samcheong Re-education Camp.
Say what?
To the Samcheong camp?
Find out what's going on.
All right.
The Samcheong camp?!
He didn't lock it?
All the better.
Ohh... So messy.
Dad...
Let me explain.
Explain what?
How you deceived me and
kept pushing it under the rug?
- Dad...
- Or is it...
the pathetic excuses of a
foolish son who got miserably dumped?
I just needed some time.
I tried my best to make Jeongyeon
change her mind before the elections...
Think I only did this
to gain a daughter-in-law?
Have you forgotten
what your purpose was?
First, completely erase
that Jeongyeon from your mind.
Rid your mind of that cheap
sentimentalist claptrap you call love!
And when you're done with that,
find another way.
A way not to rely on anyone else and
still gain control of Manbo Construction.
Is that clear?
I'm sorry...
I was cleaning in the back, and...
Aren't you hungry?
Want to taste these out?
How will you drive later if you drink?
There aren't that many cars anyway...
Just try one.
When I feel down, eating
something usually does the trick.
I wasn't looking on purpose...
But was that your father, earlier on?
Shut your mouth.
You should consider yourself lucky.
Even if I got scolded all day,
I wish I still had a father.
My father passed away
when I was little.
I'm not in the mood, so stop it.
You don't even want kimbap...
How can I cheer you up now?
Either leave,
or just keep your mouth shut.
Did you just laugh at me?
One minute.
No... Just stay put
for thirty seconds.
It'll make you feel better.
When you're feeling down
and someone holds your hands,
it'll give you strength.
How is it?
Doesn't it feel better and better?
See? You're laughing.
This is a wonder drug.
Hey, what the hell are you...
Now that you're all cheered up,
have something tasty.
Then you'll kiss the blues goodbye.
What are you doing?
You need to chew now.
Are you just
swallowing it like that?
With those dirty hands...
My hands are clean!
Forget it, then!
See what happens if you ask again...
Did you sober up?
You can just take me to the bus stop.
Oh?!
A few are missing?!
Was it a rat?
I'm sure you didn't eat them...
Do you know where
they could have gone?
I ate them, why?!
Where are you spitting all that?
Ehh... He always acts so clean...
Look at this...
As if they tasted any good...
Director Ju tried
looking for him all over,
but there's no way to know
where they've taken him.
We're still looking for him,
so we'll soon find out.
This doesn't sound right.
What doesn't?
I tried looking for what
this Samcheong camp really is.
It's unlikely for prison inmates
to be transferred there.
Then, are you telling me
someone forced Gangmo there?
That's the only explanation.
Could it be...
What, Dad?
Never mind.
You must be tired, so go to sleep.
Get moving, you pricks!
All right... All right...
No. 523.
You prick...
It's always you...
All right! I'm going...
We'll all be punished again
because of that idiot.
Hyung...
Gangmo.
We have all the time.
Eat slowly.
Have some yourself.
Jo Pilyeon ordered me to kill you.
Gangmo.
Let's just give them that land.
I'm never going to give that up.
Gangmo...
You have the land deed, right?
Register it back to me,
under some kind of namesake.
As long as you keep that land,
they won't give up.
They'll try to kill you,
whatever it takes.
Just report my death
and get it over with.
What?
File Lee Gangmo as deceased.
People call this hell.
But to me, the real hell was everything
I had to go through all these years.
This whole farce?! It's nothing.
You just wait, Hyung.
How I survive this place,
how I get revenge on those people...
Just wait and see.
As that's when the real hell
will begin for them.
You useless twat...
What do we have to go through
because of you prick...
I'm sorry...
Please... Spare me...
Everyone, listen well.
I'm the Chief Inmate here.
Can you read?
Should anyone get on my nerves,
consider yourselves dead.
Is that clear?
Same goes for you, you prick.
No. 523.
This is going too far.
Everyone is just worried
about his own survival.
There's no need for
cheap compassion here.
Lag behind, and you're dead.
Resilience is all you need here.
This is just a deposit.
Let's say you'll get
the rest after completion.
Instead, you must keep
this secret no matter what.
You said ANSP, right?
What on earth are you scheming here,
buying someone's death like this...
I could tell you,
but then you'd have to die.
Still interested?
No.
Let me repeat myself one last time.
If only a single whisper about all
this escapes these four walls,
all that this money will be
spent for is your funeral.
I'll take it to my grave.
Haven't you scared him off too much?
The carrot alone doesn't work
with people like him.
So with the money Jo Pilyeon
gave you to kill your brother,
you end up saving him.
It won't be easy to bear for Gangmo.
I must destroy Jo Pilyeon with my
own hands before Gangmo is released.
That is the only thing
I can do now for him.
Open it.
No... The encouragement you put
inside that case is more than enough.
Elections aren't won
with encouragement alone.
Aigoo!
It's tight enough that even
a coupon wouldn't fit inside.
How's the situation proceeding?
Yes... Jo Pilyeon is
pressing on with his campaign,
but Candidate Min is still ahead.
So, what will you give us
in return as interest?
I can't say... If it was money,
I'm not too confident I could make it.
If money was what I was going after,
I wouldn't have accepted this deal.
I will contribute to our area's
development through honest politics.
Gyeongok, seems like
we spent our money in vain.
Yes, Sir.
Ohh Ohh... This!
Is that all you can tell him?
I will serve you
for the rest of my days.
What are you waiting for?
Take that briefcase!
I will pay you back
through my triumph.
I will defeat Jo Pilyeon at all cost,
and win the elections.
The most inept money lender is he who
lends money he knows won't be paid back.
The same goes for elections.
There is nothing as foolish as
entering a war you know you can't win.
Don't let this money blind you
into making careless decisions.
Jo Pilyeon is not someone
you can take lightly.
I will treasure and always keep
in mind your words of advice.
Here you are.
I have bad news.
Does it concern Lee Gangmo?
No.
Min Honggi has started receiving financial
support from lending kingpin Baekpa.
What?!
Baekpa?!
If Baekpa is getting involved,
then these elections
become impossible to predict.
That old fart...
dares to deceive me?!
What now?
We can't compete with them when it
comes to mobilizing campaign funds.
Call Chairman Hwang Taeseop.
If they shovel money at us,
we'll answer with truckloads.
Yes.
That's right.
Go ahead.
Is that true?
Yes.
Understood.
No... We will come firsthand.
What's the matter?
We've found an informer claiming
Min Honggi's father was a collaborator.
Where is he?
I jotted down his address.
Let's go there right now.
Are you in?
Is anyone home?
Min Honggi and I used to
live in the same neighborhood.
From what we know, Candidate
Min's father ran a pharmacy?
And he's renowned for
his many good deeds.
Aigoo... That's just a
bunch of shameless lies.
He was a notoriously
ruthless colonial officer.
Will you give us some more details?
So what I was saying is,
because my father helped
the independence movement,
he died at the hands
of Min Honggi's father.
No matter how rotten
this world has become.
Does the descendant of an independence
activist living in this state...
while sons of pro-Japanese collaborators
run for Congress make any sense?
I understand the feeling.
But there were plenty of
opposition candidates to contact,
why did you choose
to inform me instead?
Ahh... That's because...
That's because I liked
your campaign program!
My program?!
Politics for the working class!
Uh? So I thought you'd give people
like me a chance to redeem themselves.
There soon will be a
joint stumping session.
Would you be prepared to help me out?
Then, should I just
hand you all the evidence?
No, more than that...
Why don't you bring that evidence
and speak on the stage?
Who... Me?!
I know it's a burdensome favor.
But that's the most effective way
to derail Min Honggi's candidacy.
Yes...
Let's do it.
If that helps shed light
on my situation, I'm all for it.
We finally found what can
give Min Honggi a fatal blow.
Seems like Lady Luck is on
your side for these elections.
Even if Baekpa is helping him out,
could it compare with providence?
Jaechun, you dig into him.
Investigate his past, whether they
really live in the same neighborhood,
and how and when his father died.
All right.
How did it go with Lee Gangmo?
I put everything in place.
So all we need to wait
for is his death notice?
I don't think you'll have
to wait that long for it.
Jo Pilyeon's time in the
limelight is about to come.
Seongmo, Jaechun...
Your struggles will soon be over.
How did it go?
It's done.
Jo Pilyeon completely fell for our bait.
That's great.
You changed all of
Mister Gong's records, right?
Yes.
Good job, Chanseong.
You just wait.
This stumping session will
be Jo Pilyeon's very last.
There's no one going by that name here.
Turn to the left!
To the right!
To the right...
We had another one from
your company break from ranks.
You'll move like snakes
all the way to your barracks.
Proceed!
Get moving! Do it!
What are you waiting for?
All right...
Hey... Get up!
Wake up, you bastard!
Hey!
All down on your head, you pricks!
Hey... Halfwit.
Halfwit.
Why don't you just croak?
Because of you,
we can neither sleep nor eat.
The hell is this?
I'm sorry, man.
"I'm sorry, man..."
Is that all you can say?
You're killing us in here, you prick.
What will you do?
I'd just step on you if I could...
Anyhow, see you outside.
After you made us go through all this,
think you'll be safe?
Hey... Halfwit.
Better keep that in mind.
Son of a bitch.
Hey.
- Jaesuk -
Her name's Jaesuk.
She's this girl I met at the
orphanage, when we were little.
Her face was round as a full moon,
you can't imagine how pretty she was.
So that I would never forget her,
I pierced her name right here.
But I was brought here during
inspections because of this.
Because I had a tattoo.
I'll be damned, really...
Having to endure all this
because of the woman you love.
Still, when you get out,
there will be someone waiting for you.
She died already.
In the Gwangju riots.
A bar girl stubbornly getting
all up in arms, and for what?
She wanted me to join her
and demonstrate on the streets.
If I knew I'd be living this way,
I would have just joined her there.
But, you know?
Surviving can be even more painful.
You feel so sorry for the dead...
I'll always regret not dying
together with my Jaesuk there.
Listen.
Didn't you say your only sin was
falling in love with the wrong woman?
In this world of ours, there is
no such thing as forbidden love.
Look at me.
Even though Jaesuk is
no longer here with me,
look at how much I still love her.
- If You Live On By Deulgukhwa -
(Wild Chrysanthemum)
If you live on,
One day...
- the sun will shine upon you.
- Keep quiet, you bastard!
Even after hazy and gloomy days,
Wouldn't the sun
grace you in the morning?
Being so young and reckless
are the only riches you have,
So don't look down like a petty fool,
And always keep your head up.
Tomorrow the sun will shine.
It will shine upon you.
It will shine upon us.
No. 534!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and cross!
Quick, you bastard!
No. 534.
Go, you...
Go on... Quick!
Hurry up and run, you pricks!
Hurry up!
Hey! Quick!
Because of him...
it's collective punishment again.
Eat it, I'm all right.
You eat it.
If you want to survive and
get out of here, you need to eat.
Eat...
Go ahead.
Only those who earn
their keep should eat.
I can't even do that.
I don't think
I can bear it any longer.
I can't stand to see everyone
else suffer because of me any longer.
Forget the others and just
worry about yourself.
You must do that here.
I miss Jaesuk so much,
it's driving me crazy.
I miss her so much,
I can't even eat anymore.
Jaesuk, I'm sorry...
You died because of me.
Jaesuk...
It's me...
I said it's me.
Jaesuk!
Jaesuk.
Ahh... That prick...
He's a nuisance even when dead.
How could there never be
a day of peace here?
Chief Inmate?
I've had it with this!
Someone just died.
Is that all you can say?
Say what?
No. 534.
You killed him.
You were pretty much
responsible for his death!
Did you go batty
in groups or something?
He made it just as hard
for you, you pricks!
Wouldn't getting rid of him solve...
Look at you people.
I'm Chief Inmate here, you pricks!
This... Uh?
Can't you see this?
I'm sorry!
Gangmo... Gangmo!
Help me out!
Gangmo!
Until further notice,
keep your current position.
Should anyone break from ranks,
you will bear the grunt as well.
Eat...
Go ahead.
Only those who earn
their keep should eat.
I can't even do that.
I don't think I
can bear it any longer.
I can't stand to see everyone
else suffer because of me any longer.
If you live on,
One day the sun will shine upon you.
Even after hazy and gloomy days,
Wouldn't the sun
grace you in the morning?
Being so young and reckless
are the only riches you have,
So don't look down like a petty fool,
And always keep your head up.
Tomorrow the sun will shine.
It will shine upon you.
It will shine upon us.
Tomorrow the sun will shine.
It will shine upon you.
It will shine upon us.
No. 523.
Yes, Sir! No. 523!
Take that cart and follow me.
No. 523.
Yes, Sir! No. 523.
Change clothes with No. 534.
From this moment in,
you're no longer No. 523,
but No. 534.
Didn't you hear me?
Wear his clothes!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com