This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
- Episode 26 -
Whether you'll choose
this land deed as collateral,
or my business plan instead,
I leave the decision to you.
How much are you looking for?
I'd like to borrow five hundred million.
Listen to that.
Not a penny of interest,
and 500 million?
If I choose your
business plan as collateral?
You'd eventually be rewarded
with immense dividends down the line.
And if I choose the land deed instead?
I no longer need you.
Choose one of the two.
I need neither, so take them back.
Haven't you heard
I don't need any of this?
I apologize for wasting your time.
Might be a contract
without any conditions,
but you still need to sign it
before you leave.
The money will be wired to
your account in the morning.
Sir.
What I need as collateral...
is neither that land deed
nor any business plan.
It's none other than...
James Lee, you.
I will not disappoint you.
It's the only part of my body
where blood doesn't flow.
I must have been about
your age when it happened.
I needed money to buy
medicines for my mother,
so I pledged this hand as collateral
for a mere sack of rice's worth.
Unable to pay the money on time,
that loan shark forever
took away this hand from me.
That is what money can do to people.
Everyone desires it,
but if that desire is only marked by greed,
money can truly become poison.
Always bear it in mind.
All I lost for not living up to
my end of the bargain was this hand,
but you will lose everything,
from head to toes.
And you brought this
daunting ordeal upon yourself.
I will take it as an encouragement
to succeed at all cost.
The keen memories of my first kiss were
like a light wading through my destiny's path,
- Han Yongun's "Your Silence" (1926) -
A feeble step into the shadows
of darkness, soon vanishing.
Deafened as I was by the
sweet sound of your words,
That fresh and delicate beauty
of yours blinded me with passion.
Here...
Anyone willing to talk about these
"keen memories of a first kiss"?
Why, nobody is willing?
- Hangang Construction -
CEO James Lee
I never imagined you'd end up
running a construction company.
We just got started.
You will do well
no matter the path you take.
It might be from afar,
but you'll always have my support.
I don't need your support.
What I need is your strength,
which is why I'm here.
As you're well aware,
I know nothing about construction.
From here on in, we'll use new technologies
to fight off huge corporations.
I need people like you,
who know how to deal with the press.
By "huge corporations,"
do you mean Manbo Construction?
And Jeongshik?
He didn't come home last night.
And your wife refuses to eat,
always looking for the bottle.
Make sure she doesn't drink.
It's not like she would listen to me.
Jeongyeon, you...
Pretending you were still suffering
from aphasia even with me...
made me feel betrayed as your father,
not to mention all the disheartenment.
I apologize, Dad.
However,
as the chairman of Manbo Construction,
I only have compliments
for your brilliant plan.
We will soon have to announce
the new personnel changes...
Where would you like to work?
I'd like to be promoted to
Director of Planning.
Director of Planning?!
But I was already planning to
assign that post to Jo Minwoo...
I need no other position.
I'd like to become Director of Planning.
Then, I'll have to give Minwoo
some other position.
I believe it's still
too early for a promotion.
For the time being,
I think working under me as
Chief of Planning would be better.
I need capable people like him working
for me to improve as a leader, Dad.
Sure.
That doesn't sound
too bad to me, either.
Go ahead, then.
You heinous brat...
So you dare stab me
in the back like that?
But that owner of the Royal Club...
Why is she looking after her interests?
Why on earth would she be doing that...
Leave.
I don't even want to see you,
so get out of my face!
Transfer all your shares
and Jeongshik's to me.
What?!
Transfer our shares to you?!
You once told me you'd grace me with
a last act of generosity, if I recall?
I will repay the courtesy and be
generous for one last time, then.
You have one week
to make up your mind.
If you let that week pass,
no excuse will be tolerated.
You ruthless wench!
Still letting violence do the talking?
Go ahead and hit me, then.
Why?
Now that I'm Manbo Construction's heir,
does that scare you?
If you believe you already
gained control of that company,
you're sorely mistaken.
Manbo Construction's heir?!
Take a good look.
I'm your mother.
The chairman's wife.
And?
Think that if I oppose it,
you will ever get to become chairman?
Dream on!
I'm not taking this lying down.
Then, go ahead and try to stop me.
And then see what happens to
you and Jeongshik if you do.
Say what?
I recall you said you'd take away
all my shares for incompetence,
and trap me inside a hospital room
for the rest of my days?
Seems like you'd be more suited
to a hospital room instead?
It's been long since the last time you've
been able to sleep without drinking all day.
Are you trying to threaten me?
Yes.
That is exactly what I'm doing.
You know, I only
learned that from the best.
Don't you remember?
When you told me to keep sleeping
for the rest of my days.
Your every day will soon resemble hell.
But if you'd rather avoid all that, you
can always sleep for the rest of your days.
Did I make myself clear?
That scary wench...
Scary, heinous wench.
My heart.
My heart...
That wench...
That wench is finally
showing her true colors!
Chief.
Have you heard about
today's personnel announcement?
I know.
I just got a call from
personnel administration,
and you weren't on
the list of promotions.
Is that true?
Yes. I'm positive.
The chairman arrived already, right?
Congratulations.
You know you had our support at the
last shareholders' meeting, don't you?
Thank you.
But, why are you packing?
Chief Jo Minwoo?
Take these and follow me.
Hwang Jeongyeon...
Chief.
Miss Jeongyeon was just
promoted to Director of Planning.
I've really learned a lot from you all.
I hope I can continue counting on you.
Take these and follow me inside.
- Director of Planning -
HWANG Jeongyeon
Yes?
Our highway construction has already
gone over budget by 30 percent.
If this keeps up, it's obvious
we'll face significant losses,
so how are you going to
take responsibility for that?
How shall I take responsibility?
Would my resignation suffice?
Even if a hundred people
like you resign,
it still won't give us any
solution to our problems.
Hey, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Careful with your language.
I'm your direct superior.
Why did you change so suddenly?
Now that you've been proclaimed heir,
you ignore everyone in your way?
You were the ones responsible
for this "sudden change."
You and Hwang Jeongshik.
What are you implying?
What were you implying
with what you just said?
If you keep up with the attitude,
I'm afraid it won't end with security
forcibly kicking you out of this office.
Whatever it takes, we must successfully
complete the highway construction.
Bring me a report on all existing
issues and possible solutions.
Is that clear, Chief Jo?
Yes, understood.
Shouldn't you show your superior
some respect and nod before you leave?
Oppa...
Oppa!
Wake up.
How can you get drunk
at this hour, already?
Oppa, you have a guest.
Hurry and get up.
Leave us alone.
Oppa!
Get the hell out!
Hey, Hwang Jeongshik.
Wake up.
Minwoo?
Let's have a drink.
Get a hold of yourself, you fool!
That hurts...
What's wrong with you?
Did you ever make a mistake
in Jeongyeon's presence?
What are you talking about,
all of a sudden?
Did you ever tell Jeongyeon
we killed Lee Gangmo?
Give me a break...
What am I, crazy?
Why would I tell her that...
Jeongyeon seemed
to be aware of something.
Ho...How would she know that?
She said so herself?
That we killed Gangmo?
- Will you marry me? -
Gangmo.
Bear witness from heaven,
to the punishment those
who killed you will have to face,
and how I will avenge you.
Take a good look, Gangmo.
- Jungwon Construction Highway Site -
Safety First ~ Prevention of Calamities
Seems like they're facing
some kind of trouble?!
They've won concessions for the longest
tract of the Daejeon-Busan highway...
out of all the provincial
construction companies.
What if they throw us out, too?
What do you think? We'll have
to face whatever comes our way.
Look, Director Im!
Think I don't know you already supplied
your entire lot of sand and gravel...
to Manbo Construction?
How can I help you?
I came to meet the director.
So only huge corporations have the
right to work in the construction trade?
He's busy right now,
so please come another time.
Just a moment.
You stubborn fool, really...
You no longer need sand or gravel.
What's with him, now?
I can give you the
solution to your problems.
What are you doing?
Get him out of my sight.
Director!
Over five million housing units
are being built nationwide.
It won't be easy to
find any sand or gravel.
And?!
Should I just give up?
Even only with mud and cement,
you can get the basics covered.
Listen... I have twenty years
of experience in this trade.
If there is such a method,
I'll put my hand into the fire.
Just give me a chance.
- If I don't make it...
- Ahh... Shut up.
What are you waiting for?
Get this conman out of my sight.
Director!
I assure you I can do it!
Just give me a chance!
I assure you...
Give me a chance!
What's the use of having a killer app,
when nobody gives you a chance?
Aigoo... Foolish twats.
They wouldn't know a goldmine
if it hit them in the ass.
Sotae.
Find out how Manbo Construction's
highway project is proceeding.
Manbo Construction? Why?
Want to work with them?
I said hurry up and go find out.
All right.
Fine...
Does it make sense you haven't
even poured any asphalt yet?
I apologize.
Chief.
Because the ground
is made of soil cement here,
it's natural that it'd be more expensive
and take much longer to complete.
Whatever it takes, you must
complete the construction...
within budget and on time, is that clear?
For starters, increase the
laborers' workload.
Anyone coming short of the mark,
fire them on the spot and replace them.
Yes, all right.
That's Jo Minwoo.
Chief Moon.
Yes?
Looked like they were using
sand and gravel to harden the land.
Is there no way to harden the
existing soil without using that?
I've cut my teeth on
engineering works myself,
but I've never heard of such method.
Call our R&D team and
tell them to find a way.
Yes, I will.
Wait.
I'll go there myself.
What?
Jo Minwoo was at the construction site?
Seeing how he just barged in there
changing all plans on the fly,
I'm sure he was entrusted
control of the entire operation.
Forget everything else,
but can we lose out to Jo Minwoo?
That prick needs to be dealt with.
Why, did he con you out of your money?
Hyungnim... When words don't work,
how do you convince people?
When words don't work,
you just start cursing a storm at them.
Ehhh... Why, don't you
use your tongue to curse?
If they refuse to listen,
you just beat it into them.
Sotae.
Put shovels and cement in the car.
Hardener as well.
And then what?
Words are not going to work with
Jungwon Construction's director.
We'll have to show him he can trust us.
I apologize for what happened last time.
It's all right.
If I think of all the help
you've given me, that's nothing.
Jo Pilyeon is acting strange as of late.
Strange?!
Seems like he gave up the elections
and remains in his office all day?
I know Jo Pilyeon better than anyone.
Once his prey is right within range,
that's when things quiet down
to an eerie, worrying silence.
There's a huge approval
rate margin, already.
Even Jo Pilyeon wouldn't be
able to turn this ship around.
That's that,
but how about you follow me
and enter the political arena?
I have no interest in politics.
It's just because you're still young.
Wait until you get to my age.
You'll discover that nothing can
tickle your fancy like politics.
Honey.
Is this the time to be sleeping?
The elections are
right around the corner!
And your approval rate
is scraping the bottom.
So?
Are you just going to
give up on the elections?
If you really want to shock the world,
you must know how to wait
for the right time.
You just wait.
Because exactly when everyone
considers me dead and buried,
that'll be the moment when
I explode back onto the scene.
I can't believe this...
I'm back.
- Everything ready?
- Yes.
All that is left is making your move.
- How about the press?
- A few major papers will be present.
What is this about, suddenly?
You get ready as well.
What?
The chief of Candidate Min's
Youth Group met with Go Jaechun?!
Yes.
The two looked to be
discussing something in secret.
And who are we dealing with?
He's a gang leader active
in the Maljukgeori area.
Where's Jo Pilyeon now?
We just got word he's heading
for the redevelopment area.
He's scheming something for sure.
Follow me.
I'm independent candidate Jo Pilyeon.
Everyone, we brought some ramen
and other supplies.
No matter how hard it is,
never lose hope.
Aigoo, thank you very much.
It must be hard, Sir.
- Thank you.
- Don't even mention it.
Seeing you face so many difficulties
just breaks my heart.
This country is being
increasingly dominated by the rich.
But if I will be elected as congressman,
I will fight for powerless
working-class people like you.
Didn't you work for the KCIA?
And?
Is there anything wrong with that?
Someone currying favor
with the big shots like you...
would fight for the working class?
Think anyone here would be
so foolish to believe that?
Not to mention that you're a
pro-Japanese collaborator's descendant.
You'll pardon me,
but I must ask you to leave.
The clearance squads are coming!
The clearance squads!
If we let them go through,
we'll all be dead!
Fight back to the very end!
I thought I told you to
clear this area by today?!
You insolent fools, how dare
you kick us out of our own homes?
We're never going to leave!
Just kill us instead, you bastards!
Is that so?
Be my guest, then.
- Boys!
- Yes!
Get them out of my sight!
Stop... Stop it!
I said stop!
Stop it.
And who are you?
These are my area people.
- Leave!
- Listen, candidate fella.
What we're doing is perfectly legal,
it's these people who are
acting against the law.
- Understand what I mean?
- People come before the law.
What kind of law
oppresses innocent people?
Seems like you don't want to listen.
- Boys!
- Yes!
Teach them a lesson!
Honey!!
Hang in there, everyone!
Justice always prevails!
Fight to the end and protect your land!
Don't give up!
He's coming... It's him!
Excuse me...
Please, free the way.
Please, free the way!
- Honey, are you all right?
- Please, move out of the way.
Can you explain the situation to us?
Give us a comment on your feelings after
sacrificing for those displaced people.
Here... Here... We need to
stabilize his condition first.
It's all right.
As hard as it might be,
just a comment.
I'm more concerned
about those poor people...
Are they...
doing all right?
This won't do it, free the way!
It's all a ruse.
That was exactly what
Jo Pilyeon was planning.
That clearance squad leader was
the chief of Min Honggi's Youth Group.
What?!
I'm sure of it.
Then, we must catch him immediately.
Take all the boys
and find him right now!
All right.
- The Birth of a Real Politician -
Gangnam's Independent Candidate Jo Pilyeon
- Independent Candidate Jo Pilyeon -
Martyrdom for the Sake of Working Class
What the hell is all this?
Jo Pilyeon becomes a hero
to the working class?
Every paper is busy
praising Candidate Jo's actions.
And Jo's approval rate in his area
is rapidly on the rise.
If this keeps up, what if Jo Pilyeon
really ends up winning the elections?
Fox hunts are the noisiest,
while tigers prefer to hunt in silence.
What is that supposed
to mean, Hyungnim?
For the entire campaign,
Candidate Min has prevailed.
But after keeping quiet
until the very last moment,
look at how Jo Pilyeon turned
the tide in just one strike.
Then, that tiger you
always talked about...
There is this old saying,
"yukchamgoldan."
Sacrifice my own flesh
to gain my foe's bones?!
Then, are you suggesting it was
all a stratagem by Jo Pilyeon?
Stratagem or not,
what would it matter now?
What really matters is that these elections
are within Jo Pilyeon's grasp now.
Aigoo... Really...
Are you laughing at this?!
I was dying of concern in there.
Minwoo, you should have
seen that firsthand.
I apologize, Dad.
I was in the provinces
and heard about it too late.
What I'm saying...
is that you should have witnessed how
your father completely turned the tide.
Was this all a plan of yours?
Do you really think I righteously
sacrificed my body to protect those people?
I don't believe in justice.
It's nothing but a pretext used by
people to rationalize their weakness.
Because if you claim
you led a righteous life,
then you'll be able to wash away that
painful stigma people call failure.
Justice will never matter
as much as success.
Winning.
So Jeongyeon became
heir of Manbo Construction?
From now on in,
she's whom you will be facing.
Find a way to contend with her
and get your hands on that company.
Min Honggi is waiting outside.
Tell him to come in.
- Please, come in.
- Are you all right?
Sir.
Honey, I'll let you two talk, then.
So... How are we feeling?
Your generosity always humbles me.
You even think of paying me a visit.
We might be rivals, but won't you
join politics as well, down the line?
We'll one day become colleagues,
so paying a visit...
So you seem to believe that
you'll win these elections.
Throwing a rock into the river
won't turn the tide.
A few ripples is the
best you can hope for.
You'll soon be able to read
quite the interesting article.
Let me borrow your ear.
Turns out that the clearance
squad leader who attacked me...
was the chief of your election
campaign's Youth Group?!
What?!
Give a good read to all those articles.
One of us will become a
hero to the working class,
while the other will become a political
thug surrounding himself with gangsters.
You were behind all of this!
It was a ruse from the very beginning.
Jaechun.
Candidate Min said
he'll have to get going.
- Orphan -
I believe my biggest strengths
are the fact I'm always...
cheerful and optimistic.
My late mother always told me there is nothing
I can't do, if I really work hard for it.
I had to grow up as an orphan
and face many difficulties,
but I never let that discourage me.
I've witnessed many people
facing even more struggles than me.
As for my biggest dream,
it is that of becoming the kind of
singer who can give hope to those people.
I wish this world could become
a better, more cheerful place.
- Oh... Here's the chief.
- Chief.
- Did I miss anything?
- No.
Chief.
While you were away,
they sent you a lunchbox.
We thought it'd all go bad,
so we helped ourselves.
There was a letter inside the lunchbox.
You haven't picked up the phone,
these last few days?!
I'm often at the library
next to the office.
My GED test is coming up soon.
Excuse me.
Drink this while you study.
I've already had coffee.
Let's talk a moment.
What's the matter?
I'm not some kind of stalker,
and I major in business
administration at Korea University.
I've had my eyes on you for a while.
I'd like to go out with you.
I already have a boyfriend.
Ehh... I could be a much
better catch than him.
You know Ohseong Confectionery, right?
I got a job there.
If you lose this chance to go out
with me, you'll regret it later.
My boyfriend is much more
successful than you.
He's already chief of planning.
Depends on what company he works for.
Being chief of planning for
a small firm is no big deal.
You've heard of Manbo
Construction, haven't you?
Ma...Manbo Construction?!
Also, you can't imagine how cool he is.
You can't even begin to compare.
What do you want from my girlfriend?
I apologize.
GED Test
- English -
If you keep staring at me like that,
how can I concentrate?
And who's staring at you?
Was just looking
if you got the answers right.
You weren't much of a student, were you?
Chief.
Minwoo.
Uh?!
You said I'm your boyfriend.
Who calls her boyfriend "Chief"?
I'm sorry, Chief.
Someone like me shouldn't
even lie about that.
Someone like you?!
Why, what's wrong with you?
It's not like I come from a good
family or have an elite job like you.
Stop it.
My family is not as "good" as you think.
Stop thinking such nonsense
and worry about studying.
With those skills of yours,
it'll take a hundred years to get your GED.
What's wrong with my skills?
They're almost all wrong, sh...
From now on, I'll give you an hour
of special tutoring every day.
What?
Why? Afraid I'll expose
the fact you're a dummy?
Aren't you busy?
I am.
Here... Let's start
with English for today.
Pay attention.
Can we finish by tomorrow morning?
We must. If you don't finish
before they come to work,
we'll be screwed.
But will this be
enough to convince them?
If they witness it firsthand,
they'll believe us.
Let's hurry up.
The sun's already up.
They'll soon start arriving?!
How long will it take until we finish?
At the very least, two hours.
But if they file a complaint with the
police because we dug up their land,
we'll be screwed, won't we?
Sotae.
Take the truck and block the entrance.
Stop them from coming in
and buy us some time.
- All by myself?
- That's right.
What am I, a seawall?
There's only an hour left
until they come to work.
So just hold them back
for the remaining hour.
Ahh... I'll be damned...
Doesn't your face
suggest a way, you fool?
What way does my face suggest?
Let's hear it, if there's one.
Come here.
I can barely stand,
why don't you come here?
Uh?!
Don't move!
Stay away... Back off!
Listen... If you really
want to kill yourself,
don't do it here, uh?
Let's... right...
Let's have a talk, shall we?
Think this is a show?
Words on his chest: "I wanna die"
Fine... Fine... Fine!
I'll set myself on fire.
Back off or we'll all croak!
I've already sold off all my kidneys,
and there's nothing left inside!
Here, if anyone wants to
croak together, be my guest.
Words on headband: "My wish is"
(with a glaring grammar mistake)
Go ahead and come!
Aigoo... It's killing me.
What kind of torture is this?
Let's hang in there, Hyungnim.
It's almost done.
Don't move!
My wish!
Is croaking here!
- What's the matter?
- He's attempting suicide.
What?! Attempting suicide?
Are you the boss here?
The boss has come? Fine!
Take a good look.
Here's the fire...
Here... Come and join me!
Let's all croak like real men!
Is that even gasoline?
I... I think so.
You think so? Can't you go
and check if it smells right?
Oh?! B...Back off!
I'll set myself on fire... Don't!
Director... It's dangerous!
Think if I set myself on fire,
I'll be the only one to croak?
The fire will just spread
and kill you all!
What the hell...
You little prick,
acting like an idiot with water?
No... No! It's gasoline!
Get him off.
Wait... Wait!
Just a moment... Wait.
Aren't you that...
I told you that you could build a road
even without sand and gravel, right?
What?
Come see for yourself.
If you witness it firsthand,
you'll finally believe me.
Are you sure he only
used cement and hardener?
I'm positive.
I verified it firsthand.
If it really tightened it up,
then it could revolutionize our business.
Leave us your number and go.
We'll call you again
once we have the results.
It will dry out
by the end of the day.
We'll be waiting here.
Should we order something to eat?
Those fools...
They don't even realize
they hit the jackpot.
Is this how you treat your benefactors?
Did it dry out?
Yes!
So how about it?
It's...
It'll be more than three times stronger
than normal sand and gravel mixtures.
In terms of simple finances,
it means you will be able to reduce
total costs by up to forty percent.
Fo...Forty percent?!
You're really impressive.
Let's sign the contract right away.
What are you waiting for?
Let's bring these
gentlemen some coffee.
You said you'd throw your hand
into the fire if we succeeded, right?
What?
That'll be good enough for me.
Have a nice day.
Help us out.
Without any sand or gravel to
work with, we're going through hell!
Tell us your conditions,
we'll satisfy them all.
I beg you,
help us out just this once.
I only have two conditions.
First, allow our Hangang Construction
to take over part of your project.
Sure.
And what's the other condition?
Royalties will be twenty percent
of total construction costs.
That's a bit...
We're so deep in the red...
Fine.
Let's make that fifteen, then.
I can't go below that.
Fine.
Yes... Let's sign the
contract right away!
Also, introduce us to
all your fellow directors.
Don't you worry about that.
I have more than one friend who was
going through the same headache.
Why are the site superintendent
and his senior staff still missing?
I told them you'd be coming today...
Try to understand them.
Few people would like to see women
prancing around their construction site.
Didn't know you'd be here, Chief.
It's the director!
Aigoo... I apologize
for not recognizing you.
- I'm superintendent...
- Already had a drink?
What?
I smell alcohol from here?!
We had lunch with a few landlords here,
so a few drinks would be natural.
That's inevitable in this line of...
Gather all your
senior staff this evening.
Director...
You make this mess at work
and still have the guts to drink?
Is this how you earn your paychecks?
It's not that,
the situation forced us...
I'm still not done talking!
When you come this evening,
bring your letters of resignation along.
Don't you know who that is?
She's Director Hwang Jeongyeon,
who recently was proclaimed heir.
Of all the people you could mess with...
Here... We're done.
I can wire you the
money tomorrow, right?
Yes. As you prefer.
Here... So...
Let's give it our best.
- Yes.
- See you again.
- Have a nice day.
- Yes. To you as well.
Next, come in.
Came to sign a contract?
I'm afraid not.
Then, what else
would you come here for?
Wait a moment...
You look familiar?!
It's been a long time.
Ahh... Right!
Samcheong!
This is Lee Myeongsu,
who writes for a trade magazine.
I've heard a lot about you.
I was really surprised to hear the news.
So I wanted to write a special
on your new method.
As long as you leave
personal questions out of it,
I'm always available.
But, have you requested a patent?
Yes.
- Here.
- Yes.
Wow... So young and
already this skilled...
Anyhow, once our
special is published,
you'll hear people wanting to sign
a contract from all over the country.
Congrats, President Lee.
Here... Let's have a drink.
Cheers... Cheers...
Here... To President Lee.
Cheers!
Hey... Heard them, right?
They'll come in droves asking to
sign with us, from all over the country.
Then, will we end up sitting
on a mountain of money?
That's not the issue...
At least for what concerns
Hangang Construction,
you and I get to
be called Director, you fool.
Di...rector?!
Going through that torture at the
Samcheong camp still feels like yesterday...
So there were days like
this even for Park Sotae...
The hell are you, crying?
Stop it!
As if you weren't doing the same.
These are not tears, you fool!
It's sweat! Look.
Isn't it sweat what's coming down?
Mine's sweat, too. You fool.
What... "Fool"?
You little prat, a little wine and
you go spouting fool this and fool that?
- When did I call you that?
- You just did, you fool!
- When did I?
- Ahh... Pardon me.
You've heard him, right?
He called me fool!
Here... Here...
Take out your respective
letters of resignation.
- Letter of Resignation -
It's a letter of resignation
giving up my rights as heir.
Always carry that letter
in your mind as you work.
If this project should fail,
I will present my resignation
to the chairman.
If that happens,
you will have to do the same.
Fill your glasses with soju.
From now on in,
we're on the same boat.
If I become the next chairman,
you will also be promoted.
If I hand in my resignation,
you will all become unemployed.
Now our goal is crystal clear.
Surviving.
Making it in this jungle
up to the very end.
And all that depends on you.
Here.
To Manbo Construction
and our survival!
- Cheers!
Are you all right, Director?
- So why did you drink so much...
- Gangmo.
Gangmo, how was I today?
Did I do well?
You should compliment me...
I really gave my best...
You were great today.
If Gangmo could have seen you,
he really would have liked it.
- Hwang Taeseop's Daughter Jeongyeon -
To Become Future Chairman
- Hero and Traitor Switch Places? -
This is serious.
Electors have gathered before the
campaign building and are protesting.
And why are you
telling me that, you idiot?
Call the police and
get them out of there!
All right.
Jo Pilyeon won't participate at
the last stumping session, anyway.
I can use that to turn this ship around.
That will be it.
Speak.
Where is your boss?
Where's that prick who
attacked those people with you?
If you don't confess,
you won't get out of here alive.
Is that clear?
Seonbaenim.
The other confessed.
Where is he?
He's got a woman in Cheongju.
Looks like he might be hiding there.
Dispatch all the boys and capture him.
We don't have much time.
We must expose Jo Pilyeon's ruse
before the elections.
Hurry up.
All right.
- 11th Congress Elections - Gangnam District -
Stumping Session
Hurry up. Come!
Mom!
Did you need to take me along,
especially in this state?
So, what, should I just let
you doze off at home all day?
Aigoo... They even served you drinks
at other stumping sessions...
Aigoo... You really...
- Yes! Yes!
- It's not our side.
It's not?!
Then stop clapping.
Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon
is currently hospitalized,
so he could not participate today.
He shouldn't have missed
the very last session...
He barely made it out of
there alive, could he come here?
No matter how much better
his approval rate has gotten,
if you miss a day like this,
the consequences will be serious.
Excuse me.
I, Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon!
Am standing here before you again!
And what gave me the strength
to get back up on my feet...
was what I most love and respect,
my people!
Jo Pilyeon! Jo Pilyeon!
The people's choice, Jo Pilyeon!
- So hardener would do the trick.
- Yes.
It was already used for bricks,
so I tried to adapt it to the situation.
Well done.
Yes.
Chief.
I made a few calculations,
and we could reduce costs
by at least forty percent.
File a patent request.
The quicker, the better.
Yes.
I'll get right to it.
- Hangang Construction -
Patents Revolutionary Road Construction Method
Our R&D team found a solution to
our highway construction problems.
We wouldn't use sand and gravel,
but take advantage of the existing mud...
You really are more
dull-witted than I thought.
Don't you know that
information is crucial?
Read it out.
If we don't join forces with
Hangang Construction right away,
we'll be weeded out of business.
Chief, have you heard the news?
A construction company in the
provinces developed a new method...
Find everything you can
about Hangang Construction.
What?
What tricks they're up to,
the company's scale,
who is running it...
Find everything right now!
Yes, all right.
Are you all here? Is that all?
Ahh... Come on, let's do it right!
You want to sign a contract
when you can't even stand in line?
Just go, all right?
- I apologize.
- If you are, then stand in line.
Can't you even get that right?
- Then...
- See you again.
Yes?
Hangang Construction, right?
Yes, that's right.
Who am I speaking to?
Manbo Construction here.
I'm Director of Planning
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Is the president there?
I have a business proposal for him,
can you get him on the phone?
Hello?
Are you listening?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I have nothing else to ask from you.
Just don't do this to me.
What if they come here looking
for you? It'll be trouble.
Park Sotae?!
The man who framed Gangmo?
You can bet on this.
Chief Jo likes you.
So be the first to confess.
Big Oppa! Little Oppa!
Every time I see you,
I feel so happy...
Who is it? Who is trying
to steal this project from us?
But this is Manbo Construction's?
Forget all the rest.
That is where it ends.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com