Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 34 -
Found it?
I found it, Dad.
That's a relief.
Go freshen up and eat breakfast.
Made you some beansprout
soup to sober you up.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Yes.
So are you going to
let Miju have that baby?
Minwoo has plenty of
things to do these days.
I'll take care of everything,
so don't let him in on this.
The sole thought gives me the chills...
All you need to do then is take
chilling measures to deal with it.
Oppa... Oppa!
Chairman Hwang Taeseop
has disappeared!
What?!
My mother said Madam Oh
and Jeongyeon argued all evening,
blaming each other for it.
The hell is going on here?!
There's no way he would have
done that by himself, in that state.
Find out what happened.
Who might have taken him out and why.
All right.
Why aren't you allowing us to resume
construction for the Songpa apartments?
Seems that someone up high
is opposing this construction.
And who is that?
I can't say...
This kind of situation
is not very common...
in our Gangnam development campaign.
So it must be Lee Gangmo.
I don't believe President Lee
could have that much influence.
I know him well.
He's the only one
who could be behind this.
He must have his connections as well.
I was actually
suspecting someone else...
Who would that be?
Once I have clear evidence,
I will tell you.
How much longer will we be able
to keep the construction on hold?
How long would you need?
Until company stocks crash to the point
where I can buy them on the cheap.
Then, we can wait until then.
Because of the Olympics and Asian Games,
it can't be stopped indefinitely.
But I'll make sure they'll keep them
on hold as long as you need.
Thank you, Dad.
There soon will be
a shareholders' meeting.
That's when Chairman Hwang's
testament will be presented.
So are we sure Jeongshik will be
proclaimed chairman at Jeongyeon's expense?
His mother fixed the testament
for that very reason,
so that's what will happen.
She fixed the testament?!
When they present it at
the next shareholders' meeting,
Hwang Jeongyeon will be ousted,
and Jeongshik will take her place.
The money we took from them is not
even half their secret fund's total.
They'll soon sell the rest of
the land and encash those funds.
I'm sure they won't be
using the same account.
They likely won't.
I'll find what their other account is.
They'll soon find out I took the money.
You must be careful, Hyung.
Don't you worry.
I'm always prepared for that.
If we can get our hands
on their secret fund,
even Jo Pilyeon won't be able to
gain control of Manbo Construction.
What is that supposed to mean?
Our entire deposit was withdrawn?!
Every necessary procedure was followed.
Does that make any sense?
We have both account book and seal,
how could they withdraw that money?
That's what we should be
asking you, on the contrary.
Can I see CCTV recordings
from that day?
Wait.
Rewind the tape, please.
"Jo Minwoo."
"Take a good look."
Chief...
Isn't... Isn't that...
Do you know him?
Shall I report this to the police?
There is no need.
Fortunately, it's one of our employees.
And how could that be possible?
I can't explain it myself.
To get that money,
they not only needed book and seal,
but also the account password.
You said you lost your
account book that night, right?
I dropped it in the car.
Now that I think about it,
it was the same day Lee Gangmo
withdrew that money.
And you must have found
your account book right after.
That's right, Dad.
Then...
Are you suggesting
there's a traitor among us?
The only people who knew of
that account were you and me,
Seongmo Hyung, Jaechun Hyung...
and Chief Moon.
It couldn't have been Chief Moon.
He wouldn't have gone this far
just to steal some money.
Also,
there's no way
Seongmo Hyung would do this.
Even more so for
what concerns Jaechun.
We'll have to get
our hands on Lee Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo...
He must have known that we
couldn't report this to the police.
Minwoo.
You know how you can
force your enemy into a trap?
Lure them to the place they would
trust enough to never suspect it.
What brings you here?
Get in.
Is anything the matter?
There is something you
must do for me, Seongmo.
Minwoo thinks of you like a brother,
so I thought you'd be
better suited than Jaechun.
Tell me.
There's this leech of a wench
who's been sticking to Minwoo.
I need your help to force her
out of the picture.
Seemed like Minwoo really likes her...
He's just frivolously
flirting with her.
If you really care about Minwoo,
they need to be separated.
Who is that woman?
- I need to know what she looks like...
- Tomorrow,
Chief Moon will withdraw our secret funds
to be wired to the Swiss bank account.
When we've dealt with that,
I'll give you all the details.
All right.
Ahh...
Come to my office tomorrow morning.
We'll finish talking about that woman.
All right.
Let's go.
What did Jo Pilyeon come
all the way here for?
What's wrong?
Just felt like his only purpose for
coming here was letting me in on that.
Even someone like Jo Pilyeon
wouldn't suspect you.
Tomorrow?
That will make our plans
a lot easier than I thought.
I'm feeling a bit nervous about this.
Just feel like things are
going a little too easy.
No need to be nervous, Hyung.
I'm just fine,
but I fear something
could happen to you.
You must really be careful, Gangmo.
Sotae and Shideok,
let's have a word.
What is it now...
Shideok, you know where Chief
Moon Seongjoong lives, right?
Keep an eye on his movements
starting early tomorrow.
Why, all of a sudden?
Chief Moon will go withdraw the rest
of Jo Minwoo's secret fund in the morning.
So we're going to get that from him?
Still, doing that in
the middle of the day...
Chief Moon has both
book and seal with him.
If we can get our hands on that,
it'll be game over in a moment.
Don't you worry.
Even if they find out who did it,
they can't report it to the police.
It won't take long, so wait here.
Yes, all right.
Come on in, Seongmo.
- Breakfast?
- Already ate it.
Shall we get to the point?
Didn't you say you had something
to tell me about Minwoo's girlfriend?
Right... I did.
Yes?
Chief Moon just called me,
saying he'll leave now.
How long will it take?
Two hours should be enough.
All right.
Lee Gangmo will be caught today.
What's that supposed to mean?
Lee Gangmo will be caught?!
If Lee Gangmo snatches that
money away from Chief Moon,
he won't be getting
his hands on my money,
but incriminate himself for
stealing the president's secret fund.
It will only take two hours at worst,
so I'd like you to remain inside
this room for the remainder.
By any chance,
are you suspecting Seongmo and me?
Not long ago,
Lee Gangmo seized secret funds I was
about to transfer to a Swiss account.
The only people aware of
that money were us three,
Chief Moon and Minwoo.
Of course I don't suspect you,
but Minwoo said this.
That if Lee Gangmo ends up learning
of this and seizing that money as well,
it can only mean that
there is a traitor among us.
Find the right opportunity
to hit his car.
There are too many cars around.
There's a bypath leading
to the bank's main offices.
Chanseong.
Look at me.
Please, look!
Tired?
Yes... A little.
It'll just be another hour.
T...
Tr...
Tra...Trap?!
That's our chance... Do it!
Who taught you how to drive, you...
It's a trap!
Stop this right away.
Yes?
Just now,
I've been informed he
successfully withdrew that money.
I may not know how Lee Gangmo
managed to find out,
but it's now clear that
it wasn't from any of us.
Who is... it?
Lee Miju!
How nasty... You wanted to
come here all by yourselves?
She found out I was going
to meet you, so here she is.
- Glad you came, Miju.
- Congrats, Little Oppa.
Heard business is
doing great these days?
You're really something...
It's all thanks to Seongmo.
So you'll save an
apartment for Miju, right?
Will it just be an apartment?
She's our youngest,
we must do everything she wants.
That's right... Miju.
Just tell us.
Why, what did I say?
I'm not the youngest, Junmo is.
The nicer you are calling me that,
the sorrier for him I feel.
Miju...
I hired some people to
look for Junmo in the States.
It might take some time,
but we'll find him.
When we find him,
I'll treat him ten...
No, a hundred times
better than I treat you.
Want to sing a song on the stage?
Over there?
You wanted to hear her sing, right?
Here.
- "Creek" by Shim Subong -
What is the reason you do this?
Sinking down the creek
in all loneliness.
Luxuriant weeds spurting all over,
As the dregs scatter about,
moved by the spring breeze.
It must have been a promise
from days long gone by,
Leading you there even if
your mind no longer desired to.
Sitting by the creek every single day,
Vacantly abandoning yourself
in those thoughts.
It must have been a promise
from days long gone by,
It must be asking you
not to ever forget it.
As if she was in any condition
to stay out this late...
It's already past ten...
Where on earth is she?
- Why, what's wrong?
- It hurts.
Looks like I got too
nervous while singing.
I'm getting cramps.
- On my back.
- Get on my back.
So who are you going to choose?
If you don't get on my back,
better forget about any apartment
when you get married, Miss!
Ahh... You really...
- Come on.
- Ahh... Right!
Ahh... Hyung.
Did you take your
wallet after paying?
I remember I saw you dropping
it right as you went out?!
Everything is in there... Ahh...
- Go ahead first.
- Go look for it, Hyung.
Take this, and get on my back.
Big Oppa!
Hyung got fooled!
He fell for it,
hook, line and sinker!
What's this?
Good Lord, take a look
at the photo on his ID...
- Ahh... Stop it...
- What kind of photo is this?
What am I, some model?
- Ajeosshi!
- Ahh... How embarrassing.
You call that a photo?
Sorry, Hyung.
I ended up putting even you at risk.
It's all right.
As long as you're safe, I'll be fine.
But what do you need
their secret fund for?
Jo Minwoo will soon start
buying Manbo Construction shares.
We're going to buy them as well.
So you're not using that
money to build apartments,
but just to buy
Manbo Construction shares?
Aren't you rushing things?
You still aren't big enough to...
That's what
Chairman Hwang always did.
When your enemy
starts gasping for air,
stab him without mercy.
There isn't much time left
for Manbo Construction.
Before it's Jo Minwoo
who stabs them,
I must deal with this
with my own hands.
Just wish they could all
end up on the street.
But what's with all
these Chinese characters?!
What does this mean?
What...
This one?
How many strokes is this...
Get that bowling ball out of the way,
how can I see these characters...
Ehh... You dare joke about
an elder's noggin?
If you're illiterate,
don't blame it on my head!
The light is reflecting there,
can't you see?
The hell do you know,
you clueless little fool...
Gangmo...
Take a look.
- Manbo Construction Continues to Crash -
Project Resumption is Uncertain
What we want to hear
is a concrete plan!
Tell us how you're
going to deal with this mess!
If you want any answer,
shouldn't you first keep quiet?
First, we will form a team
to investigate those relics.
We will use the relics'
level of preservation...
as our possible evidence
for the works' resumption.
We don't have any time for that, do we?
Once the verdict is out,
we can restart the construction
even without the ministry's approval.
Are you just asking them
to clamp down on you?
The City Council is supporting
the resumption as well.
If we collaborate with them
behind closed doors,
I don't envision any
particular trouble down the line.
Once the construction restarts,
stocks will start climbing again,
and everything will return to normal.
So just trust me and rest assured.
The director's plan
seems to be quite concrete.
If they manage to restart the
construction before stocks stop falling...
That is never going to happen.
Just think of it as Hwang Jeongyeon's
last, desperate move.
Mom...
What if the company goes belly-up
even before I become chairman?
Your father's incompetence
verdict will soon be out.
Once we present the testament,
you'll automatically become chairman.
Ahh... I'm worried stocks
will keep crashing...
If we sell them now,
at least we'll get some money.
How can you say that?
You're the chairman!
This company belongs to you!
So what if I am?
If the company fails, it's all over.
Just shut up.
That's that, but how
about finding your father?
Ohh... You know...
It's really strange.
I looked into anyone remotely
suspicious both here and at the hospital,
and there are no traces whatsoever.
Just in case...
Anyone in mind?
Nah... Can't be.
Why would that woman waste time
with a man on the brink of death?
Madam Yoo of the Royal Club?
Ehh... Make some sense!
Right?!
You managed to reassure
the shareholders,
but I don't see this
situation getting any better.
Even Commissioner Han said that
someone is buying time on purpose.
So that would be
President Lee Gangmo?
Is Chairman Hwang doing well?
Yes...
I've heard he disappeared
from the nursing home...
You knew?
No need to hide it from me.
I know you've taken him out of there.
Who says I did?
So it wasn't you?
I am looking into it...
But we can't find any traces.
Then...
Who could possibly...
At the last elections,
turns out that the situation forced me
to turn my back on you gentlemen.
If you bear any ill will towards me,
please be frank and speak out.
Ahh... Well...
What ill will could I possibly bear?
Seeing you act this way
feels a little strange?!
I've learned two precious lessons
while serving my sentence.
One, that excessive greed can
only further expose my shortcomings,
and the other is that outcasts
are not cut out for politics.
Is it because you want the ruling party
to recommend you for the next elections?
Sounds like you need an ally...
That sounds even better.
Looks like you're finally starting to
understand what politics is all about.
In politics, aren't friends and foes
just two sides of the same coin?
That's right.
If there's anything that
can be turned upside down,
that's political rivalries.
You should be practicing that kind
of mentality a little more often?
Things got a little overheated
between us at the last elections.
I'll admit I was to blame.
Will you accept my apologies?
As long as you don't turn me from
friend to foe at the flip of a coin...
Of course.
How have you been?
Come on in.
And what are you doing here?
I invited him.
Doesn't look like he would fit here?!
Baekpa is one of my
company's shareholders.
I really appreciate what
you did for me, Congressman Oh.
Nah... Nah, you should thank
Congressman Min, on the contrary.
I've heard that Hangang
Construction is doing great.
We have huge expectations
for your new apartments.
Yes, I will not disappoint you.
You really are something.
You manage to make
this kind of connections?!
But... How did you make
President Lee's acquaintance?
He devoted a very large sum to me.
Are you telling me he
invested in Hangang Construction?
Well...
Wouldn't really call it investment,
and I'd rather let him tell us
what kind of money it really was.
Give me my money back.
Return the money you seized from me.
If it really is your money, and I
seized it, then report it to the police.
What?!
If you can't report it,
then it means it either isn't yours,
or I didn't seize anything.
Guess it's one of the two?!
Brilliant, I'll admit it.
Artifice, resourcefulness,
it's all remarkable.
I've had the perfect teacher in you.
Back in the day,
that was the same exact stratagem
you used to steal that gold.
Since they were goods
you couldn't report to the police,
you had no qualms about
killing someone for them.
Think you'd survive
an all-out war against me?
Shall we give it a try?
And that's because...
tax audits or whatever else you use your
dirty connections to throw at me...
will be powerless against me.
Yes, all right.
Good night, then.
What did he say, Mom?
Your father's testament will be
presented at this shareholders' meeting.
Then, do we have a verdict?
What are you talking about?
Why would they present my father's
testament, when he's not even dead?
And how do you know
whether he's alive or dead?
Do you?
My father is alive.
How could you consider him dead,
when you still have no idea?
It's a letter...
A letter.
There was a letter outside.
What's all this commotion
for a damned letter?
It's a letter from the chairman!
Take a look here.
This letter came from him.
What?!
- Is it really from him?
- Give it here.
It's for me.
- From Hwang Taeseop -
My dear Jeongyeon.
I'm still not dead.
I'm alive and well.
But your stepmother
changed my testament.
It's all a conspiracy to give my entire
fortune and the company to Jeongshik.
Don't let them
take that away from you.
Whatever it takes,
you must protect it.
That's the only way for
Manbo Construction to survive.
Jeongyeon...
What's all this about, Mom?
Dad wrote a letter?!
No way.
There is no way.
Your father is in a vegetative state.
How can he write in that state?
You two changed his testament?
Let's hear it.
Did you change that testament or not?
Hey... You really
believe what this says?
Take a good look.
It's Dad's handwriting.
Speak to me!
Did you change it or not?
And if I did?
What?
Let's suppose I did.
The hell are you going to do about it?
Have any proof?
Any witness?
So that's why...
you wanted to present it
at the shareholders' meeting.
To gain control of my seat
with that forged testament?
Whatever you're thinking,
that testament will be presented.
No, I'm afraid it won't?!
That letter only means
Dad is alive and well,
so how will you present that?
Mom...
It will make no difference.
Because Dad will
show up at that meeting.
Dad...
Ahh... Come on!
Mom...
What do we do now?
There's no way
your father has recovered.
How can someone in his state
recover this quickly?
You've seen that letter!
It's Dad's handwriting for sure!
I said no!
Something is wrong here.
I'm sure.
Hello?
Go ahead and speak.
Who are you?
I said who!
Tell me.
Is... Is it you?
If it's you, go ahead and speak!
Speak to me!
Do it!
Hello...
Hello?
Hello?!
Here... Give it here.
Did you hear his voice?
Was it really Dad?
Stop it...
Miju, now that you're
marrying into a good family,
you better not start ignoring us!
Even after the wedding,
I'll keep coming to practice.
Wait until you have a baby...
You'll soon give up your dreams of singing.
Baby?!
Just thinking about it scares me.
Yes?
Father...
What do I owe this call to?
Right now?
Yes, certainly, Father.
Yes...
Your father-in-law?
Yeah...
He wants to meet?!
Is he going to buy me a drink?
I really envy you...
Tell me about it.
Wanna die?
She will soon be here.
But when Minwoo seems
to like her so much, why...
She doesn't suit him in any way.
So what do you
want me to do, exactly?
She is pregnant.
Then, you want me to...
You'll forgive me for
forcing this burden on you,
but I just thought you were the
only one who could convince Minwoo.
Take her to the hospital,
and stay there until
the abortion is completed.
Jo Minwoo...
You poor fool.
How have you been?
Right... Come on in. Sit.
Yes.
I wired some money to
this account for you.
It will be of great help when
you marry someone else later on.
What are you... trying to say?
Stay out of Minwoo's life.
Father...
I have no intention of accepting
you as my daughter-in-law.
I can't leave Minwoo.
If there is anything I am lacking,
I will give my best to improve, Father.
- I sincerely love Min...
- And I thought you were only uneducated...
Looks like we should
add gullible to the list.
If you really love Minwoo as you say,
I suggest you leave him alone.
After I have left, someone will help
you wrap things up on my behalf.
Follow what he tells you to do.
Father... I beg you...
You will have to spend the rest
of your life pretending to be dead.
Because if you ever show up
before Minwoo or me again,
you might no longer
need to pretend that.
Big Oppa...
Until I tell you otherwise,
pretend you don't know me.
Yes?
Ohh... Hyung. Tell me.
What did you just say?
Miju... with Jo Minwoo?!
I'll tell you
everything in detail later.
Is your room empty?
Guess Seongmo convinced her.
Let's get going.
Yes.
Big Oppa...
I did try to tell you earlier...
How long have you
been seeing Minwoo?
You know him?
You're not alone anymore.
Uh?!
I said you're pregnant!
Pre...gnant?!
I'll have a baby?!
Minwoo's father sent me
so that you would get an abortion.
I must talk to Minwoo!
Please...
It's no use, Miju.
I know his father better than anyone!
I can't leave Minwoo, I just can't!
You must, Miju!
Then, how about my baby?
My baby...
What about my poor baby?
Give that baby up.
Give what up?
What's wrong with you?
Please, Miju...
I trust Minwoo.
He will solve everything...
He's more than capable of that!
It's nothing that Minwoo can solve!
Minwoo really loves me.
He can't live without me.
If he learns I'm pregnant, Father...
Don't ever call him that!
Little Oppa...
Never,
ever call that bastard "Father" again.
Gangmo Oppa...
We...
will never accept
you and Minwoo being together.
What's wrong with you two?
Why can't we be together?
Because our father!
Was killed by Jo Pilyeon.
What?
What did you just say?
Are you telling me...
that Minwoo's father...
Back in Busan,
those people who tried to kill us all
were sent by Jo Pilyeon.
And you know all too well...
how Mom died because of them.
But you still want to...
- Miju!
- Miju.
Miju, wake up!
Miju!
I can't even reach her...
Where is she?
Take care of Miju's apartment.
The sooner, the better.
All right.
Thanks, Chanseong.
Where are you going?
I'll just kill that Jo Minwoo.
Gangmo.
Do you know how Miju
and I had to grow up?
Do you know how
I felt after losing her?
You don't...
You don't know...
Calm down, Gangmo.
If anyone kills him, I will.
Don't get involved.
Calm down, Gangmo.
You can't imagine...
You can't!
Jo Minwoo...
Jo Minwoo!
The shareholders' meeting is
right around the corner...
You still don't know
where your father is, right?
He sent me a letter.
Are you sure it was his handwriting?
My stepmother tore the paper apart
so I couldn't look closely,
but I'm sure it was his.
What was it about?
If he sent it to you directly,
it must have been about something.
He says my stepmother
changed his testament.
To oust me from the seat of chairman.
If the chairman doesn't
show up at the meeting, then...
The testament will be presented, I guess.
If that letter isn't just a fake,
I'm sure he'll show up.
But I can't really figure out...
why he still hasn't shown up.
You must get up!
Get up, and rescue your company!
If only for my daughter Jeongyeon,
I must get up!
For the time being,
Miju will have to live with you.
How about the baby?
The longer we wait,
the harder it will be for her.
What can I do...
You poor baby, what now...
Baby...
Baby.
Oppa...
Miju!
Minwoo.
Don't ever look for me again.
We could never
go back to the way it was.
You did nothing wrong.
It's my fault that I need to leave you.
You said you wouldn't forgive me
if I left you a third time, right?
You don't need to.
I wish you happiness,
Minwoo.
You silly...
Hey... Lee Miju!
What did you do to Miju?
Which one of you did it?
What are you talking about, suddenly?
Miju would never
disappear out of the blue.
Where did you send her?
Guess she got scared.
Afraid we'd completely
expose her, she ran away.
What's that supposed to mean?
From what I hear, she had
another man other than you.
And you think I'd believe that?
Ask Seongmo.
He'll tell you every detail.
Don't get Seongmo Hyung
involved in your dirty dealings!
Yes?
It's Seongmo.
Get the phone.
He's asking for you.
All right.
See you there.
They're dead.
Minwoo, Jo Pilyeon...
I'll get rid of them.
Calm down, Seonbaenim.
Miju...
is the only thing I live for.
And they took that away from me.
I have no intention of
living in this world any longer.
Seonbaenim!
Where is Miju?
What did you do to her...
Do I look pathetic to you as well?
But...
Without Miju, I...
Just... kill me, Hyung...
If you're not going
to tell me where she is,
just kill me!
Without her,
my life...
will be meaningless.
I just want to die this way...
Ahh... Hyung!
What is it?
Hyung...
You really feel like a brother.
If it weren't for you,
I would have never endured my father,
and I'd be dead by now.
I love you, man.
You know that?
Minwoo really loves me.
He can't live without me.
I beg you...
Tell me where Miju is.
You know that.
I don't know, either,
so don't ever look for her again.
Hyung...
Hyung.
Hyung!!
Miss Lee Miju?
Come in.
The anesthetic will
soon put you to sleep.
Count from ten, and you'll
fall asleep right away.
Wait.
I'm not doing this.
What?
Gangmo.
Miju?
She's going through surgery.
How is she...
Did the surgery go well?
What?
I'm Lee Miju's guardian.
Ahh... Her.
She said she couldn't do it, and left.
What?
Sorry...
Big Oppa... Little Oppa...
Miju...
Miju!
Miju!!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Did Miju call you?
I have no idea where she went.
You're Miju, right? Miju!
Is that really
Hwang Taeseop's handwriting?
Are you telling me you
won't reveal the testament?
This could get you into trouble.
All you need to do is to
come back once I'm chairman.
Here are the Manbo
Construction shares you bought.
What did you buy all those shares
in Hwang Taeseop's name for?
Put in a good word to turn the tide.
Are you finally starting to wake up?
Don't you get any illusion.
It's not for you, but for Miju's sake.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com