Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 40 -
Your boys are keeping
their mouths shut, I hope?
Yes.
Okay...
I'm going.
The hell are you looking at?
What's the matter?
I'm done, anyway.
If you want to play,
find some money and do it,
stop drooling after other people's cards.
Ehh... You lousy son of a...
You little...
I raise twenty more.
Call.
Triple.
You'll have to forgive me.
Straight.
Ahh... Goddamn...
I haven't seen a full house in ages.
Ehh... Lousy twat,
the hell would you know anyway?
You...
Do you have anything left for me?
Who's that?
He's a Hangang Construction
director, on paper.
But he's really no one special.
Hangang Construction?
Then he must know
Lee Gangmo quite well?!
You think?
He's one of the
company's founding members.
I said give me some more money!
Lee Gangmo is interfering with
your acquisition of that boiler company?
And where would he possibly
have found the money?
I think he's being backed by Baekpa.
Baekpa?!
That old fart is always getting in the way.
With Baekpa's resources,
any bidding war will be
no foregone conclusion.
Listen...
Would you be able to
convince Hwang Jeongyeon...
to present a joint acquisition
bid alongside Lee Gangmo?
You want to drag Lee Gangmo to our side?
If we only manage to do that,
we'd solve all our problems with one strike.
As you're well aware, my top priority
is bringing Hwang Jeongyeon down.
There will be no changes to your plans.
You will just join forces with Lee Gangmo
and present a higher bid than ours.
And once the bid is finalized,
you will take the deposit and
disappear at the last minute.
Then, Lee Gangmo's contract
will be rendered null,
and Manbo Construction will win
the acquisition as the second in line.
That's exactly the plan.
We will end up acquiring
that boiler company,
and you will still manage
to ruin Hwang Jeongyeon.
We will also be able to stop Lee Gangmo
from presenting impossibly high bids.
How about it?
Isn't this having
your cake and eating it?
I understand.
I will try to make it happen.
What are you trying to say?
That we should make a joint bid
along with President Lee?
I think selling my real estate
overseas might take some time.
Just in case,
having him join forces with us...
But he's got no reason to do that.
We're not completely out of options.
I'll start by bringing it up,
so I'd like you to try and convince him.
A joint acquisition?
I'm sure you're well aware...
that such a move would
bring us no benefit whatsoever?!
But if you take a look at this,
you might change your mind.
- Gas Boiler Business Plan -
Isn't this a business plan?
Beaute gas boilers are
tailor-made for radiators,
*underfloor heating via masonry floors
so they're not exactly
compatible with our ondol* culture.
I've been researching to build a Korean-style
gas boiler suitable for our ondol floors for years.
But I've repeatedly been
running into setbacks.
So what you're saying is that you need
Beaute's core technology for your boilers?
That's right.
It's quite the concrete plan, I see.
Yes, since it's been
a few years in the making.
Once the acquisition is complete,
I'll share all my findings with you.
It is certainly fascinating,
but I don't think it's something
that can be decided on a whim.
President Lee, may we have a word?
It will only take a minute.
I think I saw a coffeehouse nearby?
Sure.
Did Lee Gangmo look
like he might fall for it?
Hwang Jeongyeon must be
trying to convince him as we speak.
If she's the one asking,
he won't be able to refuse.
Lee Gangmo asked for a meeting.
He took the bait.
Director Hwang and I
will take care of the deposit.
So you said you'll be investing
about 300 million, right?
Yes.
You will receive ten percent
of company shares,
and will be proclaimed directors as well.
So are we presenting that bid
in Hangang Construction's name?
Since you were the first
to propose this partnership,
let's use your Taeyang Trading instead.
Ahh... Well, that's fine with me.
Kindly sign our joint venture agreement.
As we promised, I will present all
the necessary paperwork for this bid.
What kind of bidding
price were you looking at?
I can't disclose that information.
Are you telling me that you
will keep it secret even to us?
Manbo Construction must be trying
everything in its power to find that out.
So I hope you'll understand.
Still, leaving us in the cold like this...
Isn't that a bit excessive?
I still haven't signed this agreement.
If you disagree with my methods,
we could just pretend no
agreement was ever signed.
Fine.
We're leaving it to your discretion
anyway, so do as you wish.
Thank you, Director Han.
I never imagined
President Lee would do that.
Would you be able to
find out that bidding price?
I mean... I should at least have a
ballpark figure to start gathering those funds.
I know President Lee very well.
He's never going to tell me.
I see you didn't come for the fish,
but to lure some people...
How did you know?
There's this suspicious
fella hiding back there.
Didn't you lure him here?
He works for Jo Pilyeon.
Jo Pilyeon...
If you lure him well enough,
that sure would be a big fish in your net.
So? You couldn't find his bidding price?
I apologize, Congressman.
He's so tight-lipped about this...
Lee Gangmo met with Baekpa again.
The two looked on particularly good terms.
He'll do some heavy betting for sure.
If it's a war fought with money,
we have no reason to fear them.
The real issue is that we
must end up second at all cost.
Doesn't that mean we're pretty much forced
to find out Lee Gangmo's bidding price?
I do have something in mind...
Let's hear it.
A certain Park Sotae works
for Hangang Construction.
Park Sotae?
He's selling raw materials under the table
to fund his gambling escapades.
So you want to use him?
According to my sources, he's one
of Hangang Construction's main men.
He'll be more than capable of
finding out that price for us.
What do you think, Minwoo?
It is true that betrayal for
Park Sotae is like second nature.
But because of his
close ties with Lee Gangmo,
this could actually get us
into even more trouble.
You don't need to worry about that.
I'm a pro when it comes
to people's Achilles' heel.
So you'll find his weak spot?
Nobody addicted to gambling
can resist money's temptation.
You need to be prudent about that.
I'll give it a look first.
Jo Pilyeon is here as well.
I know, Hyung.
Looks like they're giving it their all
to find out your bidding price.
So tell me,
why aren't you asking me to find out
Manbo Construction's price as well?
If they can't find our price first,
they won't easily decide theirs.
I could throw some
misleading information their way.
You could get into trouble again.
Whatever your plans are,
if you need any help,
I'll always be there for you.
Get moving!
Nothing missing, I hope?
There you go. Get out of here.
What the...
What is this?
H...Hyungnim...
What? "Hyungnim"?!
Give me that money.
Wh...What is wrong with you?
Already forgot who helped us
live like decent people?
Do this to Gangmo,
and you'll be punished.
And who the hell is Gangmo?
What's so special about him,
to treat him like some kind of god?
You ungrateful twat.
I always thought of you
as my little brother, you fool.
I wanted to spend the rest of my days
living a honest life with you.
But was this all you amounted to?
I'm afraid that's who I am,
so mind your business,
and get out of the way.
You can't go!
Go beg Gangmo for forgiveness.
Ask for forgiveness,
and make a new start, Sotae.
Ehh... The hell with you!
Sotae!
Stop there!
Stop there, you fool!
Sotae!!
How about it?
Was that good enough for you?
The hell is this?
Ace house...
You're already down ten million tonight?!
You can pay on time, right?
Don't you worry about it.
I'll be paying back the whole sum
before the night is over.
Tell our man to go all out
on him right away.
All right, Hyungnim.
You'll pay it back tonight?
Didn't you say you had
something to talk about?
Gangmo.
From now on, I'll give my entire
salary back to the company.
What's that supposed to mean?
Don't get angry and just listen, uh?
Sotae, that fool...
Aigoo...
That useless, foolish twat...
He's selling aggregate behind our backs.
So that's theft.
Embezzlement, maybe?
So that's why I told you
I'd give up my salary!
Just take my money and
pretend you sold that aggregate.
Uh? Gangmo.
Just as a favor to me.
Don't fire Sotae.
He'll eventually wake up.
I'll take responsibility, Gangmo.
From now on, you'll handle raw materials.
Sotae will go back to office duty.
Right...
So you're going to forgive him
for what he did, right?
I'll buy back the aggregate
he sold with my own money.
- Would that do?
- Thanks, Gangmo!
Aigoo!
Thank you so much, Gangmo!
- Let me pour you a drink.
- Sure!
Thanks, Gangmo.
I'm so thankful...
It's her newly released album.
Your name... Ahh.
It's written here.
Cha Soojeong?!
Yes, PD Seonsaengnim.
Get up.
Shall I sing you a song?
Turn around.
Excuse me?
Are you deaf?
I said turn around.
Come here.
What?
What are you doing?
Go sit next to him.
You know, getting a spot on the radio
for a newcomer like you is no joke?!
When I get to work in the morning,
my desk is filled with tapes like that.
Am I making myself clear?
Pour me a drink.
What?
Serve me a drink.
Why, you can't?
Don't you want to become a singer?
Soojeong...
Come on, serve him that drink.
That's right... You're not too bad?!
- Are you crazy?
- Hey! Soojeong!
I apologize...
What do I have to see...
I'm really sorry, PD Son.
I apologize.
Ahh... Really...
I apologize, Director.
I can't do it.
You mean it?
Yes.
I won't do that.
I quit.
Director...
Go back inside.
Go back in, and tell that man
why you don't want to do it,
and what he did wrong, got it?
I have no intention of forcing you
to do what he asked you.
But I can't tolerate the fact you
ran away as if you did anything wrong.
I'm putting my name on the line
to help you become a singer.
Who the hell are you
to disgrace me like that?
Go get that tape back.
If anyone throws it away, I will.
What's with you?
Am I finally getting an apology?
Give me back my tape.
What?
You don't deserve to listen to this.
Didn't you come here to meet a singer?
Have you been choosing singers this way,
without ever listening to a song?
Are you out of your mind...
You might have the
power to choose singers,
but I'm not going to let
people like you listen to my songs.
I have every right to do so.
Listen to this little brat...
Listen, Director Yoo.
Did you call me here just to
listen to this brat's excuses?
This brat?!
Have you completely
lost your eye for talent?
What?
You just wait.
See what will become of
Cha Soojeong in just a year.
I have no intention of letting
someone who can't tell gems from stones...
handle someone like her.
Let's go.
Hey, Cha Soojeong!
Don't ever dream of becoming a singer.
Is that clear?
You must always be humble,
but never lose your dignity.
You must never be afraid of making
bold decisions, if you want to make it.
Yes, Director.
Let's go.
So that's what happened.
Yes, tell me about it.
We already had him write a
letter of apology for his conduct.
I will make sure his actions
don't affect the other PDs as well.
Were you looking for me, Director?
Who the hell do you think you are?
What?
The disciplinary committee
will terminate your contract soon!
- But, Director...
- Shut your mouth!
I've had it with you,
so get out of my sight!
Right...
Give this a listen.
Cha Soojeong?
She's my niece...
She recorded an album?!
If you like it, give me a call.
Sure.
These days we're facing difficulties
trying to find new talents.
It's not because she's my niece...
I really think you'll fall
for her voice right away.
Your song's still not on?
No, Mom.
Will be on in a minute.
So Mommy's song is
coming out of this thing here?
That's right, Wooju.
Your mother's a singer.
The police is doing what
they can to find her,
but because her address hasn't changed,
looks like it might be difficult.
If they really can't, file a missing
report and start printing leaflets.
All right, Chairman.
Should I turn off the radio?
And now, debuting
singer Cha Soojeong with...
"To you."
You're going to leave me anyhow.
It must have finally come,
Time to leave each other.
My heart is telling me to hold onto you.
But after going back
and forth a thousand times,
It is finally time to say goodbye.
I guess it looks as if I'm laughing,
But it hurts so much I feel like dying.
The path leading me back to you
is disappearing far away.
If we part ways like this,
we might never meet again.
Aigoo... Congratulations, Chairman.
Forget Chairman.
Just call me Director.
But, Chairman.
Director of what?
Aigoo, you brat!
Haven't you seen the sign outside?
Doesn't it say "Urban
Development Research Center"?
Ahh... Urban development.
There's a realtor downstairs,
so all the better!
Aigoo... Enough! Stop with the
nonsense and let's get going.
Aigoo... Right. Chairman.
Come down for lunch,
and if you need anything,
just give us a call.
- Yes, yes...
- You too, Director Ju.
Why is that butt of yours so heavy?
Time to meet Jeongyeon now,
don't you think?
There is something
I must do before that.
Find out how Baekpa
is doing these days.
Baekpa?!
I thought long and hard
where to make my first step.
It's Baekpa.
If Baekpa agrees to help me,
then my first step will leave an
enormously influential footprint.
All right.
I guess it looks as if I'm laughing,
But it hurts so much I feel like dying.
Have you seen Sotae around?
I haven't seen him all day?
He's not even at the site?
Ahh... Really, not seeing him around
automatically makes me nervous.
What's wrong with you?
Stay put!
No... Please...
You know what happens
when that hardens, don't you?
Don't kill me...
It goes straight into the water,
you along with it.
And you won't come out of it
even in a hundred years.
I'll pay that money back!
Isn't that all you need?
I beg you, spare me...
You're already down a hundred million...
How are you going to pay that back?
What... A hundred?!
How can twenty million
suddenly become a hundred?
Still does not know how
we run our business, does he?!
Anyhow,
if you don't pay back that money
before that gets hard...
slang is fishes, but it would be correct
anyway (same species/fish, several/fishes)
Guess you'll end up
sleeping with the fishes?!
No... Please...
- Don't kill me!
- Shut it!
I don't wanna die this way...
Please!
I see there's a much bigger
price on your head, Park Sotae.
Don't kill me... Please...
I can't die this way...
Park Sotae.
Doesn't it feel like, at this point,
I might be the only one
who can save you?
Please... Please help me...
And if I do,
what will I get in return?
Anything... I'll do anything you ask!
Just let me live...
You know I'm trying to
acquire a boiler company, right?
I'll pay back the
hundred million for you,
so find out your company's
bidding price for me.
How about it?
Will you be able to?
Throw him into the water.
- Yes.
I'll do it.
I will...
I'll find out the bidding price.
The bid is this Friday.
You have until the day before
to find out. Is that clear?
Instead, you must
pay my debts at all cost.
The day you bring me that
information, you'll get your cash.
A hundred million.
What are you staring at?
Uh?
It's nothing...
How do I look today?
Went to Myeong-Dong
and got myself a new set.
Why, nothing special?
Yeah.
What's going on?
He'd usually be drooling by now?!
Kinda feels bad?!
What's wrong with him?
Good morning, everyone!
President, good morning.
All come to my office.
Let's have a meeting.
We decided on our bidding price
for the Beaute Boilers acquisition.
We will present a bid for 12.7 billion.
If it's that much, considering they'll be
transferring all the technology to us...
That's quite a figure?!
What if Manbo Construction
presents a higher bid?
They'll think 12 billion
will be sufficient.
I don't think there's
anything to be worried about.
So we're acquiring the company
through that Taeyang Trading or something?
It's a joint venture,
so it doesn't matter much either way.
We're the only ones
who know our bidding price.
You must keep utmost secrecy
until the day of the bid.
Don't you worry, President.
Is anyone of us ever going
to leak something like that?
You can go back to work.
Sotae.
What's this?
Thought you might need it.
Yes.
It's me.
You prepared my money, right?
Where are you now?
I'll send someone your way,
so wait there.
Go to the Namsan Hotel
and bring back Park Sotae.
I'll take him to my office to
avoid any unwarranted attention.
The bidding price.
First give me that briefcase.
Speak.
What will Lee Gangmo's price be?
Twelve...
Twelve-point-seven billion.
12.7 billion...
Then, I'll take this...
Write a receipt first.
That will only be written
after all is said and done.
What?
Instead, that money
is all yours until then.
I can guarantee you that.
After what he said,
think I'd try to steal it from you?
You'll stay here until the bid is over.
As if those 12.7 billion won
turn out to be a lie,
you won't get out of here alive.
I'm 100 percent sure,
so don't worry about it.
12.7 billion is quite the money...
How much do you plan to answer with?
All the others will
reach 12.5 billion at best.
Then, Manbo Construction?
Our goal is ending second.
With about fifty million
less than Lee Gangmo's side,
it should be enough to end second.
Until we acquire Beaute, just stay here.
If you want to catch some fish,
you'll have to change bait more often.
How have you been?
Aren't you Chairman Hwang?
When did you come back from the States?
Yes... A few days ago.
If you don't mind,
can I fish here with you?
As you wish.
Thank you.
You don't seem to have too
much desire to catch fish?!
I've already spent enough years
being consumed by greed.
What else could I possibly covet?
I've also made enough money
to last for a few people.
And I've also experienced
losing it all at once.
I survived a near-death experience,
and have done terrible things to
other people for the sake of personal gain.
It's the frailty of human life.
Desire is fruitless.
So you feel the same way?
Ever since I lost all dreams,
I suddenly feel like doing nothing.
Wouldn't it mean my time has finally come?
Allow me to make you a proposal.
And what kind of proposal would
you make to a feeble old man like me?
I no longer have anything to lose now.
Nor have I anything to show for.
Sir.
Just this once,
allow me to roar at
the world one last time.
All I have left is that passion and
fire that guided my life all these years.
Allow me to spout out that
raging fire one last time, Sir!
What for and against whom
will your last roar be?
Jo Pilyeon, Sir.
Jo Pilyeon?!
Yes!
That scumbag is not even human.
He's a devil in disguise.
I want to punish him
with my own hands, Sir!
Get up now.
Sir!
You've suddenly thrown a dilemma at my feet.
A... dilemma?!
And what would this dilemma be?
I suddenly feel the urge to do something.
I have a newfound desire.
That's all I'll say.
*1985 foundation for the
victims of the Aung San bombing
We have the Ilhae Foundation*,
the Peace Dam...
It's as if the closer to the end of his term
we get, the busier the president becomes.
So where does the scope of your duties
really end, Congressman Jo?
Are you curious?
Why ask such things?
I sure am!
Just thought there was
no reason to hide it among peers...
Whatever the president
wishes for or plans to do,
it is all under my jurisdiction.
No need to spell it out, I hope?!
Doesn't sound like
something I'd brag about?!
What?
For whose sake do you think
those people elected you?
- Congressman Min...
- Go on the streets and take a look.
Not only students, now even average
salarymen are joining the demonstrations!
Congressman Min, that's enough.
Isn't it because people like you
keep misleading the president...
that this country is
going to hell in a handbasket?
Hey! Min Honggi!
I said give it a rest!
I call you here for my birthday,
and look at what I have to witness!
I apologize, Congressman.
But Baekpa said he
wanted to introduce someone...
Why isn't he here yet?
He should be here any moment.
I apologize.
I'm a bit late.
Aigoo... Chairman Hwang?!
When did you make your return?
Are you feeling better?
Yes... Well...
I'm fully recovered now.
It's been quite a long time, indeed.
So, tell me...
How come you two
showed up here together?
Hyungnim wanted to see me.
Hyungnim?!
This fella and I have
vowed eternal friendship.
We're now blood brothers.
You never fail to amaze me,
Chairman Hwang.
You two put together
make quite the impression.
What on earth is wrong with him?
Baekpa is trying to provoke me.
What are you trying to say?
Despite fully knowing
what went on between us,
he took Hwang Taeseop under his wings.
How is our Beaute
acquisition matter proceeding?
Minwoo said he's got it all under control.
Is that so?
Once tomorrow's acquisition is over,
I'll have to focus my attention
on Baekpa and Hwang Taeseop.
Sotae?
They're still keeping him confined.
Will they be able to
find out by tomorrow?
We'll just have to trust Sotae.
- Han Sojin -
REAL NAME Cha Bucheol
Previous Occupations: Loan Shark, Gang Boss
Convictions: 3 for Assault, 6 for Fraud, etc.
Jeongyeon.
Do as he wishes.
I'll tell you
everything in detail later.
My name is Cha Bucheol.
I've heard a lot about you.
So you're being of great help
to Chairman Jo, I hear?
I'm actually the one who's being helped.
He's going to come in handy.
To people like you,
he could become rat poison,
but it could also be the opposite.
I never forgive people who commit sins.
I'm sure you're not the type?!
Of course not.
Here, let me pour you a drink.
So tomorrow's bid should go as planned?
It's already game over.
You just wait.
I'll make him pay back tenfold for what he
made me go through with the Suseo project.
President Lee Gangmo
told me to give this to you.
- Watermelon Apple
Plum Peach Apricot Melon -
How about Park Sotae's whereabouts?
I already found out
where they're keeping him.
This on top, and then...
Okay! All stop!
All stop.
*Three flowers **Five fruits
Hongdan*, Godori**...
*Junk cards that double your points
You have Pibak* and Gwangbak*, so that
would make it, what... and you even swung...
- Double the double, and even...
- Ehh...
Ahh... really!
You flushed your manners
down the toilet, didn't you?
Hey... I'm hungry.
Order something.
Yes!
Hey... Wait. Forget this,
and let's go eat down the street.
You can't take a step
outside this place.
Who ever delivers in the morning?
And yesterday I spent
all day eating jjajangmyeon.
Aren't you tired of that?
Also, if you have any
brains up there, think about it.
Think I'd leave my money
here and run away?
Would you do that?
Of course not!
If I was going to do that,
I wouldn't have even shown up.
I'll treat you!
Ahh... Let's go.
This place is filled.
Wait a moment.
Let's get ourselves
some beers and fruit.
Ajumma, we'd like some fruit.
What should I give you?
Let's see, I don't know how
much money I have left...
Watermelon (100), Apple (10), Plum (1)...
Ohh Ohh...
A watermelon, two apples, and...
Six plums.
The hell are you, setting up shop?
Let me think, what's wrong with you?
How much do I have left here?
Ahh... Right!
Wow, look at those peaches.
Five of those, please.
Five. Yes...
Had sweet dreams last night?
Can you interpret them for me?
I dreamed of eating really tasty fruit.
But, why is Lee Gangmo not around?
You're better off eating fruits than meat.
- Enough with that...
- Just listen.
Vegetables as well, you know?
- Then you'll get a lot healthier than you think.
- Worry about yourself.
- Ma'am.
- Yes.
Some fruit, please.
What can I give you?
You know what those folks just bought?
The same exact amount.
Uh?!
We have no time.
Please.
Yes... Yes.
- Beaute Boilers Korean Subsidiary Sale Bid -
It should start any minute,
where on earth is President Lee?
Ohh... It's me Hyung, go ahead.
Write it down.
One watermelon.
Two apples.
Two apples...
- Six plums.
- Six plums...
Five peaches.
Is that all?
All right.
Thanks, Hyung.
12.65 billion...
12.65 billion?!
We will now start
the Beaute acquisition bid.
We ask every president to please
come forward and convey their bids.
What is going on?
He didn't even tell us the price.
Wait.
President Lee could
never be so irresponsible.
I'll just have to write it down myself.
Wait...
Thought you'd given up.
Think that would be possible?
We're still talking about
a fight against you, after all.
I don't want to lose any
battle against you, either.
Now that all we have to
wait for are the results,
can you finally
tell us our bidding price?
I presented a 12.7 billion won bid.
Don't you think that's a bit excessive?
That's the idea,
to make sure we win that bid.
Wise decision.
12.7 billion should be more
than enough to secure a win.
The company which will acquire the
Korean subsidiary of Beaute Boilers,
presenting a bid of 12.7 billion won,
is Taeyang Trading.
Tell them to let Park Sotae go.
Yes, Chairman.
Here is the contract.
You have all the time to read it,
and if we can confirm the
deposit has been wired by five,
we'll then proceed to sign the contract.
Ahh...
Since we promised we'd
take care of the deposit,
I'll go get it ready.
So you wired the 300
million to my account, right?
Yes.
Go ahead,
we'll be waiting here.
Then...
If the money is not wired by 5,
then the contract will be null.
After which he'll be accused of fraud.
You informed the police already, right?
Of course.
By 5, detectives will
be swarming the place.
But if they end up losing him...
No need to worry.
The man I put on his trail
is never going to fail.
Good job, Jeongyeon.
Thanks to you, I escaped
from a surefire fraud.
And thanks to you, I will
acquire that boiler company.
Not to mention ruining the Jo's plans.
I will withdraw 300 million.
300 million?!
In 10,000 won bills, please.
Please, come this way.
Yes?
It's me, Director Yoo.
Can I talk with Baekpa?
He's sleeping.
Then, convey him a message.
I snatched all of
Hwang Jeongyeon's money.
I won this test.
And I'm afraid
Hwang Jeongyeon will no longer...
Mister Cha Bucheol?
And you are?
You're under arrest for fraud.
Get him!
Let go, you prick!
I said let go!
Hello?
Are you listening?
I said let me go!
What are you doing?
Why is there still no news
from Cha Bucheol?
Director Moon is at the Beaute offices.
Once Lee Gangmo's contract is
rendered null, we'll get our call.
Yes.
It's me, Chairman.
How did it go?
Lee Gangmo's side couldn't
wire the deposit on time.
The bid was invalidated, Chairman.
Yes.
I see.
We made it.
Sotae, that's not how you act
with friends, you twat...
Know how I felt, thinking
you had betrayed us again?
Listen to you...
Think I'm still the old Park Sotae?
Come hell or high water, I'm never
going to betray Gangmo again.
Shideok, when did you find out?
At first I didn't know,
and Gangmo only told me
after Sotae disappeared.
Then I was the last to know?!
You twats have no shame, all right...
Why, did anything happen?
Why are you all taking
it out on Director Park?
Aigoo... Looks like she
has even less of a clue?!
There's no time, let's hurry.
Go faster.
I hear you couldn't pay the deposit?
So what are you doing here?
The boat has already sailed.
Just to congratulate you.
You did the same to me last time,
and you know that debts
should always be paid back.
As Taeyang Trading defied
a few contractual obligations,
the acquisition will be won by
the second highest bidder.
The new owner of Beaute
Boilers' Korean subsidiary,
with a bid of
twelve-point-six-five...
-one (12.651) billion won,
is Hangang Construction.
You...
Didn't you bid in
Taeyang Trading's name?
Hangang Construction
Taeyang Trading
Congratulations, President Lee Gangmo.
Thank you.
President.
I brought the deposit.
Let's go sign the contract.
Park Sotae...
Thank you.
For letting me know your bidding price.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
You know how many times I risked death?
Everyone come at me,
you stinking piles of shit!
Ohh... That's so cool...
Stinking piles...
I'll have to handle
Jo Pilyeon firsthand.
I have a secret weapon against him.
Let me join in.
I want to enter politics.
This is serious.
A boiler exploded.
Again?!
This Cha Soojeong is your sister.
Your death will not put an end to this.
Since your fortune will still be here,
ready for me to snatch it all.
Even if this spells my demise,
the dagger of vengeance
will pierce Jo Pilyeon's heart.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com