Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 37 -
Let me introduce a great newcomer
who will stir up the scene like no other!
Give her an applause!
What are you doing?
Hey... Music.
Turn it on!
Hey... This won't do it.
Get her off the stage
and turn the lights off.
- Lee Eunha's Don't Cry For Me -
Don't cry for me.
Don't be sad for me.
Don't stare at me that way,
With that expressionless face.
Don't fall in love with me.
It's too late by now.
Don't hold your breath waiting for me,
Because our love is now over.
Why did you just
make me leave that day,
If you knew you'd
end up regretting it so much?
You wouldn't have had to
suffer through all these ordeals.
I no longer feel any love for you,
Or any other feeling,
Just like when you sent me away
with that empty smile of yours.
Why did you just
make me leave that day,
If you knew you'd
end up regretting it so much?
You wouldn't have had to
suffer through all these ordeals.
I no longer feel any love for you,
Or any other feeling,
Just like when you sent me away
with that empty smile of yours.
With that empty smile of yours.
What are you doing?
Tell her to come out!
Yes, Manager!
Taxi!
Wait!
Wait there!
Wait! Wait!
She's disappeared?!
Yes... I think she just took off.
What's her name?
They introduced her to us
in a rush, so we couldn't...
Look for her number and find her.
All right, Di...Director.
After all I did
to get this opportunity...
Should have done
a little better, you fool.
Where should I take you, Miss?
What?
Hannam-Dong, please.
Take a look here.
What's that?
Don't!
I'm shooting a film.
A film by Jo Minwoo, starring Lee Miju.
But better give up any box office hopes.
My leading star is too ugly for that...
You're not making it any better,
staring at me that way.
And now, Lee Miju sings a song.
What?
Go ahead and do it.
Come on.
- Jo Yongpil's Bobbed Hair -
I recall this lady who
always brought me flowers.
I wonder why I
miss her so much today.
Her bobbed hair,
finely combed like wet weeds.
Those glittering eyes of hers,
haunting my heart.
Whenever I feel down,
Those days come back to mind.
- Suseo Housing Area Business Conference -
I am truly grateful
for your participation.
Today's conference involves concessions
for the new Suseo residential area.
This project's foremost purpose is dealing
with the metropolitan area's housing shortage,
while at the same time creating
an eco-friendly example...
that will hopefully put an end
to sprawled development,
by developing a residential stronghold
alongside neighboring Suwon and Yongin.
We will now look at how the Suseo
residential area will be partitioned.
We will divide it
into six areas in total,
so let's begin by looking at Area A.
With construction starting in 1986,
the planned completion is for 1988.
And that concludes our conference call
on the Suseo residential area project.
The Deputy Major will now give us
a few comments on the matter.
As everyone should know,
out of all the construction
firms present today,
only a selected few
will take part in this project.
Just as you can expect a fair
and balanced assessment from us,
we ask you to accept any verdict
in the spirit of fair competition.
That would be all.
Lee Gangmo.
Baby...
Just letting you know in case you were
already preparing a champagne bottle...
Minnows like you won't
even enter this Suseo pond.
You're just a competitor like us...
Doesn't feel like anything
you should be bothered with?!
Competitor?!
You still believe that?
Why...
Will you try to lobby
my way out of this, again?
Lobbying is a business, too.
But maybe you're too green
to understand that.
People who only depend on lobbying
are no businessmen, they're just brokers.
Anyhow,
it's survival of the fittest here.
All you can become
is bait for the big fish.
Are you really sure about that?
But, you know...
My eating habits are a bit eccentric.
Any time I see minnows
trying to act like big fish,
I get the urge to devour them?!
Say what?!
Is that all you can say?
Why, did I say anything wrong?
Saw that?
Tail between your legs
when dealing with the strong,
and then going at each other's
throats when they're not around.
That's what you weaklings do.
If you want to go at
anyone's throats, go for ours.
We're the ones who are taking
food away from your table.
Strong, weaklings...
Wouldn't waste time with
such big words if I were you.
Because they're not going to
help you win this showdown.
Is the world really as idealistic
as you make it out to be?
Do you really believe we'll get a
chance to participate in this project?
I can't say,
but shouldn't we create our own opportunities
instead of just waiting for them?
You don't create opportunities,
they are given to you after
being chosen by the higher-ups.
Right as we speak, we might be
sharing a bottle of cheap soju,
but the construction committee will be
already putting its lobbying power to use.
It's game over already.
That's the wretched reality we're facing.
Manbo Construction will be dealing
with the everglades in Suseo.
Your respective areas are listed there.
Then, the only lot left
is Area B, isn't it?
Area B... Isn't that Dolsan*?
*literal meaning: rocky mountain
That's right.
We'll let the other competitors
fight each other over that area.
It's pretty obvious it'd be
more trouble than it's worth,
who would ever
undertake such a project?
That's for them to worry about.
As long as we can live up to our
end of the bargain, that'll be all.
But... Are you sure they're
going to follow this plan?
The reason I preside over
this committee...
is because I have never
disappointed you in matters like this.
Isn't that right?
It's been such a long time...
Can't ignore each other
like that, can we?
Is there anything I can help you with?
Will you do me a favor?
Sure.
Start worrying about
Manbo Construction.
Because the day when I'll
take it back is not too far off.
It's ludicrous, no doubt...
But I'm glad that verve of yours
still hasn't died down.
Don't take my words lightly.
Or you'll one day regret it dearly.
Here are all the bill
collections for this month.
I've already wired all the money.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Baekpa would like to see you.
Did he mention why?
You'll find out when you meet him.
What separates the living from the dead...
is the fact that they still have dreams.
If you have no dreams
despite being alive,
you're no different from a corpse.
So what is your dream?
I want all the money in this world.
And what would you do with it?
I'll buy the dreams I
haven't been able to fulfill.
So I see that collecting interests...
wasn't a complete waste of time.
Inside that account
are 400 million won.
Take this money and
buy that dream of yours.
Sir...
I won't set any
deadline or interest rate.
Instead,
if you end up losing that money,
you'll have to leave
this business for good.
What I mean is that you will
never get another chance to dream.
Yes, Sir.
I will use this money to succeed.
You may go now.
Thank you, Sir.
It won't be easy for her.
If she can endure this trade,
she'll attain great success,
but if she can't, she will lose
all happiness along with that money.
I'll make it.
I'll succeed,
and get back Manbo Construction...
with my own hands.
- Happy Credit -
Same-Day Loans, Low Interest Rates
How about now?
It's slanted.
A little more to the right.
Now?
A little to the left.
Just a little... A little...
Ohh... Okay.
I told you we needed a man for this.
But shouldn't we
have an opening ceremony?
We still aren't done with the
leaflets, there's plenty to do.
Follow me.
- Quick and Precise Loans -
Happy Credit is Here For You!!
- Should work, right?
- Ohh, Eonni, it will go well.
Come here!
Who was that, Eonni?
What are you two doing here?
Who gave you permission to do this?
Take them off.
Yes, we apologize.
Do it now!
Yes, right away.
- Where are you going?
- I said now!
I said I will, just a moment!
Ahh... What do I have to see, really...
Will you take it off or not?
I will, just a moment...
A moment.
So do it!
What are you waiting for?
I said I'll take them off!
This is serious, Gangmo.
They just announced
the Suseo concessions,
and they all went
to committee members!
Who brought this?
I wasn't expecting one from anybody?!
Maybe it's Director Yoo
of the Royal Club?
All the better... Now this will
really create that opening atmosphere.
What about us?
The only lot left in this
Suseo project is Area B.
But isn't the entire area
covered by a rock bed?
And you want us to work there?
We will accept applications
until the end of the week.
This is excessive.
So you leave all the best spots
to huge corporations,
and are forcing us to take
a fall and build there instead?
I'm afraid your complaints
will make no difference.
Here... You may leave now.
Tell me.
What kind of standards were used
in choosing the candidates?
I'd like to know in detail what criteria
were used during your assessment.
Or else, neither I nor these people
will accept this decision.
That's natural.
I will be happy to tell you.
Citizens from Suseo and the neighboring
area formed a housing cooperative.
Our selection was based upon
this cooperative's requests.
Is there anything else
you'd like to say?
- Area B -
Manbo Construction has been
buying land in Suseo for years.
After which they transferred
many of their employees there.
Then, that housing cooperative...
It was formed by
Manbo Construction employees.
Same goes for the
other committee members.
Then, you're suggesting
they plotted this all along?!
They found out before everyone else
that Suseo would be next in line.
The only way to join this project
is applying for the Dolsan area.
As it stands.
Dolsan?!
So you're telling me that Lee Gangmo
will be forced to choose that,
if he wants to join this Suseo project?
Because it's the only lot left.
It's obvious that they'd
end up deep in the red,
will they even bother?
The New City development plan
will be based on this project's results.
Lee Gangmo will try to join
the construction whatever it takes.
Even if he tears down the entire
Dolsan and builds his apartments,
I will be put in charge
of the New City development.
And that's because I'll make
sure that's what happens.
Look down on your foes and you
might even lose an easy battle.
I will get going.
Dolsan is out of the question.
Here.
The entire area is a rock bed.
If you want to build foundations,
you'll first need to get rid of those rocks.
How are you going to pay for that?
Fine, then... Let's suppose we'll run
ourselves dry and deal with that.
What will you do with all those rocks?
If you only count transportation fees,
it'll be enough to build a few apartments!
So to make a long story short,
the game is not worth the candle.
We should just give up
this Suseo project.
And if we do,
we'll be left out of the
New City concessions as well.
Still, we can't just go for it,
when we know it'll bring us great losses.
I think there could be a way...
Really?
Like what?
Every time he says that,
I get chills down my spine.
Gyeongja.
Bring me a list of all the companies
excluded from these concessions.
Yes, President.
Are you suggesting we form a
joint construction syndicate?
I have a verbal agreement with
Deputy Mayor Han Myeongseok.
He promised that if we form a syndicate,
he will grant us government funding.
And you think that kind
of funding comes free?
That's all money
you'll have to pay back!
If you're really that
confident, do it by yourself.
We can't help you with this.
How much longer are you going
to let them walk over you?
If we're weaker than them, shouldn't
we join our forces and fight together?
Think we don't want to fight them?
Just a project gone wrong,
and anyone of us could be closing up shop.
- Let's just go.
- Right.
Listen to me!
President!
President.
President Lee...
You came all the way here to meet me?
- Inn -
The deadline is tomorrow.
I'm counting on you.
Try to convince the others for me.
When I was your age,
I had just the same
energy and verve as you.
But, have you seen me now?
I'm just a coward.
A coward who fears every last
of the month, when salaries are paid.
Losses?!
That's part of the game.
But, you know what?
My company couldn't cope with that now.
Hundreds of lives are
hanging from my pockets...
By any chance,
did you lose your house
because of that?
Because of me,
my family got separated
and is facing hell.
I guess drinking made me
lose myself in nonsense again...
Get going.
Seonbaenim,
you're no coward.
If you truly had been one,
you would have never given up
your house for your employees' sake.
Even if I have to do it alone,
I will join this project.
If only not to betray
my employees' expectations,
I will never give up
on this construction.
Thank you.
You taught me what real courage means.
There are only 10 minutes
left before the deadline!
I don't think they're coming.
But what if he refuses funding
without that syndicate?
That was his condition for
giving me government funding.
This won't do it...
We'll just have to apply by ourselves.
But you said this
construction could fail...
We'll have to give our best to the end.
- President Lee!
Sorry for being late.
Had to convince these gentlemen, so...
So you're all joining in?
You've taught me courage as well!
Let's all join forces.
We have no time to waste!
Let's run!
Here...
Here is this month's addition
to the president's account.
I've heard some rumblings
about possible M&A's...
If you know anything
about this, could you...
I don't accept money from anyone.
But I've heard that our
Buseong Group could be in danger.
At the last party
organized by the president,
I've heard that you
made quite the blunder...
Is it because of that?
If you made any blunder,
couldn't you just make up for it?
Please, help me out.
I'll keep in contact.
You may leave.
This month's addition to the
secret fund has just been wired.
You can verify it.
Already did.
Good job.
The higher-ups are
quite satisfied as well.
I think choosing you
was a wise decision.
Whatever it is, just say the word.
Come on in, Minwoo.
Called you so that we could
all go out for drinks.
I'm a little busy at work,
so I guess you'll
have to go without me.
Minwoo, are you still resenting him?
I'd like to postpone it
to another day as well.
I've got work left to do.
Let's have a word, Hyung.
Miju...
You really don't know where she is?
Told you not to
mention her again, didn't I?
It's been four years.
No matter how hard I try,
four years without leaving
a trace is hard to believe.
Stop looking for her.
You're only going to make life
worse for the both of you.
No...
I'm strong enough to
protect Miju from my father now.
I don't need your help.
I'll just find her on my own.
They're so cute...
Come on i...
You...
How could you just leave like that?
Do you know how long
we've been looking for you?
I apologize.
- If you've lost a lot of money because of me...
- What's your name?
What?
Lee... Miju.
Is this store yours?
No...
There's an owner,
I'm just an employee here.
No other experience on the stage?
None.
You're not seeing anyone, are you?
What?
The director wants to
sign a contract with you.
An exclusive contract.
R...Really?!
If you want to work for me,
your private life needs to be clean.
Can you promise me that much?
Yes...
Then, I'd like to sign it right here...
Here's the contract,
so give it a read and seal it.
You must leave no trace of all this.
If people learn of this,
both you and I will
be as good as dead.
Are we clear?
We are.
The day you die,
I will die as well, Jo Pilyeon.
By building a huge embankment here,
the everglades we secured will become
the most expensive land in Suseo.
Nice.
Your business acumen
is improving by the day.
But, from what I hear,
Lee Gangmo chose Dolsan?
It's what I'd hoped for.
Lee Gangmo never disappoints.
It might be a problematic
area to deal with,
but that fella is scary.
He wouldn't make that
kind of choice without a plan.
Dolsan is well under control.
You don't need to worry.
Chairman.
Please, follow me.
What is the matter?
A line of construction machinery
heading for Area B is forming outside.
If it's Area B...
Lee Gangmo.
- Suseo Area B Apartment
Joint Construction Syndicate -
How do you do, Congressman Jo?
You spared no expenses, I see.
We need at least this much
to deal with that rock bed.
Aren't you pushing it?
It's likely you'll run out of money
before you touch a single brick?!
If I were alone,
I guess you'd be right.
But, can you see that?
So you're all in on this?
Couldn't take a few pompous fools
acting all important anymore,
so these weaklings
got together for once.
Take a good look.
How mere grains of sand can gather
together to make your mountain collapse.
Let's move.
And you said you had everything
under control... What is this?
I never imagined all those smaller
enterprises would get together.
You must stop them.
If he manages to succeed here,
Lee Gangmo will get involved with
the New City development as well.
You must stop Hangang Construction
from growing any further.
I see you've been dealing
with quite the loan sharks.
We're trying to pay what is due, but
they don't pick up the phone on purpose.
It's a pretty common trick they use.
If we lose the house...
She's even fallen ill.
We will both end up on a street.
Let's wake up, and start by
paying your deposit via the court.
Then, your debts will all be cleared.
Was there such a way?
But do you have enough
money to pay those debts?
Not the principal, just the interest...
We'll help you with that,
so start by paying off the interest.
What?
Can you really do that for us?
I'm just doing it so that you won't
have to deal with those loan sharks again.
Thank you, Miss.
Our rates will be based
on interest rate-caps,
so don't miss your payments.
Should there be any delays,
expect legal litigation.
We will pay down to the last penny.
She will let you in on
all the other details.
- Yes, yes...
- This way, please.
So they had you write a body forfeit
contract for a mere million won.
Yes...
As they threatened
to sell off my kidneys...
Let's be clear on this.
Body forfeit contracts
have no legal validity.
A private lender giving legal counsel?!
I wonder if she'll be all right...
While offering legal counsel,
Jeongyeon is taking customers
away from those loan sharks.
I've never seen anyone in the
lending business work this way.
But, if she keeps doing that...
You just wait.
She'll be just as meticulous
in collecting her interests.
Hearing you say that
does reassure me a little.
I think it's time we put her
through a little test.
Isn't it too early for that?
Why, does it worry you?
Ohh... Maybe we should use Bucheol?
If she ends up overcoming Bucheol,
then she might be ready
for bigger responsibilities.
That's certainly true, but...
I don't think Jeongyeon is ready...
No test will ever
be as harsh as reality!
If you really have
Jeongyeon's fate at heart...
Sir...
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Let me listen to the
Heart Sutra and go.
Of all people,
that ruthless loan shark?!
Forty-two...
Forty...three...
Forty...fo...fo...four...
Looks like you've been
working out here for long?
Don't really like
women with muscles...
Welcome, Congressman Oh.
If you'll please escort us to where
the committee members are...
- This way, please.
- Let's go.
About that new singer
we saw last time.
Doesn't she sing here?
Why...
Are you interested as well?
Her performance that night
really left an impression.
A lot of people are
looking for her, actually.
I'll bring her here soon.
Let's have a toast.
I apologize for being late.
President Lee, come on in.
Have a seat.
You're really working hard these days.
Let me pour you one.
You know...
I was really touched by what I saw
at the Dolsan construction site.
If that "turning the impossible
into reality" mentality...
is not what our country
needs to survive, what is?
You're flattering me, Sir.
Just in case...
If you manage to deal with that rock bed
and build some solid apartments there,
I'll take full responsibility and
entrust the New City development to you!
Congressman, making such statements
in their presence is a little...
A little what?
I always called a spade
a spade, and always will!
And honestly, if he manages to succeed
at something everyone else tried to avoid,
doesn't that itself
vouch for his abilities?
Sure, it sure does!
Doesn't this call for
a toast, Congressman?
Ohh... Shall I?
Here...
Let's see those glasses.
To the successful development
of our Suseo project!
Cheers!
This is my pride and dignity.
With this as collateral,
how much can you give me?
What?
This is the first
of its kind in our country.
Sir, I'm afraid you
misunderstood what we do here...
And it doesn't stop here.
Here.
Take a look at this.
It's used in stonemasonry, and with this
you can deal with any kind of rock.
We developed this.
Eonni... I'm here.
Will you only pay the interests again?
Even that alone is hard.
Why bother building in that area...
Will you do it or not?
Gyeongja said she's
gaining quite the reputation,
and I guess she's
also making good money.
Gangmo.
Can't you two get back together?
Even Chairman Hwang
asked for forgiveness...
And you forgave him.
That won't change the fact that
he's responsible for my father's death.
Sorry, Gangmo.
It must be so hard for you...
As long as Jeongyeon is doing fine,
that's enough for me.
With Oh Byeongtak and
Min Honggi supporting him,
stopping Lee Gangmo's
subsidies will be hard.
Is that so?
Then, as bothersome as it might be,
I'll need to move onto Plan B.
You already had something in mind?
If there's anything in life
that can easily break,
that's a business partnership.
So you want to go
for the syndicate itself?
Since that was the
condition to receive funding,
even his subsidies will bear the brunt.
So you'll turn his hidden card
into his own Achilles' heel?!
It's a brilliant plan.
Director Moon.
Yes, Chairman.
Find everything there is to know about
Lee Gangmo's fellow syndicate members.
Everything from company status
to their personal lives.
Certainly, Chairman.
We barely got started,
aren't we spending too much already?
We'll receive funding by next month.
Still, this is much too expensive.
Let's endure it a little longer.
Our destiny depends
on this construction.
President Maeng Gukhyeon
of Ogam Construction.
As it stands, he's facing the
biggest cash flow crisis of them all.
Even his private residence was
taken by the bank as collateral.
Setting aside Lee Gangmo,
he's practically the syndicate's leader.
Call him and set up a meeting.
All right, Chairman.
A joint syndicate...
Weaklings are easily pulverized,
just like grains of sand.
I see you were already here.
- As we already explained on the phone...
- You'll forgive me,
but I can't break off this partnership.
Of course that doesn't hide the fact
I find your proposal quite alluring,
but President Lee Gangmo
did a lot for us.
What was our proposal again?
To pay back his bank debts
at zero interest.
We can add all expenses for
your current construction project.
Same goes for all the other members
with the exception of Lee Gangmo.
Would that suffice to convince you?
If you don't think you
can make it, just fold.
Call.
Straight.
5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Ahh... And of all times,
look when a full house shows up.
Almost makes me feel sorry.
Jeongshik, aren't you losing too much?
Give him a winner's tip...
He's had it hard enough.
If you need any more money,
feel free to ask.
No need.
You people... Don't even
dream of going home and wait.
If even one of you leaves,
consider yourselves dead!
Is that clear?
So he's still acting as if he's
the heir of Manbo Construction?!
Here... Card.
- Let's have another round.
- Okay!
So it's tomorrow's flight at four?
All right.
Yes...
I will wire the money to your account.
Of course...
Need to keep one's promises.
Yes, thank you.
Yes...
So Hwang Taeseop is coming back?!
Jeongshik...
What are you doing?
Mom...
Give it to me.
The seal... Where's the seal?
You little...
You gamble all day,
and now even steal?!
Mom... This is the last time.
I swear!
You said the exact
same thing last time!
Give it here.
Hey... Hwang Jeongshik!
Are you going to wake up or what?
Ahh... Just back off!
Mom... Sorry...
This time I mean it... I mean it,
it's the last time.
- I'm sorry.
- Jeongshik...
What can I do...
What do I do with him?
This is all my fault.
I didn't raise him properly.
Aigoo, what about my boy now?
How have you been?
I'm fully recovered now.
Take a look... I'm just fine.
Also...
I didn't call Jeongyeon on purpose.
We have all the time to meet later.
Here... Let's get going.
Taxi! Taxi...
What the hell are they doing?
Who is that wench
to come all the way here?
We might be divorced,
but he's still Jeongshik's father.
I have the right to
discuss our children.
That's nice.
Stop making all that noise.
All right.
Where are you going to stay?
Ahh... Well...
I didn't have the time to
make any hotel reservation?!
Stay at my apartment
for the time being.
Will be much better
than staying at a hotel.
Shall I?
Let's do that, then.
What are your plans?
You see this?
It's filled with business plans.
I've already secured
investment in the States.
Don't you worry, Gyeongok.
I'll soon jump back onto the scene.
I'll start a huge venture that will make
Manbo Construction pale in comparison.
I got it all cleaned in the morning.
I'll get going.
Will you?
Director Ju, shall we unpack?
Have some rest.
I'll come again tomorrow.
Business plans, my ass.
The bank balance is
pretty much done as well.
Jo Pilyeon, you son of a bitch...
I won't find peace until
I kill that rat bastard.
Come on in.
So we meet again?!
Can't you recognize me?
Right... At the Health Club.
So you run this place?
I see you have a lot
of real estate overseas?!
How much were you looking to borrow?
How much can you give me?
We only give small loans here.
I'd like to go for about 500 million?!
I'll introduce you
to some colleagues, then.
Just a hundred, then.
Even that is too much for us.
How about fifty?
You can lend me fifty, can't you?
Come back tomorrow.
After we're done examining your
documents, we'll give it a try.
Yes.
Check it, everything is in order.
He has a lot of real estate,
judging by those documents...
Check them thoroughly.
I have a bad feeling about him.
At first glance, all she's got is
probably two to three hundred million.
It's kind of disappointing,
but that Hwang Jeongyeon
is really something?!
Well done!
Great job.
It's about time someone shows him
that everyone should know his place.
Any good news, Sir?
Lee Gangmo is about to go bust.
Then, did Minwoo manage to
create a rift in the syndicate?
He did.
And with no partnership,
his funding will soon run dry.
How is he going to dispose of
all that rock and build apartments?
Being reckless is a sin.
He deserves to be punished for it.
Why did your employees leave the site?
We decided to abandon this project.
You did what?
We can't face any more losses.
What's that supposed
to mean? You leave now?
What do you suppose we do?
Deal with that rock bed
all by ourselves?
Instead, we'll pay for all
construction costs up to this point.
Does that make any sense?
I'm sorry, President Lee.
We'll soon receive government funding.
President Lee...
Can't you... Can't you
endure it just a little longer?
Gangmo...
Are you going to
let them leave like that?
Won't make any difference.
They were bought off, by Jo Minwoo.
What?
It was all a scheme by him.
Jo Minwoo?!
- Gangmo!
- Let go!
- You've lost all reason!
- You bet I did.
There's no stopping me now.
Gangmo...
That's the piece of shit
who ruined our Miju!
And now he's trying to ruin me as well!
And in conclusion, you've become
chairman at such a young age,
can you tell us your future aspirations?
I have a keen interest in the
social role corporations can play.
Profits are certainly important,
but they always pale in comparison
with the contribution your...
What is President Lee Gangmo of
Hangang Construction doing here?
There's a limit to my patience!
So, what?
Are you gonna hit me?
Think I couldn't?
If you want your face on
every major newspaper's front page...
Be my guest.
You don't have the guts to do that.
Know why?
Because you can act tough all you want,
but you still remain a weakling.
A joint syndicate?!
Know why you were swept away
like leaves under the autumn wind?
Because you're weak.
And a bunch of cowards.
So that's why you'll never make it.
You'll only be bait for the big fish.
Gangmo...
Weakling?
Coward?!
I told you, didn't I?
That any time I see pompous fools
trying to act like big fish,
I get the urge to devour them!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Manbo Construction is just
hoarding all raw materials.
The price of raw materials
has more than doubled.
Isn't this because
you've been hoarding them all?
Can you see this?
Can you?
This mountain is a goldmine!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com