Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 35 -
How is she...
Did the surgery go well?
What?
I'm Lee Miju's guardian.
Ahh... Her.
She said she couldn't do it, and left.
What?
Miju!
Miju!!
Sorry...
Big Oppa... Little Oppa...
Did Miju call?
No.
Did you find out where she could be?
I asked her friends
and looked everywhere...
I have no idea
where she might have gone.
It's our fault.
She must have been
shocked by all this.
Nah... I'm the only one to blame.
I should have dealt with this
more carefully from the very start.
Hello?
Miju, is it you?
It's you, right?
Answer me, Miju.
Sorry... Little Oppa.
Miju!
I've made you
really angry, haven't I?
No, Miju.
It's all right.
You didn't make us angry.
Hello?
Miju.
Where are you now?
We'll come to get you.
Give me some time.
All right, as you wish.
Going through that all alone
must have been scary.
And we didn't even realize that...
I'm really sorry, Miju.
I'm sorry, Miju.
Don't be, Oppa.
I just need a few days on my own,
and then I'll come back strong as ever.
You can't even eat properly,
how can you remain all alone?
I just wanted to be alone
for a few days, that's all.
All right, then.
Instead, you must call us every day.
Are we clear, Miju?
Yeah, Big Oppa...
Jo Minwoo, that son of a bitch!
I won't let him get away with this.
They just fell for each other.
Hyung!
If only for Miju's sake,
I think it would be better
to just forget about it.
Dearest Manbo
Construction shareholders.
I am Chairman Hwang Taeseop.
I'm rapidly recovering as we speak.
I ask you to kindly cancel the
upcoming shareholders' meeting.
I will soon fully recover
and meet you in person,
after which I will organize the
next shareholders' meeting firsthand.
Mom!
Shareholders are storming
the offices with phone calls.
They're asking whether the
meeting will really be canceled.
Don't let this intimidate you.
What do we do now?
What do you think?
We'll present that
testament as planned.
If he can manage to write letters,
wouldn't it mean
he has fully recovered?
Your father hasn't recovered.
And how do you know that?
He could have just shown up
and it'd be the end of it,
why threaten us with letters like this?
You don't need to worry.
Ahh... But a look at that letter,
and it looks like he's about
to show up there for real?!
Bring me some water.
What? Yes, Ma'am.
I'll go meet my lawyer,
so get the car.
Yes, Ma'am.
Hello?
Chairman!
Aigoo...
Sure, everything is fine!
Where are you now, Chairman?
He...Hello?
Is it you?
Hello?
Say something!
Hello... Hello!
Was it Dad?
Was it really him?
Was that really the chairman's voice?
Yes... Without a doubt.
Mom...
Blow harder.
Give it another try.
You must eat this, Chairman.
Only then you'll get back on your feet.
It's you.
She must have gotten rid
of that child, by now?!
I escorted her to the hospital myself.
So, that Miju...
Where is she now?
I witnessed her moving out of her house,
but don't know her new destination.
She won't ever show up
before Minwoo again,
so you don't need to worry.
All right. Good job, Seongmo.
How is Minwoo doing?
Looks like he hasn't come to work again.
- I ought to just teach him...
- I think...
it would be wiser to just
leave him alone for a few days.
Is this the time?
Seongmo, you go and
try to reason with him.
Don't you even know
where she moved to?
No...
We're looking for her as well.
But what happened to you two?
You didn't break up, did you?
If you hear anything about her,
please give me a call.
They did...
They broke up, Eonni.
I could barely recognize him.
Thanks to you,
I found happiness for
the first time in my life.
I'll never let you go.
So don't even dream about leaving me.
Minwoo...
To make you mine,
there's nothing I can't do.
Miju!
Hey... Lee Miju!
I can't live without you.
I said I can't live without you!
Where on earth are you?
Where have you gone...
Miju... Lee Miju!!
I can't meet you anymore.
You even fell in love
with someone like me...
I'm sorry, Minwoo.
I'm sorry.
I love you, Minwoo.
Oppa!
Oppa...
Gyeongja is here! I'm here!
Here...
Let's have a toast.
I hope you'll always work here
with a smile on your face.
And that is because this will always be
the base upon which we build.
Let's all cheer.
Here... To our Hangang
Construction's future!
Cheers, cheers, cheers!
President...
Let me pour you a drink.
Thanks.
All right.
- Here...
- It's all right, I can handle it.
Gyeongja?
Tastes good?
Have a drink, brother-in-law.
Ohh... Sure, go ahe...
You little prick,
how dare you say that?
What... Brother-in-law?!
What's wrong with you?
When did I ever call you that? When?
I'm completely innocent.
Did I call him that?
Yeah... Heard it loud and clear.
And when did I
ever say that, you fool?
"Fool"?!
Finding any excuse to
call me that, you twat?
Did I just call him fool,
brother-in-law?
Here he goes again
with that "brother-in-law"!
Ohh... President Lee.
Seonsaengnim.
Here's how Manbo Construction's
stocks are faring.
They keep falling non-stop?!
And these are the Manbo Construction
shares I bought with the money you gave me.
Good job.
But why did you buy so many
shares in Hwang Taeseop's name?
It's a long story.
What on earth is going on here?
The meeting is being postponed?
Here's the letter I
received from Hwang Taeseop.
If you go ahead and
reveal that forged testament,
you can consider yourself dead!
You better not take my warning lightly.
Is this really
Chairman Hwang's handwriting?
Yes.
It perfectly matches
his original testament.
So, what,
are you telling me you
won't disclose the testament?
If we do that now,
the repercussions could be fatal.
A Hwang Taeseop on the brink
of death suddenly disappears,
and now blackmail?!
Doesn't this smell a little strange?
So how about it?
This is a fake.
A meticulously devised forgery.
I don't know who's
helping Chairman Hwang,
but he's quite the resourceful fella.
Everything is going fine here,
so don't you worry.
You know the shareholders'
meeting has been postponed, right?
Thank you for all the help, Ajeosshi.
I'll be there in a moment.
What is Jeongshik's mother
trying to kill the chairman for?
I heard she was going to fix his
testament, but that's all I know.
Don't worry.
They're just supplements.
The chairman?
He's completely lost all motivation.
Gangmo...
Can't we tell Jeongyeon
about you helping the chairman?
I'm not doing this for Jeongyeon's sake.
Don't tell her.
Take it.
They're the Manbo
Construction shares I've bought.
Jo Pilyeon is taking away
your fortune behind your back.
And this is what I bought
with the money I stole from him.
If you feel wronged,
then get back on your feet.
Do it, and protect Manbo
Construction from Jo Pilyeon.
Gangmo...
It's over for me.
Just resign yourself.
You might have given up
on this, but I can't!
I can't let Jo Pilyeon gain
control of Manbo Construction!
Harder! Don't let go!
A bit more...
I've managed to stop them from
revealing that testament for now,
but I won't last long.
If you want to show up
before them in good shape,
you must shed ten, a hundred
times more sweat and tears.
This letter was sent from Gangnam?
That's right.
Search all the
rehab centers in Gangnam.
All right, Ma'am.
Dearest Director Yoo Gyeongok.
I am proposing to cancel the
upcoming shareholders' meeting.
I plan to organize another
meeting once I can stand before...
you all after a full recovery, so...
I ask you to kindly give me some time.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
I'm a little late.
No.
It's a letter the chairman sent to me.
The meeting was postponed, after all.
But this letter is a fake.
A fake?!
I'm sure of it.
And what makes you think that?
If he was going to send me a letter,
he wouldn't have addressed me that way.
But there is no doubt that
this is my father's handwriting.
What's the reason
you're so sure it's a fake?
The chairman would have
never called me "director."
Then, what else would he call you?
He's always...
called me Madam.
I'll just have to file
a missing report with the police.
I think it would be wiser
to postpone that for a while.
Still...
I don't know who took the chairman,
but we're now sure
he's trying to help you.
Does anyone capable
of this come to mind?
No matter how hard I try,
I can't think of anyone.
Who is trying to help me...
Couldn't it just be
Hwang Taeseop's daughter?
For that to be the case, this whole
scenario feels a little strange.
Strange?
What makes you say that...
All Hwang Taeseop needs to make
that testament useless is showing up.
She could oust
Hwang Jeongshik right away,
why just buy time trying to stop
it all by writing these letters?
The only one who knows our plans
and is trying to get in the way...
is Lee Gangmo...
You're not telling me
he's behind this again...
Wouldn't Lee Gangmo be the first to
wish for Manbo Construction's downfall?
Whomever it might be, what's for sure
is that Hwang Taeseop is recovering.
Jaechun, you go tell the lawyer
to go ahead with the meeting.
All right.
Hyung.
What's the matter?
You didn't even call me.
Have you heard of
Chairman Hwang's disappearance?
Yeah.
Someone is using him
to blackmail Jo Pilyeon.
Is that what Jo Pilyeon told you?
That someone was
using Chairman Hwang.
By any chance,
are you that "someone"?
I'm asking if you're the one
who's taking care of Hwang Taeseop.
What makes you think that?
If you're indeed helping him,
stop right now.
It's not me, Hyung.
I have no doubt that Jo Pilyeon
is the one who's making sure...
Manbo Construction
doesn't resume its project.
Is there no other way
to resume construction?
That's surprising.
I thought you and Manbo Construction's
top brass were on bad terms?!
I only want to compete
with them honestly.
Is that so?
Interesting.
Hwang Jeongyeon seemed to believe
you're the one behind all this?
Looks like I should be the one
to clear this misunderstanding.
No.
There's no need for that.
The fight is not over yet.
It would be wise to abandon
all your illusions of victory.
Agasshi, Gangmo is the one...
You better wake up,
Hwang Jeongyeon.
What?
Don't let anyone get his hands on Manbo
Construction before I bring you down.
Take good care of it.
Jo Pilyeon is keeping the
construction from resuming...
to get his hands on the company.
Go ask Commissioner Han
if you don't believe me.
He'll confirm what I just told you.
If what he says is right...
Jo Minwoo hasn't
come to work again, has he?
It's been a few days already.
Yes.
Minwoo...
Hey...
Minwoo!
Look at you...
This won't do.
Come back home with us.
Honey.
Call some of your men and bring
him home even against his will,
we can't leave him here any longer.
Leave us alone.
Honey...
I just want to have a word with him,
so don't worry and go.
Aigoo, look at what meeting
that wench has done to my son...
Ahh... It's so upsetting...
I wished you'd just close this chapter
and come out of here on your own feet.
I like that fire in your eyes.
At times, hatred can become the
perfect catalyst to achieve one's goals.
Dream on.
I'm never going to let your goals...
control my life again.
Take a look at this mirror.
See how pathetic and foolish you look.
Why don't you look at it yourself?
See how wicked
and cruel you really are.
Know what people the world likes
to call "villains" have in common?
They're exceptionally thoughtful.
Theirs is a reality that
is not made for everyone,
and they merely live abiding by
their own personal set of values.
Weaklings and minions like to call them "evil"
just to feel better about themselves.
So you still think you lost
your beloved because of me, I bet?
All I did was
protecting my beloved son.
That's the difference
between you and me.
That I succeeded in
protecting you, and you lost her.
Because you still are no match for me.
One day,
old age will cause my downfall.
And I wish the only man who
manages to bring Jo Pilyeon down...
will be you, Minwoo.
If you can't defeat me,
you'll never gain what you
want for the rest of your days.
Are we clear, son?
I'll cover your ears,
so just close your eyes.
Then, you'll suddenly feel at peace.
Miju...
Miju.
I'm sorry, Miju.
I should have protected you.
I'll get a hold of myself.
I will find you again at all cost.
And when that happens,
you won't have to
witness me in this state.
Miju, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
You have a guest, Ma'am.
Miju...
Ma'am...
How did you find this place?
You wrote me that letter,
saying you were moving here from Jeju.
I'm so glad you came, Miju.
I was just thinking of
how much I missed you.
I'm relieved to see you in good health.
Did you already have lunch?
I'm so hungry I could die.
Will you cook me lunch?
Tell me...
Something is up, isn't it?
Why?
Does it look that way?
You'd always start eating non-stop
whenever something was up.
Everything's fine.
How did it go with that man?
What?
You said you fell in love with
someone in those letters you sent me.
That you might get married soon.
Come here, Miju.
Come on.
I know...
Even if you don't tell me,
I can imagine.
Must have been hard?
And painful.
Ma'am...
That's right...
Cry all you want.
Let it all out, Miju.
Your guest is here.
Come on in, Jeongyeon.
You're a bit late.
Have a drink.
Don't you worry about a thing.
You'll soon be able to
resume the construction.
Chairman Hwang and I are on
the same boat for the long run,
I can't possibly let this go on...
So that's how you've been
deceiving my father all this time.
You set your sights on Manbo
Construction from the very start.
Starting with that
contract marriage you wanted.
Looks to me like you're
misunderstanding things?
Don't even dream of lying to me.
- Commissioner Han already told...
- Manbo Construction...
was always mine to begin with.
Say what?
It all started a long time ago.
To save his company, Chairman Hwang
killed Lee Gangmo's father,
and seized some gold bars.
But, you know what?
That gold was actually mine.
Since I had no use for it right away,
I saved Manbo Construction instead.
That's when your father swore to me.
That he would support me like a
loyal mutt for the rest of his days.
That he'd devote
his everything to help me.
Are we starting to get it?
He's merely giving Manbo Construction
back to its rightful owner,
so no need to feel wronged, darling.
I don't feel that way at all.
Because I'll never let you and
your son get your hands on that company.
Will you really be able to?
My father is not dead yet.
You just wait.
Dad will soon reveal the truth.
Is this letter really a fake?
But who made this forgery?
Who do you think?
It's another one
of Jeongyeon's shenanigans.
You know that...
the shareholders' meeting is
going on as planned, right?
So?
If you can't resume
the construction by then,
you'll have to renounce
all your company holdings.
Things are finally
starting to go the right way.
When I become chairman,
I'll make you the happiest woman alive.
Awww... My boy.
I get teary-eyed just hearing that.
Might not have been lucky at the altar,
but look at what boy Lady Luck gave me.
Aww... My cute boy...
Mom...
Dad...
Daddy.
Where on earth have you gone?
I found where Chairman Hwang is.
Get the car.
Yes.
Get back up.
I said get up!
The only man I want to see in charge
of Manbo Construction while we fight...
is not Jo Pilyeon, but you!
Give me a chance to beat
Manbo Construction in all fairness!
Are you just going
to accept this lying down,
and take that
opportunity away from me?
Uh?
After taking my father and
even Jeongyeon away from me,
you should at least
have done that much for me.
Forget it.
Just give up, then.
I'll never meet you again.
This is only the beginning.
Don't pat yourself
on the back for so little.
So you still haven't
forgotten Hwang Jeongyeon?
Is that the reason why
you're helping her father?
Hwang Taeseop...
is the last man you should
forgive, Jo Pilyeon included.
He betrayed and killed
a friend of his, our father.
On the contrary, this is the
perfect opportunity to get rid of him.
And you don't need to be the one.
- I'll take care of...
- I am well aware...
of what I should do.
If only to bring Manbo Construction
down with my own hands,
I can never let Jo Pilyeon
gain control of it.
That is all.
Even if your ultimate goal
is bringing down Jo Pilyeon,
if Hwang Taeseop will
gain anything from this,
I'm against it.
Hwang Taeseop
Hwang Jeongyeon
Hwang Jeongshik
Thank you.
For being alive.
Thank you so much.
You don't need to worry now.
If only for my daughter Jeongyeon,
I will help you recover.
But who has been looking
after you all this time?
Can you write who it is?
So you were the one who's been
taking care of the chairman?
What is the reason?
What were you looking
to accomplish by doing that?
His recovery is going
better than expected.
If everything goes according to plan,
Hwang Jeongyeon will be able
to protect Manbo Construction.
Jeongyeon thinks that all
this happened because of you.
It doesn't matter what she thinks.
I thought you two were in love?!
Why are you doing this?
Then, let me ask you something myself.
Jeongyeon has been looking
for you so ardently over the years,
so why don't you tell her
you're her mother?
Our reasons might be different,
but know that mine is
just as good as yours.
Jeongyeon can't learn I'm her mother.
If you promise not to tell anyone
that I've been helping the chairman...
Gangmo...
Ohh, Gangmo.
It's all right.
Go ahead.
This is serious, Gangmo.
They're going on with
the meeting as planned.
What?
They found out the letters were forged.
He can't even communicate properly...
It's serious, all right.
The only solution is Jeongyeon taking
the chairman to the meeting with her.
Call her.
Yes?
We found the chairman.
Where are you?
Don't tell Jeongyeon I was
the one who's been helping you.
You must protect
Manbo Construction at all cost.
- Yang -
Don't overdo it.
With all this willpower,
you'll recover in no time.
Gangmo...
Your father's grave...
is in Yangsuri.
When you've fully recovered,
I'll come at you at full force.
You'll have to give up
that top spot to me.
Gangmo, you fool.
Jeongyeon will be here soon.
I'll get going.
Dad!
Chairman!
Dad...
Can you sit like this?
It's not a dream, is it?
It's real, right?
Dad...
You really don't know who's
been helping Dad all this time?
I don't.
But why were you
the first one he called?
I wonder...
But, will you let him stay here?
Even if he's released,
there's really no place for him to go.
And I don't want him
to face my stepmother.
I have an empty apartment.
I'll take care of him.
I'll bring him there so
he can continue his treatment.
Can you really do that for me?
You'll be really busy until
the shareholders' meeting.
Leave the chairman to me,
and focus all your
efforts on the company.
I know how shameless it is,
but I'll be counting on you.
Thank you, Director.
Aigoo, who did you take after,
being so radiant?
My mother?!
Mister Yeom.
What are you waiting for?
The chairman is leaving,
aren't you getting the car?
Ch...Chairman?!
Don't you know that Jeongshik is
becoming chairman starting today?
Yes... I'll go get it.
- See you later, Mom.
- Ohh... Right.
And Jeongyeon?
She left early in the morning?!
Aigoo... The meeting's finally here,
so I bet that brat will be desperate.
Get me an appointment
at the beauty salon,
and go get my clothes
from the dry cleaner's.
Aigoo... That cunning wench...
You will do just fine.
I have faith in you.
Come on in.
How does he look?
You look really great, Dad.
But is he able to speak now?
How are you?
Hey... Lee Gangmo.
What are you doing here?
Bought myself some
Manbo Construction shares.
So I hear they're proclaiming
a new chairman today?
Why...
Here to congratulate me?
Nah.
I'll be the one to
bring this company down,
I should at least see who gets
the honor to lead it on the way out.
What?!
Lee Gangmo...
The moment I become chairman,
you'll be the first on my list.
Mom... Isn't Jeongyeon coming?
Did she run away or something?
We will now begin this
shareholders' meeting.
As you've been informed,
Chairman Hwang Taeseop's
testament will be revealed today.
But he's in good enough shape
to send letters to us,
why are you revealing his testament?
Yes...
I will tell you why.
After employing a specialist
to verify their authenticity,
he confirmed to us that
those letters were a forgery.
This is an adjudication of incompetence
acknowledged by the court.
As a result, a new chairman must be
proclaimed to fill the vacant post.
Mister Kim, if you could
please reveal the testament.
I will announce it.
I, Hwang Taeseop, transfer
possession of all my company shares...
to my son Hwang Jeongshik.
Also, all personal and
real estate in my possession...
will go to my wife, Oh Namsuk.
Accordingly, for being the
company's largest shareholder,
Hwang Jeongshik will be proclaimed
the new chairman of Manbo Construction.
That is all.
Then, we will now hear the
new chairman's proclamation speech.
No matter if it's what
the chairman's testament states,
wasn't Director Hwang
Jeongyeon the company heir?
Including Park Gidong's five percent,
Hwang Jeongshik now holds
55 percent of company shares.
You can force another voting out of this,
but the result won't change.
Chairman, if you will.
I'm Manbo Construction's
chairman, Hwang Jeongshik.
To help restore faith in the eyes of
the fellow shareholders who supported me,
I will not merely stop at making Manbo
Construction the leading company in our country,
but the world leader in our sector,
fulfilling our...
Fulfilling our noble aspirations!
Can you...
really do this to me up to the end?
Honey...
Why can't you answer me?
Maybe you really can't?!
As everyone can see, the chairman...
is perfectly fine.
I'll ask the lawyer, then.
The chairman was curious why
the testament presented today...
was so different from
the one he personally wrote.
Maybe the lawyer and Oh Namsuk
plotted together to fix it?
Director Hwang.
Enough with the nonsense.
Shouldn't the chairman ask
that kind of question firsthand?
Go ahead and say it.
Do you really think the lawyer and I...
fixed that testament?
Take a look.
He can't say a word.
Director Hwang.
No matter how much you
coveted that chairman seat,
you exploit the chairman despite his
condition, just to make those insinuations?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Shouldn't you first assume responsibility
for the failed apartment...
They...
forged it!
Dad...
You!
Forged!
My testament...
I...
am not...
dead yet.
Hwang Taeseop!
Is fine!
I'm fine...
Dad...
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
So you want me to
abandon Manbo Construction?
They won't steal it from you,
you'll leave it to them.
To those ruthless beasts.
Get stronger, and start anew.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com