Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 23 -
No. 523.
Change clothes with No. 534.
No. 534.
Yes.
Lee Gangmo will be filed as deceased.
For the rest of your time here,
you will live as No. 534.
Is that clear?
Dear, Seongmo is here.
Come on in.
Still haven't had breakfast, right?
- Serve breakfast to him as well.
- Yes.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you, Ma'am.
What brings you here so early?
Lee Gangmo passed away.
I just received his death notice
from camp administration.
Jaechun.
Yes.
This is a will transferring
possession of Lee Gangmo's land to you.
We already managed to win over his lawyer,
and complete all notarial acts.
Now that Lee Gangmo is dead,
the mudflats in Gaepo are yours.
But everyone will be well aware that
these documents are nothing but a forgery.
And why would we care?
What matters is that you, Minwoo,
now legally own this land.
Didn't Manbo Construction already
give up on this land, anyway?
Even if these documents are forged,
is there anything they can do to us?
With prospects of marriage
out of the window,
shouldn't you have something
like this in your hands,
if you want some
leverage in this fight?
Once you win the elections,
all our plans will come into fruition.
That's right.
Minwoo gaining control of
Manbo Construction means...
I won't have to rely on
Hwang Taeseop any longer.
Do it properly!
No. 534!
Yes, Sir! No. 534!
Follow me.
Hyung.
Gangmo.
It's been tough, hasn't it?
I can manage.
It feels strange to survive
instead of a fallen fellow inmate.
Jo Pilyeon forged a will to
get his hands on your land.
You registered it
under a namesake, right?
No worries.
I made sure they'll never
be able to find the owner.
Thanks, Hyung.
Once your re-education is over,
you'll go through a final examination.
Some of the inmates will get released,
while the rest will complete their
sentence through volunteer community labor.
Hang in there a little longer.
I'll make sure you'll
pass that examination.
No, Hyung, you don't need to.
I'll go through community labor.
Do you realize what awaits you there?
It could be much harder than
anything you've gone through here.
Whatever the case, it doesn't matter.
I'm confident I can endure it.
Gangmo...
If I leave now,
I will never get my name back.
I have all the time to get it back
after the end of my sentence.
Mistakenly reporting my death would
be blamed on the military, anyway.
You just wait, Hyung.
It's as Lee Gangmo, the name my father
gave me, that I will get my revenge.
For all these years, I was consumed
by my thirst for vengeance.
It made my heart turn into a cold
machine pumping vitriol in my veins.
If I hadn't met you two,
I would have been
drowning in misery by now.
It pains me to see how I might have
passed that same grief onto you.
I don't know how
this will change me, either.
But I am sure of one thing.
The fact that you, our Miju and I...
are the most precious
family in this world.
That never...
Never again will I let anyone...
take away my family from me,
just because I'm powerless.
Whatever you do,
I will help you until every bone
in my body is broken into pieces.
I will devote every day
I have left on this earth...
to give you and Miju everything
they took away from you.
Hyung...
You don't need to
bother coming anymore.
I can do that by myself.
It's not like it's hard
or anything, Ma'am.
When is my Jeongmi coming back?
I told you she had a
concert in the provinces.
Just wait, and she'll make
lots of money and come back to you.
I should just die.
Then my daughter
wouldn't have it so hard...
You should rather hurry up
and get better, for Jeongmi's sake.
Do you know what a blessing
being able to call someone "Mom" is?
Thank you...
What brings you here?
Ohh...
Someone I know
was hospitalized here.
Just a moment,
I'll go deal with this.
But it sure is peculiar?!
How can we just meet here?
By any chance...
What?
You didn't come for me, did you?
What?!
What are you, crazy?
Why would I?
"Right."
"Now that I think about it,
I feel sad for you."
"So I'll just withdraw the lawsuit."
What are you, daydreaming?
Was just hoping you could say that...
Just close an eye for once, Chief.
Let alone what happened to the master,
Jeongmi is in trouble herself, being
detained at the police station and all.
Don't you ever get angry?
Uh?
You couldn't debut
as a singer because of her.
Are you in any position
to worry about her?
Then, what else can I do?
Her mother is ill.
The older I get, the harder
understanding people becomes.
Everyone is struggling to make it
at someone else's expense,
but there are still gullible
people like you around.
What are you, making fun of me?
So you at least can understand that?
I see not all hope is lost, after all.
I know that's a bad habit
of mine, but what can I do?
I lost my mother when I was little,
so what can I do if, every time I witness that,
it feels too close to home to ignore?
I haven't been able to visit
you these days, so I was worried.
I'm glad we met.
Promise you will withdraw
the lawsuit before you go.
Go on daydreaming, then.
Where are you going?
Hey... You really...
Go take a look at that patient.
Do you even know in what
sad state Jeongmi's mother is?
I don't prance around minding
other people's business like you do.
If you want to deal with this,
then compensate us for the damages.
There's no talking to him...
This is serious.
It's not like I can continue
looking after her forever.
Come on in.
Here... It's here.
How are you?
How did it go?
Did you find Lee Gangmo?
He's not in our camp.
Look elsewhere.
Wait.
I'll compensate you
with whatever you ask.
Look for him just once more.
You won't find him this way.
And even if you do manage to defy
the odds, they won't let you meet him.
Wait...
I just think...
maybe we should give up
trying to find Gangmo.
Jeongyeon is here.
- I'm back.
- Agasshi, you're back?
Aigoo... You haven't
had dinner, right?
I'll prepare it for you right away.
I have no appetite.
Where are you going around
all day, missing work?
I took a few days off.
You still go around
looking for Gangmo?
Aigoo... How touching.
Ohh Ohh... Keep it up...
They said the Samcheong camp
will end in four weeks.
There isn't much time left,
so just wait patiently.
Right!
Today a letter from Gangmo
came in the mail?
What?
Aigoo... Why are you only
saying that now, you ajumma!
I forgot, what else?
Where did I put it again...
Ahh! Right.
- Death Notice -
- Subject -
Decease of Lee Gangmo
- We extend you
our sincerest condolences -
What is it saying?
What is this...
Gangmo is dead?!
D...Dead?!
Gangmo... has died?!
Give it here.
That's right...
It's a notice from the camp
announcing his death.
- Agasshi!
- Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon... Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon!
I should have done something.
I shouldn't have allowed them
to arrest him that way...
Gangmo is not dead.
There is no way he died.
Jeongyeon...
I've heard sometimes the military makes
mistakes sending out those notices.
He didn't die, Gangmo.
He would never die that way.
No. 534.
So your hometown is Gwangju
in Jeolla Province?
Yes.
Here...
- Park Chungkwon -
Where is Gangmo?
Lee Gangmo didn't die, right?
You made some kind of mistake.
He had no family,
so we took the liberty
of cremating him.
No way...
It's not Gangmo.
It can't possibly be him.
Gangmo...
is not dead.
I can confirm it's Lee Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
What happened to you?
Gangmo...
Gangmo! Gangmo...
Jeongyeon.
It's heavy, so give it to me.
Don't touch it.
Nobody...
Nobody can touch Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Sit down.
For the time being,
take some time off,
and have a good rest.
All right, Jeongyeon?
This was Gangmo's.
Let's leave her alone.
- Will you marry me? -
It will be hard to bear.
We can't possibly predict
what difficulties we'll be facing.
But you still...
You'll have to give everything up.
Your dreams...
Your family.
Maybe even the life you're living now.
I'll come.
Together with you.
Wherever it might be,
it doesn't matter.
Agasshi!
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Agasshi, get a hold of yourself!
Agasshi... Agasshi!
Agasshi!
Help!
Aigoo... What now?
Agasshi!
What happened, Seonsaengnim?
It looks like the psychological
trauma caused a state of aphasia.
Aphasia?!
You mean she lost the ability to speak?
In her current state,
she might not even be able to hear.
Her symptoms resemble
those of a stroke.
Then... What will happen to her?
Will she be forced to live in that
state for the rest of her life?
It's a case by case scenario,
but some even return to normal in a day.
So it might be a very long recovery?
Yes.
Some patients even take
several years to recover.
But for now it's best to stabilize
her condition and keep watching her.
What on earth is all this?
Jeongyeon has aphasia?!
Jeongyeon.
Was it this serious?
Enough for you to
lose the ability to speak,
did you love Lee Gangmo that much?
I shouldn't have gotten
involved from the very start.
My love for you paled in
comparison from the beginning.
I'm sorry, Jeongyeon.
I...
I found out...
I found out your
true feelings too late.
Quick, step out!
Let's hurry up, quick.
Everyone who needs to step out, quick!
Quick, come in.
Your token.
If no one else's coming in, all right!
Here... Step out!
Your token... Thank you.
Here you go. Thank you.
Hurry up.
Everything clear... All right!
Are you taking the bus?
Or else, it's "all right."
All right!
But your office is the opposite way,
where are you going?
No idea.
You don't know?
So why did you take the bus?
I'm asking myself the same question.
There are plenty of empty seats
over there, why don't you sit?
It'll crease up my pants.
And those seats are way too dirty.
So why even bother riding the bus...
Something bad happened...
Right?
Why?
- Is it written all over me?
- A little.
How should I put it,
that you look a little sad?
When do you get off work?
Why are you asking?
By any chance,
want to withdraw the lawsuit?
If I do that,
what will you do for me?
Here.
What's this?
Gum, can't you see?
Chew it.
Never mind...
Who am I kidding,
expecting anything from you...
You don't have a clue, do you?
When you feel down, nothing beats chewing
gum while riding the bus around town.
I said chew it.
The bus is always half-empty
around this time.
I won't ask you for any tickets,
so come anytime.
Don't feel burdened.
Hey.
So, what, you want to exchange a few
tickets and chewing gum with a lawsuit?
You really seem to think I'm a...
Who left a goddamned mutt
lying on the street? Ehh...
I'm sorry.
I didn't spill anything on it, I hope?
It's all right.
Big Oppa...
Miju, you're back?
What?!
Did you just cook me dinner?
Hungry, uh? Let's eat.
Follow me.
Here... Let's eat.
Here... Miju.
You always liked
seasoned beans, right?
I boiled some in soy sauce.
Try them out... here...
They're good.
They taste just like the ones
Mom used to cook for us.
Try the stew as well.
Here we have boiled beef,
and fried eggs.
By the way...
Can't you take off that apron?
Why... Looks strange?
Ahh... Was afraid
something would spill.
What is it?
Does it taste strange?
Is it bad?
Gangmo Oppa cooked
for me on my birthday, too.
I was so sad without you, that day.
Now you're here,
but Gangmo is not with us.
Miju.
When will we all eat together?
Gangmo will soon be out.
How "soon" can that be?
He's still a long way
from coming home.
I'll get him out of there soon.
Really?
Sure.
I don't lie to my Miju.
We will soon be able to eat
all together, the three of us.
Oppa...
Let's eat, it'll get cold.
Yeah.
You look like you
were born to shovel?!
Keep it up and your bones
will wear out. Take it easy.
It's not like they're
paying us for this.
Can't we just fill in the strict
necessary and get the hell out?
Ahh... Wretched fool.
Did they stick your
tongue down your ears?
If one talks to you,
have the courtesy to say something.
Say what?! A fortnight?
Are you telling me it'll take
two weeks to build that road?
It's a mountainous area,
so it's filled with rocks...
You want to see heads
rolling around here?
I take that back, Sir!
Whatever the case,
get that road done in a week.
If you don't make it by then,
prepare to hang up your boots.
Is that clear?
Red hunt!
I'll be damned.
We are forced to
leave all this to No. 471.
- No. 471?!
- Yes.
He's made a name for himself
around construction sites.
Where is he now?
Always prancing around together like
a bunch of beggars, aren't they?!
No. 471.
Hey... No. 471!
Did... Did you just call me?
If we leave the construction to you,
how long will it take you?
What are you talking about,
all of a sudden?
The division commander
will pass by this road in a week.
So you're telling me you need to
finish this road within the week?
Or it's a quick trip to
detention camp for all of us.
Help us out just this once.
What is this, a rug? You can't
just roll it and get it over with.
I've heard you have no peers
when it comes to construction.
I'll give you a very simple
estimate, so you can understand.
Here... First, just digging and
hardening the soil will take four days.
Uh? Add to that another
three days for the cement.
Your week is already
gone by, just for that.
And tell me, is concrete ready
the moment you're done applying it?
It'll take another good four-five
days for that to be ready.
So that's four plus three,
and if you add another five, how much...
There is no way in hell you
can get that done in a week.
Think we don't know that?
Aigoo, then, what
am I supposed to do?
If it can't be done, be honest.
Why say you can make it and
then have to piss blood after?
Starting now,
you're working day and night.
We must end this all
by the end of the week!
We will not tolerate any laziness!
Proceed!
Hurry up and keep working,
you useless twats!
Next.
Ahh... Is this all?
- Give me more!
- Go, you prick.
I've heard about you.
So you're famous
around construction sites?
Who... Me?
I used to be.
Only with a hammer in hand,
I can tell you how many reinforcing rods,
and even the cement and sand proportions...
they used to build a pillar.
We can finish this construction
in a week, can we?
In my estimation, we can
harden the soil in three days.
And we can lay
the cement in two days.
You're something?!
But how about
drying out the cement?
Will you stand there with fans
hoping it'll dry faster?
It takes at least four-five days.
And if it starts raining
even once, you're screwed.
If you can make it on time,
take over this construction.
Or by next week
we'll all be screwed.
Why, think if we finish this on time,
they'll leave us in peace?
Sure... You saw right.
I can certainly complete
this road within a week.
But what am I, crazy?
Why should I help out people
who beat me up all day?
Just a month and I'm out of here.
Let's hurry up!
Get up!
I said hurry up, you fool!
Get moving!
Hurry up!
Are these all the
reinforcements you could get?
More are coming
from other battalions.
What's with him?
Come down.
What the hell?
Get up, you fool!
Let's go.
G...Gangmo!
Hurry up and go!
I said go, you prick!
Do you know him?
Why send us such damaged goods?
People like him
can only be a hindrance.
How can you do it?
What? Fix damaged goods?
How can concrete dry out faster?
Look at him... Asking the
magician to tell you his tricks?
Can't you see everyone is suffering?
If someone ends up dead,
will you take responsibility?
If you really want
to end this quickly,
then find a way yourself.
Want me to give you a hint?
You can find it all around us?!
Take that and use it wisely.
Then you can finish
this all in a week.
But if you do find out what that is,
that'd make you a genius,
nothing but.
But tell me, would a genius go
through hell in a place like this?
I mean, a genius?!
How is the apartment sale proceeding?
Your strategy was right on.
After we got famous movie
stars and singers involved,
requests are raining down
on us from everywhere.
Widen our spectrum by adding sports
stars and politicians to the mix.
We must build a strong
image for our apartments,
as the kind of luxury residences
that win over many celebrities' favor.
All right.
Chief.
But regarding the
record company's lawsuit?
I'm sure I told you to withdraw it?!
We did withdraw it
as you instructed us,
but should the board
of executives find out...
No need to worry.
If we succeed with this
apartment sale as planned,
then I will convince the board.
Let's conclude today's meeting.
Ohh! Chief!
I'm busy.
If you have anything
to say, do it quickly.
Didn't you hear I'm busy?
If you've got nothing to say...
Thank you, Chief!
Hey... What's wrong with you?
You saved us all, Chief.
Everyone including
Jeongmi and her mother.
I only did it because
I've had it with you!
You stick to people like
a damned chewing gum!
I'll never forget what you did for us.
I can bring you
a lunchbox every day, and...
Didn't you hear that
I've had it with you?
As if they were any good...
Get out of the way.
Thank you, Chief.
Chief, you're the best!
The best.
Jaechun.
How does this necktie look?
Is it a bit flashy?
It looks great to me, Ma'am.
Give me another one.
It doesn't suit my image of a
candidate for the working class.
Ahh... That's right.
Then, how about this one?
Yeah... That one would be fine.
Mister Gong, you said?
How about that informer who
will reveal Min Honggi's past?
Seongmo will take him
to the speech himself.
We'll finally start seeing
some fireworks today.
This will be Min Honggi's
very last stumping session.
Are we still far?
We're almost there.
We will soon reach
the campaign platform.
*Colonial-era independence activist
You remember Yoon Bonggil*?
Yes, I deeply respect what he did.
You will become
today's Yoon Bonggil.
But, unlike him,
you must not let yourself be captured
after setting up that bombshell.
When you reveal the truth to everyone,
that place will fall into chaos.
He will help you get out of there.
You must never,
ever let Jo Pilyeon
get his hands on you.
Yes... I understand.
It is with hard work and
dedication that we have achieved...
this miraculous
economic development.
All that remains for us is becoming
a developed nation like Japan or America.
And do you know what's the most urgent
step to take to make sure that happens?
That is security!
Bringing security to our nation!
Ladies and gentlemen,
take a look at those demonstrators,
parading the streets every day.
The commies have infiltrated
the very fabric of our society!
And to cope with these
daunting threats of war,
what our people need is a stronger
and more powerful government!
If that is the
government you wish for,
you must cast your vote and
choose Candidate No. 1, Min Honggi!
Well said!
Min Honggi! Min Honggi!
Look at those gangsters...
Jo Pilyeon! Jo Pilyeon!
My colleague Min Honggi spoke of
the rosy future which awaits us all.
It was a remarkable speech, indeed.
However, while our future is full of hope,
our present is still mired in poverty.
Do you have money to
spare at home, by any chance?
The price of land in Gangnam
is skyrocketing,
did you by any chance buy any of it?
No!
Of course not.
We still remain poor.
The rich become richer by the day,
but your hunger
only seems to get worse.
What kind of situation is this?
In this country,
it is more likely a camel will
pass through the eye of a needle...
than to see a poor man become rich.
And that is because our problems
start at the very root of it all.
Take a look around you.
The people who enjoyed a life of
luxury during the colonial period...
still continue their frivolous
excesses and keep becoming richer.
And at the very root of this evil
cancer afflicting our society...
is the fact we couldn't do away
with that terrible legacy.
On the pretext of being
a passionate patriot,
one of this election's candidates
is hiding his pro-Japanese ancestry!
You deserve to know the truth.
I, Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon,
have brought someone
who can enlighten you all...
on this despicable facade.
Gong Seonsaengnim.
Will you please come to the stage?
You may speak.
Everyone.
My father passed away in prison after
participating in the independence movement.
One of these candidates is the son of
the ruthless pro-Japanese collaborator...
who caused my father's death.
Folks!
I have all the evidence here!
The boy next to the
pro-Japanese officer in this photo...
is right here among us!
His father's name...
is Jo Mangeun,
while his son...
is Jo Pilyeon!
Everyone!
What is he talking about?
Many patriots who fought for our
future died at the hands of Jo Mangeun!
Jo Pilyeon cannot be elected!
You cannot let this happen!
Minwoo, do something!
Are you all right?
Catch him... That informer!
You must catch him at all cost!
All right.
Who could imagine someone bearing a
grudge against Jo Pilyeon would appear?!
The way I see it,
it was no coincidence.
Candidate Min,
do we owe you the honor?
With your keen eye, there is
nothing I could hide from you.
What?!
So it was all a ruse?
There is no such thing
as a ruse in politics.
Let's just call it strategy.
The elections are as good as over,
considering this scandal.
If all the morning papers cover this,
then there's no more hope
for Candidate Jo.
It's all thanks to the
support you've given me.
That sounds like a
victory speech, already?
Ohh...
Did I really sound like that?
I apologize.
But it'll be interesting to see how
Jo Pilyeon will react to all this.
You bastard.
Did I tell you to investigate
him thoroughly or not?
What the hell did you dig into?
I apologize.
If you are, then die for it,
you son of a bitch!
Stop!
Please, calm down.
What happened to
that damned informer?
He moved and
completely disappeared.
Seongmo, you...
Even if the entire ANSP has to
get involved, find him at all cost!
Min Honggi is behind him for sure!
All right.
But, there is another bad news.
What, again?
Those mudflats Lee Gangmo owned
are registered under someone else.
And who is that?
A certain James Lee,
a Korean expat living in the States.
An expat?!
Are you telling me the man who
owns that land lives in America?
According to the copyist in charge of
the transaction, there's no way to trace him.
I can't let them ruin me this way.
Jo Pilyeon won't take this lying down.
I can't...
I won't die this way!
This is only the
beginning, Jo Pilyeon.
You will slowly...
and painfully come face to face
with your destruction.
Hurry up!
Let's get moving!
Move!
I said move!
The hell are you doing?
I... I'm sorry...
What are you doing? Get up!
I apologize.
- Hardtack -
It's just that I get chills every
time I see gravel like this now.
Show me that leg of yours.
It's nothing.
- Let me see!
- Forget it...
Sit.
Pull it up.
Come on.
You stupid fool...
Let's go to the infirmary.
It's no use.
They'll have to cut off
your leg, you fool!
Want to live the rest of
your days as a cripple?
Think I never tried going there?
I got on my knees
begging them to fix it,
but all I got in return were lashes.
Get it?
Just...
Don't mind me.
Quick! Let's get moving!
Come down, quick!
What's with you? Get up!
Get moving, you fool!
What are you waiting for?
Get moving!
We'll be moving that calcium
chloride to the warehouse.
Load it all on the truck.
- Proceed!
Get moving!
You pricks, get moving!
That precious cement
will all become stiff.
Sotae, isn't this strange?
Only the cement next to
calcium chloride sacks got stiff.
And what does that matter?
Calcium chloride
dissolved in rainwater...
hardened the cement?!
Want me to give you a hint?
You can find it all around us?!
Take that and use it wisely.
Then you can finish
this all in a week.
I told you Jeongyeon has aphasia!
We don't even know
when she'll wake up from it.
So let all the
shareholders know about it.
I told you, even the chairman
can't do a thing about it.
Anyhow, I'll be counting on you.
What did he say?
Will they push for me as heir
at the next shareholders' meeting?
Jeongshik, starting now,
you start preparing to become heir.
All right, Mom.
- You're the best!
- My boy.
You'll finally inherit
Manbo Construction, uh?
- Mom.
- Uh?
Should I let you in on a secret?
Secret?!
What secret?
Actually, what happened to
Jeongyeon was all my idea.
What's that supposed to mean?
So she caught aphasia
because of you?
Yeah...
It was Minwoo and I who sent
Gangmo to the Samcheong camp.
Really?!
And how did you manage?
We just asked Minwoo's father.
To send Gangmo
to the Samcheong camp.
Think it was an accident
that killed him?
Minwoo's father paid
someone off to get rid of him.
So... Minwoo's father killed Gangmo
on Minwoo's and your behalf?
Yeah!
What's she doing,
prancing around like that?
Aigoo... Really...
We're screwed.
There's no completing
the road on time, this way.
Only a moment will do!
What's with you?
I have something to tell you.
Are you out of your mind?
Give me control of the construction.
You little...
What did you just say?
If you entrust me with
this construction,
I will finish it on time.
- We only have four days left.
- We can just lay the cement in two days.
And it'll take four-five days to dry.
We can do it in just two days.
What?!
Two days are enough.
And if it's not?
If we do make it,
what will you do?
Accept my conditions.
I only have two.
I think she needs to be
hospitalized once again.
Will it take long for her
to regain consciousness?
Yes, I'm afraid so.
Jeongyeon?
Just remain in this state forever.
Are we clear?
Forever, and ever.
I will get my revenge.
Everyone who caused Gangmo's death...
will suffer...
indescribable pain for what they did.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Tomorrow...
Gangmo is coming out!
Now we can all live together?
Here's all the shares owned
by the board of directors.
Even if the chairman takes
your side, it won't be easy.
I need your help.
- Give me your support.
- And why should I?
He's a gang leader with a long list
of indictments, quite the rat bastard.
Take a good look at
how I turn this around.
If it weren't for you, I...
Thank God nothing happened to you.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com