Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 31 -
The man who did that to my father...
Lee Gangmo, I know it was you.
You're free to think whatever you want.
Since my goal is and will always be
defeating Manbo Construction.
You avenged your father, right?
So now it's time for me to avenge mine.
Don't ever forgive my father.
Since, I myself...
will never forgive you.
I've been trying to avenge you all this time,
running around like a lunatic.
But...
Seeing what a fool you made out of me
is almost too embarrassing to bear.
If I think of all the time I wasted
thinking about you and our memories,
I get chills down my spine.
Know that?
Done talking, yet?
I'll get going, then.
I still need to wrap up
a few things at the office.
When did it start?
Did you come into our family with
revenge in mind from the very beginning?
After which you pretended to be a
friend, a companion and a lover to me?
If you really had a shred
of consideration for me,
whatever could have possibly happened,
you first would have come to me.
Because I abandoned both my
father and all my ambitions,
and chose you instead.
You still have feelings left for me?
What?
All that this looks like to me is someone
drowning herself in petty nostalgia.
Just resent me and get it over with.
Stop dwelling on the past.
I'll get going,
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon.
So the reason you want
to join the committee...
is to get yourself that construction
permit for your apartments?
You'll have to pry that
from my cold, dead hands.
If you've got what it takes
to stop me, you're free to try.
I can't wait.
- Will you Marry Me? -
Throw it away with all
your strength, Jeongyeon.
Let it drown along with all
the feelings you have left for me.
Only then...
Only then will it
stop hurting you so bad.
So I hear Lee Gangmo is alive.
Why, didn't know yet?
James Lee was Lee Gangmo, after all.
Seems like Lee Gangmo bears quite
the grudge against Hwang Taeseop.
He'll do everything in his power to
bring forth Manbo Construction's downfall.
All you need to do is
take advantage of that,
and devour that company with one blow.
Couldn't you just stop trying to
get your hands on Manbo Construction?
What?
- Not only it will be no laughing matter...
- Have you already forgotten...
who made Manbo Construction
what it is today?
What are you trying to imply with that?
You'll soon be presented
with a crucial opportunity.
All you need to do is
prepare to take advantage of it.
Don't tell me you were involved...
with what happened to Chairman Hwang?
You can be honest with me.
Were you behind that?
Are you that curious about it?
It was an act of God.
He gave us this golden
opportunity on a silver platter.
So can we just turn
our backs and ignore it?
What?!
G...Gangmo is... is alive?!
Didn't you say you met James Lee?
Shall we go,
- President James Lee?
- Sotae!
- Good night to you!
Park Sotae, that lying son of a...
My suspicions were right.
The man who set his sights
on Manbo Construction...
was Lee Gangmo.
So why did my father
do that with his testament...
What?
Ohh... Never mind.
It's nothing.
So that's what your hands looked like.
Every time I asked
to cut your nails for you,
you'd always rebuff me,
saying it was corny.
But only now...
you finally start
feeling like my husband.
Because the only way
I can hold your hands...
is if you end up in this state.
I sure wasn't blessed with luck.
Don't you agree, Honey?
Honey.
You just moved that, didn't you?
Right?
Honey...
Can you see me?
Can you see me, Honey?
Mental paralysis?
There's a very strong possibility.
But is he conscious?
He will be able to see and hear,
in all likelihood.
And when will he recover?
Are there good chances that he will?
There are instances of full recoveries,
but the very opposite
is much more likely.
We really can't be sure.
Mom.
Jeongshik.
Call our lawyer and tell him your father
has just regained his consciousness.
Dad has woken up?
Do it!
All right, Mom.
If you really can hear my voice,
look at me just once.
You know that this is the first time
you do something nice for me?
I will change that testament of yours.
Guess you'll hate me even more, now?
You'll curse the ground I walk on.
But...
that is certainly not
going to surprise me.
I've gotten used to it already.
- Construction Committee MOU -
Approval
The chairman wished for
Gangmo to join the committee.
And I'd like you to respect
your father's wishes.
The first to throw down
the gauntlet was Gangmo.
And I have no intention
of letting him defeat me.
I'm asking you to reject President
Lee Gangmo's acceptance into the committee.
You're going to manage
that company from now on,
so I trust you're aware that a company's
foremost goal is the pursuit of profits.
If President Lee can't benefit
from the committee's joint liability,
he'll be forced to sell his land
in Gaepo-Dong at bargain prices.
I will offer you the chance to join me
in the joint purchase of that land.
But you can't be sure President Lee
will sell that land to us.
Commissioner Han
already gave me his word.
That should President Lee Gangmo
fail to obtain that joint liability,
he would give me the construction
permit for that Gaepo-Dong lot.
What the...
If you manage to
build apartments in Gaepo,
the profits will make what you're
earning through President Lee's...
highway project pale in comparison.
I'm sure you know that
even better than me.
Director Ju?
It's an MOU for our joint
purchase of the Gaepo land.
President Lee must not be
informed of this until voting day.
Only that way will we
avoid any complication.
Come on in.
- Let me pour you a drink.
- Yes.
I owe you my gratitude for helping
overturn my conviction at the appeal.
But... About the favor
I asked you last time...
You said you'd like to join the consultation
panel for the Ministry of Construction, right?
Yes.
Congressman.
But that's just a
non-permanent consulting post.
Just an honorary post
and nothing more, you know?
It's all right.
May I ask you the reason?
Isn't that post just a formality
without any power or retribution?
Those chairmen of the
construction committee betrayed me.
Shouldn't I first deal with them, if I
want to pave the way for the next elections?
The idea that power only comes from
high-ranking appointments is obsolete.
You just wait.
You'll see how even a seemingly
insignificant post can do wonders,
depending on who's appointed.
Wait for me here.
Yes.
Wow... Looks tasty.
Who is it?
I was about to have some ramen...
Minwoo, you still haven't had din...
Do I have to keep standing here?
Come on in.
How far did you and Minwoo go?
What?
- We're just...
- No.
No need to answer me,
I don't even want to know.
You know that someone like you shouldn't
even dream of dating Minwoo, right?
Do you, or not?
I do.
You do?
If you do, then why do you
keep sticking to him?
So, what, is an orphan like you trying
to marry Minwoo and hit the jackpot?
You're barking up the wrong tree.
I don't know what
you did to seduce my son,
but Minwoo would never be miserable
enough to fall for someone like you.
*used for close acquaintances'
mothers, or mothers-in-law
- Mother*...
- What?
"Mother"?!
How dare you call me that,
you insolent brat?
Ajumma...
What?!
Ajumma?!
I'll finish eating dinner.
The ramen will get all bloated.
Hey!
Who taught you to act like this?
This is my house.
You're the one who forced
your way in at dinner time.
You!
Let's make things clear right here.
You'll stop meeting Minwoo, right?
Why aren't you answering?
You'll break up with him right away.
I don't know if I can.
You what?
I was told that
I shouldn't lie to elders.
To be really honest, I don't think
I'd be able to break up right away.
You little wench!
Are you trying to make fun of me?
So? You won't break up?
What's wrong with you?
"What's wrong with you"?!
You insolent brat...
So, what, are you implying
you'll marry my son?
- Get up!
- You're hurting me!
Get up!
Uh? Speak to me once and for all!
Why are you doing this...
What did I ever do wrong?
Miju?
Say it!
Please, don't!
Miju, what's wrong?
What's the matter?
This is not your first time, is it?
How much could you
possibly want to stop this?
How much money have you made
fooling men this way?
Mom?!
Promise you'll break up
with Minwoo right now.
Do it!
Mom!
So you're going to
keep refusing, aren't you?
Fine...
Let's see how long you last.
Brats like you need to be taught
a lesson before they can wake up.
You stubborn wench...
Oppa...
Minwoo...
Don't let that startle you.
I was just doing some housecleaning.
I always tend to go a little
over the top when I clean, so...
Why are you lying to me, you silly?
I know that my mother was here.
Did you tell her
you'd break up with me?
Miju.
I feel terrible about
what happened to you,
- but I...
- I told her I wouldn't.
That I wouldn't be able
to break up with you.
You told me that if I
dumped you a third time,
this time you wouldn't forgive me.
And since I was afraid
I'd really end up losing you...
That fool is out of his mind.
How could he go after
such a lowly wench...
You're back?
Had dinner?
Minwoo...
What are you doing?
The apartment is empty, right?
I'll go live there starting today,
just so you know.
Guess that brat came crying to you?
Minwoo!
What's wrong with you, really?
Want to get on your father's bad side?
You know?
The days when my father could
dictate how I live my life are over.
Minwoo!
Be it marriage or anything else,
I'll deal with that by myself,
so stop trying to interfere
all the time... Stop it!
Minwoo!
Where are you going at this hour?
We were going for some drinks,
care to join us?
What's with him?
I guess something
happened to him outside.
Minwoo's not the type to react that way.
What's going on?
Honey, it's nothing...
I'll set the table right away,
so wait just a moment.
- Hyeeun's Titti Bang Bang -
Riding the bus,
Speeding on the highway
like a fresh breeze,
As the sound of waves surrounds us,
In that place we loved so much.
Beautiful Gyeongja?
What?
This snack bar opened next door...
You like "Dung Ass"?
Dung Ass.
Ehh... How vulgar...
*sliced pork cutlet
It's not "Dung Ass..."
You probably mean "tonkatsu*"?
Yes... Anyhow,
I could buy you that for dinner tonight?
Eat that all by yourself, "Dung Ass."
If you don't like that,
there's plenty more to choose.
What was that again...
Beef steak? Hip steak...
You perverted rat!
I didn't do that...
Ehh... You dirty pervert!
Gyeongja...
Sotae. Can you get me
some of that "hip steak"?
That decrepit bald twat...
Hip steak my ass!
Here...
Let's all gather.
We'll now begin preparations
for our apartment construction.
How is it going with the subcontractors?
I'm meeting with them right now,
so we'll probably wrap everything
up by the end of the month.
Sotae, you hurry up and
gather men for goods & services.
Focus on those with
construction site experience.
All right...
Then, were you accepted
into the committee?
They'll decide it tonight.
It will all go well.
- Kim Chuja's "My Dear is Far Away" -
More distant than he's ever been,
my dear is far away.
Forever distant as he was,
Just one hesitation
and he went far away.
They're all gathered.
Judging by the mood, it'll be hard
to contain Hangang Construction.
The winner is only proclaimed
when all the cards are on the table.
Aigoo... Come on in, Jeongyeon.
Everyone is here, so let's begin.
Since our committee chairman is not here,
we'll let Madam Yoo preside
over this meeting instead.
We will now decide on the motion
regarding Hangang Construction's admission.
You all brought your
admission agreements, right?
Let's just use those
instead of simple voting.
First, Chairman Cheon?
I...
approve.
Chairman Baek.
I approve as well.
Chairman Hwang Taeseop expressed
his approval through this agreement.
I think he just wished for the same man he
once considered like a son to really succeed.
However, I don't agree with him.
I oppose it.
Next, Chairman Jo?
I agree with Miss Hwang Jeongyeon.
I oppose this motion.
What?!
We have two votes for, and two against.
All that is left now is
Chairman Park's decision.
I oppose it as well.
With this, I declare the motion to accept
Hangang Construction into the committee...
rejected.
Wait... Wait!
Chairman Jo!
Chairman Park!
What are you...
I'll admit it.
This time,
I lost to you.
You're impressive, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Better enjoy the spotlight.
Because it won't last very long.
You weren't sleeping, yet?
I'm just back from making
Hangang Construction's motion fail.
I told Gangmo.
That I will avenge you with my own hands.
Don't, Jeongyeon...
It wasn't Gangmo who did this to me.
I'll also get back all
the land you gave to him.
You just watch, Dad.
I'll trample down on Lee Gangmo
with all my strength.
Jeongyeon, I said it wasn't him!
If it weren't for Gangmo,
I would have been dead already!
- 8th Ministry of Construction
Consultation Panel Meeting -
Why are there still no news about the
concerns we raised with the minister?
He's currently abroad, so...
So what is it that you people really do?
Aren't you here to
consult with the minister?
Anyhow, this panel is not working!
Have you accomplished
a single thing, all this time?
I apologize.
Ohh... Come on in, Mister Jo.
Let me make the introductions.
He recently joined our panel, and...
How nice of you to meddle in this...
Tell me about it.
How long has it been
since they released you...
So you knew each other already?
I wouldn't say I was proud
to make his acquaintance.
May I have a word in private with them?
If you don't mind, I have to
tell them something personally.
Certainly.
This is all the data I've been
collecting since my KCIA days.
A look here and you'll find everything
from your personal history...
down to every single detail
about your business ventures.
Chairman Cheon...
I see you have your own
sophisticated approach to tax evasion?!
Also, both Chairmen Park and Baek
have a long history of price fixing.
And I guess because
he's the youngest here,
our dear Chairman Jo seems to exhibit
quite the controversial lifestyle?!
Not to mention the affair
you've long been hiding.
Also, last but not least,
our eldest here...
Ahh... Chairman Park.
Me?
May I borrow your ear a moment?
Listen, Chairman Cheon.
Wanna die?
Is that what you want?
Shall I get rid of you all?
You people betrayed me and went
groveling at Min Honggi's feet.
Open your eyes and take a good look.
This seat you loved to look down on
is now occupied by Jo Pilyeon!
From here on in, I'll directly
report to the minister on...
every single consultation
regarding your projects.
I'm sure if I tell him I'll tame all the
complaints of those committee members,
the minister will be ecstatic.
Seonbaenim.
Jo Pilyeon has started making his move.
What?
He's trying to gain control
of the construction sector.
But... That position
doesn't even allow him that.
He's not even human...
He's the devil!
Seonbaenim.
All it takes to destroy a devil
is becoming one yourself.
I'll just become an even
scarier monster than Jo Pilyeon,
and squash him like a bug.
Miju.
Ahh... Why isn't this working?!
Hey... Lee Miju.
Stop eating and look at me.
Hey...
You really...
Open it.
Wow... Almost looks real.
Even if a fake, it's still pretty.
It's yours.
What's the occasion?
It's not even my birthday.
Don't you even know what a man
giving you a ring means?
I don't think I can accept it.
You just rushed into a decision
because your parents are against it.
And?
Later, when I become someone
you don't need to be ashamed of,
then I want to gain
your parents' consent.
That is never going to happen.
What do you mean?
Give me your hand.
Are you telling me you're just going to
forsake your parents because of me?
I said give me your hand.
Minwoo...
Let's wait until they
give us their approval.
If I keep showing them all the efforts...
Minwoo!
See? Why force it...
That's a real diamond.
What?!
Why are you only telling me now?
Have you lost something?
Stay away!
Please, don't come here.
Where did it go?
Hey... Is a diamond
more important than...
I found it!
If I lost it,
I don't know what I'd have done...
Here.
It's expensive,
so take good care of it.
Keep it for the rest of your days.
If you ever take it off, you're dead.
What brings you here?
Here.
It's tomorrow's morning edition.
- Expansion of South Seoul
Development Areas Confirmed -
- Gaepo chosen as residential area -
I've heard they didn't
accept you into the committee.
All you'll be able to build
in Gaepo are apartments,
but if you can't get a
construction permit, that land...
Yes?
It's me. Hwang Jeongyeon.
Better take good care
of that land in Gaepo.
Or else it'll soon start
tearing up like toilet paper.
It's the land you got in exchange
for selling me out.
Think I'll let that alone?
But that's not the only thing
I've set my eyes on.
It's much more than that.
You better bear that in mind,
President Lee Gangmo.
What do you plan to do now?
All we need is that
joint liability, anyhow.
If I can't obtain it
from the committee members,
I'll have to find another solution.
Unless major players agree
to sign a joint liability,
it will be easier said than done.
President Lee is here, Sir.
Have a seat.
People running a business can end up
taking backward steps, at times.
But if you let that
setback hold you down,
that's when the real problems begin.
That is never going to happen.
You've been prancing around pretending
to be a president with my money.
If that investment doesn't
bring me any tangible fruits,
wouldn't that be a fraud?
Sir...
Take a good look at this hand.
You wrote on your business plan
that you'd build apartments.
But if you used that to con me,
your entire body will face the
same fate as this hand of mine.
We never even mentioned it.
I don't know who you heard that from,
but we never said we'd sell.
- How many times must I repeat myself?
- I said that's the truth!
- Hello? Hello?
- We're not selling.
I said we're not selling that land!
Who said that nonsense?
We'll soon start
building apartments there.
What do you think this is, a realtor?
You really...
Who are you calling wench?
How dare you swear at me, you prick?
What?! A penalty?! What penalty?
Did you use a single sack
of cement there, or a brick?
Listen to you!
We can just start
the construction, you fool!
Looks like rumors that we can't build
those apartments started spreading.
Everyone is in a frenzy
asking us to sell.
Even the subcontractors
said they'll cancel our deal.
Why are you getting angry at me, then?
It's me, Hyung.
I have a little favor to ask you.
Ever since the former regime,
he's been playing a pivotal role in
the government's development planning.
He's like a mentor
to Commissioner Han.
So you're telling me
those immense mudflats...
will be filled with apartments, right?
Exactly, Congressman.
This land will soon go
through monumental changes.
Monumental...
Just hearing that makes my heart race!
How are you, Sir?
President Lee,
what are you doing here?
Was just out here taking a breather.
Right...
Those fields belong to you, right?
Who is this fella?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Hangang Construction's
president, Lee Gangmo.
So you run a construction company.
So all that land is yours?
It was confirmed as a residential area,
so he'll soon have to sell it.
If he can't build apartments here,
then current policy states he must
sell it back at bargain prices.
I'd like a word with you,
Mister Congressman.
It will be no use, President Lee.
We plan to give that construction
permit to Manbo Construction.
Congressman.
Just give me a moment of your time.
Seems like he's here for a "favor."
Let's get going, Commissioner.
Yes.
Despite accepting
plenty of political funding,
he's never once been involved in
bribing or even doing personal favors.
Convincing him
is not going to be easy.
You can dig some intel
on Congressman Oh, right?
Help me out, Hyung.
If I can't get past him, it'll be
the end for Hangang Construction.
Congressman Oh Byeongtak has an
Achilles' heel that can never be brought up.
Even if you do try to convince him,
don't ever go there.
Hurry up and recover, Chairman.
Seeing how your wife treats
Jeongyeon is just killing me.
Why are you telling him
that nonsense?
Who are you?
It's you, Ma'am?
I came to see the chairman.
We'll let you two alone, then.
- Follow me.
- Who is she?
She's the Royal Club's...
I mean, one of Manbo Construction's
major shareholders.
Hurry up and come.
Get moving!
I wanted to at least spare you
from seeing me in this state.
If only for Jeongyeon's sake,
you must recover.
If you'll spend the
rest of your days in bed,
I think I'm really going
to resent you until I die.
Gyeongok...
What are you doing here?
Is this all you could
do for the chairman?
So, what, were you trying to
compensate by caressing his face?
Watch what you say.
I wasn't caressing him,
I barely wiped his face.
Who the hell are you?
Excuse me?
What's your relationship with him?
Don't you know that already?
As one of Manbo Construction's
major shareholders...
You own a night club!
So, what, were you having an affair?
Mom!
Are you done?
Answer me.
What is with you?
Guess I'll have to summon a
shareholders' meeting tomorrow.
What?!
Let's see what happens to you when I
tell everyone the chairman might die...
because of the treatment
you're giving him here.
After stocks crash to the bottom and
shareholders ask for those responsible,
think you're going
to survive that meeting?
- I really ought to...
- Mom!
Ma'am... She's easily upset these days,
so please be understanding.
Start by taking care
of the chairman for real.
Or else, this won't just end
with me selling my shares,
and I might just force Manbo
Construction into the pits of hell.
So she wants to take this to the end?
Why did you need to
waste your time asking that?
Go dig into that woman's past.
What?!
Find out what's going on
between her and your father.
Ehh... Mom, you really...
Always having me
do all the dirty work.
So you joined forces with her
to make Jeongyeon your heir?
You can't fool me.
This is not just business.
Right?
- Wau Apartment Collapses -
27 Dead, 3-4 in Dire Condition
- Congressman Oh Byeongtak's Son
Found Inside, Killed by Briquette Gas Leak -
Yes?
I got you a meeting with
Congressman Oh, tomorrow at 2 pm.
Thanks, Hyung.
Congressman Oh Byeongtak has an
Achilles' heel that can never be brought up.
Even if you do try to convince him,
don't ever go there.
Yes...
What's this?
So you were the one
Congressman Min Honggi sent?
Just listen to me for a moment.
I can imagine what you'll
say already, what's the point?
Just go.
- Congressman.
- Ohh Ohh... I said leave!
Yes?
It's me, Congressman.
Listen, Congressman Min.
Who is this man, to send him here?
Have I ever done anything
to compromise you, Sir?
So trust me on this
and have a talk with him.
Yes...
Yes, I'll soon repay the courtesy.
Yes.
Thank you, Seonbaenim.
Ehh... What are you saying?
If it weren't for you,
think I'd be sitting there?
On the contrary,
I feel bad I couldn't help you more.
I'm afraid I haven't needed
political funding for quite some time.
It's not that.
Then, what is it, pocket money?
Min Honggi will have to hear from me.
What's this...
Aren't they just articles?
These are all about construction-related
accidents from the Seventies.
- Wau Apartment Collapses -
All those accidents, including that
collapse, started from faulty constructions.
So?
What do you intend to accomplish
by showing these to me?
I'm sure you're well aware of the
reasons behind those faulty constructions.
On one hand, you pressure the
construction companies and pocket some,
while on the other hand you help them gain
construction concessions through bribes.
What are you trying to imply?
That the responsibility
for this all lies with you.
What?
Because you're the one
who pocketed all that money.
- Say what, you...
- My mother!
Lost her life because
of a briquette gas leak.
There is only one reason why
I want to build apartments.
So that people...
will never have to die
because of a gas leak,
and will be able to share their happy memories
in reliable and inexpensive apartments.
If you used any of that political funding,
you could have easily developed new technologies.
If you feel even just a
shred of guilt for what you did,
help me secure
that construction permit.
Leave.
I might have a conscience,
but my hands are clean.
- Congressman...
- Get out of my sight!
- Gaepo Development Plan -
Gangmo!
How... How did it go?
So did you get his consent?
Here he goes again with his shows...
Don't do that and just tell us.
He gave you that permit, right?
I think we'll just
have to sell that land.
I apologize to you all.
Right!
Why, who said we must build
apartments there at all cost?
We can just sell that land and
build somewhere else with that money.
Isn't that right, Sotae?
Of course!
Don't you worry, we can make
plenty of money even without that.
Yes, Hangang Construction.
Yes, how can I help you?
All right.
Yes.
Who called?
Was it the City Council?
They said they're giving us something.
Giving us? What?
What did he say?!
Ahh, right.
A construction permit.
They said they're giving us that.
Are you sure it was
a construction permit?
Oppa...
Forgot how smart I am?
Think I wouldn't know what that means?
Did they really tell you
they were giving us that permit?
Are you all deaf?
I said yes.
That's it!
- We did it!
- Right!
I knew it... There was
no way Gangmo wouldn't make it!
- Am I dreaming?
- Course not.
- I can't believe it!
- That hurts, you twat.
You're our good luck charm, Gyeongja!
What's wrong with you?
You're messing up my manicure!
Thank you.
I've heard you're giving us
a construction permit.
Congressman Oh said
he'd take full responsibility.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Commissioner.
But...
There is still a little problem.
A problem?
I did file a request for that permit,
but the final decision rests with
the Ministry of Construction.
But if City Council asks for it,
wouldn't it just be a formality?
In most cases, that's what happens,
but there's a surprising
factor at play here.
What would this factor be?
These days, the minister puts a lot
of faith in his consultation panel.
And the man leading that panel...
is Jo Pilyeon.
If Jo Pilyeon shows opposition,
there's a very strong possibility the
minister might refuse to grant you that permit.
Where must I go to meet Jo Pilyeon?
Hey... Gangmo!
What would be the use of going there?
Unless he's gone crazy, Jo Pilyeon
would never give us that permit!
Already forgot what
it took to get this far?
We'll have to face
whatever's in our way!
Don't go in.
I said don't.
Then, I'll get going.
I'm always here for you, Jeongyeon.
You were one step
too late, Lee Gangmo.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
You know what this is, right?
Your testament.
But I don't need this any longer now.
So these relics were found
at the construction site?
Just cover it up.
Cover this up and go ahead
with the construction.
Leave Hangang Construction to me.
And that's because I could
never accept the fact...
that someone like you and me
share the same dream.
I'll never let you go.
If it's to gain you,
there is nothing I can't do.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com