This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 3 ~
Close this one.
Yes.
Where are the Korean Army
support quarters?
Yes... Go straight
until the very last building.
You're sure she's dead?
I saw her body firsthand.
And the kids ran away?
They're still children
who know nothing of the world.
I don't think you need to worry.
Briquette gas...
That's that, but stealing that secret
document will be no laughing matter.
Of course it won't be.
We don't even know
where they keep it, do we?
Loyalty.
General Hampton
just arrived at his office.
Tell him we will be there soon.
Yes. Loyalty!
Do you at least have any plan on
how to get our hands on that document?
- This should be enough, right?
- Yes.
You know how to
make those boots shine?
I don't want to see
a blemish on them, got it?
All right.
I'll count on you, then.
I won't steal it.
What's with the boots?
They're General Hampton's.
And why isn't his orderly
taking care of them?
Ahh... He went out.
What?
Ehh... Lazy bum...
By the way, Seoul's tallest building
is the 31 Building, right?
Yeah. Why?
Never mind.
They said it's 31 Building.
31 Building?
Yeah... The tallest building
in Seoul is 31 storeys high.
That's why it's called that way.
Then, if we go there,
we can meet Big Oppa?
What could have happened to him?
When you have a death wish,
anything is possible.
Crazy fool...
Jumping off a moving train...
We can meet Big Oppa there, can't we?
Yeah.
We can.
Don't worry.
Aigoo...
The baby is eating like a champ?!
How long have you been
starving the poor little thing?
Are you orphans?
You have somewhere to go, don't you?
We have a house in Seoul.
And where's our house?
Here...
Take a look.
This is the land Dad bought in Seoul.
When we meet Hyung,
all we need is to go live there.
I miss Mommy and Daddy...
Ajeosshi.
What?
You're going to Seoul, right?
My mother told us to ride this truck.
And your mother?
- My mother is coming la...
- Our mother is gone.
Gone? She's dead?
Yes.
Let's see the money first.
How much is it?
I'm Major Jo Pilyeon,
appointed to the Korean Army support.
I welcome you, Major Jo.
I've heard you like orchids.
Please, accept it.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Where is General Hampton's office?
Take the stairs all the way up.
It's on the second floor.
I hear you were in Vietnam,
before they sent you here.
I was working with
Korean forces there, too.
So that explains your excellent Korean.
As long as I'm in charge of
the Korean support unit,
we will spare no effort
to assist the Eighth Army.
I appreciate that.
So...
I've heard that you worked
for the Security Command,
before your recent assignment here.
Yes...
Down in Busan.
That's strange... I...
I don't recall seeing your name on the
recent defense department promotion list.
I'm surprised you looked into
low-ranked personnel like me.
I wanted to get to know
who you are before your...
Your recent assignment here.
I was just lucky.
Well... Congratulations on
your recent promotion, anyhow.
Thank you.
What is it?
I brought the General's boots.
Leave them over there.
~ Jo Pilyeon ~
He's no pushover.
But he won't figure out our plans.
We're facing the man leading the
Eighth Army's Intelligence Brigade.
If we don't finish this quickly and
with the utmost accuracy, we're screwed.
Understood?
Yes, Sir.
You're back?
Hyung.
At the laundry down here, do you work
on the Korean troops' uniforms as well?
Yeah... But why?
Allow me to work at the laundry, then.
Be it dry cleaning, ironing,
or cleaning, I can do anything.
I'll look if there's any opening.
Ehh... It's so damn noisy
I can't even drive.
What's wrong with the baby?
Oppa, the baby's burning.
What?
Ajeosshi.
Is there any pharmacy nearby?
Give me a break...
I'm busy as hell,
what damned pharmacy?!
*name comes from old Joseon
horse post, current Yangjae-Dong
We'll reach Maljukgeori* in a while.
You should find one there.
~ Civil officials preying on our
fellow citizens, enough is enough! ~
~ Invalidate Contracts!
Against the redevelopment! ~
~ Bought over for a sack of rice.
Down with the Yankee thugs! ~
Ajeosshi.
Let's hurry up and find a pharmacy.
Aren't you going with him?
Why should I?
You said you were headed for Gangnam.
We're in Gangnam.
I'll step out when Oppa comes back.
Come here...
Ajeosshi... My bag!
Ajeosshi... The bag!
Give me the bag!
- Ajeosshi.
- Ajeosshi is busy.
I'll get going.
Ajeosshi, give me my bag.
Ajeosshi!
Oppa... Oppa!
That Ajeosshi took our bag and left!
What?
The bag!
Ajeosshi, the bag!
Ajeosshi...
Ahh... Scared me to death...
What are you doing?
Follow that truck, please.
Let's just go, Honey.
You crazy little runt...
My bag...
Leave!
What is going on?
Jeongshik.
Jeongshik... What is this?
- Mom...
- Look at this blood!
You!
He insulted my mother.
You little brat...
Why did you slap me?
Who are you to slap me?
Takes after her mother, all right.
You steal someone else's money and run away,
but still have the guts to make a scene?
Don't insult my mother.
How could I not?
And who could a thieving
little brat like you take after?
Does a bar slut's blood
just vanish into thin air?
Don't insult my mother...
Don't even think about it!
Aigoo... And she has the balls
to call scumbags like her, "mother."
Listen well, uh?
- Your mother!
- You're schizophrenic.
What?
If my mother's a scumbag,
then you're schizophrenic.
You act all kind and accommodating
when Dad's around...
You make me sick.
You brat...
Honey! Honey...
Jeongyeon that brat wasn't content
with hitting him in the head,
but do you know what she called me?
Let me look.
Take him to the hospital.
I can't live with her any longer,
just so you know.
Jeongshik, let's go.
Aww... My boy... What now?
- You little...
- Let me meet my mother.
You can't meet her again.
Why not?
You said you'd let me meet her,
after I'd recover.
And what do you plan to
accomplish by meeting her?
You won't meet again.
So...
Just pretend she's dead.
What kind of person was she?
What kind of person could she be,
for you to abandon her like that?
Your mother...
was a really kind...
and beautiful woman.
She was smart as well,
so she was a good student.
So...
Why did you abandon her?
She was the first to abandon me!
Because I was poor and ignorant.
So, now that you know,
stop looking for her.
Liar...
Anyone in?
Hey... Miju!
We have no place to sleep,
is anyone in?
Looks like they're all asleep.
It's not as cold as I thought?
Let's sleep here just for tonight.
Oppa, what now?
The baby must be hungry.
No milk left, I bet.
Yeah... We ran out.
Is that a pear?
Oppa! That's stealing!
Ohh... Look!
Must be tasty.
Have one.
I'm fine, Oppa.
It's all right.
I'll make a ton of money
and pay them back later.
Go ahead and eat.
Then, you eat, too.
All right.
But where's our house?
We have no house anymore.
Why?
We lost the bag, you silly.
Everything we had was inside that.
Then, what happens to us now?
It's okay.
When we meet Hyung,
we'll be able to find everything.
Don't worry.
Go ahead and eat.
Here... Have some of this as well.
Here you go.
Honey, any soup left?
What are you,
counting the grains of rice?
Eat and go back to your room!
Why are you taking it out on us?
You'll leave when
you're done eating, right?
What?
Yes.
Didn't they say
they have nowhere to go?
- In this cold...
- Is this a damned orphanage?
Go take a look outside.
The streets are filled with beggars!
We'll leave right away.
Hurry up and eat.
Aigoo...
They'll get indigestion.
Eat slowly.
And what is this smell?
Must have pooped!
- Uh?
- The smell...
How can one eat with this smell?
Didn't you bring any diapers?
I'm sorry, Ajumma.
I'll take care of it.
It stinks...
- Do your homework right away.
- I did it all already.
Load them right.
You'll get hurt that way.
Take it easy.
It's all right.
I must earn my keep, at least.
Aigoo, you little...
What are you doing there?
I'm almost done, Ajumma.
The other bowls on the shelf were dusty,
so I took care of those as well.
Why are you boiling that water?
So I can do the laundry.
Because of the baby,
the covers got dirty.
Seems like you think that
by doing this we'll let you stay,
but it's no use.
Are we clear?
But what's with these leftovers?
So you can take
them along when you leave?
I'm sorry, Ajumma.
~ Jo Pilyeon ~
Sir.
More intel from Vietnam.
Recent CIA activity
has been a bit... strange.
What do you mean?
Think they've noticed that we're
working on a secret document.
We'll be done with the
document pretty soon.
Just pay special attention to
maintain a tight sense of security.
Roger, Sir.
There is no doubt now that General Hampton
is holding this secret document.
Problem is the location.
We must find out where he's keeping it.
We will find out soon.
I really don't get it.
What's so special about that document,
sending our government into a frenzy
to get their hands on it?
A bug?!
Hampton, Hamburger or whatever...
You wiretapped that fella's office?
Yes.
Wouldn't that be dangerous?
What if they find out?
They will never be able to find it,
so you needn't worry.
Anyhow, there's no time to waste.
Find out where they keep that document.
But I'd like to ask you something.
What do you plan to do with that
secret document regarding Vietnam?
Ohh... You don't need to know.
I know that a few of your colleagues' heads
depend on this mission of mine.
What's with all this curiosity?
All you need to do
is complete your task.
By any chance,
does it have anything to do with
your development plans in South Seoul?
To my knowledge, you've bought land
in Gangnam under a namesake,
without informing the president...
Listen to you!
That's what I don't like about you!
Never minding your own business.
Seems like my guess was right.
May I see those development plans?
Look, Jo Pilyeon!
I'm staking my life on this task.
I have no intention of
being moved around like a pawn,
without even knowing what benefits this
will bring to our country and the president.
If you insist on treating me
like an outsider,
then we can part ways right now.
You can do the dirty work yourselves.
- What are you doing?
- We'll show it to you.
But before that,
let's make one thing perfectly clear.
If you use these plans
for your personal gains,
you're making a mistake
you will dearly pay for.
If those were my intentions, I'd have
focused on real estate from the start.
Why would I ever risk
so much doing this, then?
Here's our development plans
for South Seoul.
~ South Seoul Land Development Plan ~
If my behavior insulted you,
accept my apologies.
I merely was wishing for you to
think of me as a brother in arms.
Should you fail...
You'll be the first
to pay with your life.
You really seem to have
riled up Congressman Oh.
As he wishes.
We'll continue needing his support,
so shouldn't we avoid enraging him?
Always do as they tell you, and you'll
only amount to a puppet they control.
There soon will be a
revolution in Gangnam.
An epochal change we
couldn't possibly fathom.
Those quick on their feet will
see Gangnam turn into a goldmine,
while the rest will only
be left with useless gravel.
I told you, didn't I?
If you want to gain power,
you need money.
It's a dog-eat-dog world
we're dealing with,
so nothing says we shouldn't
fight to survive as well.
I'll go see Director Hwang, so call him.
Yes.
Dead?!
Are you telling me
their mother is dead?
I went to the district ward,
and saw the certificate of death.
And the kids?
I asked around, but couldn't find them.
Even if you have to ransack
every orphanage in Busan,
we must find them.
I already set some
of my men in motion.
Jo Pilyeon...
That wretched scumbag...
What on earth is he
trying to accomplish?
Yes?
Yes, that'd be me.
Sure.
It's the development plan for South Seoul.
They're soon going to erect a huge
integrated government building in Gangnam.
Paddy fields or forest land,
it makes no difference,
*right at the center of Gangnam District
so buy all the land
you can in Samseong-Dong*.
It's only a matter of time
before that land turns into gold.
I just gave you precious information,
but you don't look too pleased?!
I just found out my friend's wife died.
That man who drove the truck.
I must find out what happened.
I trust you're not responsible, again?
Regrettably,
it wasn't me.
Did you say it was a
briquette gas accident?
Yes.
Happy now?
You're not telling me you're looking
for your late friend's family?
Seems like I was mistaken about you.
Why did you become so weak?
We're a mortal enemy to them,
both you and I!
Keep acting this way,
and I'll make sure
I find them before you do.
Is that clear?
Forget them.
Erase all those squalid
memories blinding you,
and start worrying about making money.
I'll help you out.
I need no help, so just go.
Go.
Ajeosshi.
Anything I can help you with?
No need.
Have a nice day.
I'll help you.
I have no jobs to give you.
Just go.
It's okay, I'll still help you.
I said I'm not hiring. Leave.
You don't need to pay money.
I'll just help you with this.
Think I don't get what
you're trying to do?
Don't even think of trying
to get any of these, and leave!
You little scoundrel,
as if I wasn't busy enough...
Ajumma!
Ajumma.
Can you breastfeed the baby?
I'll sing you a song if you do.
I just fed my baby...
Ajumma!
Ajumma...
Ajumma.
The baby is starving.
Could you help me out?
Sorry.
Ajumma...
Aren't you that...
I won't steal your briquettes,
so don't worry.
Ohh... All right.
Aigoo... That won't do it.
Come and help me pull.
The wheel is stuck, so it won't work.
Ahh... Really, I'm delivering
right around the corner.
Aigoo... What now?
What else can I do?
I'll just have to go back.
- Here...
- Just a second.
It's all right now, so you can go.
I'll help you carry it all the way.
Don't ask me for money later.
I'm not expecting any.
You live here?
Yes.
Is that the welfare center?
Yes. A young boy, and a little girl...
Also, there's an infant as well.
They're orphans with nowhere to go.
Yes.
When are you coming?
Oppa, where have you been?
Know how worried I was?
Sorry.
Did you eat?
Yeah... I fed the baby as well.
But, how about you?
I'm fine.
You didn't eat a thing, did you?
I knew it.
Have this. Ajeosshi gave it to me,
so I kept some for you.
By the way,
why is your face so dirty?
I found a job.
A job?
Yeah. Briquette delivery.
Here... Look.
It's all the money I made today.
You're really great,
now you even make money.
I'll have to start by
buying you some new shoes.
It's all right.
We need to save money, if we want
to buy some milk for the baby.
Is it them?
Yes.
What's the matter, Ajumma?
Follow us to the orphanage.
Orphanage?
You'll have it much easier there.
Right. Listen to them.
You can even have
your baby adopted overseas.
Adopted overseas?
Do you know how nice
a place to live in America is?
There's plenty to eat,
and with a nice foster family,
they can even send you to college.
Isn't that right?
No way!
Forget the orphanage
or taking the baby.
I'll raise them all by myself.
You're too young
to have any authority over them.
And we have the responsibility
to protect children like you.
Do you understand
what I'm trying to say?
Oppa...
Open the door!
We're here to help you!
I don't need your help, so just leave!
If you really insist,
then let us just take the baby.
You can't raise a baby
all by yourselves.
Oppa, I don't want
to give them the baby.
Let's all live together.
Uh?
I'm not sending you anywhere.
I'll raise you by myself.
Open the door!
What if something happens to the baby?
I said open!
Open!
Whomever it is, try to mess with
my siblings and you'll pay!
Look at him staring down at us!
Drop that down!
I don't need a thing!
I don't need your money,
or anything else,
so just leave us alone!
We're not trying to hurt you.
Our job is taking care
of orphans like you.
We're no orphans!
We have a brother.
A brother?
And where is your brother?
I don't know.
Still, we're going to meet soon.
When we meet,
we'll live together by ourselves.
So we don't need your help!
- All right, so just...
- Who are you?
Honey...
What are you doing here?
You said you'd be late?!
You came home early?
Aigoo... You brat...
We found out where they're
keeping the secret document.
Where is that?
Inside General Hampton's office.
Remember the frame behind his desk?
Behind that frame is a secret safe box.
How many troops there on night shift?
There will be sentinels
guarding the entrance,
while those on day duty are always
on stand-by to reinforce them.
I think we should act during
the day, on the contrary.
Then, it has to be when
Hampton leaves his office.
But even without him,
his aide will always be there.
It's not going to be easy.
Keep your ears on the wire.
We will get a chance to act.
Yes, Sir.
Who's out there?
Who are you?
I brought back the
uniform from the laundry.
Wait.
The laundry delivers even at night?
I was passing by,
and saw the lights on...
Are you an army officer?
I'm not.
Quite young for a paramilitary.
Keep your ears on the wire.
We will get a chance to act.
Were you looking for us?
What's the closest oil depot
to the Compound B barracks?
Yes.
On the hill right behind the barracks.
Personnel on duty?
All troops from our Korean support.
Make that oil depot explode.
If you cause an explosion there,
they'll be forced out to tame the flames.
That's when we'll act.
Understood.
Find when Hampton will be on leave.
That will be our D-Day.
How are you?
Oppa!
It's cold, why did you come out?
You said you'd be home early,
why are you so late?
I had a lot to do today.
Instead, I made a ton of money?!
Really?
Here... See what comes out of here.
They're shoes?!
Put them on.
They fit just right.
They're really warm.
Thanks, Oppa.
It's cold... Why take them off?
I want them to last.
I said I'll make a lot of money.
I'll buy another pair,
so come on and wear them.
Nope.
I'll put them on
when we go meet Big Oppa.
What if Big Oppa
forgets to come tomorrow?
Think he's like you?
Forgetting things...
If he finds out Mommy died,
he'll start crying?!
Miju.
Will you sing me a song?
Want to hear one?
Yeah...
All right, since you
even bought me shoes...
~ Thinking of Oppa (old lullaby) ~
"Here comes the water cock,
quacking on the paddy field."
"Here comes the cuckoo,
echoing in the forest."
"When my Oppa will ride
to Seoul with his horse,"
"He said he will bring me silken shoes."
Aigoo... I said I won't steal it.
Iron this one for me.
I'm going out now.
Out?
Meeting someone?
I'll finish this one first.
Ohh... You...
First time I see you this way?!
Going somewhere nice?
Tell me.
Is it a girl?
It is... Right? It's a girl!
Admit it.
It's not...
General Hampton just left the base.
How about the oil depot?
We've completed all preparatives.
If this fails,
we're all dead.
You must succeed
without a single blemish.
Is that clear?
Yes, Sir.
Loyalty!
I think we should act during
the day, on the contrary.
Yes.
Yes, copy that.
Fire in the oil depot!
Hurry up and put out the fire!
Aigoo... You're going?
Yes. Thank you for everything.
You had started growing on me
the last few days?!
So your brother
is only a high schooler?
You're going to have it hard,
dealing with an infant and all.
They're clever,
so they'll find a way to make it.
You can find 31 Building
by yourself, right?
Yes. Goodbye.
Goodbye.
Aigoo... Right...
- Bye
- Bye!
- What's wrong with you...
- Bye.
Drop the knife.
Drop it!
Who's there?
Goddamned kid.
Jesus... Halt!
Halt...
Jesus... Kid.
Kid... Kid... Are you all right?
Hey... Medic!
Hey... Kid, come on!
Did he see your face?
Did he see your face or not, you idiot?
He... might have.
You useless fool!
I deserve to be punished!
Who are we dealing with?
It's that paramilitary from the laundry.
Where is he now?
He's in the infirmary,
still unconscious.
If he regains his senses,
it's all over for us.
Do you get it?
Before that happens,
I'll get rid of him myself.
We have done all we can.
It's up to him now.
Take him to a specialist.
He needs to wake up.
We have an eye-witness,
who can positively identify
the criminal leaving the building.
We're working on a composite sketch.
The suspect was looking
precisely for the document.
Hurry up!
Get going! Quick!
Who are you?
What brings you here, if I may ask...
I came to the wrong ward.
Wait.
Wait a moment.
Stop.
Wait...
You!
Major Jo's assistant?!
Looks like him.
What are you doing here?
You were here.
I was looking for you.
Ahh... Here's my aide.
Remember?
Good.
You and I have to talk, Major.
You bring him with you.
Fine with me.
This fire at the depot was without
a doubt our support officers' mistake.
As their officer in charge,
I take all responsibility,
and I'd like to extend
my sincerest apologies to you.
Someone ransacked my office.
Are you saying a theft took place?
Luckily we have a soldier who
witnessed the person leaving this room.
Come on in.
I think this is the right guy.
Are you trying to accuse him
of being a thief?
No, not a thief. A spy.
Arrest him.
What if it turns out your
subordinate made a wrong call?
I'm sure that most Koreans
look the same to you.
If you accuse my aide of espionage
based only on his assumptions,
then I'll have to officially
file a complaint to my superiors.
Sir... We're being bugged.
He knew exactly
where the document was.
Only you and I knew where it was.
So the only way
they could have known...
is if we were bugged.
Bugged?!
Go ahead.
File a complaint.
But if there's a bug
inside this orchid pot,
it's gonna be you who's
held responsible for destroying...
the military relationship
between our two countries.
Wait!
But instead,
if there is no bug inside,
what will you do?
It's a shame.
I thought of you as
a good friend of mine.
However, for the sake of
our countries' relationship,
I will make a personal effort
to ignore this incident.
We have another witness.
Until he regains consciousness,
we'll keep your aide.
Oppa!
It's snowing!
Mom told me,
that when it snows,
you'll meet the people you miss.
Hyung will be here for sure today.
I have no doubt.
Big Oppa!
Hurry up and come!
I miss you, Big Oppa!
Gangmo...
Miju...
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Why isn't Big Oppa coming?
He's hiding somewhere else,
and then will suddenly appear.
Who are you?
Where do you come from?
Why did you send me that note,
and who the hell are you?
Ohh?! Big Oppa!
Oppa!
Little Oppa...
What are you doing?
Just getting rid of all the dirt.
For free?!
Tell me.
Is he the one responsible?
It was not him.
Who gave you permission
to shine shoes here?
Why, can't I do that here?
How dare you barge in
on someone else's turf?
I'm no real estate speculator.
Listen, Director Hwang!
Sell that land or block the river,
I couldn't care less.
All I want you to do is making the most
money in the shortest amount of time.
If you lose my favor,
you'll only end up in misery.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com