Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 59
Excuse me.
I'd like to ask you something.
Among the patients here,
is there a certain Lee Seongmo?
Lee Seongmo?
Was he hospitalized here?
This would be him.
Ahh... He comes
here regularly for check-ups.
Right, it's him.
May I have a look at his medical record?
What for?
Actually, he's the younger
brother I lost back in my childhood.
I really want to find him, so please help me.
Is this him?
Yes, that's the man I saw.
Take a closer look.
Are you really sure?
I'm a big fan of Miss Cha, so I knew
that she was looking for her brother.
I have no doubt.
Oppa...
Gangmo...
Your brother was really alive.
Where did you see him?
I'm looking for this man.
Have you ever seen him here?
Seems like everyone is looking for him today.
Did anyone else come asking about him?
Ahh... Earlier on, someone
saying he was his older brother came.
His older brother?!
Are you telling me this
man's older brother came here?
He just said he was his long lost brother...
The address was wrong.
Wrong?!
It is true he went to that hospital,
but the address he gave them is fake.
Then, just leave.
Leave?!
But, Congressman.
Lee Seongmo might not be
mentally stable, but he is alive.
I have my plans, so just come back.
Then, I'll take another quick look
around the port and leave.
Excuse me.
What is the matter?
Does a certain Lee Seongmo live here?
And who the hell is this Lee Seongmo,
pestering people all day asking for him...
You'll pardon me,
- but the address I was given is this.
- Ahh... He doesn't live here.
Just go. Aigoo... How annoying...
Ma'am...
That's strange?!
The address is right.
Seems like your reputation
in Sokcho precedes you.
I'm still nothing more than a private lender.
He's Lee Gangmo's older brother,
currently hiding in Sokcho.
A bullet penetrated his skull,
so he's barely surviving.
Seems he doesn't even know who he is.
So do you want me to find him for you?
Would that be possible?
I was about to join my
father's camp and help him, actually.
Help him? I guess you
just want to benefit from him.
He's a congressman from the ruling party,
so isn't taking advantage of his
influence what you're really after?
If I'm allowed to, why not?
This is what business
acumen is about, after all.
Your father won't cut it.
He has no ambition.
Think about it.
What would you possibly get from someone
who acts as if a gold badge is all he needed?
Then, what would you do for me instead?
I will be soon nominated
as the new prime minister.
If you bring Lee Seongmo to me,
I'll give you everything your father can't.
Let's have a drink.
They taste great.
- How much is it?
- Two for 50,000 won.
You like this, right?
Look here.
Are his conditions that bad?
Enough not to remember a thing?
There's a bullet stuck in his head.
Just being alive is a miracle.
I've looked at the village office
and asked the realtor,
and seems like they moved quite frequently.
So there's a woman
looking after him, right?
Yeah... On his hospital records,
it was listed as Hong Jisoo.
It's obvious that they
know they're being chased.
So that's why they
were hiding their real address.
Who is that woman
and why is she helping him?
A spy.
Spy?!
That colleague of Seongmo who
was exploited by Jo Pilyeon?
I guess that's an alias.
Because there is no one else
who could be looking after him.
Yes?
It's me, Gangmo.
Can we meet?
I'm not in Seoul right now.
Is it urgent?
Seems like Jo Pilyeon might have
been chosen as our next prime minister.
I was wondering if you could come
and discuss a solution with me.
All right. I'll call you
again when I get there.
I think I'll have to
go back to Seoul right now.
You remain here.
All right.
- How much for this?
- 10,000 won.
Miju....
Mi... Miju.
Miju...
What's wrong, Oppa?
Get in the car.
I'll be right back.
Ajeosshi!!
Ajeosshi!
Ajeosshi...
What's the order this time?
Did Jo Pilyeon...
tell you to find my brother and
get rid of him once and for all?
I always thought this,
but I can't still can't stand
how you just call him by name.
Did he order you to kill him?
Die!
Oppa, don't!
Don't do it... Don't!
Listen well!
Whatever you try,
you'll never stop him!
Go back...
and convey my words to Jo Pilyeon.
Tell him that as long
as Lee Gangmo is alive,
he will never, ever gain what he wants.
Because I will...
I will force the most
miserable of downfalls on him.
Ajeosshi...
Ajeosshi.
It's all right.
It's me, Yeonsoo...
Let's go home.
What?
Lee Gangmo?
He found out that
Lee Seongmo is in Sokcho.
Looks like he'll bite me and
never let go like a rabid dog.
We have no time to waste.
Even if we send out all our men,
we must find Lee Seongmo at all cost.
No need to worry.
Hwang Jeongshik will take
care of our matter in Sokcho.
You mean Hwang Taeseop's son?
Seems like he's got
quite the clout in the area.
If we leave it to him,
he'll take care of it in no time.
But they say blood
is thicker than water.
With Hwang Taeseop gritting
his teeth waiting to destroy you,
how can you leave
something so crucial to his son?
Ambition is
much thicker than blood.
Not to mention that Hwang
Jeongshik still resents his father.
But when will the new
cabinet be announced?
This weekend.
Then, will you be
nominated prime minister?
It's already been decided.
What?
Only the announcement is left now.
Congratulations, Congressman!
You've worked hard all this time, Jaechun.
So... If there's anything you
want, don't hesitate to tell me.
Just seeing you attain glory and
success is enough for me, Sir.
I have no eyes for people with no ambition.
Would a building in Gangnam do?
Congressman...
Fame is all fine and dandy, but growing
old without money will only bring you misery.
Just accept it.
Then...
I will gladly accept it.
If Hwang Jeongshik finds Lee Seongmo,
everything will be solved.
Nobody will be able to stop us.
How did it go?
The rumors are true.
Jo Pilyeon will be announced
as the next prime minister.
Then, are you telling us that
there is no way to stop him now?
There are rumblings in the opposition
to motion for a special cabinet hearing.
A special cabinet hearing?
Is there any chance to make this reality?
Considering all the rumors about
the former president's secret fund,
many people in congress
still find Jo Pilyeon's behavior suspect.
If all the former opposition members
who joined the ruling party through...
the 3-party merger join forces with them,
then there will be no
way for Jo to avoid that hearing.
That cabinet hearing is our very last chance.
But we're still dealing with a cabinet hearing.
Unless he's accused of
critical wrongdoings,
it will be hard to revoke his nomination.
If this hearing does take
place, when will it happen?
Since they'll have to form a special
committee made of congressmen,
I guess early next month?
I'll volunteer for the committee
and help bring him down.
You will?
Is there any other congressman
who knows Jo Pilyeon as well as I do?
Fine.
Let's give it a try.
Gangmo.
Can you find Seongmo
before that hearing begins?
I must find him.
Whatever it takes, I will.
A cabinet hearing?!
Whose idea is that?
That's not the issue.
The chairman of this
special committee is Min Honggi.
What?!
Min Honggi?
And Hwang Taeseop already
volunteered to participate.
If you add the opposition party,
out of 13 members in total, the
majority will be there to attack you.
Seems like you'll have to take
very strong countermeasures, Sir.
Get your hands on the
list of committee members.
What for?
We still have enough time.
We can just convince
them to jump ship.
Get yourself a seat in there as well.
It will be hard for me.
I was already assigned to the special
committee for the minister of defense.
Look, Congressman Oh.
Have we already forgotten who bought
you that golden badge of yours?
You said the hearing will last a day, right?
If I can get through that day,
I will become prime minister.
Sorry for not calling
you more often, Mom.
Is Wooju...
Let me talk to him.
Wooju!
It's Mommy.
Yeah...
How are you?
The art class?
Then draw me a
portrait and then send it.
Let's see how good you've become.
All right.
I miss you, too.
Soojeong, the director is here.
Wooju, I'll call you later.
All right.
I love you, Wooju.
We're not doing scene 42,
we'll just start from scene 27, so get ready.
Yes, Director.
- Remember the right costumes.
- Yes.
Right...
By the way, Director.
Is Sunny Film the main investor, again?
Looks like their president
is a huge fan of yours.
They've invested in my films for years already,
I was just wondering if I could meet him.
I don't really know... He's away on
business abroad, so he'll be busy.
- Production/Investment -
Sunny Films
You want a five billion loan?
We have no time.
- The four billion you added...
- Have I ever failed...
to pay our interests on time?
Not even once.
I'm busy, so let's
wrap this up quickly.
Miss Choi? Bring me that
data about Manbo Group.
Here it is, Chairman.
I see we've got quite
a few bank loans here?!
Not to mention that
Manbo Plaza is your collateral.
Will you do it, or not?
What's the reason you still haven't
completed those apartments in Ilsan?
I didn't come here for business advice.
You'll have to forgive me, but
there will be no additional loans.
Hey... Hwang Jeongyeon.
With finances in this state, would
you be able to pay on time?
So you've had your cake and that's it...
Look at me.
You're talking to Manbo Group,
fighting for the top of the sector!
I know.
You should have taken better care
of what you so despicably stole from me.
Miss Choi.
Check their loan terms and make sure
they don't miss payments by a single day.
All right, Chairman.
This is serious, Chairman.
Where are we going to
find those five billion now?
I'll start by canceling Sunny
Film's investment projects.
Go ahead with those
film projects as planned.
Chairman.
We'll just have to make that money.
But your father is asking for it right now.
Anyhow, our film investment...
What is a famous movie
star like you doing here?
Should have seen your film at least once,
but I really have no time for that these days.
Whenever I can, I'll go see it.
Come in, Miju.
Any news of your brother?
Nothing new yet.
How about Gangmo?
These days he's completely
focused on finding Seongmo.
That's not what your
sleek image suggested.
Feels more like a dorm in here.
Even if you have to hire
more people to find him, don't stop.
We have no time, Shideok.
We must find him
before the cabinet hearing.
Don't worry.
We're not going back to Seoul
until we find Seongmo Hyung.
All right.
What do you mean?
You're just going to live here?
So let's hurry up and find him.
Ahh... I miss my wife and kids
so much, I can't take it anymore.
Get out of the way.
Baby?
It's me, Sotae.
[literally *first male **second male]
I see... How about Ilnam* and Yinam**?
They're playing?
But I miss you so much...
It's driving me insane.
What's wrong with me?
This is so corny I can't bear to listen.
If it's corny, get out of here
and spare yourself the spectacle.
As if you weren't curious...
[*slang for goosebumps]
Hello? Nah...
Your brother has chicken flesh*.
Chicken flesh?
Ohh... I suddenly feel
like eating chicken!
Chicken?
Eat it, then.
You're pregnant, so you should
eat whatever you want.
I went to the hospital earlier on,
and they say this time it's a girl.
- Aigoo... Our son-in-law is a stallion!
- The hell are you saying! The kids will hear you...
Aigoo... Ilnam, eat this.
Want some milk, Yinam?
But, since it's a girl,
what do we call her?
[*lit. third one]
Samsoon*?!
Don't know... It is easy on the ears...
That's nice, uh?
Ilnam, Yinam, Samsoon.
[*lit. fifth one]
- Go all the way to Ohsoon*.
- Aigoo! Want to make a baseball team?
As if you were doing all the hard work.
Keep quiet, will you?
Nah... Go ahead...
I miss you...
Jeongyeon.
You're back?
Hungry, aren't you?
Come have dinner.
How did you get in here?
I asked Miju to give me the keys.
She was worried about you.
Let's eat.
I'm hungry, too.
I remember back in the day...
I cooked for you once in the past.
Remember how salty
that stew you made was?
Right, it was.
And you still ate it all
without saying a thing.
It was so long ago,
but it still feels like yesterday.
Have you seen?
From here on in,
Hwang Jeongyeon is mine.
I, Lee Gangmo,
join Hwang Jeongyeon
in marriage here and now.
I have nothing to give her,
but I'll love her more
than anyone in the world.
May you watch over us,
and help me give her happiness.
What are you thinking about?
What were you thinking
about, to get so surprised?
It's nothing.
You...
have become a lot better at this.
It's really good.
Great.
Gangmo.
Do you have time tomorrow?
People who were part of our
organization opened a business in Sokcho.
Their specialty is finding missing people.
Jeongyeon...
If your brother is there,
I'm sure they'll find him.
Leave it to me, Gangmo.
What are you trying to say?
I told you I needed the money today!
I'm doing everything in my power,
so give me a little more time.
How many times do I have to
tell you that there is no time?
Before the cabinet hearing begins,
I must buy that committee's favors.
Think that money will just
pour out like water from a tap?
If nothing else works, then just
sell Manbo Plaza and get it over with!
The finish line is near, Minwoo.
Money is not the issue.
The day when the entire world
will be at the tip of your fingers is coming.
Just keep going.
If you stop the pedal,
then the bicycle is only going to fall.
Are we clear, son?
I'll get you that money by tomorrow.
Don't you ever
break your promises again.
Take five billion from the
Manbo Plaza construction budget.
That would be embezzlement of public funds.
So?
Are you going to press charges?
Chairman!
I can't stop this anymore, either.
Then, are you going
to delay the construction?
No, speed it up.
What are you trying to accomplish?
I'll deal with it, so just
proceed as instructed!
Come on in, Chairman.
He's Chairman Lee Gangmo
of Hangang Construction.
Nice to meet you,
my name is Go Bongshik.
Nice to meet you, I'm Lee Gangmo.
- I'm Kim Wooshik.
- It's a pleasure.
Come on in, President Hwang.
Say Hi.
Here's Chairman Hwang
Jeongyeon of Happy Bank,
and Chairman Lee Gangmo
of Hangang Construction.
Nice to meet you, I'm Hwang Jeongshik.
So you're going to open a resort here?
I feel it every time I come,
but the scenery here is just fabulous.
Once the highway gets here,
it will become a major tourist attraction.
How much do you plan
to invest in the project?
Find this man for us.
So you're positive that he's here?
We're sure.
It's really urgent, so please try
to find him as soon as possible.
We'll discuss our investment
projects after you find him.
I'm sure that's okay with you?
Fine.
We'll do our best to find him right away.
The government announced
its fourth cabinet selection.
Chairman of the Korean Policy
Development Committee Jo Pilyeon....
has been announced as candidate
for the seat of prime minister.
With a past in the army's
intelligence department,
Jo joined the 12th legislature as congressman,
and is renowned for combining
boldness with determination.
But over a hundred
congressmen from both parties...
filed a motion requesting a cabinet
hearing regarding this reshuffle.
Ajeosshi!
What's the matter?
What's going on?
It's all right... Everything's fine...
It's a true honor to have you here tonight.
The cabinet hearing is
right around the corner,
I wonder if Jo Pilyeon's son
should really meet us this way.
I'm the one who arranged all this.
If it made you uncomfortable,
allow me to apologize.
That's not what I meant,
it's just that people
have eyes to see, you know...
If he learns of this meeting,
my father will angrily reproach me.
Since we're here, I'll be honest with you.
I'd like you to help out my
father at the upcoming hearing.
It's something the president already decided upon,
so why would we oppose it?
Thank you, Congressman Park.
Here...
Let's have a drink.
Are they all gone?
Yes.
Hwang Taeseop didn't come?
Weren't you expecting that?
Guess he must be
preparing to bring me down.
Isn't it a little too early to
give up trying to convince him?
You want me to ask
Hwang Taeseop for help?
If there's anyone who can be
swayed by power, that's politicians.
You've been proclaimed prime minister,
so there's no way he would take this to the end.
You do have a point.
Try to approach
Hwang Taeseop as well, then.
All right.
You must be prepared for the
possibility that they might not find him.
Should that be the case,
we'll have to stake everything
on that cabinet hearing.
I'll prepare all the data for the hearing.
If you need any witness, I will do it.
Right... Do it yourselves
without any aide's help.
This way, please.
Careful.
Leave it here.
What's this?
What the hell is this about?
It's by Robert Mann,
he's a very famous painter.
Must be really expensive?
It would sell for at least
100,000 dollars in New York.
What... 100,000 dollars?
That much money for this painting?
And who sent it?
Even the courier
didn't know the sender.
I don't really know if I can accept this.
I think a guest might visit you very soon.
A guest?
Yes.
Hwang Taeseop speaking.
It's been a while, Congressman Hwang.
What is all this data?
Tell me about it...
If we need to go
through this all, it'll kill us...
Shall we get started?
We'll have to first classify
them by content, right?
So you sent me that painting?
It was hard to get my hands on it...
Why, you don't like it?
The world must have really changed.
The sight of me groveling at your feet and
throwing money at you feels like yesterday...
Now you're the one sending me that...
I came here to bury the
hatchet, Congressman Hwang.
What is politics, after all?
Isn't it all about using people
to help you gain more power?
Why don't you get to the point, then?
You can use me for real, this time.
If I become premier,
your path to success
will be like a walk in the park.
So you're asking me to be on your
side at the upcoming cabinet hearing.
At a time like this, the
both of us need political allies.
That's interesting.
But, you know... While those
who hit might not remember,
the ones who get hit always
seem to recall quite clearly.
Dwell in the past and you'll
never evolve, Congressman Hwang.
Let's only think about
the future ahead of us.
Fine.
That's all fine with me...
But there's one little
issue getting in the way.
Tell me.
Let's speak our hearts
out and make a fresh start.
Have you forgotten
that you once tried to kill me?
What are you saying, Congressman Hwang?
I remember clearly what you told me,
right as I was on the brink of death.
Are you starting to understand now?
What the price
to pay for betraying me is.
Take a good look, Chairman Hwang.
At how my son Minwoo devours Manbo
Construction while you're not around.
Do you even know why I entered politics?
Power?!
I don't need any of that!
I only did it to deal
with you once and for all!
Congressman Hwang...
There must be a misunderstanding here.
Take a good look.
This is what awaits you.
I will destroy you with
my own hands, Jo Pilyeon!
Still as foolish as ever...
We'll soon find out who
ends up like that painting.
You want to increase
the theater's seating to 500?
I want to make Manbo Plaza's
theater the best in the country.
But, Chairman.
With all the structural
changes we already made,
the load will be unbearable.
When are you ever going to complete it,
if you keep worrying about that?
Because of those lobbying funds,
we had to use 23 inch pillars
instead of the 32 inch ones we needed.
- And that's not the end of it...
- Director Moon!
Just complete construction, for starters.
All the aspects we
sacrificed for lack of funds...
will be addressed after my
father becomes prime minister.
Is that clear?
Are you that obsessed with this
theater just because of Cha Soojeong?
It's for my sake.
Because it's what I want.
You were here.
How did it go with Congressman Hwang?
That fool declared war
on me right in my face.
Lee Gangmo won't just sit
back and watch at the hearing.
Unless Lee Seongmo shows up,
he won't be able to do much,
but he'll surely help Hwang Taeseop.
Then, is it war?
So you'll have to help me.
What kind of questions do you think
the hearing committee will focus on?
Considering Congressman
Oh Byeongtak's secret report...
That's right.
They'll focus on our connection
with the private lending cartel.
And my father's past political
actions will be added to the plate as well.
I want over a thousand possible
questions for every single scenario.
Select three hundred questions
most likely to be asked, and create a questionnaire.
This sums up the connection
between Noh Gapsoo and Jo Pilyeon.
How about the data
involving Manbo Construction?
We're almost done
with their tax situation.
How about the construction committee?
It's quite complicated,
so it may take some time.
If we want to bring Jo Pilyeon down,
we must get a hold of
even the slightest blunder.
Any news from Sokcho?
They say they're still looking for him,
but looks like there were no
particular developments.
Timing is the problem.
We must find him
before the hearing is over.
Here...
Is it good, Ajeosshi?
Have some stew, too.
This is really good.
Sorry, Ajeosshi.
Are you all right?
Did you get burned?
I wish you could say my name just once.
"It's all right, Yeonsoo..."
Like that.
I... It's...
all right... It's...
It's all... right.
Yeonsoo.
Ji Yeonsoo.
Go ahead and say it.
Yeonsoo...
Mi... Miju...
Again Miju?
Finish eating by yourself.
Here.
I love you, Ajeosshi.
Even if you don't like me,
I will love you more
than anyone in the world.
You're going to go on the
offensive against Jo Pilyeon,
what will you focus on?
We'll talk later.
- Any other issue other than this?
- Later. I'll talk later.
Are you ready?
I did my very best,
so let's just go for it.
Chairman Lee.
- Sir.
- Good job.
First, our congratulations.
What do you think about
people expressing their surprise...
for your nomination as new prime minister?
Yes...
I think there's a good reason why
the president chose me as prime minister.
Several rumors have been spread,
tell us your feelings about this cabinet hearing.
I pride myself on having
devoted my entire life...
for the sake of this country and our people.
And that is why I hope this hearing will
help put those groundless rumors to sleep,
and reveal the truth once and for all.
We will now begin the cabinet
hearing for the prime minister.
First, we'll have
the official candidate's oath.
I now ask the candidate to raise
his right hand and recite the oath,
after which he will sign
and seal the pledge,
and present it to the
chairman of the committee.
Oath.
As the official candidate,
I swear to tell the whole truth and
nothing but the truth, so help me God.
March 6, 1992.
Official candidate, Jo Pilyeon.
Next, we will hear the official
candidate's opening speech.
Candidate, you are kindly encouraged
to keep your speech under ten minutes.
Esteemed Chairman Min Honggi.
And gentlemen of the committee.
I stand before you today as official
candidate for prime minister,
a privilege I was
honored to be bestowed with.
I also must extend my sincerest gratitude
to the committee members who took time...
out of their busy schedules to be here.
Should I be proclaimed prime minister,
I would devote my every effort,
regardless of partisan affiliation...
So I hear you're cutting corners
to fund your father's lobbying?
Still engaging in
flights of fancy, I see...
At least do that properly.
Because if things go wrong, everything
you built could collapse out of nowhere.
We'll begin with the DLP's
Congressman Oh Segwang.
You've spent quite a few years
in the intelligence department,
what were your duties?
I was in the inspection division.
My main duty was that of bringing
to light subversive acts of corruption.
Do you believe to be righteous enough to
deserve judging other people's behavior?
As you can see in the data
which was distributed to you,
all my assets amount to
is a villa in Yonhee-Dong,
and the ancestral graveyard site
I inherited from my late father.
But of course I already pledged to
devote that land to a welfare institution.
Your son is chairman of
Manbo Construction, right?
My son was hired as a mere clerk,
and reached that position all on his own.
I always thought I could win one over him,
so if you help me become prime
minister, I'll finally save face for a change.
- Yes.
- President.
We found Lee Seongmo.
Where is he?
That's the woman who's
looking after Lee Seongmo.
Where did you hide that videotape?
Uh?
And the account?
- Search everywhere!
- Yes.
Next, Congressman Hwang Taeseop,
you may begin your inquiries.
I'm Hwang Taeseop.
The data and questionnaires
you gave us seem really flawless.
Thank you.
If I hadn't known a certain Jo Pilyeon firsthand,
I'd be led to think that you're
the most honest and deserving...
candidate for premier that
our country has ever seen.
But, unfortunately for you,
and most thankfully for this country,
I can pride myself on knowing
Jo Pilyeon more than anyone else.
Congressman Hwang,
I'd like you to refrain from...
such invectives moved only by personal grudges.
You just worry about
answering my questions.
Remember what
happened on April 17, 1987?
Well... I'm not the kind of man
who would write diaries, so...
It is the day when Congressman Oh
Byeongtak died under mysterious circumstances!
Where were you on
that day, from 2 to 4 pm?
I don't remember.
You don't?!
Then, I'm sure you don't remember
who you met eleven days after the fact,
on April 28 at 9 pm?!
Chairman.
The prosecutors already found
me not guilty of any such allegation.
I'd like you to caution him against
engaging in unnecessary mudslinging.
Yes.
Chairman Hwang, I must ask you to
present clear evidence supporting your claims.
Fine.
Candidate Jo seems
to suffer from bad memory, so...
Chairman.
I would like to call a witness.
We will accept your request.
The witness may enter.
Witness, do you swear to tell the
truth before this court and your fellow citizens?
I do.
You may begin your inquiries.
Witness.
On April 28, 1987...
At 9 pm.
Where were you
and what were you doing?
I was in an abandoned factory in Shiheung,
meeting Jo Pilyeon.
What happened there?
He pointed a gun at me.
And threatened to kill me,
asking me to give him the account.
By account,
what was he referring to?
Chairman.
The witness is engaging in despicable
perjury before the entire country!
I ask the questions!
Keep your mouth shut!
Look, Congressman Hwang!
Are we here to settle old scores?
Settle what?!
Please, be quiet.
Witness, you may continue.
There was an account.
It listed all the large sums of money Jo
Pilyeon received from corporations...
on behalf of a very high ranking official.
Witness.
Who would this "high ranking official" be?
The former president.
Ajeosshi, I'm ba...
Ajeosshi...
Ajeosshi!
What's this?
It shows nothing.
Seems like it wasn't recorded properly.
So no account,
and we did all this for nothing.
How should I deal with him?
What do you think?
We'll just hand him to Jo Pilyeon.
It might have been a
good showing on your part,
but I'm afraid that won't cut it with me.
So let's hear it, what's this clear
evidence you wanted to lure me here with?
Were you so scared of it
that you abducted me?
I wasn't scared, just curious.
And I also came to
get something from you.
Speak!
What on earth is this
clear evidence you talked about?
I guess only the audio is fine.
The witness' testimony is a travesty!
A secret presidential fund account?!
Let's hear what else
he has to say, shall we?
What else would you listen to?
This is a cabinet hearing!
Look here!
Is the cabinet hearing
the real issue here?
Chairman!
We must sue the witness and
Congressman Hwang for contempt of congress!
Sue?!
We're just exposing the
truth, what damned lawsuit?!
You're just a traitor, shut your mouth!
Traitor?!
How old are you, little prick?
How dare you talk to me like that?
Back when you
were in the KCIA, who...
Like I needed your help...
What did you say?
The hearing will be briefly adjourned.
Give it a rest, everyone!
Jo Pilyeon...
Don't you try to give
up that candidacy.
What?!
Because...
it's judgment day for you.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Are you telling me
that Manbo Plaza collapsed?
Miju is inside.
Miju is still inside!
I can't take this anymore.
If I'll ever be born again,
I want to be born as your brother.
Congressman Oh Byeongtak
was killed by Jo Pilyeon!
This is the account for that presidential fund.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com