Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 19 -
You still haven't left?
I can't go home.
I couldn't possibly face...
my father and the rest of my family.
Dad!
Dad, you can't do this.
Don't do it, Dad.
I'm sorry, Jeongyeon.
Jeongyeon.
Did you really mean what
you told me yesterday?
Have you really...
never been attracted to me?
You've never been...
in love with me?!
Yeah.
I meant it.
I see...
Then...
Where can I go now?
I have a hard time taking
care of myself as it is.
Go and worry about your own life now.
Jeongyeon... Jeongyeon!!
- Let go!
- Stop it!
- Hwang Jeongyeon!
- I love you.
I said I love you!
I love you, Gangmo!
Follow me!
I'm going to leave soon.
Can you follow me, wherever I go?
It will be hard to bear.
We can't possibly predict
what difficulties we'll be facing.
But you still...
You'll have to give everything up.
Your dreams...
Your family.
Maybe even the life you're living now.
I'll come.
Together with you.
Wherever it might be,
it doesn't matter.
Have you seen?
From here on in,
Hwang Jeongyeon is mine.
I, Lee Gangmo,
join Hwang Jeongyeon
in marriage here and now.
I have nothing to give her,
but I'll love her more
than anyone in the world.
May you watch over us,
and help me give her happiness.
~ Affection by Jeon Youngrok ~
You will leave my side
before the sun sets,
For what will be our last farewell.
Ahh... I'll be damned.
Jeongyeon.
What?
I brought some hot water...
I'm fine.
If I leave it here, it'll get cold.
It's all right with me,
so I'll just come in a second.
I'm fine... Don't.
What?
- I'll leave it here.
- Th...anks.
Ahh... It's hot!
- Are you all right?
- It's okay.
Did he look?!
I'm sure he didn't...
If I had known earlier,
I could have gone on a diet.
Why is it so hot?
This looks like fun?!
Aren't you washing up?
Already did it earlier on?
Should I just do it again?
I kept sweating and stuff.
It's all right.
Why bother doing it again?
Really?
Seems like you're done?
Uh?
Your hair, it's dry already.
Aren't you tired?
Should I turn off the light?
Yeah... Let's do that.
What is it?
Nothing.
What?
This is really awkward.
Isn't it?
Tell me about it.
Can I hold your hand?
Give me your hand.
It feels good even to
only hold hands, doesn't it?
And if I do this?
If it feels good just by holding hands,
how about now?
Clean this.
Wipe the blood.
You know Hwang Jeongyeon
of Manbo Construction, right?
Yes.
Find out what's going on with her.
All right.
Anything new on
Lee Gangmo's whereabouts?
As you ordered, we're searching around
every port involved with smuggling.
Where is Seongmo now?
He went to Incheon Port.
Incheon?!
I'm taking care of Busan,
while Seongmo is dealing with Incheon.
Yes... Jemul Port Coffeehouse.
Just a moment.
Mister Kwak? A call for you.
Yes.
Yes, who am I speaking to?
Did you get the goods?
Yes, I did.
They're leaving the day
after tomorrow at eight.
He will be wearing
a green New Town cap.
Let's use "lighthouse" as password.
All right.
Don't... Stop it!
Look, isn't it fresh?
Gangmo. Just a moment.
Do that again?
This just won't do it.
I'll worry about groceries,
so you go back first.
Will you be all right by yourself?
Why? Afraid I'll get lost?
Hyung.
When did you get here?
Ohh... Just now.
But, tell me...
What's with those clothes?
Actually, I was about to
call you because of that.
Hyung, can you get me
another spot on that boat?
Were you seeing a woman?
How much longer were you
going to keep it secret?
I know it won't be easy,
but help me out.
I really want to go with her.
What kind of woman are we dealing with?
The one I love.
We'll soon get officially married.
Must be really something, this lady?
Following you couldn't
have been an easy decision.
You'll make it happen, won't you?
I felt uncomfortable sending you alone,
but with someone by your side,
a big weight is off my shoulders.
Thanks, Hyung.
But, where is she?
She'll be back in a moment.
Why don't you meet her before you go?
I certainly would like to,
but I need to go.
You're leaving the day after tomorrow,
here's the password and instructions.
I'll meet her then.
What's wrong with your hand?
It's nothing.
I hurt myself at work.
But, isn't Jeongyeon a little too late?
You know, about that...
I sent Jeongyeon on a business trip.
What is that supposed to mean?
You invite both families to lunch,
and the protagonist is missing?
Something urgent came up at work,
so it couldn't be helped.
I apologize, Chairman.
I should have told you in advance.
Considering how suddenly
things change at work these days...
Let's just finish lunch
and get up for today.
When Jeongyeon is back from her trip,
I'll bring her home myself.
Is there any other issue
between you two?
The only issue is that we're busy.
That is all.
All right, then.
Since Jeongyeon is not here,
if you're done eating, shall we get up?
What's wrong with you?
Someone you know?
Uh? Nah... I don't.
I'll deal with the bill,
so you go ahead first.
- Your wife?
- She went ahead first.
What do I owe this unexpected visit to?
Did you sell out your daughter?
What's that supposed to mean?
Was Jeongyeon's marriage
just a strategic pact?
I didn't push for that.
Don't lie to me!
Don't you remember
how you abandoned me,
just because your wife's parents
funded your business venture?
You're the kind of man who would
do anything for the sake of success.
Look, Gyeongok...
I don't want to hear you call my name!
I'm sorry.
- Back then, I...
- All this time for me has felt like hell.
But the reason I decided to endure it
all was merely for my daughter's sake.
To make sure she would never
have to go through the same thing!
But...
But now you...
Jeongyeon is my daughter.
I want her to be happy just as you do.
And you expect me to believe that?
After forcing her into a
marriage she never wanted?
I will not tolerate seeing her unhappy.
- Gyeongok...
- I said don't call my name!
Cancel her marriage and
let her do what she wants.
It was Jeongyeon's decision.
Don't look down on me.
If anything ever happens to Jeongyeon,
I'll put everything on the line
to destroy Manbo Construction.
I am powerful enough
to fight with you now.
Think I wouldn't be able to?
Jeongyeon will soon be back.
If you really don't want to believe me,
go ask her what she really wants.
I'll follow her wishes.
Chief.
We're in trouble because of the apartment
ads Hwang Jeongyeon was working on.
What are you trying to say?
The shoot is right behind the corner
but she's nowhere to be found.
We have a meeting with
the composer today for the song.
Write a report on our current
progress and bring it to me.
Are you going to take
care of this yourself?
Why don't you just assign
the project to someone else...
Think about it.
How would Jeongyeon find Gangmo,
when even the police can't?
There is someone in the company
who's in contact with him.
And who's that?
Yeom Shideok.
Shideok?!
I'm sure...
that he'll call Shideok again.
Jeongshik.
You'll have to help me out.
Should I just force it
out of Shideok's mouth?
No... Forget that.
Just do as I say.
Whenever a call is directed
to the Goods & Services office,
this phone will ring as well.
But you really think Jeongyeon
went looking for Gangmo?
It's been two days already.
That can only suggest
they spent the night toge...
Hey... Hwang Jeongshik!
Ahh... What the hell...
Ohh... You little...
Just mention Jeongyeon,
and he catches fire.
Don't you worry.
Think there could be anything
between Jeongyeon and Gangmo?
I'll be right back, so stick
to this phone all day. Got it?
Hey... Think I have nothing to do?
I'm busy, man!
Is it anything more important
than this, by any chance?
What if Gangmo told her everything?
All right... I get it.
~ New Talent Auditions ~
Excuse me, what number is in right now?
56 just went in.
Thank God...
I'm 58.
But, did you come to the
audition dressed like that?
Must be really hard to get in.
Haven't you heard about
the composer's nasty temper?
Really?
- Number 57?
- Here!
Come.
- Fighting!
If you're done fighting,
just come in.
Here's Number 57, Seonsaengnim.
~ Opera Records Seasonal Audition ~
~ Jury ~
How are you?
Start.
I'll be singing
Yoon Sinae's "Passion."
At first I thought it was like a stranger
passing by, a feeble breeze grazing my heart.
Hey...
The hell is this, poetry reading?
Sing, will you?
Yes... Of course, sing...
And as if this was
the last thing I'd do.
For the very last time,
let the raging fireworks of love
flutter inside my heart.
Leave, just get out!
What? The song's not over yet?!
Get out, quick!
Will you get out or what?
Out!
Aigoo...
I really had it with this.
How could they all be so useless?
Seonsaengnim. Finding someone
like So Jiyoung will be hard.
So, what?
Want me to give up?
Still... A few of them
seemed to show some potential?!
What do you have,
peanuts in your ears?
I told you I have no intention
to teach third-rate amateurs!
I'll find someone who
can upstage even So Jiyoung.
Don't cry.
You can try again next time.
It's the eighth time already...
Seonsaengnim. Manbo Construction
is here for their commercial ad.
Can't you see we're
having an audition here?
Go on and finish it, I'll just wait.
Number 58.
Yes.
What's with her?!
Are you fools going on
a picnic or something?
Hiring a bus and all.
I apologize, Seonsaengnim.
I finished late at work.
What do I have to see...
I told you to examine
the candidates first!
Bring in the next one.
I'm confident I can do well,
give me a chance.
Let's go, uh?
Just once...
Give me a chance, Seonsaengnim!
Just this once.
Don't act like this.
Then... Let's only do
one verse and then leave.
Thank you.
~ Hyeon & Deok's
"The Girl & The Street Lamp" ~
It was a silent, eerily silent night.
A young lady, standing
by the window in solitude.
She looked at the evening sky,
a dark mantle where no star shone.
Tears flowing down her face,
her cries vanishing in oblivion.
Will the street lamps outside
the window see and hear her tears?
Ghastly, feeble lights, the sole companion
giving her solace in this sad night.
The sole companion giving her
solace in this sad night.
In this silent night,
The only thing she could lean onto,
Fatigued by that mantle of darkness.
Seonsaengnim?
Uh?
Song's over?!
Ohh...
- You!
- I... I'm sorry.
Let me do it once again, Seonsaengnim.
I can do much better.
So you're an amateur who never
received any formal training.
Yes...
What are you, singing at the
market downtown or something?
Going off-key and
missing all the beats.
Today's audition is over.
You can go.
Have a nice day.
You...
You're cleaning this place
starting tomorrow.
What?
Come and clean this place.
Yes...
Park Seonsaengnim.
I thought I made it clear that I
wouldn't do any song for commercials?!
And I'm sure you know that
it would breach our contract?!
Did we sign already?
Because of next month's rent,
they were about to kick us out, so...
It's for the advertising campaign of
Manbo Construction's new apartments.
Would you be able to compensate us
for the damages incurred?
Is it going well?
What?
Seemed like my father was
searching for Lee Gangmo.
It's not working.
Why are you asking?
What's the matter?
Jeongyeon...
might be with Lee Gangmo as we speak.
What are you saying?
Why would your fiancee
be with Lee Gangmo?
Those two...
You're not telling me they...
Anyhow, Hyung.
If Jeongyeon is found with Gangmo,
you must never let my father know that.
You know what I mean, right?
Yeah. Sure.
I've never felt this way before.
It feels as if...
Gangmo completely beat me.
Push harder, will you?
- Like this?
- Yeah.
The weather's so nice, do we have
to waste all day doing the laundry?
Then, are you going to wear that
all the way to Hong Kong?
It's still our honeymoon, after all.
Honeymoon?!
I just decided to consider it as that.
As our honeymoon trip.
- Ohh... Sorry.
- You did it on purpose...
You really...
So what? I kissed my wife.
All right, don't... Stop!
Enough with that, will you?
Hyung!
You could have come in,
what are you doing here?
Let's go.
Jeongyeon...
can't come with you.
I could only find you
a spot on that boat.
How did you know it was Jeongyeon?
Did you...
tell her about me?
No.
Don't ever tell her about that.
You're hiding something
from me, aren't you?
When you helped Chairman Hong, he said
you had a grudge against Chairman Hwang.
- Nothing of the sort.
- No.
You're acting strange.
Not to mention you're trying to betray
Jo Pilyeon despite working under him.
What is all this, Hyung?
What are you hiding?
What is all this grudge about?
Don't hide it and just tell me!
Gangmo...
Hwang Taeseop and Jo Pilyeon...
Those two men...
killed our father.
What?
They conspired to get their hands
on those smuggled gold bars,
and killed our father.
You're lying, right?
Gangmo...
If you're lying,
I'll never see you again!
I saw it with my own eyes!
Our poor father shedding bitter tears,
as those two bastards killed him!
The reason I couldn't die and
stuck to Jo Pilyeon all this time...
is exactly that.
Bringing their downfall
with my own hands.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you to know this...
Forget that woman.
Forget her,
give it all up,
and just go.
I'll find the right opportunity
and send you to the States.
You'll get your American citizenship,
and then you can succeed
the way you wanted.
That'll do it.
Hyung...
How can you be so late?
I thought I'd die in here,
waiting all day.
Still no calls?
I think we just wasted our time.
Listen, let's just call it
quits and go for a drink.
Yes?
Hello?
It's me, Shideok.
Ga...Gangmo?!
Are you all right?
You're doing okay, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm leaving for
Hong Kong early tomorrow.
Hong Kong?!
How about Jeongyeon?
She's with you, right?
It's a mess here,
with everyone looking for her.
Is Jeongyeon coming with you?
Hey, Lee Gangmo!
Jeongyeon will soon go back home.
Take good care of her while I'm away.
Wait... Don't hang up! Gangmo!
What did he say?
Did you find out where he is?
Follow me.
You're back?
We should have
brought some more money.
They said Hong Kong
is really expensive.
We'll just tighten our belt.
Look.
This is all we have.
When we get there, we'll have
to get ourselves a place to stay,
and as for our monthly
allowance, at least...
This won't do it.
I'll have to start again from scratch.
It would be much better to buy
bare necessities here, and...
Did anything happen outside?
No.
Nothing.
Don't worry, Gangmo.
Everything will go well.
Should we go out a while?
- We need to go before they close...
- There's no need to do it today.
Uh?
They postponed the date.
Then, when are we leaving?
We have to wait another few days.
We'll have to save some money.
It's ramen for lunch from today, got it?
We'll have to buy some, then.
Hong Kong?
Find out any port from which
boats headed there will leave tomorrow.
So you're suggesting Lee Gangmo
will try to smuggle himself out?
It's absolutely reliable information.
- Detective Kim.
- Yes, Chief.
Find out all the boats leaving
for Hong Kong tomorrow, quick.
Sleeping?
How nasty... Already?
Gangmo.
Thanks.
If it weren't for you,
I probably would have never
learned what love means.
Thank you for loving
someone like me, Gangmo.
I know...
You did nothing wrong.
I shouldn't have fallen in love
with you to begin with.
I won't look for you again.
Live happily, Jeongyeon.
Gangmo...
Gangmo.
Seonbaenim, look.
Do you know where the... lighthouse is?
Follow me.
Let's go.
Seems like the police
got a hold of this?
Turn around!
- What?
- Take a bypath and let's go get Gangmo!
This is a forged passport.
I only got it for you because
he insisted, so don't ever lose it.
Hyungnim! The pigs are coming.
Run!
Hurry up!
Come in, Gangmo!
Hurry up and come in! Gangmo!
Seonbaenim! Seonbaenim!
Gangmo!
Go back, Hyung!
It's still not too late, come!
If we leave here together,
they'll catch you too!
So what, should I just save myself?
- Hyung!!
- Do what I say!
Arrest me.
What?!
Do it!
No way.
I can't.
Wake up, Hyung!
If they catch us here, it's over!
Gangmo!
I beg you, Hyung...
We've located Lee Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Do it, Hyung.
Hyung...
I beg you.
Don't shoot! Don't!
Don't shoot.
We're from the Inspection Department.
What happened here?
We had long been
investigating Lee Gangmo.
I see we were one step too late.
Let's go.
Director Jo is waiting.
Gangmo!
Gangmo... Wait...
Wait... Gangmo! Gangmo...
Move... Out of the way...
Gangmo...
Let go. Let go!
Gangmo... Gangmo!
No...
Gangmo...
Let go!
Gangmo!
Move! Gangmo...
Gangmo.
Gangmo! Gangmo...
Gangmo...
Ajeosshi. Wait a moment.
Gangmo, look at me!
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Follow after Gangmo.
I'm taking you home.
Follow him!
Let's go after Gangmo right now!
Hwang Jeongyeon!
Hurry up.
Let's go to Gangmo.
I must go and prove he's innocent.
Let's hurry up...
What now...
Come out.
Let go... What are you doing?
- I must go to...
- Wake up, Hwang Jeongyeon!
Because of one man, you want to
betray your father and brother?
Did you already know Gangmo
wasn't responsible for this?
If people learn that the chairman
was involved in this murder,
Manbo Construction
will be ruined, you get it?
So you knew all along, and you've
been deceiving me all this time?
Follow me.
Let go.
Let go!
Let go... Let me go!
I must go to...
I'm your fiance.
I'm the man you will soon marry.
Do you even realize
what you're doing to me?
Shouldn't you first apologize to me?
Is this how you treat
the man who loves you?
Just let go of me, Minwoo.
Let me go to Gangmo.
I'm sorry, Minwoo.
I'm sorry.
I'm begging you.
Let go of me.
Uh? Minwoo.
Get up.
I don't want to see you
kneel before me.
Get up.
I said get up!
Wasn't leading Manbo Construction
what you were after?
Where did all those ambitions go?
All that spite and fervor,
where did it go?
You will never understand me.
I never imagined I could love Gangmo
so much to put everything at stake.
Shut your mouth.
You must listen.
Only if you do you'll
be able to give up on me.
Shut up, don't say another word!
We...
got married.
Gangmo and I.
We got married.
What's wrong with you, Minwoo?
I'll never give you up.
Take just another step.
And I'll die right under your eyes.
Think I wouldn't have the guts?
Am I...
Am I really...
nothing to you?
Do I mean so little to you...
that you'd rather die?
It's not because I dislike you.
It's because I love Gangmo.
Put it down.
I'll do nothing to you.
What's with that arrogant stare?
Find out who instigated him at all cost.
Yes, Sir.
If you keep refusing any confession,
then I'll gladly introduce you
to our Namsan questioning room.
- Take him away.
- Yes.
Well done.
If it weren't for you,
we would have lost him for good.
Aigoo... Come on in, Director Min.
No, wait... Should I
make that "Candidate Min?"
Have a seat.
I've just heard the news,
about your resignation from the KCIA.
I feel both relieved
and sad at the same time.
I just felt that it would help my
preparations for the by-elections.
It was a smart move.
Is Director Jo aware of
your resignation?
He probably doesn't know yet.
By now he'll be focused on
that Chairman Hong case,
since they caught the culprit.
So how did it really go with that case?
Seems like Director Jo was convinced
the Intelligence Department was involved?
I would never do something so rash.
Anyhow, Jo Pilyeon will soon
hand in his resignation, too.
Bear in mind that this will mean
the beginning of your battle.
Don't you worry, Congressman.
I'm confident I can beat
Jo Pilyeon no matter what.
Here... Here...
Let's have a drink.
Hwang Taeseop and Jo Pilyeon
killed our father.
They conspired to get their hands on those
smuggled gold bars, and killed our father.
I saw it with my own eyes!
Our poor father shedding bitter tears,
as those two bastards killed him!
You will assign a
lawyer to Lee Gangmo?!
Yes.
There's no doubt that Min Honggi
is behind Lee Gangmo's actions.
We must get him to confess
before the elections.
Lee Gangmo has nothing to do
with Director Min Honggi.
And how can you be so sure of that?
By any chance, that account...
I burned it to shreds.
Look, Chairman Hwang.
There is no more account
belonging to Hong Gipyo now.
Don't you realize how
important that account was?
With that in our hands,
winning the elections...
I'll generously fund
your election campaign.
Isn't campaign funding
what you were after, anyway?
Leave Gangmo alone.
He's like a son to me.
Fine.
You yourself want to take the harder path
when an easier way was available,
so be my guest.
There's nothing to worry about.
They'll think I'm questioning you.
And Miju?
She still doesn't know about you.
She's in a frenzy these days,
wanting to become a singer.
You must take good care of her.
You worry me the most.
I'll try to get you out
as soon as possible.
Don't worry about me, Hyung.
On the contrary,
this solved a lot of headaches.
Because now my goals
are clear and definite.
Leave revenge to me.
There's no need
for you to get involved.
You still don't realize.
How our mother died,
what kind of struggles
Miju and I had to go through,
what forced me to
send away our youngest...
You can't realize that.
Gangmo.
Who destroyed our family?
Who turned me into a murderer, Hyung?
What do you want me to do,
just sit and stare like a retard?
I just want you to live a
normal life like everyone else.
I can't live like that.
I'll get revenge my own way.
And what's your way?
Destroying Manbo Construction.
When I'm done with them,
they'll face a miserable,
pitiful downfall.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com