Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Previously on GIANT ~
Gold bars, you said?
You saw me kill him,
so I can't allow you to survive.
Whatever I'll end up doing,
I will always be loyal to you.
At the end of this month, let's meet
on top of Seoul's tallest building.
Where is my mother?
I mean my birth mother.
So you're looking for your mother?
I'll always be looking at you,
so take good care of your siblings,
and whatever happens,
you must never cry.
He will be in possession of a top secret
document regarding the Vietnam war.
Bring us that document.
Did he see your face?
If he regains his consciousness,
it's all over for us.
Got it?
Big Oppa, hurry up and come.
I miss you, Big Oppa!
~ Episode 4 ~
Gangmo...
Miju...
It's really cold.
How about we go somewhere
and warm ourselves up a little?
No way, what if Big Oppa comes?
We haven't eaten a thing all day long.
Let's at least have something to eat.
When Big Oppa comes, we'll eat together.
You silly! Hyung...
Hyung might not come at all.
After falling off that moving train,
he might have even died.
It's getting dark,
why isn't Big Oppa coming?
Miju, you really are silly.
You're telling me you really
don't know why he's so late?
Why is he late?
Think of how much he'll be missing you.
But would he come empty-handed?
If he needs to buy your favorite
dolls, candies and all those gifts,
it's only natural he'd be late.
Really?
Of course.
What gift will you have for him?
Now that I think about it,
I don't have anything to give him?!
I'm sure he'll be disappointed...
Then, what can I do?
I don't have any money.
Hyung likes your songs.
Then, should I sing him
a song when he comes?
Yeah. A really exciting one at that.
There... Imagine Hyung is coming,
his hands filled with gifts.
What are you waiting for?
Aren't you giving Hyung his present?
Big Oppa, wait there a moment!
"Just a look and my heart throbs."
"Just a thought and my heart throbs."
"Ignore the blooming first love
of an innocent nineteen-year-old."
"So that nobody in the world will know,"
"And he will remain hidden
at the bottom of my heart."
"Hidden in my heart."
"As red as a bed of roses,"
"The beating heart of an
innocent nineteen-year-old."
Miju, I have a nice idea.
What?
Let's hide somewhere,
so we can surprise Hyung when he comes.
He will never expect that.
That's got to be fun.
Before Hyung comes, let's go hide.
Hurry up, Oppa.
All right.
Looks tasty.
Go ahead and eat.
We're playing hide-and-seek now.
Until Hyung screams "I can't find you, I lost!"
we must hide here.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
I'll go out and wait for Hyung,
so take good care of the baby.
Oppa.
Don't even think of
telling him I'm hiding here.
All right.
Are you sure he saw Jaechun's face?
Yes.
Go find out.
What?
Find out when he'll
regain his consciousness!
Yes!
No... Wait!
It's all useless.
There's no solution!
None!
I'm sure this room is bugged.
- Otherwise...
- When the kid wakes up,
he'll identify the criminal.
The kid's gone!
What?
I checked the ward,
but he wasn't there.
Hyung...
You're not really dead, right?
Hey.
How much longer are
you going to stay here?
Ohh?! It's Big Oppa!
Oppa!
Ajumma, I'll be back right away.
Hey...
Where are you going?
Oppa!
Big Oppa!
- Eonni, wait a moment!
- Hurry up.
All right!
Big Oppa...
Oppa.
Oppa!
Oppa...
Little Oppa...
Where is my sister?
Why ask me?
She left the baby to me and ran out.
Hey! Bring the baby along!
Miju!
Lee Miju!
Miju.
Miju!
Lee Miju!
Where are you?
Miju!
You silly...
Hide-and-seek is over!
Come out now!
I can't find you, I lost!
Miju, come out...
I can't find you, I lost...
Miju!
Come out...
Miju, come out...
I can't find you, I lost...
Miju!
Miju...
Mom!
Mother!
Gangmo.
Miju.
Mom!
It's okay.
I hear your witness has disappeared.
What do you plan to do now?
Listen carefully, General Hampton.
You must never forget that you
didn't only damage my reputation,
but also that of this country.
Follow me.
Yeah...
Her name is Lee Miju.
He said he lost sight of her
around here, so search around.
Right.
I have no idea, either.
Yeah...
All right.
Did you meet today for
the first time, or something?
Let's see some smiles, shall we?
Hyung. Give me that hat.
Here... I'm shooting.
1... 2... 3!
Where on earth have you gone?
Where?
Honey! Honey, come out here!
Aigoo, what are you screaming for?
What are you doing here?
You couldn't meet your brother?
Did my sister Miju come here?
She hasn't.
Why, have you lost your sister?
Forget your sister,
and go to the health center.
- Why?
- This baby is burning!
Uh? What?
Aigoo... This is trouble.
Untie this load.
Untie it.
Come on.
She's too young to
search for her around here,
so it would be better to
look around where you lost her.
The baby is suffering
from severe malnutrition.
Unless you do something,
the situation might become even more serious.
Leave the baby to our care.
I really think that's the only way.
I'll never accept foreign adoption.
I'll raise that baby myself.
The baby could die if you keep this up.
No matter how young you are,
you must be aware of the situation.
I'll come back in the evening.
Make up your mind by then.
I'm sure they moved that
secret document elsewhere.
Unless they discovered our bug,
we will find out,
no matter where they put it.
But it won't be easy to
make them stop suspecting us.
You can never repeat
the same mistake twice.
I will bear it in mind.
This is serious.
What, again?
That eye-witness who vanished
has just returned to the base.
What?
Yes, Jo Pilyeon speaking.
All right.
I will head there soon.
I'll take all the blame for this.
I am the only one responsible for this.
Even if I have to stake my life for it,
I will make sure you
face no repercussions.
Jaechun.
Remain here until the end,
and complete your task.
~ We are being bugged ~
Can you recognize the
suspect, if you see him?
Is he the one?
Yes.
With God as your witness,
you must speak nothing but the truth.
Is that clear?
If my aide does indeed
turn out to be the culprit,
I won't be able to forgive him myself.
If he brought dishonor both to me
and to this country's armed forces,
allow me to punish him firsthand.
Speak.
Is this the man you
witnessed on the scene?
Go ahead and say it.
Is my aide the man you saw here?
No.
Look carefully.
The man I saw...
is not him.
Have you heard?
I trust you'll stop
with the insinuations now.
What is going on?
You said he saw you.
I can't explain it myself.
There's a possibility he
might have not recognized you.
Or he probably hasn't seen you at all.
He has no reason to lie.
Are you positive?
Isn't he the guy?
~ We are being bugged ~
We... We couldn't find anything here.
You know how to make those boots shine?
I don't want to see
a blemish on them, got it?
What is it?
I brought the General's boots.
Leave them over there.
I'm sure that was the man I saw.
But if I had revealed it now,
that aide would have taken all the blame.
You're right.
We won't be able to
arrest Jo right about now.
- He might be working with the CIA.
- Nah.
Someone in the ROK
government is behind this.
Why would the ROK government
try to get classified intel...
about the Vietnam war?
They're about to have a presidential
election pretty soon, it's plausible.
Remember, the relationship between
the ROK and American government...
isn't exactly peachy keen
right about now.
Yeah... Could be true.
He's right.
We need to get Jo,
in order to end this.
Got any ideas?
We will use the trap that
they've set up against them.
You mean using a bug against them?
Will you help us out?
We need a spy.
Jo Pilyeon is going to approach you.
We need to make him trust you.
Got it?
Your name is Junmo.
Lee Junmo.
Your brother gave it to you.
I'm really sorry.
When you grow up,
your brother will
make a lot of money,
and will find you once again.
I'll find Hyung and Miju as well,
and the four of us...
will all live together.
I will never,
ever let poverty force me
to abandon my family again.
I promise.
If we end up meeting again,
let's spend the rest
of our days together.
I'm sorry, baby...
I'm sorry.
Parents
~ Lee Daesoo ~
~ Jung Yeongseon ~
Adoptee
~ Lee Junmo ~
Junmo!
Don't... Junmo...
Junmo...
Junmo.
One day I will find you again.
So...
You must be in good health.
Baby...
Junmo!
Seonsaengnim, you've come.
You twat!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Is that all you could fill,
ever since the construction started?
We lack sand.
Hey... Hey!
It's all sand and gravel by the Han River,
but "we lack sand"?!
Our competitors have been digging
it all up down to the last grain,
so there's nothing left for us.
Make some sense, will you?
If there's none left, buy it!
What did you do with
all the money I gave you?
The entire country is suffering
from a lack of raw materials.
Particularly so when it
comes to construction sand.
Then, head to Mount Bukhan
and dig whatever you need!
If we don't fill this lot,
it's over for us!
Director Hwang.
Go.
Major Jo Pilyeon is here.
What?
And what is that fella doing here, again?
What brings you here?
I was curious about what happened
to that land I told you to buy.
I couldn't buy it.
You couldn't?!
I'm sure it wasn't for lack of money?!
I have no money.
I shared those gold bars with you.
Not to mention giving you the kind of
precious estate leads only the elite know.
But you didn't have
enough money to buy it?
I'm just in the construction business,
not a real estate speculator.
Say what?
If we manage to reclaim
that public water surface,
the Seoul City council
will authorize construction.
It's the chance of a lifetime
Manbo Construction had been waiting...
Listen to me, Director Hwang!
Dig the land or stop the river,
I couldn't care less.
All you need is to make the
most money in the shortest time.
"Real estate speculator"?!
Are you tired of making money already,
or did you bury your guts
under that landfill?
If I complete this land reclamation,
I can make enough money.
Halt the construction immediately,
and buy more land with that money.
I will first complete the construction,
and only then buy more land.
Let me make myself clear.
If you lose my favor,
you'll only end up in misery.
I'm facing enough misery as it is.
So, please, stop
interfering in my business.
You really...
Having to repeat myself...
is something I really hate.
Before my next visit,
I want you to buy all that land.
Insolent little bastard...
How did it go?
We can't keep this document here anymore.
I'm going back stateside this weekend.
I can take it with me.
You know the importance of
this document, take care of it.
Yes, Sir.
Now everything depends on you.
I will get my hands on that document.
It's a piece of cake.
If this isn't luck knocking at
our door, what else could be?
But if this intel is fake?
What?
I'm sure they know they're being bugged.
If it's Hampton we're dealing with,
he could easily fabricate
false intel to lure us into a trap.
But if it's not, we'll forever lose
our chance to get that document.
We can't sit and stare while it happens.
Verifying this intel's authenticity
is our most urgent priority,
but I can't figure out
what they're scheming.
- Have a nice day!
- Come again.
Hyungnim, take these.
Out of the way.
You're back?
No calls for me?
Your wife called,
saying she'll come by this evening.
How about the sand?
We did give it a try,
but it didn't go as we expected.
I'd advise to use whatever we secured
and start the construction right away.
And what are you
going to fill with that?
I'll be damned, really...
Miss Kim.
Hand me the brush.
Every time I go to the construction site,
my shoes become a mess.
And you are?
Was just wondering if
anyone needed his shoes shined.
Nobody, go.
Kiddo.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm just brushing them
a little to remove the dirt.
What, for free?
Yes. Take a look.
I only brushed them,
and they're clean already.
Little runt...
If you ever need your shoes shined,
you must let me do it.
Have a nice day.
Come here.
- Here... Shine mine.
- Uh?
Yes.
Thank you.
Why don't you
have yours shined as well?
Forget it.
Why should I bother?
They'll get dirty again in no time.
You said you're going out for
dinner with your family later.
Are you going there in that state?
Ohh... Do mine, too.
Yes.
Hey.
Take these as well.
Yes, Director.
Ahh... So embarrassing...
That damned brat...
I'll make them shine in a moment.
All right.
The hell is this...
Have a nice day.
Who gave you permission
to shine shoes here?
Why? Is it forbidden
He's got more guts than brains.
*Japanese for turf/territory; gained
popularity as post-colonial Korean slang
This is my nawabari*.
Na...Nawabari?!
What's that?
You fool.
We're paying protection
money to work here.
How dare you try to
steal food from our table?
I need to make money.
So stop barging in.
Did you stuff your ears
with shoe polish?
Hey!
Stop... It's my polish box!
Don't!
Let go...
Give it back!
Kick him!
Give it back to me!
My box!
No...
My polish box!
You idiot... Should have listened
while you still could.
Stay put, will you?
Prance around my turf again,
and I'll throw you into the fire
instead of your polish box.
Got it?
Let's go.
Do you know how hard
convincing her to come was?
It's not like I was forcing
her to the slaughterhouse...
All I asked her was to go out for dinner
with us, and she makes such a scene?
Why force someone to
do something against their will?
You said to bring her along.
I'll just go back.
I can, right?
First have dinner with us.
You can go out without me
and have a nice dinner together.
Hey...
What did you do with these shoes?
They're all ruined.
I apologize.
You fool.
Is that all you can say?
They're so expensive...
You...
Are you a shoeshiner for real?
Today was my first day.
When someone prances about
as if he had any clue,
that's a fraud, you fool!
I'm sorry.
Pay us back for the shoes.
I... have no money.
You don't?
Then, can't be helped.
Miss Kim. Call the police
and tell them to take him in.
I'll shine your shoes every day
until I pay back the damages.
So...
Close an eye just this once.
Ahh... Really, is anything
ever going right here?
Get out of my face!
Leave!
What do I have to see...
I'll go as well.
Jeongyeon... Jeongyeon!
Just let her go.
We'll just go by ourselves.
And your mother?
She passed away.
You don't need to
show compassion to me.
And how could I not
feel compassion for you?
You've lost your mother
and are even shining shoes.
You're still as annoying as always.
Same goes for you.
Arrogant as always.
I'm in no mood to be arguing with you.
Take it.
It's the money I couldn't give you,
when I lost my wallet.
Why, would it hurt
your pride to accept it?
Forget it, then.
Give me back my box!
- My box!
- Out of the way, you pricks!
My box!
How dare you?
Who the hell are you?
- Give me back my box!
- You bastard.
Wanna die?
Do you have a death wish?
Ahh... You annoying twit...
You... Show up around me again,
and I'll cripple you for good.
Stop it.
Move!
I can just buy another box for you.
And who the hell are you?
They're the ones who
ruined my polish box.
Still, why would you do this?
You'll only end up getting hurt.
Both my parents died,
and I lost my brothers and sister.
I have nothing left to lose,
and nothing can hurt me anymore.
Hurry up and clean that, will you?
We don't have all day.
Th...There!
You can come any time, you bastard.
I, Park Sotae!
I've sent dozens of blockheads
like you to hell already.
Please, stop.
You idiot!
Keep this up and they'll kill you!
Don't stare at me, I don't like it.
Why, think I'm enjoying this?
You blockhead...
That's what he told you earlier on.
That you're a blockhead.
He really has a point.
You're foolish and stupid,
not to mention stubborn as hell.
Where are you going?
I'm not done.
You're going after them again?
Thank you for the meal.
Hey, you blockhead!
What the hell are you doing?
Go ahead and come get some!
I'll set the whole damned place on fire!
You... Drop that!
Give me my box back.
You really have a death wish, uh?
Sure, go ahead.
Let's all kill each other!
Don't, you fool...
Why?
You burn someone else's box to shreds,
and you're scared I'll burn your tent?
I'm sorry.
I beg you, don't do it.
"I'm sorry"?!
Yeah... I shouldn't have done it,
so please don't kick that.
If you set the tent on fire,
we'll all become beggars!
Give me my box back.
All right, I'll buy you a new one.
So, please... Stop.
Also, from now on
I'll shine shoes here, too.
What?
Ahh... Damned blockhead...
Are you against it?
Then, we can just all become beggars...
Fine, work here.
It's all right, shine them...
Shine them all you want.
And I'm not paying a penny,
just so you know.
Ahh... He's scary...
What did I do to deserve this?
All right.
We'll do everything you asked,
so get out of there!
You mean it?
I'm a man, too!
Everyone is looking,
would I go back on my word?
I'm Park Sotae.
You?
Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo.
Forget all the bullshit,
and work under me.
I don't want to work under you.
Let's be partners.
Partners?!
Right. We make money
together, and share it.
Fine.
We have a deal.
Never seen a blockhead like you before.
How much longer will you make us wait?
Worst comes to worst, within a month...
Listen, Jo Pilyeon.
The elections are right behind the corner.
The opposition candidate is
yapping his mouth left and right...
criticizing the government, and the
public is all too happy to eat it up.
I'm well aware.
Then, imagine if they learned that we
bought land in Gangnam under a namesake.
Not only the president,
but everyone here would be screwed!
Calm down.
One month is too late.
You must get your hands on that
document within the next ten days.
Only then will we be able
to stop the Americans...
from disclosing the namesake
account list to the public.
I will spare no effort.
Whatever it takes, you must succeed.
You have ten days!
Go even a single day over that deadline,
and you'd better be prepared
for the consequences.
It's tomorrow.
Tomorrow, Michael will take
the document and leave the base.
We have no other choice, do we?
Before that document
leaves for the States,
we must get our hands on it at all cost.
I still can't figure it out.
Whether that intel is legit,
or just a bait to lure us into a trap.
~ Jo Pilyeon ~
Captain Michael just left the base.
I will trail him.
It's our last chance.
Issue your order now!
Go.
Go, and get that document.
Assistant!
Yes!
Go get Jaechun, quick!
Yes, Sir.
It's false intel, don't fall for it.
Who's the man?
That black boxer is really something.
Well, I've never seen a Korean
soldier able to bring him down.
Why don't we choose two representatives
and have a real match sometime?
You really think a Korean
can take an American down?
In boxing?!
I see you're confident.
Come on, yellow monkeys!
You!
What?
You're scared?
You wanna fight?
Who's the man?
Who is this?
Are you out of your mind?
Come down, you fool!
I better not get locked up for
knocking out a yellow monkey today.
Get up!
I said get up!
Get up! Get up!
Your fighting spirit is really impressive.
It was an entertaining fight.
Give me my jackknife back.
Your aide must have my knife.
There's a peculiar fella inside this base.
Where he was born, how he grew up,
how old he is, his name...
Why he is helping me,
or whether he's just trying to kill me.
There's this phantom-like
presence I can't really figure out.
Who are you?
How did you get here?
Why did you lie,
saying he wasn't the culprit?
And why did you send me that note?
Who the hell are you?
I'm a Korean.
What?
Just like you,
I'm a Korean man.
There is no other reason.
And that's because I'm no American.
Because we are all fellow Koreans.
Stop.
I've heard he's got amnesia.
That is why we couldn't
verify his identity.
If dealt with properly,
he's a potential gem.
What?
If we use him well,
he will become a
great commodity for us.
Weather isn't helping today, again.
But, where the hell is Gangmo?
Haven't seen him all day.
I'll be damned...
You really are doing this for free?
Of course.
To pay you back for the shoes I ruined,
it'll take more than a year.
- You little...
- Be quiet.
"As it's expected the rain
will continue until tonight,"
"low-lying areas around the Han River
are expected to suffer serious damage."
"We alert all people in the area to
be prepared and react accordingly."
"And that closes today's weather report."
It's me.
Why aren't you answering my calls?
How's the situation there?
What?
Hey... Hey!
If the river floods,
what about all that sand?
Does that make any sense?
Mobilize all workforce, and block it
yourselves if that's what it takes!
All the employees already went home,
and there's no one left.
Say what?
Are you out of your mind?
How can you send people home,
during a state of emergency?
I'll head there right away,
so gather everyone you can.
You foolish twat...
Everyone, follow me.
Me too, Director?
Why, aren't you getting paid?
Everyone!
I'm coming, too.
Come on, let's hurry!
We have no time.
Let's move, hurry up!
There is no time!
Director, the dike
is about to collapse!
So what? Can't you see all
this sand wasted in vain?
If the dike collapses, then the
water will flood the entire place!
You crazy fool!
Isn't that why I asked you
to make an embankment?
This will never be enough!
You might even risk your...
You little... You're doing this
because it's not your money, right?
This might only look like sand to you,
but this is my flesh and blood!
If all this is wasted,
I'll be dead anyway!
Calm down, Director.
Doing this will not solve a thing!
Forget it, you fools!
I'll do it myself,
so get out of my face!
Director!
It's too dangerous!
If this collapses, it's all over!
Think I'm going to give up
after all I went through?
I even had to kill to get to this point!
I'm not going to let a
natural disaster ruin me! I won't!
Come get some!
I'm Hwang Taeseop!
I'm afraid of nothing!
Ajeosshi!
It's dangerous!
Director!
Ajeosshi!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Ajeosshi!
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Ajeosshi!
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
You haven't lost your memory, right?
What's your name?
The final construction company
which will renounce its contract...
is Manbo Construction.
The daughter of
Manbo Construction's Director?
How do you think she
would treat people like us?
Killing someone like you
and throwing him in the ditch...
is a piece of cake for us.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com
About the landfill near the river.
I know how to fill it.
Briquette ash.