Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Student Demonstration in
Support of Direct Presidential Elections -
Episode 49
Hey... Aren't you guys hungry?
Should we order some chicken?
I'm fine.
I'll give you the
money, so go get some.
Where did I put my wallet...
What's going on?
Seonbaenim!
Open the door!
Open the door, Chief Lee!
Open it!
Chief!
Hands up.
Call the director right away.
Do it!
What?
Seongmo is holding them hostage?
He's in a standoff with
the agents as we speak.
What is he asking?
To talk with the ANSP director.
So? Did they report this to Director Kim?
He is currently at the Blue House.
If people learn of this,
it'll only create more headaches.
Follow me!
All right.
Where is he being confined?
A villa in Yeonhee-Dong.
Give me the address and phone number.
It's not going to help anyway.
All the phones there are already bugged.
He doesn't know
what's happening outside.
I'm just worried Jo Pilyeon
will get his hands on that account.
Still, we have no way of alerting him!
We have no time, do it!
Yes.
What's wrong with you?
I need to see the director.
I told you I'd solve everything!
Didn't I tell you to wait just a few days?
How much longer do you want
me to just endure all this like a retard?
Hey... Lee Seongmo!
You didn't even let me take all the blame.
If I have to keep enduring
being treated like a criminal,
I'd rather prove my innocence instead.
I know what you're feeling, Seongmo.
I understand perfectly.
If you do, then let me do as I wish!
I'm coming your way right now.
We're almost there.
Until I arrive,
don't do anything foolish.
Understand, Seongmo?
Why aren't you answering me?
Do you understand, Seongmo?
I'll be waiting.
Fine...
Ending it all right here might beat
waiting for that account to be revealed.
We're going down together, Jo Pilyeon.
There's no way in.
The place is swarming with ANSP agents.
What do we do now?
Because of the bugs, calling would
likely get him into even more trouble.
Gangmo...
Jo Pilyeon is here!
Can he really stop your brother?
He'll kill him.
Uh?!
Seongmo... could kill Jo Pilyeon!
Then... what?
That would kill him as well.
Here you are.
Lee Seongmo is refusing to listen.
Tell him I'm going in.
Congressman.
Seongmo is armed.
Not to mention quite agitated.
If you really want to try
and convince him, do it from here.
Nah... I'll go in and talk to him firsthand.
Seongmo.
It's me.
Can I come in?
First, it'd be wise to let
those two agents go.
You're the one who talked about
meeting on top of 31 Building, right?
We found your siblings.
All you have to do is
wait until the end of the month.
Park Seungcheol.
Are you listening to me?
You called the wrong number.
Did he get it?
He did.
I'm sure he understood.
Seongmo!
- Close the door.
- Ohh... Right.
Seongmo.
Give me that g...
Hey... Lee Seongmo!
No matter how dirty or dangerous it was,
I never refused to do anything before,
if it was for your sake.
So why...
are you suspecting me?
S... Seongmo...
I think you're misunderstanding something.
Shut up!
You're not going to fool me any longer.
You saw that right.
I'm suspecting you indeed.
Congressman!
But suspecting someone
with the intent of killing him...
and doing it to save him
are two very different things.
Do you know what I mean?
If only to prove your innocence
to everyone, I must suspect you.
Only then will people
stop trying to accuse you.
Look, Seongmo.
The world I always wanted
is right around the corner.
And if only to make sure
we all get there together,
I must suspect you until
we find the real culprit.
But if you are the culprit, then this
is your best chance to pull that trigger.
If that's not the
case, give me that gun.
Do it.
Congressman!
Seongmo.
What people call suspicion...
has no gray areas.
You either let go of it once and for all,
or keep suspecting to the very end.
They way I see it,
you're still suspicious of me.
Giving up the gun wasn't what
a pro would do, don't you think?
So are you going to use it to shoot me?
Because you and I are different.
You saw wrong.
From the very start, I had
no intention of shooting you.
If I was still suspecting you, I
would have neither removed the bullets,
not let you take that gun.
That's right, Seongmo!
This is exactly what I wanted.
To either clear any suspicion,
or take it to the very end.
Of all people...
Of all people, why is it Lee Gangmo?
Of all damn people...
Did you find out anything
more about Lee Miju?
Chairman...
I...
Go ahead and tell me.
What is it?
Why were Miju and Lee Gangmo...
The apartment Lee Miju lives in...
was bought by President Lee Gangmo.
But there is no evidence proving
they're seeing each other.
Even the private investigator
followed them for a few days,
but he says that this was their only meeting.
And there is something
else that is a little strange,
the fact that the deputy mayor
helped Miss Lee get a spot on TV.
Deputy Han Myeongseok?
Yes, Chairman.
Find out where I can meet her tonight.
All right.
Okay, I understand.
I'll call you.
Gangmo just left for the Royal Club.
Did he say Seongmo was fine?
You can rest assured. He said
he was able to talk to him.
For the time being,
nothing big should happen.
That's a relief.
I'm so glad to hear that.
If this event goes well,
Gangmo will rescue him.
You can believe that, Miju.
Yes, Eonni.
A car has been following us for a while.
I know.
Just drive as if nothing happened.
Who are those people?
I think they're
heading for the Royal Club.
I did follow Hwang Jeongyeon around
all day, but no traces of her father.
Keep checking on her.
They're father and daughter,
so they'll soon call each other.
Before Lee Seongmo confesses,
we must get our hands on that account.
Or else they'll start
breathing down our neck this time.
Come on in, Jeongyeon.
Let me borrow a room.
I need to discuss details
of the event with Soojeong.
Use this one, it's quiet.
Come on in.
Those people have
been following us all day.
Find out who they are.
Let's go in.
Welcome.
I think I've never seen you around...
Right after the opening
act, the party will start.
Soojeong, you will
open the second part of the event.
But, Eonni.
Are you and Gangmo just friends?
Uh?!
Yeah...
I was hoping otherwise...
He's no fun, is he?
Nah... He's fun to hang out with,
not to mention really manly.
So he's not just a
childhood friend to you?
That's not what I meant...
I really wish Gangmo could
marry someone like you.
Yes?
Come on in, Deputy.
How are you?
Ahh... Miss Cha, you were here as well.
I'll let you talk.
No. I need to go see Director Yoo.
Discuss the rest with the deputy.
Yes, Eonni.
- I...
- I'll let you two talk it out.
Have a seat.
Yes.
Let's... have a seat.
Here's the event's program.
But...
It's upside down.
Ahh... Yes... Of course.
Come on in, Chairman Jo.
Which room is Cha Soojeong in?
If you want, you can go.
I won't mind.
I should have thanked you the other time.
I really appreciated it.
What?
The director told me of all
the help you've been giving me.
Ahh...
That...
That was just...
I did it as a favor to her.
Are you all right?
Yes... I'm fine...
Everything is fine.
It's all right. Let me do it.
Chairman Jo.
What brings you here?
I was told you
were here, so I came.
Have a seat, then.
I was about to order some drinks.
Sit.
She's a new singer.
I'm sorry, excuse me a moment.
Remain seated, Miss Cha.
So you two knew each other?
I'm a big fan of hers.
And I've been for quite a long time.
Is that so?
I'll let you two talk.
Are you a fan of hers as well, Deputy?
Yes.
Well... I guess you could say that.
As you said, Min Honggi
sent men to spy on us.
There is no doubt.
The director checked their identity.
Where are you now?
I'm almost there.
I'll arrive in a minute.
Let go.
Minwoo...
What are you doing?
Before I make a scene,
keep your mouth shut.
I don't know what I
might be capable of right now.
So let's get to the point.
I need to leave.
Who else are you going to meet?
Other than Lee Gangmo and Han Myeongseok,
is there anyone else?
What are you talking about?
First it was an apartment from Lee Gangmo,
then broadcast gigs from Han Myeongseok...
What else do you need?
I told you that I would
give you everything you want!
Why ask all those men instead...
Was this your way of
forcing me to dislike you?
Think that by acting this way all
my feelings for you would suddenly vanish?
You're sorely mistaken, Lee Miju.
If that's all you can do, just give up!
Whatever you try,
it'll never make me dislike you.
It's not going to work!
Before I start screaming,
let go of my hand.
Go ahead and scream!
I'm not going to let you act
like this anymore, I'll do as I please!
Stop this, Minwoo.
I told you that it's not what you think!
I know... You're not that kind of woman.
And that drives me even crazier!
Must you really do this to me...
Leave, Lee Gangmo...
Leave us alone, Miju.
Stay here, Lee Miju!
Let me handle it.
Hey, Lee Miju...
You son of a bitch...
Stop it...
Both of you, just stop!
Please...
Please, let me handle this.
I'm asking you.
What's going on between you two?
What is this all about?
Lee Miju...
is my sister.
What?
Sister?!
The sister I lost in my childhood.
And you know why Miju had to go
through all those hardships at that orphanage?
Oppa...
Because your father Jo Pilyeon...
- killed...
- Don't tell him, Oppa!
If anyone tells him, I will.
That's what I wish for.
Please, Oppa.
I beg you...
I'll be waiting outside.
Don't ever show up before Miju again.
Or else...
I might even kill you.
No!
I...
will do that with my own hands.
Is Lee Gangmo...
really the brother you
lost when you were little?
What else was he trying to tell me?
What on earth did my father do to you?
He killed...
our father.
And that is the reason
why I had to leave you.
Minwoo...
No.
It's not possible.
No...
No, there is no way.
No way...
There is no way!
No!
- Calm down...
- No damn way.
Minwoo... Calm down.
I never regretted loving you.
Miju...
I'm sorry, Minwoo.
It's not your fault...
But this is all I could do.
Just let go of me now.
Stop suffering because of me.
I told you to tell me if
you had any problem, didn't I?
Why did you try to deal with
all that by yourself, you silly?
Minwoo will suffer even more than me.
I know, Oppa.
I know everything.
But he sincerely loved me.
Not telling Minwoo about our father
was my last act of kindness to him.
Because his family means to
him just as much as you do to me.
Him and I could never become family,
so I didn't want to
take that away from him.
I understand.
That'll do.
Jo Minwoo will never bother you again.
What are you doing here so late?
I missed you.
And Wooju as well.
Right... I'm sending Wooju
to another kindergarten.
They knew you are his mother,
so what if they spread rumors
about Cha Soojeong's hidden child?
Go sleep next to Wooju.
He'll love waking up
tomorrow with you by his side.
- My Daddy -
Wooju...
Wooju.
Not only no calls, but no one tried
to approach Seongmo in person, either.
Still, you can't let your guard down.
Seongmo is not someone you can
keep in check with only a few men.
Don't worry.
I've already told the
agents to pay special attention.
Jjajangmyeon is here.
Hey...
What are you looking at?
I was told Cha Soojeong lives here?!
Cha Soojeong?
You know who I'm talking about.
The one who sings that.
She's not here.
Ahh... That's strange?!
The ajumma selling waffles down
the street said she lives here?
Enjoy your meal.
I've added two more on the
house, youngster. Come often.
Aigoo... Now that's a handsome fella.
Aigoo, you brat...
Worry about the waffles, will you?
Aigoo, why?
Am I wrong?
- Here you go.
- Yes, thank you.
See you again.
I'm so thankful...
Aigoo, what are you saying?
Today business was so slow...
We can't complain either!
But will that really help?
It sure will.
I don't really know what's going on,
but have these.
Looks like I found my new calling.
- Bought them?
- Yes.
Have you given one
each to the boys outside?
Yes, Chief.
But you really seem to like waffles?
Don't you know how great they taste?
Have these and get out of my way.
Soon something will make
them stop suspecting you.
Don't worry and just wait, Hyung.
This time I found it by my house's gates.
I got one myself.
It's the third one, already.
I'm so nervous I can't take this any longer.
What if this ends up reaching the Blue House?
They could even
proclaim martial law for this.
And if that happens,
congress will be dismissed,
making everything
we accomplished so far fruitless.
I never imagined Hwang
Taeseop would be so daring.
Whatever it takes, we must catch him.
By now, Min Honggi and
all the others will be sure...
that you're the man
behind all these threats.
I'm sure that's the case.
Since they're even following Jeongyeon.
Those were ANSP agents.
Then, what can we do now?
When you push people into a corner,
all they look for is a way out.
If we want to use
Min Honggi as our bait,
he must be shown a way out.
For taking time out of your busy
schedule, I am truly thankful.
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon
will now explain our motive...
for forming this 88 Seoul
Olympics Support Committee.
How are you?
My name is Hwang Jeongyeon.
As you're well aware, the Olympic
Games are not merely a sporting event,
but a gathering where varied
cultures and economies come into contact.
So this newly formed committee is
the very first civilian support group...
with the success of our Olympic Games in mind.
Our fund-raising event...
- Thank you.
- I enjoyed it.
Thank you.
That was a brilliant briefing.
I'm sure the congressmen will participate?
Politicians can't resist beautiful women.
Seeing how speechless they were
in the presence of such a beauty like you,
I can guarantee full participation.
But I didn't see any opposition member
from the legislation committee?
Opposition party members are
demonstrating on the streets,
so it's rare to see them in congress.
Thank you for today, Congressman.
I will see you at the event.
- Yes, Jeongyeon.
- See you again.
Was gathering members
from both parties your idea?
It wasn't.
Miss Jeongyeon suggested it.
I see...
Why are you asking?
No reason, really.
Next on our schedule?
We have a meeting with
the event's official sponsors right away,
and this evening a dinner with chairmen
from the Korean Federation of Industries.
This is hard labor...
What are you doing here, Jeongyeon?
Will you participate as
well, Congressman Jo?
A Night for the Olympics...
I can't say...
With all those factions trying
to overthrow the government,
I wonder if I'll have any time
to pop champagne bottles.
I knew how busy you would be,
so I didn't prepare any invitation.
I will get going.
How do you do, Congressman?
Jeongyeon.
May I have a word with you?
I sincerely hope Chairman Hwang
will stop with this foolish behavior.
So you're asking me to
convey those words to him.
If you care about him...
By any chance... I noticed people
have been put on my trail.
Are those subordinates of yours?
They are.
So you're also the one
who's blackmailing my father?
Black...mailing?!
He's been receiving
strange documents as of late.
Not to mention phone threats.
Are you responsible for that?
Then... Just like us...
What are you trying to say?
Would it be possible to
speak with him on the phone?
I'm being harassed by the same people
who are threatening Chairman Hwang.
And you expect me to believe that?
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
I admit I've been suspicious of
Chairman Hwang all this time.
But we must meet
and find a solution right now.
I never said it was Lee Seongmo.
I'm afraid it was pure conjecture on your part.
Didn't you see his face
when you exchanged that account?
I never saw his face even once.
And that is why I don't know
whether it was Lee Seongmo myself.
Still, didn't you have a copy of it?
Are you telling me you
didn't make a copy yourself, just in case?
Why wouldn't I have tried that?
We tried that countless times,
but this is all we got.
It's obvious this is
an ANSP agent's doing.
They used an
anti-copy spray on this.
It's a recent development from Japan,
and they're using it
all the time at the ANSP.
Still, there is good news,
the fact that Lee Seongmo
doesn't know anything.
I see.
Seongmo ended up
unfairly bearing the brunt.
What do you plan to do now?
That man's requests are pretty straightforward.
He will call us back with a time and place,
so gather those opposition party members,
and form a six-man committee...
in support of the constitutional amendment.
Congressman Min.
Seems that we're forced
to comply with his requests.
Since he's got the account,
I'm afraid we have no choice.
Miju, open the door!
Hey, Lee Miju!
Lee Miju, open the damn door!
I said open!
Lee Miju!
Minwoo...
Minwoo!
What's wrong with you?
Minwoo.
Let's run away.
Minwoo...
Let's just run away.
Let's go, you silly.
Let's just go abroad, the two of us.
We can just hide,
and never have to face my
parents or your brother again.
Let's just live happily together.
Make up your mind.
Is it me or your brother?
If...
If I lose you, I will have lost everything.
But your brother is different.
I'm sorry, Minwoo.
I can't do what you're asking me.
Without you, I will die!
Even that is not enough for you?
Is that not enough? Not even that?
Answer me.
Don't come here again.
Lee Miju.
Pretend we don't know each other,
and don't ever show up before me again.
So what you're saying...
is that you don't
care even if this will kill me.
I'm sorry.
I want to run away with you, too.
But...
But.
Here.... Let's drink.
He will be handling
all the funding from now on.
I'm Hwang Jeongshik.
I'll be counting on you.
That's what we should say to you.
Anyhow... Seeing you show so much
passion for our democratization efforts...
- can only give us strength.
- Yes...
Aigoo... I'm just an ordinary citizen.
Not just me, but every
Korean wishes for democracy.
If a better world comes for us all,
we will repay this debt of gratitude.
Don't say that.
I'm not doing it for that reason.
Just build a world where ordinary
people like me can live in peace.
We will give our best.
- Allow me to pour you a drink.
- Yes.
He has more confidence in
President Noh than I could ever imagine.
President Noh is practically
reporting to Congressman Jo...
how the opposition
party members are reacting.
Jo Pilyeon paved the way for us.
All we need to do is take advantage of it.
You want to spread false information?
Yes.
Only then we'll be
able to rescue my brother.
I'll take care of the private lending market.
So I guess all I have to do
is meeting Congressman Min.
I've been contacted.
What did he say?
Will he finally bring you that account?
He said he would bring it to you when
you meet in secret with the opposition.
Time and place?
This Friday at six.
The train for Busan
leaving from Seoul Station.
Train?!
By the time you reach Daejeon Station,
you will meet by the dining coach.
A train...
Daejeon Station?!
But these days the opposition
is under strict surveillance.
Will you be able to contact them?
You don't need to worry about that.
I have a plan myself.
Here... Assisting the opposition
party members in this situation must be hard,
so eat to your hearts' content.
I wonder if we
really can accept all this.
Ehh... How can you say that?
Myeongwol.
All these folks will
become brilliant politicians.
So you must treat them well.
Yes, Orabeoni...
Here... Let's make a toast.
To democracy.
To democracy!
Is that true?
I've heard that straight from their aides,
so it's legit information.
When are they going to meet?
There will be a massive gathering
in Busan this Saturday.
The ruling party members will
board the train headed for Busan...
this Friday afternoon at six.
Congressman Jo.
It's me, Noh Gapsoo.
We got our hands on quite
the interesting piece of information.
The train for Busan?
It's tomorrow afternoon at six,
the one departing from Seoul Station.
Who would those
ruling party members be?
We still have no names.
They're hiding their identity even to the
opposition party members they approached.
Their last secret meeting failed,
so I see they've become a lot more meticulous.
With Lee Seongmo in confinement,
there's no way our
mission will be exposed.
We must take this opportunity
to expose those traitors, got it?
That's right.
Right... You know that opposition
party members have been invited...
to that fund-raising in Seoul as well?
I've already selected the
agents who will be dispatched there.
Well done.
We can't take our eyes off
of them for a single moment.
You never know what they might do.
How are you, Congressman?
Welcome, Director Hwang.
I see you were here already.
You'll come to the event tomorrow, right?
Actually, it looks like I'll have
to be in the provinces tomorrow,
so I might not be able to come.
I'm sure you do...
The train... Daejeon.
Dining Coach.
Don't look surprised.
You're under surveillance.
Look at this and
just keep listening to me.
You'll have to follow us a moment.
What is the matter?
Who are you people?
What are you trying to do?
Let go...
Let me go!
Go.
I told you I would be meeting those
congressmen because of the event, didn't I?
Is this how you pester innocent citizens?
I apologize.
I think my men made a big mistake.
Will you wake up?
I apologize.
Good job, Jeongyeon.
For this little?
You told Congressman Jang?
Yeah.
He really seemed surprised.
When they're led astray tomorrow,
Jo Pilyeon's attention will
move to the event instead.
One single false step and it's all over for us.
We must be alert at all times.
Guess you'll be busy,
preparing the entire event.
It will be a succession of
sleepless nights starting today.
Right... Need any help?
If it's all right with you,
I can send someone your way.
- Let's do it again.
- Welcome.
- Again.
They're still following us, right?
Yes, Chairman.
Yes.
What?
Someone leaked
details of our meeting again?
Take Min Honggi to the event as well.
The opposition party members
will be here soon.
With that wig, I almost can't
recognize Youngchul Hyungnim.
How did it go?
Did you see them board that train?
They suddenly turned around.
They did what?
Are you telling me
there was another leak?
You were mistaken.
It's not Lee Seongmo,
the culprit was someone else.
Congressman.
The opposition party members
appeared at the fund-raising event.
They still haven't given up.
And what is that supposed to mean?
Their secret meeting might
in fact take place at the event itself.
You said you dispatched agents there, right?
That's right, but it'll be hard
to control the situation.
Send everyone on emergency footing,
we must surround the place.
What?! There was another leak?
So?
It's an emergency.
You two stay behind,
and everyone else
will go to the event.
Follow me.
What's the matter?
Looks like there was another leak.
Ohh... Went out a moment and told them.
- What?
I know a little black magic, you know...
See?
Told you it wasn't him, didn't I?
You little...
Wait until I leave this
place, then you're dead.
- Go fetch me some water. I'm a little thirsty.
- Yes. Chief.
Chairman.
It's your invitation
to the fund-raising event.
I'm not going.
The singer at the event
will be Cha Soojeong.
- Singer, Cha Soojeong -
Stop investigating on Lee Miju.
What?
Yes. I will.
I'm trembling for you, really...
- Soojeong.
- Eonni.
I'd like a word in private with Soojeong,
can you leave us alone a moment?
Yes, sure.
Can you remember these faces?
Are these the ruling party members?
Are you confident you can do it?
Yes.
Succeeding is the only
way to rescue my brother.
Thank you for coming,
President Lee Gangmo.
I have high expectations
about tonight's party.
I'm sure you'll welcome me
even without an invite, Jeongyeon?
It's been a long time.
Isn't it a wonderful night?
I hear there were no
demonstrations in Seoul today?
There have to be days like this.
Since you organized it, I'm
expecting even more from this party.
I'm sure it won't disappoint you.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Editor/QC: Winnie the Pooh
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I'll never forget what you did for me
by paying my hospital bills.
Your hospital bills?!
Sometimes technology is not
the only thing that can solve problems.
You need people to do that.
Are you trying to bring me down?
I will ruin you and your mother.
There might be a secret bipartisan
agreement on the constitutional amendment.
I guess this will be a good opportunity
to find out who the traitors are.
Is throwing rocks and molotovs
what you call democracy?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
Watch what you say!
Lee Miju was hiding a child.
Bring me to that child.
I said turn the car around!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com