Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
In accordance with our regulations,
~ Previously on GIANT ~
I'm here to inform you
this bid has been nullified.
Those committee fools
stabbed us in the back.
And I'd heard you were going around
threatening respectable businessmen...
So the rumors were true.
Find Daeryuk Construction's bidding price.
I'm well aware that
this is no laughing matter.
And that is why I asked you.
Are you asking me to find out
Manbo Construction's bidding price?
Hand me Daeryuk
Construction's bidding plan.
I have this friend working as a
secretary for Daeryuk Construction.
Tell me your bidding price.
But seems that this guy who's helping him
bears a grudge against Hwang Taeseop?!
We must find who that is.
The moment you see my face,
you will die.
I'm sure he will meet with the man
who brought him the bidding plan.
Jo Minwoo just left for the Royal Club.
What?!
~ Episode 12 ~
Know what year Shilla
unified the Three Kingdoms?
Not really?!
If we win that subway construction bid,
Manbo Construction will unify
our country's construction business.
So your bidding price is just like
the year the Three Kingdoms were unified?
He's here again?!
What if he finds out?
Where is the man
who was here with you?
What are you, trailing me?
I asked you who you were here with!
You didn't tell him, did you?
What?
Our bidding price.
You told that man?
When it's just the two of us,
don't think I'll ever let you hit me.
Speak!
Did you tell him?
You saw that bidding plan yourself.
Still raising a fuss despite
all that, isn't it laughable?
If he replaced the pages I tore
and gave you that, then what?
What?
Anyone would be capable of such tricks.
You've gotten better.
I almost let you fool me.
But, you know?
I know you better than you think.
All you're hoping for
is to see me make a mistake,
since you're trying to interfere
with me whatever it takes.
Listen well.
I couldn't care less
about people like you.
The company is what matters to me.
The man you tried to incriminate
is like a brother to me.
He would never try to betray me.
Did I make myself clear?
That's quite a feast
you prepared for us today?!
This must taste great.
Honey, try it out.
Here...
It's all right.
My hands are still moving fine.
I just want you to have a balanced diet.
Here, come on...
Did you just laugh at me?
What?
Of course not!
You just looked good together.
When did we ever eat with our maids?
Get out of my face!
What's wrong with you, Honey?
I told her to eat with us.
Leave us alone,
or I'll lose my appetite!
You really...
Yes, Hannam-Dong here.
Is Chairman Hong Gipyo home?
Just a moment.
You don't need to call him,
just write him a memo.
Ahh... One moment, please.
Go ahead.
Yes...
Tomorrow at noon,
at the Japanese restaurant in Jong-Ro.
Kimono.
Which room did you say again?
Ahh... The Fallen Blossom Room.
Fallen Blossom...
Who's calling?
Hello?
He hung up?!
I wrote it all down
on this memo, Chairman.
What should we build on the land around
the subway site, to bolster our profits?
Building an apartment complex
would be the most profitable option,
but considering that the real
estate sector is in a recession...
We can find the missing funds
for our subway construction...
with the profit from building
apartments around the area.
But if we fail to sell them?
Our company itself would risk collapse.
I'll take all the responsibility.
Once the bid is over,
draft a plan right away.
All right.
It's driving me crazy.
Why does that dream keep coming to mind?
Let's wake up, Hwang Jeongyeon.
After all I've gone through to get here,
I can't let him laugh at me.
This is the room.
My guest will soon arrive.
We'll order then.
As you wish, Sir.
Chairman Hong Gipyo?
You were there?!
Let me come over.
Just sit there.
How did it go?
Find out which year Shilla
unified the Three Kingdoms.
And why are you suddenly...
That will tell you the
amount you're looking for.
Then...
I've fulfilled my task,
so bringing Manbo Construction to
its destruction is your responsibility.
I'm really thankful.
How can I repay your generosity?
I want to reciprocate
for what you did.
Just tell me.
Are you listening to me?
Look, Chief Kim.
Rewrite our plan, and lower
the price whatever it takes.
As for the plan, all it will take is
some hard work from our employees, but...
But what's the problem?
Even if we win the bid, at that
price we would still be in trouble.
If we win, we can always find a way to
cover our missing funds, so don't worry.
The unification of the Three Kingdoms?!
Listen to that...
I apologize for what
happened at the Royal Club.
Let's just pretend
it was a confession of guilt,
since there's nothing else
to hide between us now.
Not long ago, I had a chance
to meet with Oh Byeongtak.
Congressman Oh told me.
So you want a recommendation
to join the the Republican Party?
I'll get straight to the point.
These elections are
all about money, anyway.
Let's just agree that whoever
loses the subway bid will step aside.
So that means you're
confident that you'll win?
Just that we shouldn't
waste time with attrition warfare.
Yes.
Director.
I found out Manbo
Construction's bidding price.
I see.
Where were we?
Ohh... Attrition warfare.
Fine.
No need to fight
each other so strenuously.
Are you agreeing?
If one loses the subway bid, what
would they use to fund their candidacy?
Let's just avoid unpleasantries
to compete with each other.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
Jo Pilyeon.
You'll soon stop putting on airs.
I really can't figure out how
he can be so confident about all this.
How did what I told you to do go?
We're proceeding well.
You don't need to worry.
Until the winner is announced,
you can't let your guard down.
No need to mention it, Director.
Right... What is Lee Seongmo
doing, these days?
Actually, I've heard very
surprising news concerning him.
You're back?
I've come more than once,
but I found no one here.
Were you busy?
I had a few issues to deal with.
What issues?
Don't you know
the situation we are in?
Thought you could fool me?
Just be honest.
I already know what you did.
What's with all the surprise?
"I did a favor to Minwoo,"
couldn't you just admit it?
Well done.
Seongmo, you really did us proud.
If it involves Minwoo,
then it involves me.
Shall we go out for a drink?
I never thought Jo Minwoo
would believe what you said,
but still!
Shouldn't at least
the chairman believe you?
I mean...
Honestly, where else would you find
someone as loyal to him as you here?
Don't move.
It's a revolver.
Try anything funny, and you're dead.
Ahh... The more I think about it,
the angrier it makes me.
Hey, you.
Who did I just speak with?
So you haven't listened
to a word I said all along?
What are you thinking about?
If the man who helped Jo Minwoo
is the same one I met,
then there is a way to stop him.
What?
So...
What is it you wanted to tell me?
I am sure the man who told Daeryuk
Construction's bidding price to Chief Jo...
is a KCIA agent.
I guess so.
There is no way Jo Minwoo wouldn't
have used his father's influence.
Find out who that man is.
Are you still believing
Chief Jo is a spy?
I never disappointed the chairman
even once all these years.
I'm sure there is some kind of
conspiracy at play here.
Find out who is the
man who helped Chief Jo.
Now that you mention it, I'm having
a drink with Director Jo tonight,
so I'll give it a try.
I will follow you there.
Minwoo will keep needing
your help in the future.
You should have
invited him here as well.
Aigoo, seems like we are a little late.
How can someone who calls
you out for a drink be late?
My apologies.
I see you've come as well.
I brought him here as encouragement
for all the hard work that awaits him.
I trust I can let him
share the table with us?
Naturally.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Here, drink to your heart's content.
I'm sparing no expenses today.
Thank you.
Here, let me pour you
a drink, Chairman Hwang.
But...
Who was the man who helped Chief Jo?
Why are you asking?
He helped us so much,
I thought I'd pay back the courtesy.
And what would that mean?
Well... Why wouldn't I
give him whatever he asks for?
You won't get too
many chances like this.
Tell him what you want.
So was it him?
I need no reward.
Don't say that.
Go ahead and tell me.
I just ask you to keep supporting the
director, even after you win the bid.
That's the kind of man
we're dealing with.
Let's have a toast,
to our neverending development.
Cheers.
How did you get your hands on
Daeryuk Construction's bidding plan?
What is moving you to ask that?
It's just natural to ask it.
So you want to extort
intelligence from a KCIA agent?!
Quite daring, I see.
If you're here to accompany
those higher-ups, just drink quietly.
You must be the one
who pointed a gun at me?
The voice of that man who
promised I'd die if I saw him...
I can clearly remember it.
You must have been bruised in the head.
May I take a look?
I'll just pretend you forgot for
a moment whom you're dealing with.
What is this grudge you bear
against the chairman?
What could it possibly be,
if you even help Daeryuk Construction
behind our backs, and...
Careful.
You might be working for Chairman Hwang,
but I won't tolerate
any more of your antics.
That Lee Seongmo...
Director Jo seems to really trust him.
Is he really called Lee Seongmo?
That's what I've heard.
Why?
It's nothing.
It's just that he and someone
I know have the same name.
Seems like he risked his life
more than once for Director Jo's sake.
So there's no reason to suspect him.
He's one of Jo's closest confidants,
there's no way he'd help Hong Gipyo.
Have a good night.
Right...
Lee Seongmo?!
He's Manbo Construction's
Chief of Services.
Find whatever you can about him.
I will.
What's the matter?
How about Jo Minwoo?
Everyone's busy beyond belief.
I have to go back, too.
How much would it take to write one
of those bidding documents from scratch?
If they present that to the bid,
it might get us into trouble.
I've heard from Chief Jo.
Aren't you overreacting?
Agasshi...
Even you can't trust me?
It's not that I don't trust you...
Everyone makes mistakes.
I told you I met him firsthand!
That man who's helping Jo Minwoo
is working for Hong Gipyo!
The bid is right around the corner.
What are we supposed to do,
without any solid evidence?
So you just let them fool you
right under your noses like a retard?
Even Jo Minwoo can make mistakes.
And we can't let that
compromise our company's future.
By no means.
I've never seen you
get so angry at me before.
I'm sorry.
Even you only trust Jo Minwoo,
so I guess it made me angrier.
Wasn't bad.
Even if just for a little while,
you looked like a man.
I'll talk to Chief Jo.
Happy now?
Where are you going,
when we're all so busy?
Review this.
I...
I'd like a word.
Didn't you just hear we're busy?
If what Gangmo says is right, then what?
Did you just meet with Lee Gangmo?
I know Gangmo well.
- He's not the kind who would just say...
- Are you out of your mind?
If you have all that spare time,
use it on the counter.
Even just 10 won out of place,
and our bid is canceled.
Still, checking one last time,
just in case you made a mistake...
What this boils down to...
is the fact you trust
Lee Gangmo more than me.
Then, go to him.
I don't need anyone working under me,
if they can't trust me.
He's an orphan,
and Hwang Taeseop has been
raising him since his childhood.
What's his name?
Lee Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo?!
It's just like the name of
the brother you were looking for,
and turns out he's not from
Busan, but Jong-Ro in Seoul.
Chairman Hwang is like a father to him.
He's also quite resourceful,
so whenever there's something difficult
to handle at work, he takes care of it.
Yes.
So you found someone
who knows Lee Gangmo?
The photo really doesn't help,
but I can confirm a Lee Gangmo
worked at our factory.
Are you sure he's from Busan?
He's from there,
and about the same age.
Then, do you know where he is now?
Or maybe even a contact number?
If you'll pardon me asking,
what's your relationship with him?
He's the younger brother
I lost back when we were little.
I see...
Gangmo, that fella, has passed away.
Passed... away?!
Last year, there was
a fire at the factory, and...
Seonbaenim...
His grave...
Where is his grave?
Because we couldn't find his family,
we cremated him, and spread
his ashes in the Han River.
Shouldn't there be
at least some relics left?
I am sorry.
Did you find out?
Don't get me started.
We should be glad my friend
works as a guard at the KCIA.
If it weren't for him, I wouldn't
even have gotten inside the building.
Where is that Lee Seongmo from?
He didn't know that,
but he said he's from the 8th US Army.
The 8th Army?!
That's where he first met
Director Jo Pilyeon.
Seeing as he has no previous record,
he probably comes from the US.
Aigoo... What was it again?
Ohh... G. I.
You know, all those Koreans
who come back with American passports.
Why, is it the first time you
see people with the same name?
It'll be much quicker
to look for your sister.
I'll find her for you.
Halmeoni!
Have you sold a lot of rice cakes?
Aigoo... Look who's here.
Came to meet your brothers again?
No, I ran an errand nearby.
Give me a few, while we're here.
I was wondering why you
hadn't been around, these days.
I only come here
the last day of the month.
We promised each other
we'd meet on that day.
Wait a moment.
Now that I think about it,
once a month,
there was this fella
always waiting for someone?
Really, Halmeoni?
Yeah... I've been selling
cakes here for about a year,
and he's come every single time.
But I haven't seen him
around the last few months?!
You're here again?
Have you sold a lot?
Have you had dinner?
I'll have a few rice cakes.
Who on earth are you waiting for,
even skipping meals?
She must be much hungrier than me.
You don't look like
you're married with children,
so is the person you're
waiting for your sister?
How much is it?
Look at me,
never minding my business.
He'd always wait and
keep waiting, until curfew.
Anything else?
His name, where he lives...
Have you asked that?
Aigoo... He was a man of few words...
But is that the man you're looking for?
Aigoo, what now?
Looks like you missed each other.
Aigoo, that's so sad...
Don't let it sadden you too much.
If it's in your destiny to meet,
one day you will.
I wonder why there are so
many people suffering like you.
Seongmo Oppa...
Gangmo Oppa...
Miju is here.
Where on earth are you?
Gangmo...
I should have protected you...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Gangmo.
I'm sorry...
Your brother is here.
Your brother is here, Gangmo!
Gangmo, I'm here!
Lee Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Here, folks!
Good job, everyone.
We matched the bidding price
without a single blemish.
Let me say this again,
but Daeryuk Construction is trying
its damnedest to find our bidding price.
Until the bid is over, secrecy is a must,
one you must never forget.
It hurts, Mom!
Hurry up and speak.
What did you do with it?
It hurts! Let go!
The three million I gave you
to find out their bidding price!
Just have some patience,
they'll call me soon.
The bid is today, when is
that ever going to happen?
It's... It's today?!
You'll drive me crazy.
What's all this noise?
So today's the day, isn't it?
Go there and beat them all, Dad!
Where are you prancing
around all day, as of late?
Prancing around?!
I spend all day reading at home.
Isn't that right, Mom?
Aww... Just go easy on that.
Your eyesight will suffer.
Listen to that...
If we win the subway bid,
come back to work.
What?
Honey!
Do you mean that?
You can finally kiss
being a freeloader goodbye.
Thank you, Dad.
I'll really do my best.
Move.
Thank you, Dad.
Have a nice day, Dear.
What's with your father?
Mom. This time, forget about me
working at the construction site.
Then, where?
Where should I ask him to send you?
Jeongyeon is in the
planning team, so forget that.
The secre...
Anyhow... You know, whatever
gives you more influence.
All right.
I'll talk it out with Chief Moon, and
find you the best position in the company.
You just wait.
Jeongyeon, Minwoo...
You're all done!
Aigoo... Aigoo!
My darling...
~ Seoul Subway Construction Selection Bid ~
We just completed our review
of the bidding plans you submitted.
In a half hour, at noon,
we will announce the results.
If I'd found out their price,
I would have told you already.
All they talked about was Unified
Three Kingdoms this and that...
Unified Three Kingdoms?!
But what's with the chairman,
and all that "Unified Three Kingdoms" talk?
But maybe he meant
unified north and south?
Educated people being so ignorant...
Did you say Unified Three Kingdoms?
That's what I said.
Unified Three Kingdoms...
Unified Three Kingdoms.
The year 676.
What's wrong with you?
Are you that happy,
that they unified them?
We're not too late, are we?
They'll soon announce
the results, let's go in.
Wait a moment!
67.6 billion won.
Is that right?
Our bidding price
is 67.6 billion won, right?
How could you be aware of that?
Where have you heard that?
Tell me!
Where do you think? Uh?
I heard it from them.
Do you get it now, Jo Minwoo?
I will now announce the results.
The subway construction
is hereby awarded to,
with a total bidding price
of 67.55 billion won,
Daeryuk Construction.
You must have worked so hard,
I'll have to apologize to you.
You bastards...
I'll make the best
Seoul subway possible.
Who did this to me?
At the bid, don't forget
to thank Chairman Hwang's son.
Ahh... Right!
Extend my gratitude to your son.
I'm sure he'll understand what I mean.
What kind of crap...
Chief Jo!
Jo Minwoo! Where has
that little bastard gone?
I just heard the news.
That the subway construction was awarded...
- Search his desk.
- Yes, Director.
What are you doing?
Why, don't you know already?
The plan you gave him was a fake!
Speak.
How did you find that?
Who did you plan all this with?
Director!
What is this photo?
Isn't this Chairman Hwang's son?
The man he's with is a
Daeryuk Construction secretary.
What?!
If any intel was leaked,
Chairman Hwang's son is responsible.
Bring me Jo Minwoo!
Where did he run to?
Calm down, Chairman.
Let go!
With our company facing collapse,
should I really calm down?
He destroyed the tower we fought
so hard to build, all in one strike?!
Quite the skilled son you have.
That's for me to tell you.
Here...
Take a good look at this photo.
And what is this?
It's your son, the one who sold
intel to Daeryuk Construction!
What?
Ahh... Right!
Extend my gratitude to your son.
I'm sure he'll understand what I mean.
That motherless little fool!
Ahh... Pathetic fool...
Careful.
Look at my son's skin.
Ajumma.
Bring some more cucumber.
I'm coming.
Cucumber's so expensive these days...
He's coming back to work tomorrow,
is cucumber the matter now?
Mom.
I need a suit
if I am to go back to work.
- A suit?
- Yeah.
Where the hell is Jeongshik?
Looks like Dad is back.
- The cucumber will fall off.
- Where is that little bastard?
Jeongshik, you stop there!
Honey, are you back?
I prepared wine to celebrate.
Shut up!
You little motherless fool.
What mess did you get us into?
Ahh... Dad... What did I do now?
Did you meet with a Daeryuk
Construction employee, or not?
Dad... That was my mistake...
You goddamned, useless twat!
I just ought to...
Today, you and I will both
get it over with and die!
What are you doing,
are you out of your mind?
Come here...
Dad.
All this for just three million won?
Say what?
Come here!
What's wrong with you, Dad?
Mom... Stop him.
Honey, calm down.
He's our one and only son!
Chairman, please, calm down.
Let me go!
What? Our only son?!
I don't want a son like that!
He must have gone batty,
just find refuge.
Ahh... Really!
The hell with this!
Where are you running to?
I'm sorry, Honey.
Hit me instead.
Don't hurt Jeongshik, Honey...
Honey, I'm so sorry...
Blame it all on me, will you?
Where are you going?
Let go.
Let me go!
- You didn't do that, right?
- I did what?
Go tell my mother
to bring me some money.
My shoes as well.
I have no idea what is going on.
He didn't do that.
He could have never
known our bidding price.
Then, just as you said...
Jo Minwoo was used by that KCIA agent.
Minwoo worked harder than ever before,
but now he becomes a traitor
in a matter of moments...
Think of how disheartened he'll be.
May I sit here?
I've been looking at you for a while...
Seems like you have no company?
You looked like you
needed someone to talk with.
Let me...
Stop annoying me and
just get out of my face.
Hey... Why did you drink so much?
Hey... You're drunk.
Go up to your room and sleep.
Come on, Minwoo.
Come sit here a moment.
I apologize, Father.
Honey!
I might forgive a son who failed,
but not one who
prances around looking down!
I have no excuses.
Honey...
That's not what I meant.
"Don't worry, I'll get back on my feet.
Give me another chance."
That's what I want to hear from you!
Honey...
For whose sake?
What?
For whose sake should I do that?
Minwoo!
What are you saying to your father?!
I'm tired of living as your son.
I'm not cut out for it!
Minwoo!
If you really couldn't take it anymore,
you wouldn't act
this way in my presence.
Starting tomorrow,
get back on your feet.
And if after walking the same path
over and over you really get bored to death,
then come die before me.
That, I would forgive.
Honey...
Yes, all right.
That's exactly what I'll do.
You really are something.
How could you say that to your own son?
Because he's my son.
If that weren't the case,
I wouldn't waste time
saying such things.
Honey.
Jaechun is here.
Come on in.
- Breakfast?
- Already ate it.
Bring Jaechun a cup of tea.
Yes.
Open it.
~ Daeryuk Construction ~
For Authorized Personnel Only
Just in case, I investigated
Daeryuk Construction's dealings.
You like baseball, don't you?
The perfect time to change the course of
a game is  bottom of the ninth, two outs.
This is all I can do for you.
You take care of the rest.
There must be a way to get our hands
on the subway construction again?!
Come in.
Here are the records for the land
we bought around the subway lot.
With all the money we invested,
is this all you could buy?
Go out and see for yourself.
The kind of difference that being
close to the subway or not really makes.
If you don't believe me,
try to buy it yourself.
Wait.
How much land did Daeryuk
Construction secure there?
About... 65 percent?!
Right... That's it!
This is it!
Say what?
Think that'll even be possible?
That's the only way we can
get the subway contract back.
It's too dangerous.
If you end up failing,
our company will really risk collapse.
I'm confident I can succeed.
Give me just one more chance.
People used to say "if there's
no way, don't ever walk on it."
Chairman.
But, if there's truly a will,
there must be a way,
even if you create it from scratch.
I'll believe in you one last time.
Thank you, Chairman.
But, Chairman!
We must take this to the end anyway.
So, what do you want me to do?
First, gather all
the funds at your disposal.
And then?
Two yearning souls,
holding each other's hand.
~ The Yearning by Park Inhee ~
A smile painted on their faces,
together walking on that path.
Lola...
Why is he coming so often?
Have a seat.
What do I owe the occasion to?
I don't have all that
time to waste, I'm afraid.
We will sell all the land
around the subway lot to you.
Seems like your company
is facing quite the difficulties?!
I can certainly
understand the situation,
but I'm afraid I won't be able to
give you that much above market value.
Help us out, Chairman Hong.
Think I would sell that land,
if I could avoid it?
Fine.
I'll raise the price by half.
What?
You want to give us only half more
for land whose price might skyrocket...
right after the subway is opened?
So you're not in as bad
a situation as I thought.
Chairman.
Let's not even sell it.
Then, I'll give you
twice its market value.
That's my last offer.
Instead, pay us all in one shot.
Chairman!
Fine with me.
I pray you will soon get
your company back on its feet.
He's been pushed right to
the edge of a cliff,
and look at him shaking his
behind as if nothing happened.
This still doesn't feel right.
The die is cast already.
Let's see if Jo Minwoo
can run with this.
He dug his own grave.
Manbo Construction holds
quite a lot of land there.
How are you going to pay for that land?
We'll soon make our investment back,
why are you even worried?
We can always find the money.
Today they don't even take a bite.
That's right.
There's no way you would
find fish in putrid waters.
This was a great
fishing spot in the past.
Didn't you turn it
into all this yourselves?
Because the first thing you ruined
with your redevelopment plans...
is exactly this Han River.
And redevelopment is the
only way to save it as well.
That's what you think.
And how about polluting people's souls?
I came to borrow some money.
The more, the merrier.
You recklessly presented that
ridiculously low bidding price,
so I bet you have no money left
to pay for the construction.
If we could only buy the land around
the subway, we'd solve that problem.
So you're in the mood
for some speculation.
It's for our business's sake,
so let's just call it investment.
They used to say that you should only
fill your boat with the fish you need,
and that if you go overboard,
your greed will drown you.
That is never going to happen.
And if you can't pay back
the interests on time?
We can just take possession
of that subway lot.
Must it really be that land?
If you're really that worried
you won't be able to pay back,
you should just give up now.
Fine.
Instead, I expect a generous deadline.
I'll come visit you at home tomorrow.
It will be all right, I hope?
He seems nervous.
Take a look.
Big fish always bask in putrid waters!
It's me, Dad.
Would today be all right with you?
Yes, all right.
Not because it's my son,
but he's quite the clever fella.
Must be something nice?
- Actually, I investigated Hong Gipyo's...
- Jaechun!
Yes.
When all is said and done,
I'll explain everything.
Let's get up,
there's somewhere we need to go.
Yes, Director.
Since the president has taken a keen
interest in the subway construction,
it must proceed without obstacles.
Certainly, Mr. Congressman.
Come on in.
Aigoo... What brings you here?
I see you're here as well.
It's tomorrow's headline.
~ Speculation Behind the
Seoul Subway Construction? ~
What is this?
Suspicions of speculation,
not to mention corruption?
- If it's the subway construction...
- Daeryuk Construction is involved.
Were you aware of this?
I had some suspicions, but I
never imagined it could be this bad.
Director Jo.
Stop this headline.
If the president learns of this,
we're all as good as dead!
I already took care of that,
considering the urgency of the matter.
Then, this is not
going to be published?
I might have stopped it for now,
but since the journalists know,
the problem is from now on.
How did you handle all this?
You assign the construction
to this kind of people?!
That's not going to happen.
Revoke that bid immediately.
If we revoke the bid,
this will only end up putting
the spotlight on this issue.
So, what are we supposed to do?
How much longer do you think
we can stop those journalists?
There is one way.
Forcing Daeryuk Construction to
give up the construction spontaneously.
How?
Chairman Hong was going to compensate
for the missing construction costs...
via real estate speculation.
If the price of estate doesn't go up,
he won't make money,
so he will be forced to
give up the construction.
A subway is going to be built there,
how do you stop prices from going up?
So you're suggesting we
change the subway's route?
Exactly.
If the subway route changes,
all the land Chairman Hong bought
will never gain any value.
Is it possible to change the route now?
If we don't, this will only become
a time bomb we can't predict.
Whatever it takes,
change that route.
Make sure Daeryuk Construction
can't go ahead with this!
All right.
We will review the matter and
make those changes as soon as possible.
How did it go?
Probably just as we planned.
Once that subway route is changed,
the land we bought will
become the new subway lot.
Are you confident?
Because that's the only
route the subway can take.
The river flows under
the third Han River bridge.
~ The Third Han River Bridge by Hyeeunyi ~
Carrying your dreams and mine,
along with our hearts.
My youth whirling around
like a blossoming flower,
like a bird, like the wind,
like the water, flowing free.
We met again yesterday,
and pledged to each other.
Once the night was over,
we'd take the first train,
And together leave for
the street of happiness.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I thought you were sleeping...
Think this is your playground?
What are you jumping around for?
Still, I'm not too bad, am I?
When it comes to dancing and singing,
I'm confident I can make it.
Just look at yourself
in the mirror, you wench.
A housemaid like you...
Why?
Who said I'll never make it as a singer?
Shut it!
Finish here and cook me lunch.
I'm hungry.
She does that because she likes you.
What?
Before she met me,
her dream was that of becoming a singer.
Thanks to you, I finally get
to hear singing again here.
I'll do it more often, then.
Ohh... Miju.
Don't you want to go to college?
College?!
Going to college was my dream...
If you promise you'll live
with us for a long time,
I'll send you to college.
That, I can't promise.
Why?
If I meet my brothers,
I'll have to leave this place.
Chairman, this is trouble.
What's all the fuss?
City Hall just announced it.
They're changing the subway route.
What?
Commissioner!
Aigoo... Come on in.
I was just about to call you.
Why did you suddenly change that route?
Can you just change that as you please?
What does that have to do with
the subway construction?
The budget will change accordingly,
why would it be otherwise?
Neither the scope nor the budget
of this project will change.
At least tell me the reason.
Why did you suddenly...
Seems like real estate speculation
is too excessive in the area.
If I can do anything to
change the assembly's position,
I will do my best to convince them.
- So if they can just stop this motion...
- Look, Chairman Hong.
The president himself has
his eyes on this project.
If you act with imprudence,
not only yours,
but the heads of everyone else
involved will start to roll.
Did I make myself clear?
If you feel you're not up to the task,
feel free to tell us.
If Daeryuk Construction
gives up this project,
the next in line, Manbo Construction,
will take over in accordance with our rules.
~ Seoul Subway Route Changed ~
Escaping Excessive Speculation the Reason
They suddenly change the subway route?!
What on earth is behind all this?
I'm sure Jo Pilyeon and
Hwang Taeseop are responsible.
We can't let them get away with this.
Weather is nice.
You're going back to work, right?
I'll go fetch the car.
Wait, young man.
How have you been?
Is the person you were
looking for your sister?
Did you find her?
No, not yet.
But... Why?
So you promised each other you would
meet here at the end of the month?
Aigoo!
It's her indeed!
It's that young lady, all right.
My sister came here?
Aigoo... Sure she did!
She's been looking all over for you.
Do you know where she is?
Aigoo... If I knew this, I would
at least have asked her phone number.
Aigoo... What now?!
Miju...
Miju!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Jeongyeon refused your proposal.
What if I really fell for her?!
I decided to recommend Director Min.
What are you trying to say?
I can't invest in a
venture that has no hope.
Daeryuk Construction's
Hong Gipyo is behind all this!
He must carry an account
with all his dealings.
He's meeting with a
reporter from Goryeo Ilbo.
His name is Yoon Gihoon.
Jo Minwoo's father?!
Only a night inside this place,
and you'll spend the rest of
your life regretting ever coming here.
Jo Pilyeon arrested
the committee members.
I think I'll have to get married.
I decided to think of it
as strictly business.
Don't do it.
If that's the kind of marriage
you're planning, don't bother!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com