This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
- Episode 41 -
Leave company matters to me.
There's no reason why I should
report every detail to you.
What?! Minwoo, you little...
You worry about Baekpa.
Chairman.
We just received a call from him.
He says he'll hand Beaute
his resignation and join us tomorrow.
That's out of the question.
Until we get our hands on
their core technology and schematics,
we won't accept him.
I will tell him that, Chairman.
The new owner of Beaute
Boilers' Korean subsidiary,
with a bid of twelve-point-six-five...
-one (12.651) billion won,
is Hangang Construction.
Lee Gangmo...
The game is not over yet.
This Beaute acquisition...
is going to be fatal to you.
Can you handle the boiler company?
We acquired it thanks to you,
and I certainly could trust you with it.
- And...
- But...
I'm enjoying what I'm doing right now.
And I set some goals for
my future as well.
Jeongyeon, seeing you
work in the private lending...
No, no matter how big
you get in this sector...
I have to go.
Did I upset you?
I know how dangerous
this line of work is.
But even the construction business
always had its share of risks.
And it's likely that the same
goes for every other job.
I really better go.
Let me drive you home.
No need.
You looked cool today, Lee Gangmo.
I finally realized how far you've come.
Will you keep watching over me?
While I get back on my feet.
Sure.
- Financial Law -
Eonni is here, Director.
If I knew you were on your way,
I would have come earlier.
Did I make you wait?
No... I just got here.
Looks like Cha Bucheol
is going to be released soon.
Already?!
And why...
This was only a test
Baekpa put you through.
What?
He'd like to see you tomorrow.
What are all those?
These are your tapes?!
We're in trouble.
I went around stores all day,
and almost no one
was asking for your album.
These were all returned.
Don't tell the director.
She must have lost
a lot of money because of me.
Let's give it some more time.
Miju.
Cha! Soo! Jeong!
Even the name is fine...
Let's go sell these on the street.
What?!
We need to sell these
if we want people to listen.
It's not like we're
peddlers or something...
How can a singer
embarrass herself that way?
I couldn't care less about that.
People must listen to my songs
whatever it takes.
That's the only way.
Cha Soojeong! Listen to this!
It's fun and exciting.
Cha Soojeong!
Face, singing, dancing...
She's got it all!
Hi, I'm new singer Cha Soojeong.
Give this a listen. It has
ballads and even dance songs.
The songs are great.
Oppa, oppa! Give this a listen!
Oppa! Try this...
Ehh... Don't just go.
Cha Soojeong, give it a listen.
Soojeong!
What are you doing here?
Did you bring my stage
costumes and the amp?
They're inside the car,
are you really going to do it here?
Yes.
Hello everyone!
Here is new singer Cha Soojeong!
Eonni, come closer.
Everyone, please come closer.
She's new singer Cha Soojeong.
Her album is great!
- That's not too bad?!
- She'll be on TV soon.
Folks... How are you?
She's new singer Cha Soojeong.
One tape for 2,000 won. Pick one.
Here you go. Her songs are great.
Thank you.
See you again.
Professor Park Seonghwa of Hanguk
University seemed particularly interested.
I bet he is.
Developing gas boilers
that suit Korea's ondol culture?!
It's a very stimulating project.
But considering the
development costs involved...
Spare no expense.
Ahh, also.
How about Beaute's core
technology and schematics?
We're in the process of acquiring them.
Why is it so noisy outside?
What's wrong?
Is anything the matter?
Just a moment...
In the midst of a movement for direct
elections aiming for ten million signatures,
163 professors from 23 different universities
joined the demonstrations and signed.
Along with them an SNU professor
who was praying at Myeongdong Cathedral...
along with 62 priests
joined the protests, pushing for...
Turn it off.
We should just teach all those fools
asking for direct elections a lesson.
Anything planned on your side?
The entire ANSP is
in turmoil because of this.
But how is the ruling party reacting?
Why are you asking?
To allow direct elections,
the constitution needs to be amended,
and without the ruling party's
approval, that's impossible.
Sure is.
But who would ever dare
to rile the president with this?
All this chaos is useless.
So you said they
released that Bucheol fella?
Yes.
Find that fool and bring him here.
All right, Congressman.
It's not my fault, Sir!
This could only happen if
someone from within got involved.
And you're suggesting
that would be me?
Let's be honest!
Unless you let Hwang Jeongyeon
in on all this, she...
You idiot!
What is even more pathetic than
a loser is someone making excuses!
I want all the money I invested
in you back by the end of the day,
so better get ready.
Sir...
Please, don't abandon me!
You may leave.
Sir!
Are you planning to disobey me?
Sir.
It's me.
Come on in.
How did you find out about Bucheol?
President Lee Gangmo helped me.
Is that so?
But, Sir.
There is something
I still don't understand.
Congressman Jo Pilyeon
was helping Cha Bucheol.
Jo Pilyeon was helping Bucheol?!
Yoo Gyeongok, Hwang Jeongyeon...
You just wait.
I will personally make sure you two...
The congressman wishes to see you.
You didn't think you could get away
with getting him in trouble, did you?
I have no reason
to meet Congressman Jo?!
Seems like I didn't make myself clear.
Stop there!
Stop!
Let's not waste time.
Get in the car
before I have to carry you in.
You prick!
Come.
You were the one who approached me.
And I did right as you asked.
But the results are a complete disaster.
Lee Gangmo ended up
acquiring that boiler company,
and you've embarrassed me
in everyone's eyes.
I apologize, Congressman.
You apologize?!
And now you're even
saying the word I most despise.
Get down, you little...
You...
You said you were a gangster?
No... An enforcer,
now that I think about it.
You know, it finally hit me.
The fact that I should
take care of things by myself.
And you'll have to
be the first on that list.
Arms down.
Stay put, you prick!
Please, don't!
I'll do everything you ask!
Everything.
Please, spare me...
Baekpa is here.
Baekpa's organization
is structured like a pyramid.
With the exception
of a few veteran members,
people in the lower tiers of the
organization have never even seen him.
So you're telling me that they
are all doing business with his money?
They pay interests every month.
Principal and interests included,
nobody knows the full extent
of Baekpa's assets.
Let's see what
this pyramid looks like, then.
I want every detail, from ranks all
the way to the members' controlled area.
You'll have to forgive me,
but I don't possess such information.
You don't?
No.
It's such a meticulously
organized operation,
with the exception
of a few veteran members,
few people are fully aware
of its structure.
How long would you need to find out?
Are you planning to
go all out against Baekpa?
That old fart and I
have a lot left to settle.
Baekpa will soon die.
All the more reason
why we need to hurry.
Because we must stop Hwang Jeongyeon
and her mother from inheriting that fortune.
You have a week to find out.
Or else you won't make it
to Baekpa's funeral alive.
All right.
And as for the Eulji-Ro area,
which Bucheol was taking care of,
this lady will take over.
So you're letting this kiddo
join the family just like that?
I'm making an announcement.
I didn't come here
to ask for your consent.
I apologize, Sir.
Remember these four people well.
They're going to lead you from now on.
I'll be counting on you.
My name is Hwang Jeongyeon.
For the time being,
help her out in the Eulji-Ro area.
All right, Sir.
Hire a few bodyguards
to protect Jeongyeon.
Bodyguards?
That's really not necessary, Sir.
Now that you've officially
been entrusted an area,
it would be wiser to follow his wishes.
Yes, all right.
I'm tired.
You don't look too good these days.
We'll install the boilers we're
producing in the new Suseo apartments.
Spare no efforts to boost our production.
Don't worry about it, President.
Anyhow, since we're
all on the same boat now,
how about you make a toast, President?
Shall I?
Here.
Have you even thought about why
Beaute would sell its subsidiary?
Watch your mouth.
President, you've been fooled.
Stop it, Director Yang!
Why, is there any problem
with this factory?
Good job.
Don't worry about
your kid's hospital bills.
You have our support
until his full recovery.
It's part of the schematics
for Beaute's boilers.
When can you get your hands
on their core technology?
Since it's restricted information,
it might not be so easy to acquire it.
Let the press in on all the boiler-related
accidents that we've been putting under the rug.
You want to disclose
Beaute's accident logs?
Now that Hangang Construction acquired it,
no need to keep hiding them.
All right, Chairman.
This Suseo sales war
will be fought with boilers.
We must acquire Beaute's core
technology as soon as possible.
Yes, Chairman.
There were this
many boiler-related accidents?
Seven cases of gas poisoning,
and nine caused by oxygen deficiency.
Seems like these ventilation issues
won't be solved so easily?!
Reporter Yoon is here.
Aigoo... How is everyone doing?
- Come on in.
- Gangmo.
Info leaks about boiler-related accidents
are pouring down every news agency.
Once those articles are published,
Beaute's reliability in the eyes
of the customers will suffer greatly.
Get in touch with the factory, and let's
find out the cause of those accidents.
Ohh... I already had set up
a meeting for this evening.
Sotae, check how those
news agencies are proceeding.
Okay.
If you want me to,
I could write a rebuttal.
Thank you, Seonsaengnim.
Right... You didn't know that
Chairman Hwang came back, did you?
I went to meet my parents,
and my mother said so.
She said he's pretty much fully recovered.
Come on in.
Director. We have guests.
Dad...
Jeongyeon.
How have you been?
So you've fully recovered?
That's right.
Come to me.
Let Daddy hug his little girl.
Dad...
You've worked hard.
Dad.
- Urban Development Research Center -
President Hwang Taeseop
I've heard about you.
So you're handling the Eulji-Ro area now?
How did you find out?
I've heard it from Director Yoo.
I told her not to tell you
I was back on purpose.
I wanted to settle
a few things first, and...
What's going on between
you and Director Yoo?
Uh?!
Why?
Actually, I knew you two were close
ever since you collapsed.
Listen to you...
I told you that it's not the case.
I can perfectly understand.
Friend or whatever, it's always nice
to have someone you can rely on.
So you're not getting married?
You're not getting any younger,
how much longer will you keep staying...
I'm very busy these days.
Even if I had a man,
I'd probably get dumped?!
There would be no one
better than Gangmo for you...
Dad.
If I think that you'll never be able
to get any closer because of me,
it just breaks my heart so much
I can't even sleep.
Promise you'll never say that again.
It's over between Gangmo and me.
There are no feelings left whatsoever.
Jeongyeon.
I'm full of plans for the future.
First, I'll make a lot of money.
After which I'll get my hands on Manbo
Construction, and give it back to you.
And you have no intention
of getting married?
Why wouldn't I get married,
unless I was crazy?
If dating doesn't cut it,
I'll just make a ton of money
and meet the coolest man on earth.
So I can take my time, right?
I'm glad to see that
you've become so strong.
What are you saying?
Baekpa has cancer?!
Looks like the hospital gave up, too.
It's legit info.
But the real issue is Jo Pilyeon.
A huge storm is about to hit
his private lending empire.
He has set his sights on Baekpa's fortune.
And is that even possible?
It's always a matter
of finding a just cause.
If he plays the secret
fund or tax evasion card,
it's not completely unfeasible.
You must stop it, Hyung!
We can't allow Jo Pilyeon
to get his hands on that money.
Yes.
I see you're enjoying yourself.
You're the one who
barged in without a call,
so you'll have to wait a moment.
And should this single move
ruin the entire game?
I never make such reckless moves.
Then, I'll let you choose.
Either accept the offer
I made you in the past,
or make the worst possible move
you could think of.
Still looking for bribe money, I see...
I'm well aware
that your days are numbered.
So what your last move
ends up being is crucial.
It can either help you protect
everything you've achieved over the years,
or else...
consign you to a miserable demise,
deprived of all your money and fame.
Seems you don't know that those
who have already lost everything...
can be much scarier than people
who have everything to lose.
What?
As you said, my days are numbered.
I'm fighting with my back to the wall.
Since I can look death in
the eyes without fearing it.
Did I make myself clear?
You will never take away
a single penny from me!
Need I remind you
of certain old practices...
You know,
beheading criminals
after digging up their corpse.
Your death will not be the end of it.
Since all I need is your fortune,
and to get my hands on it.
So watch out,
even if it's from six feet under.
See what's the price to pay
for daring to play with fire.
Sir!
Wake up!
Sir!!
Sir!
You must go through surgery right now.
When it comes to scars on my body,
this is more than enough.
Even if the Pearly Gates await me,
I want to go free of any more scars.
Sir...
I've had it with this.
I'll have to go home.
Sir.
Jo Pilyeon is trying to get
his hands on your fortune.
You must survive, Sir.
You can never let Jo Pilyeon
take all that money away from you.
You know what keeps me going these days?
It is neither my painkillers
nor any other medicine.
Jo Pilyeon...
That Jo Pilyeon is pushing me to fight
back even more than those cancer cells!
I have no intention
of letting him defeat me.
And even if this brings my demise,
the dagger of revenge
will not pierce my heart,
but that of Jo Pilyeon.
You just wait.
Thank you, Deputy.
I've heard from Director Kim.
That Soojeong's song getting
radio airtime was all thanks to you.
That?
I just didn't want to see
such talent be buried that way,
so it's nothing.
Still, I'll tell Soojeong
to come pay her respects.
Ahh... That... That won't be necessary.
Why, did you tell her I was helping you?
No. Not yet...
Don't tell her, then.
I can't stand burdensome
situations like that.
So you told Director Kim
she was your niece?
Then... Why don't you make
her your niece for real?
I'm a busy man.
Let's just end it at that.
If you prefer it that way,
fine with me.
Director...
Why did you miss this
evening's vocal training?
I apologize.
What are you, already acting like a singer
just because you were on the radio?
But... Di...Director...
It's not that...
Can't you even keep her under control?
It's not his fault.
I'm the only one to blame, Director.
Actually, Soojeong has been selling
her albums in Myeong-Dong all day.
What?!
Selling her albums?!
She's been working so hard,
fearing you'd incur losses because of her...
I couldn't bear to stop her...
I apologize, Director.
I'm sorry.
Real stars never beg
the masses for acceptance.
They make the masses go crazy for them.
Weak sales right off the bat
is nothing you should worry about.
If you have time to waste that way,
invest it on improving your image.
That's what you must do
for my sake, is that clear?
I apologize, Director.
But I wanted to overcome this challenge
without having to rely on you.
What are you saying, that you'll
keep selling albums on the street?
It won't negatively impact
my image like you fear.
And I'll follow my training
schedule thoroughly.
Please, give me permission.
But if the results aren't satisfactory,
I might completely give up on you.
Will you still keep obsessing over it?
Yes. I want to do it.
Fine, then.
I'll let you do
as you please for a month.
Thank you, Director.
No need to thank me.
Because if you fail,
you and I are history.
Our next song is one of the
most popular hits these days.
Here is new singer Cha Soojeong,
with "Under the Spotlight."
Nice, isn't it?
Wait.
Our Miju is great!
"And he will remain hidden
at the bottom of my heart."
Oppa...
You're messing up all the beats.
Why...
Didn't I, like, get it right?
Do it right, will you?
Seonbaenim, what's the matter?
She sounds just like my sister...
Miju always dreamed
of becoming a singer, too.
Singers often use stage names,
should I look into it?
It's the organizational
chart of Baekpa's group.
I still couldn't fully
figure out all the details.
This should be more than enough
to make its foundation shake.
I know I'm in no position
to tell you this,
but should those
foundations start shaking,
political circles will bear
the brunt as well.
As you well know, this "underground economy"
is used by politicians for their money-laund...
Biting more than you
can chew, aren't we...
I apologize, Congressman.
Call the Blue House Security Service,
and get the car ready.
All right.
Yes, Sir.
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'll take full responsibility,
so proceed as instructed!
Is that clear?
Useless fools...
They owe their livelihood to the state,
and still fear a bunch of loan sharks?
Who are you?
We are conducting a tax investigation.
Why did the revenue office send you?
- Search the entire place.
- Yes.
Eight places in Myeong-Dong
alone were investigated.
And all belonging to
our affiliated members.
It's clear that they're targeting us.
All the complaints within the group
are being directed at Baekpa.
We must find a solution right away,
but with him in
such condition as of late...
And he's not going to get better.
What are you trying to say?
Because even the hospital
has given up on trying to treat him.
Sir...
Come on in.
You came home early tonight.
Let me do it for you.
All right.
Do you...
remember the very first time...
we met?
Back then, you were in
really terrible condition.
You were so drunk
that I had to help you to sleep,
but then I heard
you cry the entire night.
From the very start,
what I was going for was your money belt.
I sneaked in the morning after
and took it on my way out,
but it was filled with so
much money that it startled me.
I purposely added even more money
while you were sleeping.
Since wherever you went, you at
least needed a roof over your head.
I really thought it was all you had.
If you hadn't come back that day,
you would have gained yourself a house,
but then we wouldn't have met.
Why were you...
so kind to me?
That's just what people call destiny.
The answer to that question...
is something even Buddha
himself wouldn't know.
I'm sorry, Sir...
I have no right to serve you.
I swore that I would bring you
peace of mind to the very end...
Please forgive me, Sir.
But look.
Look at whose hands are
comforting me in my final moments.
These warm hands of yours...
are more precious to me
than all the money in the world.
Sir...
Don't cry, darling.
You've done enough.
I'm thankful, on the contrary.
My only true regret...
was finding out that there is
something more precious than money...
when it was much too late.
If only I had realized
that a little earlier,
I would have been much happier.
Check!
Director Ju, check...
Checkmate, I'm afraid!
Why did it get so tangled in here?!
I guess you'll have to give
him another thousand won.
These days you're helping out
a great deal with groceries.
Ahh... This...
Aigoo... Youngguk.
What are those eyes of yours for?
See over there?
Your cannon is still free.
Ohh... The cannon.
There you go.
- Aigoo... Chairman.
- Aigoo... Chairman!
Yes.
- Urban Development...
- Chairman Hwang Taeseop?
Who am I speaking to?
I'm Lee Seongmo.
And how did you
find out about this place?
There is something I've been
preparing for a very long time.
It might become the weapon that
shocks the current regime into submission.
So, this thing you've been preparing...
Open it.
This account...
That account...
will become the perfect opportunity
to turn Jo Pilyeon's world upside down.
But...
Don't you value your life?
The moment this is exposed...
Didn't you put your life
on the line to kill Jo Pilyeon, too?
Tell me...
What do you want me to do?
I think we need to have a word.
I'm in a hurry,
so it'll have to be quick.
So the private lending... Sure,
let's call it "underground economy."
You know how much money
circulates within those circles?
No less than 18 percent of our GDP!
Why beat around the bush
and make things complicated?
Just say that you have complaints
against the current tax investigations.
What?!
There are plenty of, as you call them,
"complaints" about you in the political arena.
Baekpa is really something, all right.
But I'm afraid he's not going to
affect my convictions in the slightest.
Convictions?!
If someone makes that much
money through illegal means,
it's only natural that he should
pay taxes like everyone else.
Think I can't see through it,
that those convictions only begin
whenever your pockets are filled enough?
I'd watch my language if I were you.
Our country is in turmoil
right now. It's a mess.
Throwing the economy in the grinder
as well is not what I'd call wise.
You know what Baekpa's
greatest mistake was?
Trying to challenge this
country's highest authority.
What?!
And you'd be that highest authority?
That's what my duties state.
I know how much of an honor it is.
That's my conviction.
That fella...
This country is a mess...
Dealing with politics these days
feels like a useless chore.
I can't take Jo Pilyeon's
arrogance any longer.
So?
We'll have to destroy him
politically once and for all.
Look, Congressman Min.
Don't you know who's
backing Jo Pilyeon right now?
Unless this world changes first,
he's untouchable.
Congressmen.
Why don't you let me join the dance?
I have a secret weapon
that will shock you.
A secret weapon?
And what would that be?
I cannot reveal it quite yet.
Isn't something like that
used at the very crucial moment?
Aren't you just putting
on airs for nothing?
If I give you a condition,
would you believe me?
A condition?
I want to enter politics.
What... Politics?!
You want to become a congressman?
I'd appreciate your help.
I'm sure that the weapon
I have in my hands...
more than warrants your help.
Still believe I'm just putting on airs?
All in.
Listen.
I think it's time to settle your debts?!
And how much is that...
Forget that, and bring me
another ten million.
Follow me to the other room, please.
I will lend you the money.
You better stay put!
Uh? I'll be right back with that money.
Spare me... Please...
I... I'll pay your money back.
I can just pay it back, can't I?!
So your house is in
your mother's name, right?
So how about it?
Will you give us the house,
or give up your body?
Not the house.
That's not mine, it's my mother's...
Then compensate by giving yourself up.
Give me some time.
I'll do whatever it
takes to find that money.
There would be a way
to write off that debt...
And what is that? Tell me.
As long as you don't touch my house,
I'll do everything you ask!
You have a half-sister, don't you?
Hwang Jeongyeon.
You can go.
I feel awkward, too.
Ever since I was
moved to a new business area,
Director Yoo forced me to take them along.
But what do I owe your call to?
The tax investigations
you're going through...
were orchestrated by Jo Pilyeon.
This is a fight between money and power.
Whomever wins, you'll both
suffer the consequences.
I'm sure we will.
But neither Baekpa nor
Director Yoo will ever surrender.
This battle is like
walking on a tightrope.
A wrong step will make you lose your
balance, and fall down all at once.
When even someone like me realizes that,
there's no way they wouldn't.
I'd prefer if you stayed out of this.
My life depends on this, too.
And how are you going to handle Jo Pilyeon?
Now that the branches have started
wavering, he'll attack the trunk.
You'll become a target of his as well.
But I know how to stop him.
What?
I'm hungry?!
I can order something, right?
Hwang Jeongyeon and I
have a lot left to settle.
But with those stiffs sticking
to her now, it's not so easy.
If you help me out just this once,
I can write off a
month's worth of interests.
How about it?
Afraid I'll say no.
What?!
No?!
Make that three months.
You saw right.
But why is Jeongshik riding with him?
Are you all right, Sir?
Nobody within the organization
can learn of my condition.
Have you found a solution?
What solution are you looking for?
One that will make those
investigations stop, of course.
How surprising...
Our organization's very
survival depends on this.
So let's hear proposals
that will at least sound tempting!
We're counting on you, Sir.
What are you, children?
Sir!
When will you stop acting like
spoiled children crying for their toy?!
We have no time to waste.
Give us some kind of solution!
The solution is actually very simple.
Are you saying that you have one?
Exactly, Sir.
There is a way to solve all this.
Open the doors.
Sir...
I said open them!
Go ahead.
Tell us what this solution of yours is.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Whose idea was that?
You let Hwang Jeongyeon do that to us?
If you want, I could get rid of her.
If things go according
to Jo Pilyeon's plans,
our fight will become even harder.
What happened between you and Jo Pilyeon?
What will he say when
he finds out about Wooju?
Can you lend me some money?
And if I could find your birth mother,
how much would you give me?
The moment they learn that
I'll soon pass away,
many of them will try to betray me.
Can you protect them for me?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com