Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 27 -
- Then...
- See you again.
Yes?
Hangang Construction, right?
Yes, that's right.
Who am I speaking to?
Manbo Construction here.
I'm Director of Planning
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Is the president there?
I have a business proposal for him,
can you get him on the phone?
Hello?
Are you listening?
- Aren't you picking up the phone?
- Hey... Don't!
Hello?
Am I speaking to Hangang Construction?
Y...es...
H...How may I help you?
I'm Manbo Construction
Chief of Planning Jo Minwoo.
Hey.. Hey!
It's Jo Minwoo... Jo Minwoo!
Manbo Construction.
What should I do?
Should I just hang up?
I'd like to discuss a contract
proposal with the president.
We don't do business
with Manbo Construction.
Excuse me?
Don't call us again.
Hello?
Listen!
Hey... What if they come looking for us?
If they learn you're alive,
it'll be trouble.
They still aren't picking up the phone?
Hangang Construction said
they won't deal with us.
What's the reason?
I can't say.
Looks like I'll have to
meet their president firsthand.
No need to do that.
I'll handle that, so keep
checking the construction site.
It would be much wiser if
you left this issue to me, and...
You can't predict what kind of
conditions they'll be throwing at us.
Think that is something you
could decide on your own?
As you prefer, then.
Shideok, you go meet him.
Me?
There's no reason why a small
firm like Hangang Construction...
would refuse to do business with us.
Meet with their president
and find out what's going on.
All right.
So the area under our control
is here, here, and here.
And the contract we just
signed today would be this area.
If we keep this up, won't we
end up dominating this entire area?
Not here.
This is... what...
Manbo Construction's?!
Forget all the rest.
- South Gyeongsang Province -
Once we get our hands
on this, it's game over.
We unplugged the phone earlier, who...
Had to order lunch,
so I plugged it back.
Yes?
Hyung!
Gangmo, I don't think taking
those highway projects...
away from Manbo Construction
will be that easy.
There is another big shot
watching Hwang Taeseop's back.
Commissioner of the Seoul
City Council, Han Myeongseok.
You knew?
Yeah.
I'm well aware of all the difficulties
you're facing with the highway project.
Hearing such kind words from someone
like you can only comfort me.
Well... Should the need arise, we can
discuss possible budget increments.
Commissioner.
Thank you.
It's a golf club membership.
It's in the outskirts of Seoul,
and the view is wonderful.
Here... Shall we have a drink?
Sure.
They might have
differing political views,
but have been on good terms
for quite some time.
As long as Commissioner Han
keeps his post,
Chairman Hwang
will be protected as well.
Is there any way I could help you?
You'll already have enough on your plate
worrying about Jo Pilyeon's elections.
I'll take care of Manbo Construction.
Do you have a plan?
I'll create a rift between
Hwang Taeseop and Han Myeongseok.
- That's easier said than...
- Their political views differ,
but despite that,
they're still on good terms...
Isn't it interesting, Hyung?
Be careful, Gangmo.
You can't expose your identity, yet.
And that's when the fat lady sings!
Aigoo, don't tell me...
It's a checkmate, you've lost.
I knew that move would work.
Ahh... Look at what I have to witness...
What do you call this path? Uh?
I could just go for the kill, like this.
Ready... Done!
Wait... I didn't see that before?
When did it suddenly...
- Go back one move.
- Go back what, you old fart?
- Old fart?! To an elder, you sorry little...
- How can you pull such tricks, you old fart?
- You really... Ehh! Damned old fart!
- Didn't you have parents, you insolent twat?
Excuse me.
I'm here on behalf of Manbo
Construction for the contract issue.
Ahh... Is that so?
Let's see...
Where was the contract again?
Hey... Hey!
Get up, you fool.
So... You're going to
deal with us, after all?
Here it is. This contract...
You give it a good read,
seal right here, and it's a done deal.
Then, all I have to do is seal it here?
That's why they call it a contract.
Want to write an essay before you sign?
Right... Hey... Hey!
Hey! The hell
are you doing down there?
Get up... I said get up!
What are you doing?
Just in case,
I brought the director's seal!
So I can just seal here?
- So you're here on an errand?
- Yes.
You did look a tad on the soggy side...
Can I borrow your inkpad a moment?
No can do!
The hell is wrong with you?
Out!
We're not doing
business with you, get out!
Pa...Park Sotae?!
Saute or Flambe, we're not doing
business with you. Get out of here.
Get the hell out, quick!
Out... Out!
What is this?
What are you doing here?
You little... I'm one of Hangang
Construction's founding directors!
Hyungnim, Hyungnim!
We must kick him out!
Wait a moment.
Why, is this gentleman here a
particularly bad person, or something?
He's much worse than me!
- Even worse than you?!
- Yes!
Then he really must
be deluxe twat material!
Pick him up!
We must kick him out!
Out... Out...
You little bastard, how dare you...
Serves you right, you twat!
We're never going to
deal with Manbo Construction,
so don't even think about prancing
around here again, is that clear?
Hey... Park Sotae!
Park Sotae!
Hey! Park Sotae!
Open the door!
Until I get to meet your boss
I'm not moving, just so you know!
Open this damned door, Park Sotae!
My boss is abroad on a business trip?!
So don't even fart
in our direction, you twat.
If I spot you around here again,
next time I'll pick up water from the toilet!
Have no use for this,
so you can have it.
You little...
Park Sotae! You're dead.
Yes?
How did it go?
Did you meet the president?
They said he's abroad
on a business trip.
What?
But that Park Sotae is working here.
Park Sotae?
The one who framed Gangmo?
Yes.
They could have lied
about his business trip.
Keep waiting there, and if
anything happens, give me a call.
I'm not someone you can impress
with a good performance alone.
I don't plan to only
bank on royalties, either.
So your future business plans?
We now plan to join forces
with other corporations.
Do you already have
anyone in mind, by chance?
Manbo Construction would be perfect.
I could introduce them to you myself.
Manbo Construction is the sole
exception in our partnership plans.
And what's the reason?
Because they lead the sector.
What's that supposed to mean?
If you want to run a successful
business, it's natural you should...
You could never defeat a giant...
as long as you grovel at their feet.
So you want to defeat
Manbo Construction?
And you believe it's a realistic fight?
If you'll excuse me, I'll get going.
Will you just let him go for it?
What if I let him?
We are one of Manbo Construction's
major shareholders.
What are you, afraid that young fella
will rise above Manbo Construction?
It's not what I meant...
It's a hopeless fight.
However, that fighting spirit
moving him to fight rocks with eggs...
is quite intriguing.
But then it's only natural that the
eggs will break, along with his company.
If he goes belly up using my money,
he will dearly regret it.
Let him fight on his own.
We'll have to wait and see how
he faces off with that giant.
As you wish, Sir.
Did you really come here to study?
Chief!
Let's concentrate, shall we?
Forget that and follow me.
Hey...
Can't a woman eat
a little more gracefully?
Ehh... Everyone eats the same way.
What is eating "gracefully," then?
Anyhow, see what happens
if you fail this test.
Ahh... That's so dirty...
How can you use the same chopstick...
You can't eat fish, can you?
See? You haven't touched it once.
Who said I can't eat this?
I just don't like, that's all.
You're really spoiled.
What?
I can't stand people
who only eat what they want.
And you have the guts
to blame my chopsticks...
Hey... Who said I can't eat this?
Then, give it a try.
See? You can't!
How can an adult be fussy about fish?
If you don't like it, then never mind.
Guess we won't get to eat together
all that often, from now on.
I'll do it!
I said I will.
How is it?
Tasty, isn't it?
What's wrong?
Was it a spine?
I'm sorry...
I didn't do that on purpose...
You... Finish this and go study.
I'll hit your palm for
every answer you get wrong.
How much is it?
Yes... 6,000 won.
It's almost his birthday?!
- Library Card -
Jo Minwoo
ID: 580816 (DoB) - 1634715
What is it?
Ahh... You dropped this.
So you live here?
Yes.
What's your home number?
Why are you asking?
So I can spy on you and see
whether you're studying or not.
Chief.
Why?
Want me to mind my business?
I didn't mean that...
Fell asleep?
Uh?!
Doesn't look too safe to
walk around here at night.
I'll drive you home every
evening after your studies.
By the way...
What would you like?
Anything you'd like to have,
for instance.
Why, if I want something,
you'll give it to me?
Yes.
If it's anything I can do, I will.
Forget it.
Then again...
How could there be anything
someone like you lacks...
What I mean is just
focus on your studies.
Go home now.
Yes.
See you.
Whenever I'm with you,
I can't study anyway...
But why am I blushing,
and my heart beats so fast?
Just leave it here.
But it's headed inside?!
I said just leave it here.
Let's see how long you can
keep starving in there, uh?
That twat is eating
our jjajangmyeon again...
Fat-ass pig...
How many servings did he
stuff himself with, already?!
I'm dying of hunger in here,
I can't let it slide.
What are you going to do?
Wait... Wait! Don't!
I can't take it anymore, you fool!
Will you just starve trapped in here?
I told you! If he finds out
about Gangmo, we're screwed!
Then let's just
order a hundred servings.
So the pig can keep stuffing
himself until he croaks.
Why?
I know his appetite quite well,
and if we wait for him to pass out,
we'll first croak of old age.
Aigoo... I'm so hungry...
Hello?
Ohh... Gangmo?
What?
Shideok?
He's eating jjajangmyeon non-stop.
What can we do?
Don't mention me, and just let him be.
When I'm done here,
I'll come back and deal with him.
Here.
It's the newspaper
that recently hired me.
- Orient Economy Daily -
Go ahead and tell me, Gangmo.
What's my task?
There must be a reason
why you asked me to find work...
at a finance newspaper.
It's data on Manbo
Construction's highway project.
It should be enough for an article.
Gangmo.
Will you promise me just one thing?
That you'll never turn into
a monster like Jo Pilyeon,
just for the sake of success.
You're helping me exactly because
you know that'll never happen.
Right...
How did it go?
Have you found his whereabouts?
I think we're approaching
this the wrong way.
Should I just go undercover
in Cheongju by myself?
We have no time for that.
We must catch him
before the elections.
So how should we proceed?
I need to go somewhere.
What is this?
It's evidence that Jo Pilyeon
broke election law in his dealings.
How many candidates in this
election could be cleared of that?
Bring this up and you'll
only become a laughingstock.
But if it turns out that it was Jo Pilyeon
who ordered the assault on those people,
I guess it'd be a little different?
Did you catch him?
We can't find any traces
of his whereabouts.
There's no hope.
Unless we catch him and he testifies
about Jo Pilyeon's stratagem,
it will be difficult to turn
these elections in our favor.
Among this data is evidence that
Jo bribed the ANSP Chief of Support.
Chief Oh of the ANSP?
And?
To get him, we should make
Jo Pilyeon sway in some way...
Will you help us out with that?
Tell me.
What can I do for you?
Come on in.
Sorry for bothering you at this time.
The elections are
right around the corner,
do you have time to spend here?
Evidence of Jo Pilyeon's
activities breaking election law.
You know that he was behind that
assault on those displaced people, right?
What is all this corny nonsense?
Think you two can toss all
your dirty laundry to me?
According to this data, turns out
Jo Pilyeon tossed you a little money?!
What?!
I hope you're not involved
with that assault in any way?
Listen, Min Honggi!
Who is this man?
He's a gang boss with
seven prior convictions.
Seems like you might be
taking us lightly,
but I can throw you in the can for
breaking election law right away!
You know your director and
I are very close, don't you?
Shall we give it a go and
see whose head rolls first?
Think such pathetic threats
will work with me?
Aigoo... So you were here.
Long time no see, Chief Oh.
And what brings you here, Congressman?
I was next door, having a
drink with the ANSP director.
Listen, Candidate Min.
When you're done here,
come let me know.
I've heard rumors a senior ANSP executive
was helping an opposition candidate...
I hope it won't turn out to be you.
Sit.
Here...
Whether I'll go next door
only depends on you.
Actually, what I was about
to ask you is very simple.
That clearance squad boss
who helped Jo Pilyeon.
That Choi Taewook...
All you need to do is order his arrest.
Is it just that?
You have my word.
Nothing else.
Here, have a drink.
So you can derail Jo Pilyeon's
campaign and help Candidate Min win?
Just wait and see.
That's right!
The ANSP needs to be filled
with people like you, indeed.
I'll get going, Sir.
Why, already leaving?
Min Honggi should be here any moment?!
I'll leave you two alone tonight.
I will visit you again soon.
All right.
- Hong Gipyo -
It's been quite a long time
since Chairman Hong passed away.
Was it you?
The one who asked me to meet here?
After Hwang Taeseop gained control
of the construction committee,
it indeed seems that all the biggest
projects went to Manbo Construction.
When Chairman Hong was leading
the committee, those were the days.
It was our golden age.
Can't you turn back the page
and return to the committee of old?
Trying to contend with Chairman Hwang...
is beyond my abilities.
Will you join forces with me, then?
I will not share my new method
with any other committee member.
So you will sign an
exclusive deal with us?
Not a deal, but a partnership.
It will be the perfect opportunity
to surpass Manbo Construction.
But the more I look at you,
you really seem familiar.
Right...
I remember now.
You worked under Chairman Hwang...
That Lee Gangmo who killed
Hong Gipyo and did time in prison.
I wasn't the one
who killed Chairman Hong.
What?
Other people are responsible,
and deserve to pay for it.
What are you trying to say?
Chairman Hwang Taeseop's son,
Hwang Jeongshik, is the one
who killed Chairman Hong.
And of course Chairman Hwang
covered up the truth.
Is that really the truth?
Were I the real culprit,
I would have never met you this way.
It's natural you'd bear a grudge
against Manbo Construction.
- Ohh... Come on in.
- Seongmo is here.
- Seongo, you're here?
- Bring us some tea.
Sure. Wait a moment.
Here... Sit.
So, what brings you here so early?
Have you heard the news?
What news?
The ANSP ordered an investigation
into the clearance area assault.
So who was behind the order?
I think Min Honggi might have
gotten the ANSP top brass involved.
So he plans to continue with
his usual tricks until the very end.
The ANSP is currently after that
clearance squad leader, Choi Taewook.
If they ever get
the chance to catch him...
Even the police is on his trail,
but still no clues whatsoever.
I don't think you need to worry.
According to our intelligence,
he seemed to be hiding in Cheongju?
If he stays in one place for
too long, it'll be dangerous.
I'll keep reporting any development,
so watch his back carefully.
All right.
Thanks.
I'll get going.
I think it would be wise
to move him somewhere else.
Since we're there,
just send him back to Seoul.
What?
Place him where we can see him.
So if worst comes to worst,
we can always get rid of him.
All right.
It's him.
What is it?
Take this and come back to Seoul.
Yes, all right.
- Watch your back.
- Yes.
Who are you people?
Let me go!
Let go!
Follow us quietly.
You're making a big mistake.
Really?!
Hello?
Could you pass me to the chairman?
What kind of fool
is calling at this hour?
Aigoo... Beats me.
Take it, quick.
Ehh... Really...
Hello?
Commissioner Han Myeongseok
joined forces with Chairman Cheon,
and they're planning to
bring you down together.
Wh...What?!
Who are you?
Who are you, to make
this kind of call at...
Who the hell is it?
Hello?
Ohh Ohh... Really...
What on earth are you people doing?
- Manbo Construction's Highway
Project Goes 30 Percent Over Budget -
What were you doing while
this article was published?
Someone might have tried to
harm us through this article.
What are you trying to say?
That they made them publish
this article on purpose?
We haven't completed
even half of the construction.
Unless someone was trying to
manipulate public opinion...
And who would be trying to do that?
I'll deal with the press, Dad.
Also, why is Hangang Construction
refusing to share their new method with us?
Isn't that obvious?
They're trying to gain more leverage to
then ask for more favorable conditions later.
I'll take my boys and deal
with them once and for...
Jeongyeon, you go meet them firsthand.
Whatever their conditions,
you must get that contract signed.
Yes, Chairman.
The City Council just
requested a meeting with you.
Commissioner Han?
Guess it's about additional
budget resources.
It's not that.
I think they read that article.
So?
Are you telling me they're
refusing to increase our budget?
We'll have to go and find out.
I have an appointment
in the afternoon,
so Jeongyeon and Chief Jo
will have to go on my behalf.
All right.
You leave as well.
Director Ju.
Dig into what's going on
between Commissioner Han...
and Chairman Cheon Suman
of Gwangmyeong Construction.
Why are you suddenly asking that?
I got this really
upsetting call last night.
It suggested that Commissioner Han joined
forces with Gwangmyeong Construction,
and that they're trying to
bring Manbo Construction down.
You know that Commissioner Han
wouldn't be capable of that.
I do believe so myself,
but who was behind that call...
Wait!
The situation is urgent, so I was
hoping the chairman would come?
I apologize.
Something urgent came up.
If that's the case,
then I'll get straight to the point.
Because the company's situation was
exposed by the press in this manner,
we will no longer be able to increase
your budget for the highway construction.
Commissioner.
You know about Hangang Construction's
new construction method, right?
If they share their technology,
then I think the problem
would be solved pretty quickly?!
We are trying to
approach them ourselves,
but for whatever reason,
they refuse to do business with us.
Whatever the case, try to convince them.
We're barely stopping the Department of
Public Works' calls for on-site supervision.
All right.
Didn't you say you'd take care
of contacting Hangang Construction?
Their president is currently
abroad on a business trip.
Have you even looked into what
kind of person we're dealing with?
We couldn't dig any background
info on him whatsoever.
I'll give it a try, then.
I already sent someone
to Hangang Construction,
so we will soon get something.
Did I make you wait?
There was a little traffic on the way.
- Let's go in.
- Right.
And who is this gentleman?
Let me introduce him.
He's James Lee, an expat.
He's the president of
Hangang Construction.
Hangang Construction?
Ahh... The ones who developed
that new construction method?
I apologize, I should have
introduced myself earlier.
Ahh... Don't say that.
I was looking forward
to meeting you myself.
We just signed a cooperation deal.
Ahh... You did?
Here... Let's have a seat.
I must thank you for
the estimates you sent me.
It's really a remarkable project,
particularly considering the reduced costs.
Then, can you hand over Manbo
Construction's highway project to us?
Well... If I may be blunt
and get right to the point...
I'm afraid that would be
ethically problematic.
Is that so?
Right... Chairman Cheon.
I'd like a word in private
with him, if I may.
What?
Sure.
Then...
As commissioner, there is
a favor I'd like to ask you.
Go ahead and tell me.
Help out Manbo Construction.
May I ask you just one thing?
I'm curious about the reason you
support Manbo Construction so much.
There is no particular reason.
I'm merely fulfilling my duties as
commissioner of the City Council.
If that is truly the reason, then I'd
prefer if you didn't help them at all.
What are you implying with that?
A close acquaintance of mine
works under Candidate Jo Pilyeon.
But according to him, should
Candidate Jo win the elections,
he plans to remove anyone involved
with Min Honggi from their positions.
I heard your name
was on that list as well.
Isn't Chairman Hwang Taeseop
Candidate Jo's most faithful supporter?
I... believe we should always
separate politics and business.
I'm surprised to hear that?
I always thought politics
and money go hand in hand?!
President Lee, what I was saying...
If you're asking me to join
forces with Manbo Construction,
I might be inclined to do so.
But I leave the decision
to you, so let me know.
Excuse me.
- The 3rd Han River Bridge by Hyeeun -
The river flows under the
3rd Han River bridge.
Carrying along your dreams and mine,
And our hearts along with them.
That's not how it ends.
That's how you do it, hands up.
No, higher.
Hello?
It's me.
Why... did you call?
Why?!
Told you I'd check on you
out of the blue.
If you're just going to scold me,
you don't need to bother.
What were you doing?
I... was studying, why?
Don't lie to me.
Why would studying
make you gasp for air?
After studying, I only
practiced singing a lil' bit.
Already forgot when your test is?
Even if I didn't want to call you,
you'd force me anyway,
by acting like this.
I'll be calling again in an hour,
so start studying.
Are we clear?
Yes...
Minwoo.
Take a look at this young lady.
Who's this?
She's the daughter of Hwaseong Electric's
chairman, and the matchmaker set up a meeting.
Do you want me to go
to a marriage meeting?
Yeah.
She's a hundred times better than
Jeongyeon in any possible way.
And this has only happened because your
father is likely to win the elections.
Forget it.
Forget what?
They're orders from your father,
so you must meet her. Got it?
Here.
Hey.
Just because your precious
Chief told you to study,
you stick your nose up those books
all day without blinking once?
Of course.
He's even tutoring me,
so I should listen.
Chief Jo is even tutoring you?!
Yeah.
When did it start between you two?
Uh?!
When did he confess that he likes you.
It's not what you think.
And Chief Jo doesn't like me.
How can you be so silly?
With that temper of his,
think he'd tutor you and drive
you home, unless he liked you?
That's just...
How about you?
About what?
Whether you like Chief Jo.
You do!
Right?
I knew it!
Then again...
If you didn't like that kind
of man, you'd be insane.
Just believe me, I can
assure you Chief Jo likes you.
So be the first to confess to him.
Me?!
Ehh... No way.
If you lose that kind of catch,
you'll regret it your entire life!
If you can't say it with words,
go with a present.
A meaningful one, at that.
Is there such a thing?
I worked part-time
at a department store.
I heard this there,
and it seems like necktie pins...
are what women give to men
when they're about to confess?!
Pretty...
- To Chief Jo Minwoo -
Happy Birthday
Let's have some coffee.
A marriage meeting?!
So, what, you're going?
Then again, if it's Hwaseong
Electric, no reason to refuse?
Wow... Jo Minwoo!
So you're soon becoming
in-laws with tycoons?!
But weren't you dating that
country chick, these days?
Who said I was dating her?
I'm just helping her out of compassion.
Really?
So leave her to me, will you?
I'll wipe that country feel out
of her, and turn her into a looker.
Do whatever you want.
Really?
So we're clear on that?
I can have her, right?
Hey, Hwang Jeongshik.
Why do you keep
treating her like some obj...
What's wrong with you?
What... Was country chick here?
Ehh... You really!
Yes. If it's anything
I can do, I will.
Jo Minwoo...
You must be really crazy.
You bastard.
No need to show everyone
you're better than them.
Why is he looking down
on people that way?
Did I ever ask him to help me?
He can't even eat fish,
and acts all fussy with food.
Jo Minwoo!
Get out of the way.
- Hey... Miju.
- I said out of the way!
I know...
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm sorry.
Happy now?
Shouldn't have said what?
What I meant...
Just, all of it.
If my parents had been alive,
I'd be the most precious
daughter in the world to them?!
Hey...
Need to cry for that?
I know how great you are,
but you still shouldn't
treat people like objects.
I apologize.
But I never treated you like an object.
While talking with Jeongshik,
it just came out like that.
Also, if I'd ever considered you an object,
would I come here to apologize?
Thank you for everything
you've done for me all this time.
Why are you suddenly thanking me?
Just thought I should at least
bid you farewell one last time.
Last?
So you're not going to see me again?
I don't want any more
of your compassion.
I looked into it.
Who is it?
Who is scheming behind our backs to
get his hands on our highway project?
It's Chairman Cheon Suman
of Gwangmyeong Construction.
What... Chairman Cheon?!
The City Council informed us he signed an
exclusive deal with Hangang Construction.
So it was Chairman Cheon who
put pressure on the commissioner?
This doesn't feel right...
Chairman Cheon wouldn't have the
guts to scheme something like this?!
Listen, Chairman Cheon!
Can fellow committee members
do this to each other?
I'm well aware of your position.
But I did nothing wrong.
You didn't?!
Throwing your spoon on someone else's
table is doing nothing wrong?
Commissioner Han asked me for
estimates and I gave them to him,
and since Hangang Construction
proposed an exclusive deal, I signed it.
What?
Then, are you telling me it was
Commissioner Han who introduced them to you?
It's not like I was trying to create
a rift between fellow committee members,
but I certainly couldn't resist
the commissioner's decision.
I was put in an awkward position myself.
Why would the commissioner...
Seems that he didn't like the idea that
the committee was supporting Candidate Jo.
He even offered me the possibility
of leading the committee.
Han Myeongseok...
You bastard!
Right as planned, Hwang Taeseop
started suspecting Commissioner Han.
I don't know how the
situation will develop,
but I'm counting on you.
We can't just blindly trust
everything he says, Dad.
I received a call the other night, suggesting
that Commissioner Han would betray me.
Who called you?
I can't figure out who that could be.
Whether he was a friend or foe.
If Commissioner Han truly
abandoned us, then what?
Once Jo Pilyeon wins the
elections, it's game over.
Because Han Myeongseok will be the
first head to roll for betraying me.
Ahh... Also.
So Hangang Construction's
president is currently overseas?
Yes.
There's no time to waste,
so at least go meet with the other
employees there and win them over.
What's this, some nursing home?
Coming here to stuff himself
all day and then doze off.
Aigoo... What else is new...
- Gangmo.
- Hey.
So, what, did it go well in Seoul?
Yes.
Hey... Wake up.
I said wake up, you useless fool.
Ehh... Really.
G...Gangmo...
I... I'm not dreaming, right?
A pinch and you'll know, you fool.
How have you been?
You... You were alive?
I missed you, Shideok.
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
- Cheonan, South Chungcheong -
Munhwa-Dong, Dongnam-Gu
San 727 - 2nd Street
You're here, Chief?
Have you looked into
Hangang Construction?
Yes, their president is a certain
James Lee, an expat from the US.
James Lee?!
Those mudflats Lee Gangmo owned
are under James Lee's name.
What's the matter?
I'll have to head to Hangang
Construction's offices right away.
Get my car.
Yes, Chief.
I know you bear a grudge against
Jeongshik and the chairman,
but shouldn't you at least
tell Jeongyeon that you're alive?
Don't tell her.
You must not let her know.
Are you really plotting to
bring Manbo Construction down?
Manbo Construction's heir is Jeongyeon.
That can only mean you'll
have to fight with Jeongyeon.
If that's where things go,
I guess I'll have to.
Listen to you... Lee Gangmo!
Do you know why Jeongyeon
has been living that way?
It was only to avenge you!
To make Minwoo and Jeongshik
pay for what they did to you.
She even caught aphasia,
shocked about your death.
Seeing her struggle so much by
herself on that construction site...
It's so hard to bear, it brings me tears.
Gangmo...
You loved Jeongyeon.
You still love her!
Stop talking about Jeongyeon,
I don't want to hear it.
Shideok.
You'll help me out, right?
What drunken sack of cow shit
taught you how to drive?
You fool! Where do you think
you are, driving like that?
Know how much this cost?
You...
What's with all the cars today?
Gangmo!
Jeongyeon is here!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
We came to the conclusion that you're no
longer able to complete the construction.
Think I won't be
able to get you sacked?
Why don't you give it a try, then?
If we want him to
confess against Jo Pilyeon,
we must force him to join our side.
That James might in fact be Lee Gangmo.
I'm sure I saw Gangmo.
I have no doubt it was him.
I need your consolation today.
Try to console me, will you?
You liar...
Hey... Forget it, then!
Forget I ever mentioned it!
I'll introduce our new member, then.
I'm president of Hangang Construction,
Lee Gangmo.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com