This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 20 -
I can't live like that.
I'll get revenge my own way.
And what's your way?
Destroying Manbo Construction.
When I'm done with them,
they'll face a miserable,
pitiful downfall.
Is anything the matter?
Everyone tells me I make them
feel happier when they drink with me.
Pretty lady.
Go get us some more ice.
Ice?
There's plenty here?!
All right.
I shouldn't have told Gangmo.
You had no choice.
Don't you know yourself?
How living with a grudge
can destroy you inside,
the loneliness and sorrow
it subjects you to.
I wanted to bear that
painful fate all by myself.
Gangmo.
You've had it hard.
This gentleman here is the lawyer
who will be representing you in court.
You're a first-time offender,
and, considering the situation,
it could be ruled as manslaughter,
so we could get you out in four years...
No, even much less than that.
I'd like a word in private
with the chairman.
I'll leave you two alone,
so you can discuss.
I've heard everything from Jeongyeon.
I'm sorry, Gangmo.
I couldn't possibly find
any excuse for what I did.
Gangmo.
Tell me anything you wish.
Whatever it is, I'll do it for you.
That is the only way
I can make up for all I did.
The mudflats you bought in
Gaepo-Dong under company name.
Transfer possession to me.
Was my request excessive?
No...
It's not.
I'll do that.
I'll register that land in your name.
I'll get going, then.
Gangmo!
I hope you won't resent me.
I never, ever thought
of you as a stranger.
Tell Jeongyeon.
That Lee Gangmo...
was ruthless enough to
prefer that land over her.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you telling me you two...
Case file No. 1327.
The defendant Lee Gangmo is hereby
sentenced to four years in prison.
He's a newcomer
who just joined us today.
Don't cause a commotion
and try to get along.
Yes!
You sure are shit out of luck.
Of all the cells they
could send you to, this one.
Aigoo... Looks promising.
But let's skim the grease off a little.
Sure, Hyungnim.
The judge called me a murderer.
What?
And so what, are you trying
to intimidate us with that?
Just a piece of advice,
don't mess with me.
Because, no matter whom, I'm not
going to let anyone step over me again.
You little asswipe...
Stop him!
Let me go, you pricks!
I told you not to
mess with me, didn't I?
I told you!
- Shim Subong's "That Man, Back Then" -
The man I recall on every rainfall.
He who never was
a man of many words,
Hiding the thorns of love
behind a shadow,
Crying in solitude for
the love who abandoned him.
One day, he asked me inside that car.
October 26, 1979
~ KCIA President Kim Jaegyu Assassinates
President Park Jeonghee ~
Jeon Duhwan announces results
of murder investigation
- The KCIA is no longer allowed
to hide its budget details -
- Turn that off.
- Yes.
What is this lightning on a sunny day?
Kim Jaegyu kills the president?!
It's no lightning,
but only a roll of thunder.
And what is that supposed to mean?
Ipoyeokpo.
Violence bears more violence.
*Borne out of the Hanahwe (Group of One)
which led to Jeon Duhwan's coup d'etat
The New Military Regime*
will soon gain power,
so the real lightning
will begin to strike now.
All public servants are frantically
trying to appease them as well.
Whomever gains power, it won't affect
the South Seoul redevelopment plan,
so you can rest assured.
I've heard the KCIA top brass was
questioned by the joint investigation team.
Aren't Jo Pilyeon
and Min Honggi lucky?
They barely escaped the tide when they
resigned because of the by-elections.
I'm the problem now.
Officially, they flaunt this as
some kind of "war on corruption,"
but in reality it's nothing
but a purge, what else?!
Aren't you on good terms with them?
You even came to my club together,
from time to time.
I might have handed them a few "envelopes"
during their meetings there, but...
An era of bloodshed has just ended,
so those who bore the brunt
will not just take this lying down.
Pandemonium will soon break out.
Student protesters rage on the street
against Jeon Duhwan's dictatorship
- May, 1980 -
Gwangju Democratization Movement
- Although reported by the "authorities"
as 168, the real death toll was over 1,000 -
- September, 1980 -
Running solo, Jeon Duhwan is
proclaimed 11th President of South Korea
- 1981 -
Hyungnim. The newspaper.
- Manbo Construction Completes Subway -
I was the first to ask the
chairman to give me that land.
On the condition that I
would no longer marry you.
It's what I got in return
for giving up on you.
Even if that is the truth,
I'll still wait for you.
I'll wait, and then we'll
get married and live happily.
You and I were not made for
each other from the very start.
Gangmo...
Do you know that the more I look at you,
the more miserable I feel?
If I had never met you,
my life would have been simple,
but at least I would have been happy.
Think acting like this
will make me give up?
Don't wait for me.
Don't come visit me again, either.
I only came here to tell you this.
Let's go back.
Wait... wait, Gangmo!
Let's talk a little longer, Gangmo!
Gangmo! Gangmo...
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Lee Gangmo.
A visit for you.
It's that young lady again,
must you really send her back all the time?
Just meet her for a change,
how many times has this been already?
What can I tell you...
Lee Gangmo refused to meet you again?
Wait.
Give this to him.
All right.
Gangmo.
Are you really bent on avoiding me?
Letters.
Sit down.
Hyungnim, it's a letter.
To all the ladies and gentlemen...
gathered here today to support
Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon,
I extend you my deepest,
humblest gratitude.
Once these elections are over,
the same applause you're hearing
will be the sound heralding our triumph!
Jo Pilyeon! Jo Pilyeon!
Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon!
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- I appreciate it.
Aigoo...
Stop stuffing yourself, you brat!
Ever bought me meat before?
Now that I get the chance,
why not take advantage of it?
Are you done with this?
I haven't seen Jeongyeon around?!
These days she's completely
obsessed with work...
Be that as it may, how could
she miss such an occasion?
Tell me about it... I was so adamant
she should have come, but no use.
Anyhow, she's really something.
Postponing this marriage all by herself.
Isn't it time you tell your father
that you broke off the engagement?
When the elections are over,
I'll tell him firsthand.
You still have feelings for Jeongyeon?
I'll be honest with you.
Never in my life have I
given up on something I desired.
Here you are!
Do you have something for me?
Bring it.
All right, Chairman.
Let's leave the hall, shall we?
Thank you, Chairman Hwang.
I wish you the best of luck.
If you'll excuse me.
I'll let you in on
a shocking development.
The City Council will soon announce
the new expansion areas to be redeveloped.
And where would that be?
Gaepo.
What?
Gae...Gaepo?!
I'm aware you bought vast mudflats
in Gaepo under your company's name?!
It will soon be officially announced.
- We should begin preparations for...
- That land...
doesn't belong to me.
I gave it to Lee Gangmo.
Chairman.
What on earth are you saying?
One thing led to the other,
and that's how it went.
So, what, are you telling me
you'll just give up on it like that?
I only promised you campaign funding.
I never put you in charge
of managing my assets.
Say what?
If you'll excuse me, I'll get going.
What on earth...
What did he just do?
Chairman.
You must get your hands
on that land again.
I bought it with my own money.
You bought it under company name.
Shouldn't you invest in it
for the company's sake?
If we turn those mudflats
into a housing lot,
we'll have a goldmine in our hands.
We can't let Lee Gangmo
gain control of that land.
It's all over already.
That land belongs to Lee Gangmo.
I will get it back.
We must!
There's no need.
Since when Gangmo is released,
he'll come back to work for the company.
So you plan to welcome Lee Gangmo...
back into the company?
I never kicked him out to begin with.
When Gangmo comes back,
so will that land.
So let's not argue
about that any longer.
Listen, Hyungnim.
Someone is looking for you.
They call them the "Wild Beasts,"
and they're active in the Yeongdeung-Po area.
I hear they really have a nasty temper.
So just nod and beg.
Uh?
Got some cement around
your neck or something?
Pay your respects.
You little prick...
Looks like quite the difficult book.
You're Lee Gangmo, right?
And?
I've heard you're quite
the fierce little bastard.
Come under me.
I've got plenty of
meaty folks working for me,
but you know, none of them really seems
to know how to use the gray matter above.
So what, you want me
to become a street thug?
Street thug?!
Tell you what, I'll give you this book,
so why don't you study it?
You really...
Are you banking
on those prison guards?
Hold him.
You know, these days
I'm getting a little rusty.
So whenever I show up,
keep acting all defiant.
Got it?
What is going on here?
He got a little out of line,
so I taught him a lesson.
You little...
- Take him.
- Yes.
You fools, screw up
and it's solitary confinement.
Got it?
Saw that?
There is nothing I can't do here,
if I really want to.
I wear the crown around here.
Hyungnim, what now?
You're on that beast's bad side now.
You.
Come here.
Come wash my hair, will you?
Why is it so damn hot?
Go ahead.
Take good care of him.
Give it your best shot.
Is that all you can do?
Why? Afraid of dying now,
you sorry ass thug?
Just like you, there's nothing
I can't do inside here if I want to.
I beg you... Stop it...
If you really want to mess with me,
you better go all the way and kill me.
Or I'll embarrass you so bad, you won't
have the guts to prance around anymore.
Don't kill me...
Hyungnim, are you still here?
I'll get going then, Hyungnim.
Hyungnim, are you all right?
Must be tough in there.
So tell me, are you managing okay?
More or less.
Was it still about
two years before release?!
I've long lost track of time.
You...
got some land from the chairman, right?
And?
Sell it to me.
I'll pay you well above market value.
And how much would that be?
How much were you being paid
at Goods & Services?
Just a quick calculation,
and it would be the kind of sum you wouldn't
see even after a lifetime spent there.
You've had it so hard all this time,
shouldn't you live a normal,
decent life when you're out?
That land...
is what I got in exchange
for not marrying Jeongyeon.
Do you know why...
I chose that useless lot of mudflats?
By prancing around with 2x4s
dealing with this and that land,
I guess I started getting the hang of it.
You'll pay me above market value?!
Listen well, Jo Minwoo.
Do I still look like the poor little servant
you always showed contempt for?
There is but one thing I learned
by doing the chairman's dirty work.
That the power to rule
this world comes from money.
It's with money that you
take away other people's property,
and use it to make more money.
Isn't this world filthy?
So?
You'll make some money for
yourself and rule the world?
I see living in the can only filled
you with silly illusions of grandeur.
Nah.
I have no intention
of stealing anything.
Be it money or my life,
I won't ever let anyone
steal anything from me again.
Because no matter how filthy
this world has become,
it is too unfair to live in a place
where being powerless becomes a crime.
Listen well.
You'll never keep that land.
You don't have the power for it.
Really?
Then, since you have the power,
try to take it away from me.
Hope you don't regret it.
The visit is over.
Right...
Send my regards to Jeongshik.
Tell him I gained a few precious
life lessons thanks to him,
so I will one day make it up to him.
I'm sorry.
It's... It's a thief!
Thief!
What are you doing?
He just stole your wallet!
Hey! You thief!
Stop there, you thief!
Hurry up! Let's go!
What now?
Was there a lot of money inside?
Mind your own business and go.
So I guess you live nearby?
Since you must have no money,
I wonder if you can get there on foot.
Take the bus home with this.
I had to walk home once
because of a pickpocket,
and you won't believe how hard it was.
I won't ask you to pay it back,
so don't feel burdened.
By any chance,
have we met before?
Right?!
We met somewhere, didn't we?
Where was it...
Ahh! Right!
That's not it...
He went to Saudi Arabia
to make money...
- You wouldn't be...
- You remember now?
in cahoots with that
pickpocket, would you?
What?
Isn't it strange?
Being so kind to someone
you've never met before.
Look.
Not to mention pretending you
know me, when you clearly don't.
Give this back.
I said give me back my token!
Found it.
Do you know how much hard work
it takes to earn this token?
You don't even deserve
to get this much!
People should show some gratitude...
Wait, that tok...
Also, what's with the attitude?
Ruin the mood, will you...
Our competitors are using
a similar concept for their ads.
Seems like they're preparing a TV commercial,
so better go for something fresh.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Let's have a word in private.
It's our strategic plan
for the apartment ads.
Did you know Gangmo gained possession
of those Gaepo-Dong mudflats?
Give it a read and
let us know your decision.
Do you know how he got
his hands on that land?
And why would that matter in any way?
He got it in exchange
for giving up on you.
He exchanged it with you!
I know.
You do?!
And so what?
I perfectly understand him.
I hear he even refuses to meet you.
Doesn't it hurt your pride?
Gangmo thinks that
it's all for my own sake.
What?!
Do you realize why I only
have eyes for work these days?
To establish my footing in the
company before Gangmo is released.
Because that is what's
best for Gangmo's sake.
I respect and acknowledge
your authority as my superior.
And I'm thankful you agreed to
break off the engagement as I wished.
But beyond that, I suggest
you mind your own business.
You've got it all wrong,
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Gangmo is not the
kind of man you think he is.
He's changed.
So?
Gangmo refuses to sell that land?
He looked about to trample
anything in his way when he gets out.
Do what? To whom?
Me?
He's aware that it
was you who caused this.
With his personality,
think he'd let this slide?
The chairman is willing
to welcome him back.
And with that land, Gangmo might
suddenly find himself as director.
What do we do now...
He will try to help Jeongyeon
every step of the way?
Then this company will
fall under her control.
That land is the issue.
All we need to do is
get our hands on that land.
Then we'll cut off his wings
before he can ever fly.
You can see his vital points,
but there is no way to hit them...
So if...
It's just an "if," mind you.
If Gangmo was out of the picture,
how would things change?
What do you mean?
Gangmo is still an orphan
without a single relative.
That means nobody can
inherit that land from him.
So?
Isn't that what you
really want, deep down?
Since without him around,
Jeongyeon will be yours.
Both for me, you, and
our company's future,
getting rid of him would be...
What could you possibly have been
talking about, to act like that?
Uh?! Nah... It's nothing.
See you later this evening.
You...
The police was looking for you.
Uh?!
The police? Why?
Your boys must have
caused some trouble.
Ehh... What else could it be...
It's nothing.
Hey... Did we do anything wrong?
We'll be out in no time,
so keep your head up.
Go ahead, you fool.
Manbo Construction, come out.
See, what did I tell you?
Next time we catch you, you're dead!
Take your time, fellas.
We'll go ahead first.
What's this?
Don't you know me? I'm Chief of
Goods & Services for Manbo Construction.
Get out of here!
Uh?! Young Master...
Detective, you must have misunde...
Young Master... What is this?
Did I do anything wrong?
Hey... Hwang Jeongshik!
You!
Hwang Jeongshik!
As you said,
I only left Sotae behind.
But will he do as we say?
You know dog fights?
Nobody would feed his dog
before a fight.
You must starve them enough
to make them boil with rage,
if you want them
to bite their adversary.
Jo Minwoo...
You sure are smart.
In this first electoral registration
since the new government took office,
candidates from every region
have begun their campaign in earnest.
With the active participation
of the electorate,
pushing to expose corruption
and asking for stability,
the upcoming elections are expected to be
the most transparent and fair to date.
President Jeon Duhwan heralded
the advent of a new democratic...
I found it.
It's evidence that
Jo Pilyeon's father worked...
for the Governor-General
during the colonial period.
*How Japan defined the 1941 war
against Western Allies and China
During the Greater East Asia war*,
he even willfully provided goods plundered
in Joseon to the Japanese government.
So what's with this record about a
math professor at Keijo Imperial University?
Just someone with the same name.
That record was meticulously forged.
Keep digging into it.
We must cause Jo Pilyeon
to fail at these elections.
Yes, Seonbaenim.
Go ahead and help yourselves.
If you help Candidate No. 4
Jo Pilyeon get elected,
this is the kind of feast you
can expect from me every day.
After all, doesn't public discipline
begin from caring for our elders?
Well said!
Jo Pilyeon! Jo Pilyeon!
Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon!
Ma'am, here's some money for you.
Sir, some pocket money.
Remember, Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon.
We'll be counting on you.
Remember to vote.
Aigoo...
Seeing your noble struggle
as an independent just humbles me.
Affiliations can always change.
If you lose out, I'm sure the ruling
party will welcome me with open arms.
From what I hear, you're sprinkling
money everywhere you go?!
You can call that skills.
Shouldn't we help out those poor
working-class people, for a change?
Hope you're not taking
the election law too lightly.
It wouldn't be the first time someone
steps down and is incarcerated.
And I suggest you keep that superficial
smear campaign of yours in check.
Anyhow, let's give it our best.
Let's save that for after
the elections, shall we?
Because when they're over, more than
encouragement you'll need some consolation.
Here... Enjoy your food,
and please listen to me.
I'm Candidate No. 1 Min Honggi,
and as my entire career as public
servant was marked by integrity,
I'm afraid I don't have the means
to appease you with such generosity.
If any of my competitors gave
you money, go ahead and take it.
You can take that money,
but remember to cast your vote
for Candidate No. 1, Min Honggi.
Folks.
What our country
most requires is stability.
The northern puppet regime is
threatening our borders every day.
Remember how many struggles
you had to go through during the war?
And that is why you should
choose stability above all,
and accord your precious votes to me,
Candidate No. 1 Min Honggi.
Well said!
And so you will live a long and prosperous
life, in the stable country you deserve.
Min Honggi! Min Honggi!
Candidate No. 1 Min Honggi!
I just gave you some funding,
and now you ask for more?
Have you even listened to
what I've been telling you?
The situation is becoming urgent.
The campaign has just started.
- If you already start acting this way...
- Listen, Chairman Hwang.
Do I really need to go through
this every time I need money?
*Agency for National Security Planning,
KCIA's post-coup "rebranding"
- Be that as it may...
- The ANSP* Director...
is a close friend of mine.
I even was offered a spot back there
in case I decided to give up the elections.
Think I wouldn't have
connections in the Blue House?
What I'm trying to say is...
I'm not losing my teeth,
but new ones are emerging,
claws I'll bite this world with!
Is that clear, Chairman Hwang?
Come on in.
So what did the ANSP have
to say about public sentiment?
It's still early, but you and Min Honggi
will have a very tight race.
Have you heard?
Using the ruling party's
support as an excuse,
Min Honggi is prancing around
prattling about stability and whatnot.
What could we possibly do
to contend him?
So, how much are you looking for?
The more, the merrier.
More...
Seongmo.
You find Min Honggi's weak spot.
For weak spot...
We've learned that Min Honggi's
father was a ruthless officer...
who captured countless independence
activists during Japanese rule.
I'm sure you'll find some of
those victims if you dig deep enough,
so find us someone who will testify.
All right.
We only have two
countermeasures on our table.
Ingratiate ourselves with
the electorate through money,
and smearing Min Honggi,
there is no other way.
Hey!
Tell Hwang Jeongshik to call me!
Want to see me bite my tongue
and die inside here?
Think I wouldn't have the guts?
I'll do it! Wanna see?
Fine, you sons of...
The hell is this?
Can you do this to me?
Look.
Mister Hwang Jeongshik!
Here... Have a drink.
I've heard a lot about you.
So you're Jeongshik's accomplice?
Acc...Acco...Accomplice?!
Thanks to you, Lee Gangmo
is in the can instead of him.
If that's not being
an accomplice, what is?
I really don't know what
you're trying to do here, but...
You.
Know that Lee Gangmo
has land in his name?
La...Land?!
That lot soon to become a
residential goldmine, Gaepo.
That's Lee Gangmo's property.
What?
And when did he ever find the money...
We'll have to get
our hands on that land.
Help us out.
Me?
If you help us get it back,
half of it is yours.
With that much land,
you'll spend the rest of your life
in luxury, as people call you "Director."
How about it?
What do you want me to do?
Lee Gangmo...
must die.
Get rid of him.
Should go well, right?
Park Sotae would do anything
for the right price.
By the way,
wasn't "half" a little
too over the top?
Don't tell me you believed that?
Of course not.
What kind of land are we dealing with?!
Once Gangmo is taken care of,
we'll just give him enough to keep quiet.
And if he plays hard to please,
spending life in the can is always an option.
He gained that land in exchange
for doing time in the can.
Who wouldn't?!
Fine... All my life boiled down to was
prancing around carrying lead pipes,
why wouldn't I?
We only live once anyway.
When this is all said and done,
I'll finally live in luxury like they do.
Wait... Young lady.
Where is Park Seokchun
Seonsaeng's studio?
Ahh... Go straight down this hallway.
If you dress her up nicely,
wouldn't look too bad, don't you think?
Let's go.
Chief.
You're my beloved...
He's working right now, so I'm
afraid he won't be able to meet you.
Do we really need a composer
to sign a contract?
Seal it.
Yes.
One more over here.
*Commercial Movie,
predecessor of CFs
We'll be counting on you for
our Manbo Construction's CM* song.
As for the money,
you can wire it to her account.
Tomorrow should be fine, I suppose?
Don't you worry about that.
I might be Chief of Management, but...
Chief Moon?!
He's also the only son of Manbo
Construction's Chairman Hwang.
I'm aware.
You know me?
Wow... That's an honor!
The owner of the Royal Club knows me...
I'll get going.
Why don't we have lunch together...
Ehh... What the hell...
Have any decent looker around here?
What?
Have you any pretty lady here?
Chief...
Let go.
None?
How many cookies could a good cook
cook if a good cook could cook cookies?
A good cook could cook as many cookies
as a good cook who could cook cookies.
I wish to wish the
wish you wish to wish,
but if you wish the
wish the witch wishes,
I won't wish the wish
you wish to wish.
A-e-i-o-e-u-a-o-a-e-i-o-u...
She's so damn noisy...
Did she rent the
woman's room to practice?
Oh my! So you were there?!
You really!
Stop there, you little...
Chief!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm so sorry...
I apologize.
My suit...
Know how much this cost?
I'm sorry.
They're still so immature.
I sincerely apologize.
We apologize.
I'll compensate you for all the damages.
Compensate?!
Do you even know how much this cost?
How... much is it?
This cost no less than...
Ehh... Forget it.
You spoiled the mood,
so let's just go eat out.
What?
I'll treat you tonight.
- Hey, country chick.
- What?
You mean... me?
Yeah, you. Country chick.
What would you like to eat?
Cheers!
You two...
Have anything to tell me?
Are you really the son of
Manbo Construction's chairman?
Why? Want me to put in a good word?
If I only wanted, I could get
you on that ad any time?!
Really?
Of course, you cute little brat...
Hey, country chick.
You come all the way here
and drink cola?
Here... Have a drink.
No. I really can't handle alcohol.
Ehh...
But...
You sure are pretty.
Should we call in the band
and dance the blues?
I don't really know how to dance.
What else you don't know?
If you really want to
succeed in this trade,
just go "Sure, I'm good at it!"
- Got it?
- What's wrong with you?
Just stay put...
Hey... I told you to rush,
why are you so late?
What are you doing here?
What do you think?
I'm meeting our ad's models.
Say hi.
He's Manbo Construction's
Chief of Planning.
How are you?
How about the contract?
Yes, it...
Already signed and sealed,
so don't you worry.
Minwoo, let's have some fun tonight.
What are you waiting for?
Go get the chief.
Chief, come have a drink with us.
Hey... Token.
We meet again...
What's this...
You know each other?
You're much more resourceful
than I thought.
What is it you're after?
The CM song or
becoming model for our ads?
What?
You approached me on purpose.
To secure one of the two.
I did what?
Why? Since it doesn't work with me,
you go straight for Jeongshik?
- Listen!
- Jeongshik likes aggressive women.
Give it your best shot tonight,
you might even get the contract you want.
Girls are scary, these days.
They don't look anyone in the face
to make it big, do they?
What is he prattling about?
Hey... Did you two...
The hell is wrong with them?
Wait!
Apologize.
What?
Take back what you said.
I did nothing to deserve
that treatment from you,
and I'm not that kind of woman.
Wanna come in?
You're just doing this to ride with me.
Guess you thought
I was better than Jeongshik.
What?
Where shall we go?
A bar? Hotel?
But I'm afraid you
barked up the wrong tree.
I can't stand easy women.
If you really want to succeed that bad,
go back inside and seduce Jeongshik.
That'd be much eas...
Don't look down on people.
You insolent prick...
Taxi!
That little brat...
Hey... Stop there!
Hey!
Where shall we go?
Young lady?
Uh?
Just take me to the nearest bus stop.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry, Ajeosshi.
I don't have enough money,
so I'll just pay the basic fare.
You rotten bastard...
What do you take me for?
You'll be sent to the
same cell as Lee Gangmo.
You must find the right opportunity
and end it in one strike.
Just one.
One... Two...
- One... Two...
- Here, come in.
He's new here,
so spare me the usual mess.
Yes.
Aigoo... Just a look at him
and I lose my appetite.
Petty offense, I bet?
Right?
Theft or adultery?
You little... Got something
stuck down your ears?
Gangmo!
It's me... Sotae!
Wow... What a coincidence.
Sotae...
Hyungnim, you know him?
Never seen him before.
Gangmo!
You know I can't stand conmen, right?
What's wrong? It's me!
Sotae... Park Sotae!
How dare you mention his name
in vain and try to fool people?
It's not that,
Gangmo and I have been fr...
Teach him a lesson!
Help me!
Help me, Gangmo!
Gangmo!
Gangmo.
Have some.
Seems like you're
misunderstanding something.
I know what you're thinking,
but it's not what happened.
I was in urgent need of money
so I sort of took the easy way out,
but once I came back,
I found out what happened to you.
Hyungnim.
- Eat to your heart's content.
- Have a nice meal.
Yes.
How the hell do you teach newcomers?
Do I still have to endure
bullshit artists prancing around?
I apologize, Hyungnim.
Stop!
You! Try to talk to him just once more.
Next time I'll just bury you.
Got it?
Fine, Lee Gangmo...
You want to take it to the end?
Fine with me.
So long, Lee Gangmo.
When we meet again in the afterlife,
get all the revenge you want.
I'll just be content having a
nice life while I'm still alive.
Want to kill me, don't you?
I'm sure you do.
I know you better than you think.
You've always been easily scared.
And when you get scared,
afraid people will notice,
you stab people in the back
like a coward.
That's your style.
- What are you saying...
- If we weren't behind bars,
I wouldn't have let this slide.
- Gangmo, that...
- Shut your mouth.
Spare me those pathetic excuses.
Or I won't be responsible
for how I'll react.
What else are you doing here?
I... didn't... do a thing?
So why are you here?
I really didn't do anything.
What's wrong with you?
Hyungnim... Blood.
You have hemorrhoids or something?
Hyungnim! A knife.
Who is it?
Who sent you?
G...Gangmo...
It's a misunderstanding.
Was it Jo Minwoo?
Jeongshik?
Who sent you here...
to kill me?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Just deal with him for me.
- His name?
- Lee Gangmo.
I will soon debut.
They said I'll even get my own stage.
I will do everything to beat Jo Pilyeon.
What are you waiting for?
Take that briefcase back!
So I hear Min Honggi's father
was a remarkable man.
He was nothing
but a ruthless collaborator!
Come to the speech.
Gangmo is not here?
They took him to the
Samcheong Rehabilitation Camp.
So if he goes there,
he'll never come back alive?
Whatever you're imagining,
it's even worse.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com