Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 30 -
Gangmo...
Chairman!
You may wait outside.
What's your relationship
with the patient?
Looked like you knew each other well?
I don't know him.
You don't?
It's me, Hyung.
Chairman Hwang was assaulted.
No... I couldn't see who did it.
Where are you now?
I'll come there.
That's Lee Gangmo for sure.
Taeseop...
What is all this?
- Dad...
- Honey...
- Dad!
- Here...
He's going through surgery now,
so don't stay here and
go to the waiting room.
- Let's go.
- Jeongshik...
What's going on?!
Get out of the way!
Seonbaenim.
What are you doing here?
Haven't you seen Lee Gangmo pass by?
Lee Gangmo?!
That guy was Lee Gangmo, catch him.
Wait a moment, Seonbaenim.
What are you talking about?
Why would a dead man be here...
He's alive!
We must catch him now.
Who are you?
Are you sure it was Lee Gangmo?
I saw it with my own eyes!
He must be hiding here somewhere...
We must find him!
Seonbaenim.
Who's there?
How did it go?
How did the surgery...
My husband didn't die, right?
He suffered a truly severe
cerebral hemorrhage.
So what...
Can he make it or not?
We'll have to keep him under
observation and wait a little longer.
Aigoo... Save my husband!
You must save him!
Taeseop...
The police investigating
Chairman Hwang Taeseop's assault...
are treating the case as a simple robbery,
and have undertaken an inquiry...
in the neighboring area,
looking for clues.
They're also looking at released
convicts with similar precedents, and...
and searching for
any possible eye-witness.
It's me, Gangmo.
Things are taking a turn for the worse.
Go Jaechun has seen your face.
Jo Pilyeon is behind this.
I'm sure that Go Jaechun had been
following me from the hospital.
He might have been masking his face,
but they seemed to be
wearing similar clothes...
By any chance...
It wasn't you, was it?
What?
Jo Pilyeon would have no reason
to attack Chairman Hwang.
The fact their relationship
suddenly deteriorated...
So you're suggesting I
created a rift between the two?
And if I did?
Hyung...
We did promise we'd avenge our father,
but this was not the way I intended.
I know.
How much you want to fight and defeat
Manbo Construction fair and square.
It wasn't me.
Creating dissent between the two,
leading to bloodshed...
That's not my style.
That's right, Hyung.
We can't do things like
Hwang Taeseop and Jo Pilyeon.
Only then will Dad accept all this.
But I don't agree with you, Gangmo.
Those bastards killed
our father with no mercy.
An eye for an eye,
and a tooth for a tooth.
Revenge should be taken all the way.
I shouldn't be here.
Better wake up before it's too late.
Mom... What's wrong?
If your father dies like that,
what will that make of us?
He even changed his testament.
I must see what he changed firsthand.
If things really go astray,
your father's death might
spell the end for the two of us.
Dad.
Please, wake up.
I don't even have Gangmo
by my side anymore.
If even you leave me,
how am I supposed to go on?
Wake up, Dad.
Dad...
Trying to avoid the problem
won't solve anything.
If Jo Pilyeon found out about me,
then it's time to walk out of
the shadows and fight him off.
The real war starts now,
Jo Pilyeon.
I apologize.
I should have personally
verified his body...
I did feel strange about it.
The mudflats in Gaepo, that is.
That James Lee
was Lee Gangmo, after all.
Seeing how Lee Gangmo
rescued Hwang Taeseop,
Chairman Hwang might be the one
who got him out of the Samcheong camp.
It's now clear that Chairman Hwang was
plotting to stab me in the back all along.
But who did that to Chairman Hwang?
I'm sure they'll soon catch him.
The newspaper was
talking of a simple robbery?!
Shouldn't we find Lee Gangmo
and send him back to prison?
That's natural.
He still hasn't
served his full sentence,
so this is jailbreaking,
pure and simple.
Seongmo, you find his
whereabouts and catch him.
All right.
Ahh... Jaechun.
Yes.
You said Lee Daesoo's son
witnessed his death, right?
Yes.
According to Hwang Taeseop,
Lee Daesoo's son has shown up.
It's likely that we're
dealing with the same guy.
I'm sure he'll be around
Hwang Taeseop in some way,
so look into it.
All right.
Yes... Director Park Sotae's
workplace, Hangang Construction.
It's me, Sotae.
Ohh... Gangmo!
Are things in Seoul going well?
Pack up and come up to
Seoul right away.
Right now?
All right!
Hyungnim.
Pack your things.
Why? Did it go well in Seoul?
Looks like we'll get ourselves
a huge building over there?
Ahh... I'll finally hear people
call me director for real.
Really? Then Gangmo must have
really hit it big this time.
Wait... Let me think.
I'll be picking all
female employees personally.
Forget credentials!
If they're pretty, they're in.
- Nice body? You're hired!
- Hey... Hey!
Pack your things, for starters.
Now that Jo Pilyeon has
found out you're alive,
I don't think you
should remain in Seoul.
If I keep hiding,
I'll get you into trouble as well.
So?
If your identity is exposed,
you'll have to...
go back to prison.
Don't worry, Hyung.
I have a plan.
Did you bring
the chairman's testament?
Didn't I tell you already?
Before the chairman passes away,
I can't reveal its content
no matter what.
Listen, Mister Kim!
Let's negotiate.
Negotiate, you said?
If you show me that testament
and make the changes I ask,
I'll give you five percent
of my holdings.
Everyone knows about the
chairman's condition by now,
and changing a testament which
has gone through authentication...
is no easy task.
Then, if the chairman passes away,
you'll proceed as it states?
The issue is,
for how long he will brave it out.
If only he doesn't end up
dying right away,
I'm sure there will be
a way to solve this?!
What does that statement say?
What?
What were those changes about?
Leave us alone.
I said get out of here.
How can you scream in here?
We're in Intensive Care.
He's my husband.
This mortifies and unnerves me
even more than you, got it?
Hey, Hwang Taeseop.
Don't die on me,
and survive at all cost.
Whatever it takes, survive.
You haven't shown a shred of
affection for me all these years.
But now you're going to
abandon Jeongshik and me,
and force us to live on the street?
You can't die that way.
After I've changed the testament,
then you can die.
If you do it then,
I won't try to stop you.
Here... Calm down, gentlemen.
Please, calm down!
So tell us what on earth is going on.
It's just as I told you.
Nothing will happen,
so just calm down.
Are we in any position
to be calm about this?
You said you're a chief, right?
Tell someone in charge
to come instead!
I apologize for being late.
What is Chairman Hwang's condition?
Is he still unconscious?
You don't need to worry.
He just regained his senses.
Look, Director Hwang!
If you're lying to us,
it'll be trouble for you!
The chairman made Manbo Construction
what it is today with his bare hands.
He also managed to overcome odds
people thought impossible.
Does that look like the kind of man
who would die on the street just like that?
If that's really what you believed,
sell all your shares right away.
Forget everything else,
but as the heir of this company,
I can't accept shareholders
who don't believe in our founder.
So you're positive that he
regained his consciousness.
He looked and smiled at me.
And held my hand.
Then again,
people don't die that easily.
After all, we're talking about
Chairman Hwang Taeseop here.
You must have been worried, I bet?
You might fool everyone else,
but not me.
Is there a chance the chairman
might never wake up again?
Back in the day,
because of an accident,
everyone proclaimed me dead as well.
But there was something
I cherished so much,
I couldn't possibly die, and that
same thing brought me back to life.
Chairman Hwang is not the kind
of man who would leave you behind.
I can guarantee you that.
He will wake up for sure.
Is this the "huge building"?
And where are all our employees?
Hey Gangmo, did you call us here
to live in this place?
Just for the time being.
Be that as it may, this...
Grown-ass men
sharing the same room...
Still better than the barracks
at the Samcheong camp!
Do we get running water?
- Where is the toilet?
- There, behind you.
Aigoo... Aigoo...
He's in heaven, and stuff.
Do we really have to stay
all three in this rathole...
Sotae.
We have a little problem.
Problem? What problem?
Jo Pilyeon found out I'm alive.
What?
Then you shouldn't have
told us to come here!
If we run away now,
all we've achieved with the company
will vanish into thin air.
Then, what now?
I'll have to meet Jo Pilyeon.
Are you out of your mind?
Come with me.
All I need is your help.
You have visitors.
Politicians?
I've never seen them here before.
A surprising visit, indeed.
We'll have to speak elsewhere.
Here is perfectly fine with me.
And since we're here, might as well
record our conversation.
I could send you
back to prison right now.
Jo Minwoo and Hwang Jeongshik
will go there before I ever do.
What?
How have you been?
I could tell everyone in court
that Gangmo wasn't a murderer?!
Or should I just do it here?
Who was it again who
killed Chairman Hong...
Listen, Warden.
Yes?
If you don't mind,
leave us alone a moment.
Go ahead.
Hwang Jeongshik was the killer,
and since Jo Minwoo
ordered my murder...
Abetment to murder.
I'm quite familiar with the concept.
So?
Why didn't you just head for
the station, and came to me instead?
The way I see it, you should be
the one running away from me,
so things felt a little upside down.
What?!
What are you trying to say?
Lee Daesoo.
The man you and Chairman Hwang killed,
to get your hands on those gold bars.
That man...
was my father.
You said you're
enjoying your time here.
So what would be the point of revenge,
if prison was the end result?
Don't act cocky with me, kid.
So, what, you've been hiding
like a rat all this time,
and now that you fear you might be
exposed, you come out of your hole?
In your dreams.
I kept a low profile all this time
because I didn't have the power,
but now I'm more
than capable of facing you.
You're going to
throw down the gauntlet?
Guess you're banking on
that land in Gaepo,
but do you really think you can
beat me with a handful of soil?
You can bet on it.
And that's because cowardice
won't pave the way to my success.
You'll soon find out
how powerful a weapon...
playing fair and square can be.
Is that the reason you
assaulted Chairman Hwang?
What?
Was trying to strangle Hwang Taeseop
from behind "fair and square"?
And how do you know he was
being strangled from behind?
I knew it... It was you.
Think we don't
read newspapers in here?
The man who assaulted
Hwang Taeseop wasn't me,
it was none other than you.
Without a shred of evidence,
who is ever going to believe you?
Weren't you the first to go on
a rampage to avenge your father?!
Guess I'll have to call Miss Jeongyeon
and tell her the good news.
Minwoo.
What are you doing here at this hour?
Where's your house?
What?
Why are you asking?
There's nothing to eat.
Here... Fresh water.
Here.
Glutinous rice cakes?!
Just to wish you good luck
for tomorrow's test.
You can make it, right?
No idea.
I'm so nervous, it's killing me.
What if I suddenly forget everything?
Why are you suddenly...
taking that off?
So we can go over it one last time.
Go get your textbooks.
It's late, you don't need to bother.
Want to flunk your test?
Get ready.
Hello?
It's me, Miju.
Big Op...
The test is tomorrow, right?
Should have at least
bought you some taffy...
Should I come now?
No... I need to sleep early.
Who's calling?
A friend.
Can't we meet after the test?
I just feel sorry, that's all.
Nah... It's all right.
Then, I'll call you soon.
All right.
Good luck tomorrow.
You got this wrong again.
It's the same one
you got wrong last time.
Did you learn the formula or not?
I told you I did...
Then apply it, will you?
Here, look.
Here...
So...
What is it?
Aren't you going to show me?
Listen.
Don't you have longer pants at home?
Uh?
Go put on some pants.
It's hot, why would I put pants on?
It's so damn hot in here...
See? You're feeling the same.
I'm going to explain to you
one more time, so listen well.
So what you do here...
You made me forget it!
Give it to me.
I can just look at
the answers by myself.
I'll go freshen up, so you better
solve them all before I'm back, got it?
Why is it so damn hot...
Am I the only one feeling this way?
It's not like I can
take off my shirt, either.
- Name: Lee Miju -
How did it go?
Did you go well?
I think it might have gone well,
but I don't really know
if I got them all right.
You brought the test with you, right?
Give it to me.
Here?
Minwoo...
You...
must be out of your mind.
You've gone crazy.
I'm sorry.
You did so much to help me...
Still, I gave my best.
You...
What if you end up on top of the list?
What?
You might end up first.
Minwoo...
You didn't just guess
some of them right, did you?
You mean it?
You aren't lying, right?!
Ehh... You did it.
Look... You two!
What are you two doing here?
Hurry up and leave!
I'm sorry.
I said leave!
We need to go somewhere together.
And you'll get to meet
a very welcome person.
Yes.
It's me, Shideok.
Where are you now?
At the hospital.
How about Chairman Hwang?
Still the same.
Who is there with him?
Just me.
Jeongyeon said she's not coming today.
All right.
Aren't you sleeping?
I need to go somewhere.
Will it be all right?
You've always liked
Chairman Hwang's daughter.
If Jo Pilyeon frames you for
what happened to her father...
All that has nothing to do with me.
Just admit you're struggling,
why hide it?
You can't even sleep because of that...
Gangmo!
Agasshi...
You said you wouldn't come.
What are you doing here at this hour?
My dad is still the same, right?
Yes, no changes.
Agasshi...
I... Right...
I had something to tell you.
Let's go have some coffee.
What's wrong with you?
Did anything happen to my father?
No...
It's not that...
I never wanted to
see you in this state.
Open your eyes.
If you die now, I'll always remain
a poor little servant to you.
Wake up and look at me.
Look at the son of the man you killed,
look at Lee Gangmo!
Get up and ask for forgiveness
with some dignity!
Shideok...
Shideok!
Please, move out of the way.
Dad...
Dad... Dad!
Dad, wake up!
- Please, leave.
- Dad!
You can't die on me, Dad!
Seonsaengnim, my father
will be all right, isn't it?
Dad!
Dad!!
Dad, wake up!
Dad...
It was just a temporary shock.
Thankfully, he's out of danger.
Dad.
Gang...
Gangmo?!
Shideok.
I didn't see things, did I?
Where is Gangmo?
I asked you where's Gangmo.
You know that!
I'm sure I saw him, I did!
Where is Gangmo?
Gangmo...
It's you.
Right?
Gangmo...
Seeing you alive...
At least you become stronger.
Only if you become
stronger than your father...
will you be able to fight me off.
Gangmo.
What's wrong with you?
Should I make it
even easier to understand?
From now on in,
you and I are enemies.
Or else, you will never be able...
to protect Manbo Construction from me.
Gangmo...
Gangmo!
James Lee.
My name...
is not Lee Gangmo.
It's James Lee.
Agasshi!
Agasshi.
Have some of this.
Shideok.
You know, right?
That Gangmo wouldn't just act
like that for no reason.
There is no way you wouldn't know
why he's doing this to me.
Tell me, Shideok.
Or else...
I think my heart
is just going to explode.
Why is Gangmo acting like that?
Gangmo's father...
was killed by the chairman.
Because of the chairman
and Jo Minwoo's father,
he ended up dying.
And now I think I
should leave you as well.
Gangmo tells me to stay by
your side and take care of you,
but I think I'll just go back to him.
I apologize.
Forgive me.
Sorry again.
Anyhow, young brats these days...
Have you been waiting for long?
Hey... How many times
did I tell you not to be late?
Sorry... The bus was late today.
So you were riding the bus
dressed like that?
I'm hungry.
What will you buy me today?
Waiter.
- Shall we have meat?
- Yes.
We can just choose a kind
of steak from this menu, then.
Myeongja.
Isn't that your son Minwoo?
So is that the daughter of
Hwaseong Electric's chairman?
Listen...
Let's go to the
Chinese restaurant next door.
Go ahead first.
Why? You were the first inviting
us here because of their steak?
Go ahead first and
order whatever you want.
I'll be there in a moment.
Come on.
- Sorry.
- All right, then. Make it quick.
Mom.
Sit down.
What clan are you from?
What?
Listen, Mom...
I'm asking about your clan.
My clan?
I'm a Lee.
Who asked you to tell me your name?
What do your parents do for a living?
They both passed away.
Let's talk at home, Mom.
What college are you frequenting?
If you're not in college,
are you working?
Stop it, Mom!
I will soon get my GED.
Mom.
What are you, a beggar?
You dare stick around my son?
What's wrong with you?
I ought to...
Leave.
Do it!
Minwoo...
Minwoo, you!
You gave up on Hwaseong Electric's heir
just because of that brat?
Is that it?
Couldn't you at least let me
deal with my own marriage?
You're not suggesting
you'll marry her, are you?
And why not?
Do you realize what situation
your father is in right now?
Please, give it a rest!
You'll never convince him.
When you gave up your MBA in the
States to become a film director,
have you forgotten what
your father did to you?
I could never cope with
something so terrible again.
Minwoo, if you really think
you can win him over...
Minwoo!
Miju.
Hey, Lee Miju!
Open the door!
Miju...
Were you crying?
No.
And I promised you I
wouldn't make you cry again...
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Also, clear your
mother's misunderstanding.
Tell her that there's
nothing between us.
What?
I'm tired.
Please, go back home.
Come with me.
What's wrong with you?
I said come!
You can find your way
here again, right?
Yes.
That'll do.
Let's go home.
What's wrong with you, really?
What did I do?
We even kissed, but now... What?
There is nothing between us?
You said you like me.
When have I ever said that?
What?
I have never said those words.
Then...
Do you kiss men you dislike?
You did that all on your own.
I don't want to put you
in trouble anymore.
You and I...
live in different worlds.
So?
You know?
I think everyone should be
with someone who suits them.
*"Birds of a feather flock together"
(rough meaning from Hanja)
Yuyusanjoong*.
Don't you know?
What?! Yuyusanjoong?!
Wow... I see your studies
have started making a mark.
Ajumma, another bottle of soju here.
Yes.
Marry whomever
your family wants you to.
I'll get going.
Sit.
Don't drink too much.
It's bad for your health.
Lee Miju.
Let's stop meeting.
I'm never going to see you again.
Who are you,
to turn me down twice?
Who the hell are you,
to dump me twice?
You silly...
I don't need anything else,
just trust me!
But why don't you get that?
All I need is you, you fool!
If you do this a third time,
I will not forgive you.
Come on in, Congressman.
You're late?!
Seems like Jo Pilyeon
might be released earlier.
A few congressmen
wrote a petition in his favor.
I did hear that a few congressmen
had been visiting him, but...
I think you better get
ready for some fireworks.
What are you trying to say?
If anything, Jo Pilyeon will have
spent all this time plotting revenge,
think he'll come out
willing to forgive and forget?
I don't know who will be on
the receiving end of his revenge,
but I'm sure he'll be
furious and ready to fight.
I was surprised to
hear about your father.
Tell me, how is he doing?
He's neither getting better nor worse.
Who do you believe was behind this?
You think it's a simple robbery
like the police suggest?
I didn't come here to discuss that.
There was something I'd like to ask you.
Were you and Dad the ones
who killed Gangmo's father?
Answer me.
Is that true?
Even if it was,
I don't believe anyone would be
stupid enough to admit it?
So it is true.
Who did you hear that from?
Lee Gangmo, by any chance?
What is the reason
you did something like that?
If you really did
hear it from Lee Gangmo,
ever entertained the thought
that he might be responsible...
for what happened to your father?
If I were him,
I'd likely plot some kind of retaliation
against the man who killed my father?!
Careful, Jeongyeon.
You never know when Lee Gangmo
might visit that hospital room again.
Please, move out of the way.
Your father is still alive,
why wouldn't he try everything
to get things done?
Don't you agree, Jeongyeon?
I will soon be released.
I'll have to visit your
father one of these days.
Is Gangmo Oppa really here?
Ohh... Don't put them here, that way.
Ahh... Isn't this too small?
If the president's one is
so small, how about ours?
It's just the name
that changes, you fool.
As if "Park Sotae" would sound
any better stretched wide.
Aigoo...
Why, Nam Youngchul is any better?
Oppa!
Gangmo Oppa!
I missed you!
How have you been?
Ehh... And what's all this
vulgar material on display?!
Introduce yourselves.
They'll be working with us.
I'm Shideok. Yeom Shideok.
Ahh... Shideok or whatever,
what is he, "Director of
Belly-Stuffing Operations"?
My brother does stuff his belly a lot.
I'm Managing Director Park Sotae.
You have a fantastic body, if I may say.
Oppa... Did you hire all these
strange-looking people on purpose?
Then again, he does
look peculiar, indeed.
You're no joke, either...
Ohh... Look at him...
Back off...
Yes? Hangang Construction.
It's me, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Let's meet this evening.
I have something to talk about.
Why isn't he coming?
- Honey!
- Director!
Dad.
Congratulations on your release.
Thanks.
May I see your father?
Certainly.
Are you starting to understand now?
What the price
to pay for betraying me is.
Take a good look, Chairman Hwang.
At how my son Minwoo devours Manbo
Construction while you're not around.
What are you doing here?
I'm meeting someone.
I think I can understand how you feel.
But I doubt you'd know what I'm feeling.
How it feels to be betrayed
by the man you loved.
I couldn't care less what you feel.
You'll have to start caring.
Since I finally found
a reason to fight you off.
The man who did that to my father...
Lee Gangmo, I know it was you.
You're free to think whatever you want.
Since my goal is and will always be
defeating Manbo Construction.
You avenged your father, right?
So now it's time for me
to avenge mine.
Don't ever forgive my father.
Since, I myself...
will never forgive you.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
So you want me to get
Hangang Construction that permit?
With Jo Pilyeon entering the scene,
they might refuse to comply.
Take a look at this newspaper,
it proves your responsibility for this all.
Leave... Get the hell out!
You've been prancing around with
my money pretending to be a president.
Isn't that fraud?
I can't wait,
to see how you
destroy Hwang Jeongyeon.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com