Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
The most important thing
for the both of us to convive...
~ Episode 11 ~
is to reduce the price of raw materials
in a way that satisfies us both.
What else are you trying
to take away from us?
Aren't you being excessive?
We need to make a living as well!
I'm still not done explaining.
Please let me finish.
We have nothing else to listen.
You're just asking us to sacrifice
to benefit Manbo Construction!
That's right.
We can't go any lower
than this estimate!
We need to make it if
you want to survive as well!
That's exactly what we should say.
You need subcontractors
like us to survive!
Isn't that right, gentlemen?
That's right.
What are you wasting our time for?
Let's just all go.
I think all the directors present today...
will have to renegotiate their deals
with Manbo Construction from scratch.
What is he talking about?
Director Kim.
In accordance with
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon's requests,
I plan to lower our service costs
for this subway construction.
Indeed... This is it!
Chief Jo.
You've done us proud.
You should direct
your compliments at them.
I wasn't the one who exposed
the subcontractors' price fixing,
it was Hwang Jeongyeon
and Lee Gangmo.
I see.
Ahh... The problems start now, really.
Our bidding price must be lower
than Daeryuk Construction's.
I will look into it thoroughly.
We certainly need to spare
no effort in preparing this bid,
but there's a much quicker way.
Find Daeryuk Construction's bidding price.
That figure will be kept
hidden in utmost secrecy,
even Chief Jo couldn't possibly...
I have no need for people who
only worry about saving their spot.
Isn't it time you show
me something tangible?
I understand.
I'll find out.
Good.
Here... You can go.
Gangmo, let's have a word.
Daeryuk Construction's bidding price...
Gangmo, you find that out.
Didn't you just ask Chief Jo?
I'm sure Hong Gipyo will be trying
to find our bidding price as well.
When it comes to coping with
insidious snakes like Chairman Hong,
Gangmo, you have much more
experience than Chief Jo.
I'll do it.
You do that.
Go.
President Ju.
Inform Chief Jo of all this.
So you're trying to
pit them against each other.
Are you asking me to find out
Manbo Construction's bidding price?
I know it's shameless of me to ask,
but I'll have to count
on you one more time.
I'll give it a thought,
and call you again.
Yes.
Ohh... Minwoo.
What's the matter?
Can you spare some time later?
I have a favor to ask you.
A favor?!
All right.
I'll see you later.
What happened to you?
Residents were filling agreements,
when suddenly,
Park Sotae, that prick...
He might be threatening the
residents who signed the agreement.
Where is Park Sotae?
Where are you going?
Something has come up
at the building site.
Then, when you're done, come to
Hangang Hotel's restaurant at seven.
Rest...aurant?
Don't be late.
You know I hate
waiting for people, right?
Ahh... Really!
Mess up a perfectly fine shot, will you?
Let's do it again.
Hyungnim... Look.
Ahh... You bastard.
I told you to call me Chief.
- Say it, Chief.
- Yes... Chief!
- Let's hear it loud and clear... Chief!
- Chief!
See how easy it is?
But, what is it?
There... Look!
What the hell... Go after them!
Stop them!
Have you decided?
Yes.
Once the other guest arrives,
prepare the chef's special for today,
and as for champagne...
Gangmo...
Let's just talk it out.
Talk...
G...Gangmo, I'm sorry.
Don't...
Everyone, stop!
Go ahead and do it, you prick.
Spare me...
Gangmo. Gangmo...
Close an eye just this once.
If I do, what will you do for me?
I'll stop interfering...
with the residents' agreements.
Other than that,
there is something else
you must do for me.
That's all you need to know.
What the hell were you doing,
letting them take the pool sticks?
Are you all right?
That won't do it.
Let's head to the hospital.
We have no time for that.
Go to the Hangang Hotel.
Agasshi is waiting.
Shouldn't you get some stitches there?
I said it's all right.
It's your flesh that got torn!
Your own head!
Think Jeongyeon will care
in the slightest if you're hurt?
Should I just grab a taxi?
All right.
Find where Park Sotae lives.
What is it, again?
Give that temper of yours a rest.
You taught them enough of a lesson.
Do you have a reservation?
Sit, let's have dinner.
I'm just buying you dinner
to thank you for today.
Let's go somewhere else.
I'll embarrass you, dressed like this.
And who cares about that?
Go ahead and sit.
Promise me.
That you won't try to
help me behind my back again.
You'll pardon me,
but it wasn't really to help you.
It's the other way.
Fork with your left hand,
knife with the right.
You've never eaten this, have you?
Take a look.
How is it? Is it good?
Why? Nothing special?
This place is famous for its steak?!
Give me the fork.
I'll get you a new one.
It's good, why?!
You really looked cool today.
I'm glad we're friends.
I don't even want to imagine
living without you by my side.
How about you?
Like being by my side?
Sometimes, I'm curious about that.
The chairman will be worried.
Let's finish and go.
Ehh... Silly.
Know what it means for a man
to ask a date to leave early?
"Being with you is a total bore
and I've had it with that."
That's what.
Do you hate staying with me that much?
Does it bore you? To tears?
Stop joking.
I'm not joking.
I really want to
have fun with you today.
Aren't you eating?
Then, will you follow me
to some other place?
Know a nice place?
~ "Creek" by Shim Subong ~
What is the reason you do this?
Sinking down the creek
in all loneliness.
Luxuriant weeds spurting all over,
As the dregs scatter about,
moved by the spring breeze.
It must have been a promise
from days long gone by,
Leading you there even if
your mind no longer desired to.
Sitting by the creek
every single day,
Vacantly abandoning
yourself in those thoughts.
It must have been a promise
from days long gone by,
It must be asking you
not to ever forget it.
Ma'am.
Time to head to the stage.
I'm not in the mood tonight.
Send someone else.
Do you know her?
No. Go ahead.
All right.
I can sit a moment, right?
So you even come to places like this?
That's surprising?!
I have company.
I don't want to be bothered,
so could you leave?
Why do you get angry
every time you see me?
They say there's only two
reasons why women get angry.
Either they really hate you,
or they're interested in you.
What?
Whichever of the two,
don't make it too obvious around me.
It's just bothersome.
That's my seat.
Please, leave.
So you follow her around
even to places like this?
Thought I asked you to leave that seat?
I wanted a word with you.
Let's head out a moment.
Will just take a moment.
I'm going.
So the chairman asked you to find out
Daeryuk Construction's bidding price?
Just a little piece of advice.
You can struggle all you want,
but you won't get what you're looking for.
You better remember those words,
as you'll soon find out what they mean.
What do you do for a living?
We're on the same side, aren't we?
That's what I believe.
I can't stand women
who do nothing but talk.
Unless I'm asking you something,
I'd prefer if you kept quiet.
I'm sorry.
Leave us alone.
Bit late, right?
- Sorry, Hyung.
- Nah, it's all right.
You don't look too happy?!
Is it because of that woman
I saw down at the hall?
It's filled with women out there,
why would I let anyone upset me?
So what is this favor
you wanted to ask me?
Find out Daeryuk Construction's bidding
price for the subway construction.
I'm well aware that
this is no laughing matter.
And that is why I asked you.
Why didn't you ask your father?
At least for this, I don't want
to ask my father for any help.
Help me out.
It's you asking,
how could I ever refuse?
I'll find a way.
- Thank you, Hyung.
- Let's drink.
Ahh... I'm so hungry.
Wonder if there's
even anything left to eat.
You're out of rice.
What...
What's with you?
Did you... come here to kill me?
Have a seat.
Let's have a drink.
Sit down, you fool.
It's your place.
Here, drink.
You...
You didn't put rat poison
in there, did you?
Am I like you?
Here.
Sotae.
You'll have to help me out.
To do what?
About the upcoming
subway construction bid,
find out Daeryuk Construction's
bidding price for me.
Are you asking me that seriously?
You even drive for Chairman Hong.
You'd be more than capable
of finding that out.
Take a look at me.
I'm Sotae, Park Sotae!
Daeryuk Construction's Chief
of Goods & Services, Park Sotae.
I know that.
And I know that you
were a close friend of mine.
Friend?!
I don't need any of that,
and unless they're putting food on
my table right now, I don't trust anyone.
So, you're satisfied just living in this
rathole, worrying about your next meal?
Then, how about you?
Is your life any different?
The world I dream of...
is much bigger than people think.
All that...
Sotae, I want to dream it with you.
This will be your last chance
to join forces with me.
Next time I come here looking for you,
it'll be as your enemy.
Right...
Bought you some briquettes and rice.
Don't skip meals, you fool.
Want to get sick?
Yes, Ma'am! I'm coming.
I just saw the chairman off.
Were you surprised nobody
was home when you woke up?
Rotten wench...
What am I, a little baby, to let
something like that frighten me?
You must be hungry.
What shall I make you for breakfast?
What's with that smile
on your face all the time?
Then, should I look sad instead?
Neither smile nor look sad.
I'll just smile, Ma'am.
Chairman Hong?
Don't turn.
I was waiting for your call.
I need a bait to find out
their bidding price.
Hand me Daeryuk
Construction's bidding plan.
Are you telling me to disclose
our bidding price to you?
If you want to find out
Manbo Construction's bidding price,
wouldn't you need to
rewrite that plan from scratch?
That's certainly true, but...
If you end up failing...
If you don't trust me,
then I can't help you, either.
What do you want me to do?
I noticed there's a mailbox
at the park near your house.
When I call you, put the
documents inside that mailbox.
Using company employees
would be too suspicious,
so send that young housemaid
working for you.
Let's do that.
Then, when will I be able to get my hands
on Daeryuk Construction's bidding plan?
All right.
Thank you, Hyung.
Here's the status of our
renegotiations with the subcontractors.
Is anything wrong?
Call in Chief Moon.
If there's anything wrong,
let me deal with it.
I don't want anyone else
to take care of my duties.
Were you looking for me?
The moment we find out Daeryuk
Construction's bidding price,
we'll get together.
Can you find that out?
Prepare all our male employees.
Also, look for a hotel
with good security.
I'll get right to it.
You're getting together?!
Good job so far.
Leave the rest to your colleagues.
I'll join you as well.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
No need to worry
about me being a woman.
This bid is not like the last one.
Preserving security is crucial.
And?
Until the bid is over, all our men will
have to stay together in the same room.
And they won't be allowed
to leave it, either.
That's no problem.
But our male employees could
feel uncomfortable because of her.
I'll make sure that doesn't happen.
Starting now, ignore
the fact I'm a woman.
So?
Are you telling me Jeongyeon
is even getting involved in this bid?
Yes, Ma'am.
And did you let that happen?
I told you to make sure she
doesn't find her footing there,
so why is she getting involved
in bigger projects by the day?
I apologize.
It was decided by Chief Jo Minwoo, so...
Mom.
If this keeps up, is Jeongyeon
going to steal the company from me?
I'll kill her if she even tries!
Listen to what
you're telling your mother!
So do something, will you?
Stop prancing around
like some libertine.
Actually, I was going
to meet someone soon.
Who?
Ehh... Shouldn't talk about it...
I have this friend working as a
secretary for Daeryuk Construction.
We're meeting, and I'll find out
their bidding price through him.
If you could only do that,
you'd become the biggest
benefactor to our company.
Can you really find that out?
Who's this friend of yours?
If I tell you, will you know?
But to get this done,
I'd need some ammo to throw at him...
Ammo?!
Some money, what else?
Think he'd just bring me the
information free of charge?
I'll get you all the money you need.
How much do you need?
Go ahead and tell me.
All in brand new bank notes,
about four big ones?!
400,000 won?!
Ahh... Really, how pathetic.
Four million?!
They don't call it bribe for nothing.
Know how much money
we'll get by winning that bid?
All right. Get up.
Let's head to the bank.
Also, Chief Moon. You find a way
to kick Jeongyeon out of the company.
Consider it done, Ma'am.
When did he say he would?
He said he would contact me later.
Said to have my housemaid do it,
to maintain secrecy.
Let's give him that bidding plan.
Will it be all right?
Didn't you say he bears a
grudge against Hwang Taeseop?
Yes.
Seeing how he's been acting,
it's clear he'll try to help us.
Then, I'll count on you,
and go ahead with it.
There is one thing
that still bothers me.
What is that?
He's handling all this like a
professional, it's all too perfect.
Could it be a KCIA employee?
I can't say.
None of the employees under me
would be capable of this?!
What? He asked Chairman Hong
to hand him his bidding plan?
And who would that be?
How am I supposed to know?
When is he giving it to him?
Don't ask me.
So what the hell were you listening?
Think it's that easy?
But seems that this guy who's helping him
bears a grudge against Hwang Taeseop?!
- A grudge?!
- Yeah.
Also, they're going to let
Chairman Hong's housemaid do that.
Housemaid?!
To maintain secrecy or something...
Know how pretty that young lady is?
Didn't even know she was just a housemaid,
and I kept using deferentials.
If I meet her again,
I'll treat her to some sausage soup...
Hey, where are you going?
At least pay for the coffee!
"Just a look and my heart throbs."
"Just a thought and my heart throbs."
"Ignore the blooming first love
of an innocent nineteen-year-old."
Must be her.
But, can we really trust Park Sotae?
There might be a mole working for
Daeryuk Construction in our ranks.
A mole?!
Failing the bid at the last
moment was strange as well.
So there's a traitor among us?
He said it was someone with a grudge.
We must find who that is.
But you don't even know
when he'll come,
do we really need
to wait outside here?
Can't be helped.
Actually, I have somewhere
to go, so I need to go back.
I'll send a few of the boys.
No.
That might actually alert him
that someone's spying on him.
I'll just remain here by myself.
Ehh... What a fuss...
It hurts, you wench!
Be gentle.
Stay put, will you?
Look at how dirty you are...
What?
Dirty?!
That's right, you wench.
My body is dirty!
So why are you even touching it?
I also need to do the laundry,
and I'll be busy all day with chores.
If you keep this up,
I won't help you bathe again.
And who ever asked you to help me?
Wretched wench...
Think I don't know you're
laughing at me deep down?
Our Ma'am should just
make a business out of it.
How can you tell so easily?
Say what?
Wait just a moment.
Hello?
Yes, Chairman.
You'll find an envelope in my study.
Put that in the mailbox down the street.
I was bathing your wife...
It's urgent!
Do this first.
You must leave it inside that mailbox.
I need to run an
errand for the chairman.
I'll be right back,
so wait just a moment.
Where are you going?
Hey!
Come back here!
Hey, you brat!
Hey!
I'm back, Ma'am!
I'm sorry, Ma'am...
The chairman said it was urgent.
Rotten wench.
You're just like the others!
You wag your tail when the chairman's
around, and then ignore me later!
I apologize, Ma'am...
What are you doing?
Want me to die in the bathtub,
soaked in water?
I'll scrub you right away.
But, you know?
It's easier to scrub the dirt
away when you're soaking wet.
What?
I'll be good.
Don't be angry.
Rotten wench...
Who are you?
Speak.
Who were you trying to give...
Who are you?
Who's there?
~ Subway Construction Bidding Plan ~
Don't move.
It's a revolver.
Try anything funny, and you're dead.
Give me those documents.
By any chance,
did Chief Jo Minwoo send you?
I was sent here by him as well.
Aren't you going too far?
We're on the same boat,
so we shouldn't act...
The moment you see my face,
you will die.
Hands above your head.
You said I'll die if
I see your face, right?
Go ahead and shoot, then.
I'll have to see that face of yours.
Hey.
Are you all right?
Ohh... Here you are.
How have you been?
Sit.
Bet you must be really busy,
with the bid and all.
Just get to the point.
If they find out I met with the
son of Manbo Construction's chairman,
I'll end up in trouble.
First, take this.
What is this?
With that money, you'll be able
to get a really nice car.
Money?!
What's with the surprised look?
This is just a little deposit.
Tell me your bidding price.
I'll give you ten times
this money if you do.
Acting all hard to get...
You're the only righteous
one out there, aren't you?
Was this not enough?
Ehh... Whatever.
Got a decent sum in
my hands thanks to you,
so let's have a nice drink, shall we?
You prick...
It fits just right!
How is it?
Do I look elegant?
You look just like Audrey Hepburn.
What?! Audrey?
Do you mean that?
We have our own
Shimcheong right here!
She makes money, and even
buys her parents some gifts.
It's hard working
at a factory, isn't it?
Are they feeding you well
at the dormitory?
I'm doing fine, so don't you worry.
Aigoo... My pretty daughter.
Have some of this.
And I was so disappointed when
she dropped out of high school,
- but seems she's finally grown...
- Did she drop out for the hell of it?
With you ruining everything,
she just swayed a little!
Again with that... Aigoo...
Go ahead and drink.
Come visit us a little more often.
A gun?!
He pointed a gun at you?
Jo Minwoo might be trying to get
his hands on that bidding plan.
Ahh... Right.
Minwoo's father is a
director at the KCIA, right?
I tore that document a little.
If Jo Minwoo takes that to the chairman,
it will be a trap for sure.
Hey... What if the KCIA
takes you in for questioning?
They say that they make
cripples out of people in there.
For the time being,
we'll have to keep
an eye on Jo Minwoo.
Whatever.
I don't want to get
shot to death on the street.
Hey... Do you call that a skirt?
You can see all your thighs.
Gangmo Oppa.
Ohh... You came?
Oppa...
Are you dating Jeongyeon
Eonni, these days?
What?
You're not, right?
Don't even joke about that.
What if she hears you?
Then again, I never
thought you'd do that...
But...
Why are you asking that?
No reason...
By the way, Oppa.
Tomorrow's my day off.
Are you free?
Want to go to Ddukseom Resort?
Nami Island would be fine as well.
I'll pay for everything.
I'm making a lot these days.
Gyeongja.
Can you go sit over there?
And cover your thighs.
Oppa.
I have something to tell you,
lend me your ear.
You know...
Agasshi.
- We need to talk.
- We have a work camp, let's talk later.
Work camp?!
What am I, a seed sack?
Always hurling me around...
- Agasshi.
- You can come in.
How is this?
Was going to use it at night.
Will it be uncomfortable?
If it's not my bed,
I always have trouble sleeping...
I'm worried.
Take this.
You're used to this,
so it'll make things better.
Forget it.
Jo Minwoo is already
giving me enough stares as it is.
"Are you here for pleasure?"
"Bring your bed while  you're there."
It's obvious how he'd react.
But what are you all
getting together for?
You still haven't found Daeryuk
Construction's bidding price.
Jo Minwoo found out.
What?
Jo Minwoo found out Daeryuk
Construction's bidding price.
Good job, Chief Jo.
I knew you wouldn't disappoint me.
I appreciate it, Chairman.
Wait a minute...
These construction costs...
Hong Gipyo did this on
purpose to ruin us, didn't he?
Let's lower our bid
by five hundred million.
Will it be all right?
We'd already be losing
money offering that...
We can just find a way to
compensate any lacking funds later.
All right, Chairman.
Right.
Come in.
Where did you find that bidding plan?
And why are you asking that?
Answer me.
Who gave it to you?
What's the matter?
That bidding plan is a fake.
What?
What are you saying?
It's a fake?!
Someone is helping Daeryuk
Construction behind our backs.
If there's a spy within our ranks...
So?
Are you suggesting I'm the spy?
What are you doing,
with the chairman watching?
Take a look at that document.
There must be a few torn pages.
And if there are no torn pages there?
There is no way.
Because I was the one who tore them.
I can't find any?!
Gangmo.
Find them yourself.
So what the hell did you tear,
to make all this commotion?
A suite certainly feels different?!
We'll have to start by assigning rooms,
but with Hwang Jeongyeon...
Let's go by the rules.
Yes.
Then, we'll assign rooms
based on rank.
The chief will take the bedroom,
the other room will
be for Kim Daeri and me,
the big sofa in the living room
for Park Daeri and Choi Daeri,
and as for Hwang Jeongyeon...
Get the small sofa in the living room.
Until the bid is over,
we will live here.
Aside from me, leaving this suite
or even using the phone is prohibited.
I appreciated the money you donated
to our national development fund.
Allow me to apologize.
I should have been
a little more generous...
I'm not the kind of man
who worries about figures.
With patriots like you helping us,
who would ever worry about this country?
You're flattering me with
your kind words, Congressman.
How are things at the KCIA?
As you well know, Chief Cha
of the presidential guards...
and our director
are not on good terms.
Listen to that... They should worry
about protecting the president.
Why waste time arguing?
Actually, I had something
to discuss with you.
What would that be?
I'd like to be nominated for the Republican
Party at the next congress elections.
You want to enter politics?
Forget it, it's just a big headache.
Look at me.
I'm losing hair because of all this.
I'm not just kidding with you.
I'd like you to
recommend me for the post.
If you want to run for congress,
it'll take quite the amount?
You're a public official,
where would you find all that money?
You don't need to worry about that.
Chairman Hwang
will support my candidacy.
You really...
The other day,
in this Blue House report,
Chief Cha talked about this high-ranking
KCIA agent arguing with businessmen.
If you keep this up,
you'll force them to clamp down on you!
It doesn't concern us.
Since Chairman Hwang and I
will soon become in-laws.
In-laws?!
My son and Chairman Hwang's daughter...
will get married.
In-laws are helping each other out,
who would ever point fingers at them?
Ahh... Well, if that's the case...
Anyhow, this is very good news.
My congratulations, Chairman Hwang.
Yes.
By the way.
What did you mean earlier on?
We'll become in-laws?!
If we cut to the chase right away,
we'll avoid any future trouble.
Be that as it may...
Why? Did it upset you that much?
I didn't mean that,
but still, without first talking
to the two people involved...
I'm not forcing this marriage on you.
You winning the subway bid,
and me becoming a congressman.
That's what matters now.
And you never know.
Whether, despite our opposition,
our kids will fall for each other,
and end up asking
our permission to marry.
What the hell does
he take our family for?
How dare he just throw those
words out there so lightly?
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Are you sleeping already?
What?
How can you mess up the figures?
I'm sorry.
I'll do it again.
Miss the mark even by ten won,
and our bid will be canceled.
Let's all wake up.
Chief.
We'd already be losing money this way.
Trying to match those 67.6 billion
of total construction costs is unfeasible.
I'm looking for a way to compensate
for the missing construction funds.
You just continue
focusing on the bidding plan.
Let's continue tomorrow.
Wrap things up,
and let's sleep a few hours.
How can one sleep with all this noise?!
If I am to stay awake tomorrow,
I'll have to get some shut-eye this way.
Hwang Jeongyeon...
You're really smart.
What are you doing there?
You still weren't sleeping?
Quite the refined hobbies you have.
It's a relief you haven't
taken your pants off, yet.
What are you doing?
You told me to erase the fact
you are a woman from my mind.
I'll take a shower.
Ahh... I need the bathtub,
if you don't mind.
If you don't want to get out,
we can just share it.
Move... Out of the way!
Why is it so cold?
Feels just like someone I know.
With this, I'll probably
survive the night.
Nasty bastard...
Why do you think I went
to sleep in the bathtub?
You even have to
take that away from me?
How many degrees is this?
He never gives up, does he?
Do we really have to
spy on Jo Minwoo this way?
I'm sure...
he will meet with the man
who brought him the bidding plan.
If we want to stop him,
we must catch him on the spot.
I saw the lights were on in the suite.
Guess they worked all night.
Jo Minwoo...
Nitpicking snob...
Anal-retentive prick.
Who...
What... What is it?
What's wrong?
This is killing me.
It's three in the morning.
Wonder if we'll
collapse before they do.
Need to check the office,
once curfew is over.
Get going.
If anything happens,
I'll give you a call.
Is peeping on people
a hobby of yours?
That...
Unless you want your colleagues
to misunderstand all this,
I suggest you leave my room.
Think I had a dream last night?
And of all dreams, that?!
It's a nightmare.
Nightmare!
Nightmare.
What about nightmares?
Here...
Everyone, wake up.
Let's start the meeting.
Wake up.
Gangmo! Gangmo.
Jo Minwoo just left for the Royal Club.
What?
What's the matter, suddenly?
Take a breather, first.
What is this urgent matter about?
I think there's a spy
in Manbo Construction.
Spy?
The son of Chairman Hwang met with
a secretary from Daeryuk Construction.
Jeongshik?
I dug into it,
and turns out the guy might
spin out of control any minute.
You don't need to worry about him.
He would never be
aware of our bidding price.
Good to hear, then.
Just in case, thought I'd tell you.
Is work proceeding well?
Yes, of course.
Just in case, I made sure
the bid will be a little different.
How much did you lower it?
If it makes you feel uneasy,
no need to tell me.
I don't want to be
misunderstood for nothing.
*676 AD = 676eok won = 67.6 billion won
Know what year Shilla
unified the Three Kingdoms*?
Not really?!
If we win that subway construction bid,
Manbo Construction will unify
our country's construction business.
So your bidding price is just like
the year the Three Kingdoms were unified?
You sure are KCIA...
Didn't try to fix it
that way on purpose,
but that's how it turned out.
Sounds like a good omen.
I wish you luck.
I'm sure I don't need to say this,
but keep it secret.
If Director Jo asks me, I'm not
sure I can keep my mouth shut?!
Could it be otherwise?
He's here again?!
What if he finds out?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Find out who told them
our bidding price.
Are you laughing at me?
Who gave you permission to eat with us?
Get out of my face!
Bring me Jo Minwoo!
You sure have raised
quite a clever kid.
It's your son who sold off info
on our bidding price!
That little bastard...
You're a dead man!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com