Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 7 ~
- All right!
- Wait! Wait a moment.
Jeongyeon, quick.
All right.
We made it.
Jeongyeon, are you okay?
Girls with no prudence...
What?
What did you just say?
Girls with no what?!
When you wear a skirt,
you should be careful.
I bet all the boys here
saw your panties.
You saw them too, didn't you?
Seeing you get all red,
must be right.
You.
If you don't want a beating,
keep your mouth shut.
A beating from who, you?
Teacher's coming!
Attention.
Salute your professor.
Good morning, Professor.
Right.
He's in our class?!
Before we go ahead
with the monthly finals,
I have a new friend to introduce.
- Introduce yourself.
- Yes.
I'm Lee Gangmo.
Nice to meet you all.
Let's see...
Right.
There's an empty seat
right next to Sideok.
- Go and have a seat.
- Yes.
Put your schoolbags down.
Didn't I tell you not to put your
schoolbags on your desk during my tests?
Put them down.
Don't do it.
To ensure this test is fair, I believe
we should keep schoolbags on our desk.
We're also testing one's honesty today.
What the finals do is not testing
our honesty, but rating our performance.
In the interest of fairness, I'd like you
to keep this rule for all other classes.
Everyone with a clean conscience
can put their schoolbag down,
while the rest can go on as usual.
Other than Lee Gangmo,
is there no one else who
doesn't doubt his honesty?
Fine.
Here...
Front row, pass down the test.
Director, a call for you.
Who is it?
A certain Jo Pilyeon.
Who did you say?
Jo Pilyeon.
Tell him I'm away.
- What?
- Tell him I'm away.
But I said you were here?!
- Tell him I just left, then.
- Yes, Director.
Wait... Wait.
Yes.
From now on,
whenever Jo Pilyeon calls,
always tell him I'm away.
Is that clear?
Yes, I will.
Listen.
Start with a dike behind that area,
and then begin filling from there.
Also, about that
drainage there on the west,
we need to rush with that.
He's not in?
Didn't you just tell me he was?
Look...
Are you trying to fool around with me?
All right.
When he comes back, tell him I called.
While I'm away at the meeting,
start by reading this.
It is required knowledge
for every KCIA employee.
A treat is in order, I guess.
We won't make you wait.
Aren't you Min Honggi?
How long has it been since you
enrolled as my aide, about a decade?
Anyhow, I'm happy
to meet you again here.
Only your superiors decide
when to shake hands.
Now that you're a KCIA agent,
shouldn't you at least know
who's your direct superior?
Whatever the case...
Welcome to the Inspection Department.
I apologize for my negligence.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
You petty privy council prick.
I had to write a letter
of apology because of you!
I will rectify my mistakes!
Rectify?!
Unless you want to die under my watch,
ask for a transfer immediately.
Uh?
I want no hindrances like you
on my way to a promotion!
You prick...
The presidential elections
are right around the corner.
While all those students and
opposition forces keep prancing around...
prattling about military dictatorship,
what are you people doing to stop them?
The situation is too delicate to do anything
without risking serious repercussions.
That's something the police or
the prosecutor's office could say.
But who are we?
We're the KCIA.
The same intelligence agency
working in the shadows,
influencing what goes on in the open.
Anyhow, if this election fails,
we will bear the grunt as well.
Got it?
Control the press thoroughly,
and arrest all those demonstrators!
Director.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Our most recent acquisition,
Chief Jo Pilyeon,
requested special employment
for two of his collaborators.
And?
*table of organization
As our department's TO*
is already complete,
we cannot accept them.
I already received the
director's consent on the matter.
The Inspection Department
is under my jurisdiction.
Just give them two posts
and get it over with!
If you insist, I will first verify
their abilities and disposition.
You want them to go through a test?
I cannot assent to that.
I believe the director's
consent is more than...
Listen, Chief Jo!
Where do you think you are,
some neighborhood council accepting everyone?
If we end up employing people who don't
have what it takes and then they fail,
will you take responsibility for that?
- But...
- Give it a rest!
What he says is right.
Have them go through a test first.
You've worked hard on your test today.
Dismissed.
Attention.
No need.
Just sit.
It's not over yet.
As usual, we will assign cleaning
and other chores based on test grades.
The last ten from the bottom
will clean the toilets,
the next ten will
take care of schoolrooms,
and the next ten the garden.
Everyone else who
didn't make the Top 10...
will be on duty in turns.
I totally flunked the test...
Guess it's the toilets, again.
Why is he deciding that
instead of our teachers?
The class president is
scarier than any teacher.
Over there.
You're new, so help out with the
cleaning until grades are announced.
Jeongshik will be in charge
of inspecting your work.
Does the teacher even
know you're doing this?
You're basically forcing those
with bad grades to clean all year long.
So, what, the rest can go on doing nothing
and focusing only on studying?
This is unfair.
That little...
These are class rules.
And who made them?
You did, so that you and a few
other people could have it easy.
Won't you shut that trap?
Stop, Gangmo.
We're the top-ranked freshman
class in the entire school.
Who do you think made that possible?
If we helped raise their average,
those who are hopeless at studying...
should at least show some courtesy
and do the cleaning.
We don't come to school
to look after people like you.
That little prick...
You fools!
Are you going to start cleaning or what?
So?!
Are your parents doing well?
They still talk about you.
But why are you so scared
of the class president?
He's top of the entire school.
His father is a big shot,
not to mention that all the good
fighters in school are Minwoo's lackeys.
Make just a wrong step, and they
might take you to a quiet place...
You seem to love yapping non-stop?
You dare question the class president?
~ Dostoyevsky's Crime and Punishment ~
Little prick can fight?!
Here...
Give me one as well.
Go ahead.
Why?
Afraid my parents will kick you out?
Do you know what he used to do
before joining our school?
Ever heard this on the street?
"Shoe shine! Shoe shine!"
He can't move a finger against me.
Wanna see?
See?
He's our little servant.
Tell them yourself.
You're our servant, right?
Ohh! Do I see a fist?!
You want to hit me back?
Here... Be my guest.
Go ahead.
From 11 to 13, they're all wrong?!
What?
Still, you got the last
and most difficult one right.
It's correct.
Nuna, wait a moment.
What are you waiting for?
All right.
What are you doing?
The bus is gone.
~ Speech by Democratic Party candidate
Kim Daejung in Jangchungdan Park ~
Did anything happen at the meeting?
Remember Min Honggi?
He was under my command back
in my tactical division days.
Yes.
He's become our superior now.
You and him have never
seen eye to eye, if I recall?
He's interfering with my work
every step of the way.
Before your transfer is accepted,
Chief Min will put you through a few tests.
You must pass them at all cost.
Only then will you
be accepted by the KCIA.
By tests, what is he talking about?
They'll test your aptitude,
skills and temperament.
It won't be easy.
Did Director Hwang call me?
No, I think he's trying
to avoid you on purpose.
Seems like they're all
messing with me, in and out.
So I hear that ever since
briquette ash was used,
the landfill operations have been
proceeding at a much faster pace?
Yes.
It is all thanks to you.
The mayor expressed
his satisfaction as well.
And about that favor I asked you,
how did it go?
About the new government building,
and using lots from
Manbo Construction for the project.
Well...
I did give it a try,
but nothing is certain as of yet.
Commissioner.
You must make it happen.
It might sound like I'm
singing my own praises,
but the fact that I am responsible for
solving the landfill issue is hard to deny.
Yes, I certainly would agree, but...
Commissioner.
If you just consider the
best position for that building,
there is no place like Banpo.
The final decision is not up to me,
but to Congressman Oh Byeongtak
of the Republican Party.
Commissioner.
Set up a meeting with him.
I will ask him firsthand.
I don't have the power to do so, yet.
I'll make a suggestion
when the opportunity arises,
so let's be a little more patient.
But if the contract ends up
going to someone else...
Congressman.
Have a drink.
Director Hong has been generously
funding our National Development plan.
Is that so?
I just feel sorry it's
not as much as I wished.
Nah, don't say that.
It's exactly that patriotic fervor
of yours which matters the most.
I agree.
I know how hard it must be
for the president and his confidants,
as the elections
are rapidly approaching us.
Once the landfill project is complete,
I plan to devote as much of that land
as the country requires,
through cost substitution.
Cost substitution?!
Do you mean that?
How could I dare lie to you?
If you put that land to good use,
then you will secure enough funds
to make my donations seem insignificant.
I've never seen an entrepreneur
with such patriotic mindset before.
I really appreciate it, Director Hong.
Here, let me pour you a drink.
If you'll excuse me, I'll get going.
Why? Let's have another few drinks.
No. Go ahead and enjoy yourselves.
It's Goryeo celadon.
You'd be able to buy three-four good
houses within the four major gates...
by selling this kind of item.
I believe treasures should be
in the custody of people who deserve them.
I'd like you to have it.
I still eat with brass bowls.
You never know when
my temper might explode,
so take this back.
Congressman.
I actually...
Ohh Ohh! Keep up with this
and you'll ruin the mood.
Let's wrap things up for today.
He wouldn't bleed
even if you stabbed him...
If we want to have them choose us
for the government building project,
we need to change our plans.
What should I do with the celadon?
Change it with cash.
If Oh is such an impregnable fortress,
we need to first win over
all the confidants around him.
~ Report Score ~
Hwang Jeongyeon.
If it's tenth in your class,
you lost five spots since the last time.
Jeongshik...
38th?!
You fool.
You call these grades?
Still, he gained one spot
compared to last time.
Is that something to be proud of?
Who on earth does he take after,
with those grades?
Who else?
When he was born, you were all ecstatic
saying he was your spitting image.
He should resemble my brains.
Ehh... You useless waste of money...
Gangmo, you?
What?
You took the test as well.
Give it here.
Lee Gangmo...
Let's have a look.
Uh?!
All zeroes?!
What is this...
You're at the very bottom
of the entire school!
What can you expect
from a shoeshine boy?
- Ahh... Keep it up...
- Just a waste of money educating him, I guess.
Even on my worst day,
I never went below 300th place...
Shut your mouth!
You!
Next time, end within the top 10.
What?
Dad!
How can one who's dead last
end up in the top 10?
- Jeongshik, you too!
- What? Me too?!
The both of you,
if you're not in the top 10 next time,
I won't send you to school.
You'll just work at the construction site,
so you're warned, you runts.
Hey... You!
What are you doing?
You brat... Not even knocking...
Can't you even sharpen a pencil?
How could you get them all wrong?
If you don't know the answer,
don't write anything.
Why bother sharpening the pencil?
You said you wanted to be friends?
I'm not going to be friends
with someone who's dead last.
I'll give you all these reference books,
so start studying.
Your grades got worse, too.
I can end on top whenever I want.
You know, don't you?
That I couldn't study
because of my father.
Putting on airs...
You still have the test questions, right?
Solve them all by helping
yourself with those books,
and write the answers by tomorrow.
What are you, giving me homework?
If you don't get them right,
forget about being friends.
I'll treat you as a servant,
like everyone else does.
So make your choice.
That brat...
Hey.
Keep coming in as you please, will you?
Know how to ride a bicycle?
Uh?!
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- Can't you go a little faster?
- What?
Go faster!
- If you fall, then don't complain.
- Faster!
Let's have some fun!
You idiot.
This is wrong.
You still can't do it,
even with the book?
What are you, blind?
Why didn't you solve the math problems?
That wasn't on your reference books.
You dolt...
It's applied math, so just use formulas.
Look.
It's asking you to find a common
number between this and this.
You then use the
greatest common denominator,
so 20, 70, 90.
Got it?
Got it or not?
Yeah.
So what's the answer?
Uh?!
What's the answer.
Answer?
The answer... is...
I explained in detail...
Did you listen or what?
Why do you keep hitting my head?
Why do you keep getting distracted?
Tell me.
What were you thinking about?
This is trouble, really.
How are you going to enter the
Top 10 with that brain of yours?
Don't worry.
I'll end up first.
Really?
You promised.
To end up first.
A...All right.
I can just do it and get it over with.
Fine.
I'll believe you.
First, solve this one again.
You're top of the class again,
so I can't just ignore it.
Tell me.
What present should I get you?
How about raising my allowance?
Why would you need more money?
Know how many kids are following me?
Fine... All right.
A man needs to show leadership.
Still, don't neglect your studies.
Ehh... Don't worry.
I'm confident I'll be first
the whole three years.
And me? Where is my gift?
And why?
Think looking after Minwoo is that simple?
There are weekly PTA meetings to attend,
his tutor to take care of,
not to mention...
All right, fine.
What do you want?
How about a nice dress?
And shoes to fit.
Listen to you... Why don't you
just sell me off, then?
Ahh... Really, and how
much would that get me?
Isn't that right, Minwoo?
What? What did you just say?
Honey...
You went in my room today, right?
Yeah... Was looking for a book.
Don't enter my room when I'm not home.
Yeah... All right.
Also, I study every evening
from eight till midnight.
I'd prefer if you didn't wander
in and out of my room all evening.
And?
What else should I do?
At seven in the morning,
for about a half hour,
I need to get ready for school, so limit
your use of the bathroom to the essential.
All right.
I'll be careful.
Thank you for telling me in advance.
Anything left to say?
You seem like a decent person.
I think we'll become closer.
You didn't even have breakfast.
Thank you.
No way, I'm not eating.
Send me back to my Mommy.
Mommy...
Fine. Do as you wish.
There will be nothing to eat until
the evening, so don't complain later.
Did your mother bring you here?
My mother passed away.
Daddy, too.
Then, you don't have any parents left?
Yeah... But I have brothers.
Brothers?
When I was first brought here,
I refused to eat like you,
and kept crying all the time.
But now I don't cry anymore.
I believe my brothers
will come looking for me.
So I eat a lot on purpose?!
So I can brag to them
about how much I've grown up.
You still have a mother, at least.
If she learns you're
skipping meals and always cry,
think of how sad she would be.
And if you never eat and don't grow,
she'll probably leave you here?
There is no way to know
how and what he'll be rating.
I can only give you
two pieces of advice.
One is to never contest an order,
no matter what it is.
You must follow his
instructions at all cost.
Obedience above everything else.
The other...
is that you must never reveal your identity,
no matter how desperate the situation is.
Keep them in mind, is that clear?
Yes.
Yes, Sir.
I believe in you.
Pass that test at all cost,
and remain by my side.
You can write down your thoughts here.
You have forty-five minutes,
so you won't have too much time
to waste reflecting.
Begin.
"The grass is lying flat."
"Lying flat quicker than the gentle breeze."
"It weeps louder than the wind,"
"And faster than the wind it rises."
"Clouds caress the sky,
as the grass is lying flat."
"Lying low,"
"Low down to my ankles."
"It might lie after the breeze,"
"Rise before the wind,"
"And might even weep much later,"
"But it is the first to smile."
"Clouds caress the sky,
as the grass is lying flat."
We just read the
late Kim Suyoung's "Grass."
Anyone cares to share his feelings?
It reminds me of when my father
bought me a sickle to cut the forage.
Resistance against
oppression and violence,
and the poet's love for
freedom dominate this poem.
The world you live in today
is not as fair as you think.
So the reason you study...
is to learn about the world.
Learning what injustice is and
gaining the knowledge to contend with it...
is something you must practice.
That will help you find freedom
and protect your rights.
It might be a complicated concept,
but one day you will understand
the meaning of today's class.
Here... What does the poet
refer to with the word "grass"?
Aigoo... Again here? Again?!
- How are you?
- Ohh... It's you.
Seonsaengnim,
can you help me out with this?
You're here again?
Let me have a look.
Let your teachers rest
during recess, will you?
You're always here...
If this keeps up, what if Lee Gangmo
beats Jo Minwoo at the upcoming midterms?
Ehh... What kind of
nonsense are you saying?
He was dead last...
Who could ever know?
During today's class, Gangmo got them
all right, and Minwoo got two wrong.
Remember to tell your mother.
I will.
Then, shall we bet on who will
end up first at the next midterms?
I'm banking on Lee Gangmo.
Really?
Then, I'll go with Jo Minwoo.
Whoever loses will treat everyone else.
Fine with me.
- Right, Gangmo.
- Yes.
I enrolled you into a labor scholarship,
is it all right with you?
Labor scholarship?
Ohh... You can just stay after school
and do some cleaning, that's all.
It's not big money,
but it'll at least cover school expenses
and a little extra for you.
Thank you, Seonsaengnim.
- I will do my best.
- All right.
You must be hungry, so have it.
No, thanks.
Jeongshik.
Ohh, what is it?
You said he lives with you?
Why don't you tell your mother
to prepare him a lunchbox?
Why? He always eats so much
during breakfast.
It's got to be enough
to cover lunch as well.
Right?
You ruminate like cows, don't you?
I hear you're still complaining
about cleaning the toilets?
All those who are fed and given the same
education as us but keep failing...
are all trash.
The reason our country's so poor
is because it's filled with such trash.
I believe the rules I've set are right.
Because awarding the best students...
and punishing those with
poor grades is only natural.
You might be class president,
but still have no right to make such rules.
It's not as class president
that I made them,
but as the very top of the class,
helping raise everyone's average.
Then, if I become top of the class,
then maybe I can change the rules?
Why? Is that what you're aiming for?
- Yeah.
- Go ahead.
Nobody will ever surpass me.
You passed the aptitude test,
for starters.
Starting now,
your skills as a potential
recruit will be tested.
There's a man named Eom,
selling ironware in Dongdaemun.
Bring this to him.
You can't look at what's
inside the envelope.
All you need to do is bringing him that.
Yes, Sir.
That Eom fella,
he's a resident spy from up north.
The man you see was
supposed to deliver this envelope.
You'll take his place, just for today.
If you manage to complete your task,
you will not only capture a northern spy
plotting against our government,
you'll be accepted into
the KCIA as an elite recruit.
One is to never contest an order,
no matter what it is.
You must follow his
instructions at all cost.
Obedience above everything else.
What are you looking for?
I came to meet a Mister Eom.
That'd be me.
What brings you here?
I came to bring you this.
~ Get rid of him ~
Good job.
You may leave.
Come on in, Minwoo.
This is my house.
See? I was right.
Told you he's our servant.
As busy as you are,
think you'll find the time to beat me?
By the way, with all the noise
that piano's making,
can one even study?
Told you to stop playing.
Who?
Your mother.
I'm playing at home,
what's wrong with her?
Don't know.
Just said Jeongshik needs to study.
He must have a death wish...
How dare he tries to order me around?
Hey, and when have you ever stu...
Don't you people knock around here?
Stop interfering with our studies and leave.
Or sit here and learn.
What?
After some of my special tutoring,
your grades will go up right away.
Worry about teaching that meathead.
Where were we?
Awww... Why is our Minwoo so handsome?!
Look who's talking...
Listen to you...
Jeongyeon, are you going out?
Why did you wear that?
Minwoo.
Have some more ribs.
It's all right,
I've had a lot already.
Minwoo, teach some of your secrets
to Jeongshik, will you?
I'll cook you all your favorite dishes.
Other than studying hard,
I really have no secrets.
I bought the fruits you asked.
You did? Put them over there.
Gangmo, go wash your hands and join us.
You can eat later,
but how many times do I have to tell you
to throw out those briquettes?
Take a look outside the gates!
It's filled with trash.
All right, I'll go do it now.
Minwoo, come on... have some more.
Jeongshik, you too.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Leave.
I need to study.
Go ahead and try to beat
Jo Minwoo at the next midterms.
Why?
Are you interested in him?
Am I what?! Hey... I haven't
the slightest interest in him!
It's just...
You promised me
you'd end on top, last time.
If you win,
I'll take you to the movies.
Think I'm only studying so that
I can go to the movies with you?
If you think you can't win,
just be honest,
why are you getting angry?
Let's wake up, Gangmo.
Wake up.
Daeryuk Construction?!
Are you suggesting that government
building will be constructed...
on Director Hong's land?
He gained the upper hand, I guess.
Commissioner.
Their progress is much slower than ours.
Who on earth made that decision, anyway?
Don't you know how many people are
trying to run the ship in this business?
Commissioner.
Whatever the case, we must make sure
that building is erected in Banpo.
Don't you know better than anyone
how desperate our situation is?
All that is in my power
to do at the moment...
is being done.
However, Director Hong
has really strong backing.
If you need any lobbying funds,
I will satisfy your requests,
whatever it takes.
Just tell me what I
need to help you with.
I believe it's a bit late
for that kind of strategy.
Then, are you telling me to just give up?
Nothing is set in stone yet,
so I'll continue looking into it.
So one man sows and another man reaps?
Director Hong...
He's getting in my way again?
I ought to just...
I just gathered you here so
that you could speak your mind.
So let's enjoy the evening.
I wonder if we really deserve any free drinks
from someone in the construction business?
What are you saying, Director Min?
Who is making life easier for
businessmen like me, after all?
Ohh... Right, let me introduce him.
Here's our Inspection Department's
new acquisition, Chief Jo Pilyeon.
I didn't introduce myself.
I'm Director Hong Gipyo
of Daeryuk Construction.
Hope I can count on your patronage.
I was in Jeonju for business,
so I bought a few bottles of quality liquor.
What is it called, Igangju or something?
Secretary Kim.
You put this liquor in these
gentlemen's trunk, I hope?
Yes, Director.
I guess the introductions
went on too long.
Come on in.
You must reserve special
treatment for them tonight.
Yes.
Let's have a drink.
- Here, have some.
- Yes, yes.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
If I knew this would happen,
I would have aimed higher from the start.
What are you doing here?
What could I have come
to a place like this for?
I hear you're quite busy as of late?!
Enough that you can't be reached.
My apologies.
I will contact you soon.
If you'll excuse me...
Chief.
You were here.
Isn't this Director Hwang?
Hey!
What else are you scheming here?
What are you doing,
embarrassing yourself?
Want to advertise to the whole world
you were an ignorant construction worker?
You son of a bitch!
Sure! I used to work
at a construction site.
But at least I'm not a wolf
in sheep's clothing like you!
That is how it might look
to an ignorant fool like you,
but this is how you do business.
You bastard...
What is going on?
Who are you?
Some gangster?
Don't get yourself
in trouble for barging in,
and get the hell out of my face.
You little...
Are you out of your mind?
- Stop it, Director Hwang.
- Let me go!
Who the hell are you?
Why don't you come get some?
I apologize, Director.
Director?
Chief Jo.
Do you know this man?
No. Not really.
Let's go back in, Director.
No need to let this break the mood.
You!
I'll remember that face of yours,
so be careful.
Let's go.
What... Director?!
Just a moment.
Who is Hong Gipyo drinking with inside?
No... Forget that,
- let's just have a drink, and...
- Look, Hwang Taeseop.
I'm just as busy with work
as you are with yours.
I'm not the kind of man who
could meet you all the time anymore.
Is that clear?
What I was saying...
I have a lot of thoughts
in my head, these days.
For instance, how I should
repay a certain Hwang Taeseop...
for betraying my trust.
The KCIA's Inspection Department tends to
wield its knife before it starts talking.
You'll have to start waking up
and hope I won't have to visit you.
The KCIA's Ins...Inspection Department?
He's a chief there.
Then, that man earlier on...
He surely must be some higher-up
in the KCIA hierarchy.
I sure ended up getting my hands dirty...
It's the liquor
Director Hong Gipyo brought you.
Open it.
Seems like Director Hong's ties with KCIA
higher-ups are deeper than we thought.
Just save it as it is.
All right.
Right...
Is Lee Seongmo still unaccounted for?
Yes.
He was going to test him...
But something doesn't feel right.
Still not done?
Ahh... Just the principal's office is left.
You have a test tomorrow,
so just rush it and go home.
Yes, Seonsaengnim.
Minwoo's mother?
Seonsaengnim...
Yoon Seonsaeng, still haven't left?
I was just about to.
But, what brings you here so late?
Yes...
I had something to discuss with the
principal regarding the board of education.
Ahh... I see.
I'll treat you to dinner, next time.
- Yes.
- Here... Let's go.
By the way,
I hear that this boy called Lee Gangmo
is scoring first in drill tests?
He seems to be working hard,
but both for the sake of
our school or anything else,
there is no doubt that
Minwoo needs to be on top.
So...
Here's the list of questions
for the upcoming midterms.
Yes.
I hear that the Ministry of Education
will award meritorious schools...
with a development fund.
Yes.
I've heard it at the last PTA meeting.
I'd really love to receive that fund,
and since Minwoo's father is
chairman of the board of education...
I'll talk to him.
I appreciate it.
You're back?
Here.
I told you not to do this again.
Solve them all tonight.
I can be top of the class
even without this.
But if you end up losing that spot?
Don't you know your father?
Mom!
Think I'm enjoying this?
Your father only accepts excellence.
Do you think you could cope
with that, should you fail?
Don't get yourself into trouble
just for a matter of excessive pride,
and just solve these
before you take the test.
Fine, Jo Minwoo.
You asked for it.
I'm never going to allow you to beat me.
And Gangmo?
I'll go wake him up.
Just sit.
You'll spoil him.
He's already annoying me enough
by keeping the lights on all night,
do we even have to
wake him up for breakfast?
I said forget him!
I'm done eating?!
Little brat...
Jeongshik, you...
Have you studied?
What?
Yes...
Gangmo seems to have really worked hard,
you're not going to lose to him, are you?
Aigoo... At least Jeongshik
can land in the middle.
How can you compare him
with someone who's dead last?
Eat.
I'll go to school.
You...
If you don't want to work
at the construction site,
you better do well.
Hey! Aren't you coming to school?
Miss the test and I'll show you...
Consider yourself dead if you do.
What... What time is it?
I didn't study at all...
Lee Gangmo?
Is Lee Gangmo still not here?
What's this?
What is it?
Open the door!
Jeongyeon!
Jeongshik!
Ajumma!
Open the door!
Jeongyeon!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
What kind of test
did you put him through?
What kind of test could it possibly be?
What are you, complaining?
Wow! You're really great!
- Then, how about Minwoo?
- He's just a prick.
Are you jealous?
I'm well aware of what you've done.
He said he would contribute to
the national development fund.
And who's that?
Do you know why I like you?
Because you don't lie to me.
Whatever anyone says, I trust you.
Jeongyeon!
Agasshi (lady).
I told you not to
call me that, didn't I?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com