Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 8 ~
Is Lee Gangmo still not here?
Seonsaengnim.
It is time to start the test.
Right...
First row, pass down the test.
What's this?
Open the door.
Jeongyeon!
Ajumma!
Open the door.
Quick!
Hey...
What are you doing there?
Please open the door, Ajumma.
Quick!
Aigoo... Really...
What's wrong with him?
Gangmo.
Just sit.
You almost missed the test.
Here.
You have an hour to complete it.
You'll have to
take this test here, today.
Go in!
Try anything funny
and you might get killed.
Keep quiet.
What happened, Hyung?
I could ask you the same thing.
Haven't you heard I disappeared
while on a mission?
I did hear about it,
but I never imagined
that spies could capture you.
We must find a way to escape from here.
I don't think those people are spies.
What?
Something doesn't feel right.
There is no way the KCIA
wouldn't know about my disappearance,
and the fact that they gave us
the same task is strange as well.
Then, are you telling me...
I'm sure we're just being tested.
Whatever happens,
we must endure it until the end.
Director Min, you rotten bastard...
Come on in, Chief Jo.
I have the scores for your
associates' aptitude test.
They did quite well.
Particularly that Lee Seongmo.
What kind of test
did you put them through?
Didn't I tell you
we'd test their operational skills?
Are you telling me you didn't know?
Not only I lost contact with Lee Seongmo,
but now Go Jaechun as well.
What test could it possibly be...
So?
Are you here to complain, or something?
Let's be clear.
I'm your superior.
I'm in charge of recruiting agents here.
How dare you come in
and stare at me like that?
Just wait for the final results.
Come bothering me for that again,
and I'll stake my life to get you fired.
Thought I'd let them
do whatever you wanted?
You insolent prick...
It's a relief.
I was worried you wouldn't make it.
Here's the list of questions
for the upcoming midterms.
Yes...
Seems like you did
your best to beat me,
but now that you have no more excuses,
what will you do?
You coward...
What?
You little fool...
You must be out of your mind.
Your teacher shows some
interest in you out of compassion,
and you forget who you're talking to?
Yeah...
Seems like I've forgotten.
Why?
The teacher is coming.
Confess, you prick!
Stop wasting our time and do it!
Water.
Tired, aren't you?
I'll send you to sleep,
so just write it down.
Position.
Superior in charge.
Your name.
I said write it down!
Who sent you here?
You must never reveal your identity,
no matter how desperate the situation.
I know nothing.
I merely brought you that envelope.
What?
They still refuse to cave in?
I apologize.
You won't imagine
how stubborn they are...
- We should just accept their...
- You fool!
Are you kidding me?
I'll take that back.
They didn't even open that envelope.
We tried to contain Jo Pilyeon,
and only ended up benefiting him.
Imagine if the higher-ups learn of this.
It'll be a disgrace for us, a disgrace!
I apologize.
Since they refuse to give up,
do everything it takes to make them fail.
They're human beings after all,
a week without water and food
and they'll call it quits.
Mess this up,
and I'll kill you with my own hands.
Is that clear?
Yes, Sir.
Chief Jo.
Good job.
Where are my boys?
And why are you asking me...
What are you trying to do?
Bought a house last year, right?
And some land in Gangnam,
under your six-year-old nephew's name.
Never imagined you'd become
my first case on the job.
I see you took money
on several instances.
With this kind of figures,
Director Min will just try to get rid of you.
Help me out, Chief.
Tell me.
Where are my boys?
We'll let you feast on this all you want,
so write it down.
Chief!
We're testing their oper...
Come on in.
I have something to tell...
I was just briefed by Director Min.
So I hear we found two men
of remarkable disposition?!
Congrats.
You've got quite the
talented fellas under you.
It must have been painful to endure,
but gaining experience in advance
will always pay off.
Since that's the kind of work you'll
have to do, for the sake of this country.
Thank you.
Thanks to you,
my men passed the elite
officer test with flying colors.
I'll have to treat you
and pay back the courtesy.
Don't really need to bother.
If you'll excuse me.
Also...
I'll be in charge of their polygraph test.
Be my guest.
Seongmo can still smell a rat
like it's nobody's business.
You did well.
Here... Have a drink.
I...
What does this polygraph measure?
Just your sense of patriotism,
and your mental state.
Just answer honestly whatever I ask,
and it'll be all.
Why?
Are you hiding something from me?
Nothing of the sort.
Here... Let's drink.
This place is filled with charming ladies.
You can spend the night here.
Yes.
Are you sleeping?
You're really something...
Not even stealing a glance at me.
Aren't you taking off my clothes?
You looked quite young...
You're not telling me
it's your first time, are you?
*archaic for partner
Seobangnim*...
I'm just fine, so please leave.
You don't like me?
I said leave!
I miss you.
I miss you so much,
it's driving me crazy.
Oppa!
Miju!
Aigoo...
Miju.
We made a ton of money.
Really?
Then, are we going to live together now?
Of course!
We'll never have to separate again.
Oppa...
God.
I don't care if my brothers
don't make a ton of money,
so just let us meet.
Make sure Big Oppa and Little Oppa...
can live together with me,
and have a happy life.
Uh? God...
The top score in the entire school
is again from our class.
The top scorer in our latest midterms...
is Jo Minwoo.
But we have another top scorer.
Lee Gangmo.
What?!
You and Jo Minwoo scored the same.
I'm really happy that our class
had the two top scorers.
If you all give your best,
you can end up first like Gangmo did.
Dismissed.
Starting today,
we'll divide chores by groups,
and assign the toilets
based on student number.
What are you, giving orders
to the class president?
Didn't you say it yourself?
That if I ended up first,
I would decide the rules.
Were you the only one on top?
He was first just like you.
That's enough, stop it.
Are you putting on airs
after just one first place?
I said stop it!
What now?
I have no intention of
changing my own rules?!
Too bad, then.
We'll have to let
a majority vote decide for us.
A majority vote?!
That's right.
We'll let them decide.
How does it sound?
Go ahead.
Anyone who agrees with
my proposal, raise your hand.
We should decide
our class rules all together.
You've had it with
cleaning every day, right?
See?
Nothing left to say, right?
"The grass is lying flat."
~ Kim Suyoung's "Grass" ~
Remember this poem, right?
What did the teacher say?
That once you witness injustice,
you should fight it!
And that doing it
will help us protect our rights.
Are you all deaf?
Why can't you admit
that something is wrong?
How much longer are you going to
let them subject you to this, you fools?
Don't ever badmouth
Jo Minwoo behind his back.
You don't even deserve that.
I...
agree with what Gangmo said.
I... agree, too.
Agreed.
I've had it with cleaning the toilets.
- Me, too.
- Me too.
From here on in,
you clean like the others.
Gangmo!
Gangmo, wait for me!
First place!
~ Mokryeon Girls Middle School ~
Jeongyeon!
What are you doing here?
We'll go ahead first.
You're embarrassing me,
coming all the way here...
I ended first!
Top of the school!
Really?
Yeah.
Here.
Wow!
You're really great!
So, Minwoo?
Uh?!
Jo Minwoo.
Was he second?
No.
We both were first.
Ahh... So you had the same score?
He's quite something, too...
He never loses first place.
He's just a bastard.
Why?
What are you, jealous
because I complimented him?
What am I, some kid?
Being jealous and all...
It's much more impressive for someone
who was dead last to end first.
Let's go, I'll buy you pastries.
I said let's go.
Take your time.
- I'll buy you more.
- Thank you, president.
- What could we do without you?
- Thanks for treating us.
Ajumma, some steamed buns
over there as well.
I'm treating, so eat all you want.
Whatever.
Ajumma. Forget the buns,
and make us some dumplings.
Let's go to the movies this Saturday.
Forgot my promise?
I told you I'd take you
to the movies, if you ended first.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
I think I will have to
take you to the movies.
What?
Lee Gangmo.
Eat all you want.
As this is the last time you'll go
around bragging that you ended first.
If you're done, let's get up.
What's wrong with him?
No idea.
Don't want to know, either.
I apologize.
I wasn't aware of that.
How are you going to deal with this?
I'll take care of everything,
so you don't need to worry.
Anyhow,
I'll be counting on you.
And about that
funding issue we discussed...
I already talked with my husband.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Is this all you could sell?
I mean, that...
Aigoo, don't even
get me started, Director.
They first sold that land
for two thousand won,
would they accept buying it back
for fifteen thousand?
He managed this much
only because it's him,
anyone else wouldn't have had
any hope to begin with.
The moment they start buying,
the price will only go up.
If not us, who else would ever
sell land in Gangnam at that price?
If those country bumpkins
living in Maljukgeori knew that,
would things have gotten to this point?
Sell them all by the end of the week.
Director.
Can't you give us a
higher commission fee?
If you don't like it,
then forget about it.
I'll go sell it myself.
No, Director!
He's the only one
who can sell at 15,000 won!
Oh my...
If you're done talking, just go.
We'll sell it all by the end of the week.
- Let's go!
- I apologize, Director...
Aigoo, you brat! I knew
that you'd cause me trouble!
Let's get going!
We'll have to head to City Hall.
I truly appreciated what you did for us
regarding the government building grant.
You were the first to
get the higher-ups in line.
I really did nothing much.
I had to do at least that much,
to let you work in peace.
Anyhow, that lobby power of yours
never fails to amaze me.
It is no lobbying, just negotiations.
That is how I see it.
Yes.
Then, if you'll excuse me,
I'll get going.
I might have lost with the landfill,
but this time I won't
make the same mistake.
Excuse me.
Commissioner.
We are ready to contribute
to the national development fund.
We'll hand you all the money you need,
so allow me to meet
Congressman Oh Byeongtak.
Listen, Director Hwang...
Why is it possible for Hong,
and not for me?
May I give you a piece of advice?
For a businessman to mention things
like the national development fund in vain,
that's like digging your own grave.
You still don't seem
to know what power means.
You're never going to beat
Hong Gipyo at his game, this way.
Did I make myself clear?
Are you ready?
Yes.
To test the machinery,
I'll begin with a very simple question.
Just answer yes or no.
Did you have breakfast, this morning?
Yes.
Then, let's get started.
Is Lee Seongmo your name?
Yes.
TRUTH / LIE
Do you think the
northern puppets are our enemy?
Yes.
Can you pledge allegiance
to your motherland?
Yes.
Can you stake your life
to protect our president?
Yes.
Do you believe that remaining silent
when in difficulty is your best option?
Yes.
Your family must be somewhere,
do you miss them?
Yes.
Are your parents still alive?
I'm in no position to
answer that with a yes or no.
A short answer will do.
I wish for them to still be alive.
By any chance,
do you remember your past?
I'm asking you whether
you truly have amnesia.
Are you suspecting me again?
It's not my question.
These questions are based
upon your personal situation.
Answer.
Remember the past?
No.
That's a lie.
So you've been deceiving me all along?
Speak!
Why did you keep pretending
you had amnesia?
Because I had no power
to do anything about it.
So?
Is there a purpose
behind your approaching me?
There is someone I want to kill.
To avenge what he did to me,
I needed power.
And who is this man?
It's a long story.
I'll tell you everything in detail,
when the time comes.
So you still can't believe me.
I'm done with this.
Wait.
Let me ask you...
the very last question,
and then you can go.
Can you...
stake your life for my sake?
To protect mine,
can you sacrifice your life?
The day you die...
is the day Lee Seongmo will die as well.
That will be all.
From now on,
you're an elite agent of
KCIA's Inspection Department.
Dammit...
Do I even have to sell land
to fill their bellies?
Just go.
I thought I'd never
have to see him again...
You can go.
It's me, open the door.
Chief Jo.
I came to meet you.
I have no reason to meet you.
It will only take a moment.
Let's go somewhere quiet,
and have a word.
Somewhere quiet?!
Just wait.
I'll soon see you in the
KCIA's questioning room.
I know everything you've done.
Go in first.
Yes.
You believe that kind of blackmail
is going to work with me?
When the little mutt you kept around
starts showing its teeth,
you can just get rid of it.
Do it, then.
Still, it won't be as easy as you think.
I'm not going to let you exploit me
and then die like my friend.
Fine.
Let's move somewhere else,
and finish talking.
You've grown some guts, it seems?
I learned this all from you.
If you want to run a business,
you sure need guts.
So you'll contribute funds
for our national development?
In exchange, you'll have to grant us
the government building construction.
You're already too late.
There are people lining up outside to
throw crazy money at me for that contract.
How much will it take to convince you?
If you believed in me from the start,
what you prepared would have been enough.
But the situation has changed now.
Get me double what you brought today.
What?
If you want to upstage Hong Gipyo,
you'll need to bring me
more than he did, if anything.
Have we realized that
the more foolish the mistake,
the costlier the repercussions will be?
I will bring you the money you asked.
Also, once you start giving me funds,
you'll have to continue doing so.
From the presidential
down to the next general elections.
Will you be able to?
I will.
It's unfair...
So unfair, I can't take it anymore.
I'll give them everything they ask.
If it's money, I'll give it to them.
And if they ask for my own blood,
that's what they'll get.
Instead,
even if those beasts force me
to become worse than them,
I'll get back everything they
extorted from me, and more.
If I can't do that,
I'll never be at peace
with myself, even in death.
Listen, Yoon Seonsaeng!
Are you out of your mind?
If he didn't come on time,
just punish him with the lowest score.
How could you let him
take the test separately?
Jo Minwoo's mother called,
complaining to me.
If they learn of this, think of what
the PTA and board of education will say.
There was no dishonesty involved.
If that's not dishonest, what is?
Anyhow, fix Lee Gangmo's score
back to zero.
He answered those questions
in all fairness!
If you really need
someone to blame for this,
then I should be held responsible
for having him take that test separately.
It's my fault, you did nothing wrong.
It all happened because I was late.
Fix his score, and update the ranking.
Would you have done the same,
if Jo Minwoo was involved?
Say what?
If Minwoo came late
and hadn't taken that test,
would you have given him a zero?
Look, Yoon Seonsaeng!
Gangmo is an orphan
with no siblings or parents.
Be honest and say
that is the only reason!
Are you done?
If that's not the case, then what?
If that's not the case,
tell me what he did wrong!
This is a sacred institution
whose goal is to treat everyone fairly!
Why should Lee Gangmo
receive special treatment?
It's because of
prejudiced teachers like you...
that our country's education
has to live with a bad reputation.
Enough with the excuses.
We don't need teachers
who have no conscience,
so hand me your
resignation immediately!
You stole the test questions from him!
What did you just say?
I saw you handing
Minwoo's mother the questions.
You're the one
without conscience, not him!
You fool!
Now he even starts
to lie through his teeth?!
Where is the detention officer?
The detention officer!
Where is he?
Aigoo, my stomach...
Listen, any broth left?
Aigoo... Forget the broth.
Gangmo, that little...
I ought to...
What do I have to hear...
Why, what did Gangmo do?
He lashed out at his principal.
They called from school.
He's been suspended for ten days.
He's not the type to do that?!
Think that someone raised on the
streets would forget his nature?
That's why they always tell you not
to keep beasts with dark hair around.
What is this embarrassment?!
Nice showing, really.
Apologize to the principal right now.
I did nothing wrong.
What?
I did nothing wrong,
why should I apologize?
That... That little...
Until he apologizes,
keep punishing him.
Yes.
Stop hitting him!
Get out of my face.
Come on in.
Hey!
Gangmo.
I'm his guardian.
Ahh... Is that so?
Time to get up.
I've heard a lot about you.
So you're raising an orphan?
Yes, I'm the only one
to blame for all this.
I apologize, Mister Principal.
It's a shame we had to meet for this.
I'll take him home for today,
and will visit you again later.
Yes, go ahead.
During one's childhood,
anyone can make mistakes.
Take this opportunity
to reflect on your actions,
and return to us a better person.
What are you waiting for?
Apologize and let's go.
Do it!
We need to go home.
I did nothing wrong.
You gave the test to Minwoo's mother!
Minwoo is the one
who committed dishonesty.
He's the one who
should be suspended, not me!
Gangmo!
I apologize.
Please, try to understand.
Gangmo!
Where is your resignation?
I must have told you to quit already?!
I have no intention of teaching
at this school any longer, myself.
What?
I believe what Gangmo said.
And that's...
because you're
more than capable of that.
Listen to him!
Gangmo!
Gangmo.
You fool! Stop there.
Aigoo, you'll kill me...
I'm going to quit school.
Shining shoes is better.
It's too unfair and cowardly
for me to endure all this.
You fool, think you're
the only one facing unfairness?
This world has always been dirty.
Just think of it as mud springs.
If you give up what you were doing
just because a little mud is on you,
who would ever succeed in life?
You learned something precious today.
What will learning
a few more English words matter?
You need to learn about life.
In exchange for a little suspension,
just think of it as having learned
a much more precious lesson.
That'll do.
You fool...
Where are you going again?
Gangmo!
Can someone who's been suspended
even enter this class?
Confess the truth yourself.
What?
You know better than anyone
that you didn't earn that top spot.
Enough with the excuses,
just be a man and acknowledge defeat.
You dirty coward.
Gangmo!
Your bag.
Now the damned commies
even invaded colleges...
What is happening to this country?!
Congressman, you have a guest.
Who?
What's this?
A liquor called Igangju.
Liquor?!
Nice...
Chief Jo.
What do you think you're doing?
Hong Gipyo of Daeryuk
Construction sent me that.
What? Hong Gipyo?!
And it wasn't just to me.
Be it the KCIA or the Blue House,
this fella is throwing money at everyone,
lobbying left and right.
The elections are right behind the corner.
The opposition is trying its damnedest to
find the tiniest blemish about the government,
and Hong Gipyo goes around
throwing bribes at us?
A few journalists have started
getting suspicious already.
What?!
If they learn of our
connection with Director Hong,
it will cause our downfall
at the presidential elections.
What is the KCIA doing,
letting people like him run free?
Even after seeing this money,
you don't understand?
Aigoo...
This country is rotting
inside out, we're doomed.
By any chance, did you receive
any bribes from Director Hong?
Look.
What do you take me for?
Unless it's devoted to our
country, I accept nothing!
Then, give back the money
Director Hong donated.
During election season? It's like
water dripping out of a bucket's hole.
Think I still have it?
Thankfully, I know someone willing to
donate to the national development fund.
Is he trustworthy?
He's clean.
He won't create any problems.
And who is that?
Come on in.
Introduce yourself.
I'm Manbo Construction's
Hwang Taeseop.
The commies took
away my land back home,
and I only now
was able to settle down.
As meager as my means might be,
allow me to sacrifice myself
for the betterment of our country.
So...
How much can you donate to
the national development fund?
Shoe shine.
Ajeosshi, can I shine your shoes?
Your shoes.
I'm fine.
It's all right.
I'll shine them next time.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
I think I'll have to
take you to the movies.
You bastard.
You brat...
Didn't I tell you
not to get any illusions?
Think school would suit people like us?
I'll give you this chocolate,
so just forget it.
I'll be right back.
Come with me.
I told the director
I wouldn't go back there.
Who told you to come home?
Why don't you keep your promises?
I didn't even know you were here,
and waited for ages outside the theater.
Do you know why I like you?
Because you never lie to me.
Whatever everyone says, I trust you.
You ended first, for real.
Aim the barrel right on target,
and hold the gun with both hands,
making it stable.
You said you had to avenge someone?
Imagine the center of that target
is your enemy's heart.
Technique is not all it takes
to be a proper shooter.
Your frame of mind is just as important.
Here, try again.
Your enemy is right there.
Aim for his heart.
We'll eat dinner and then go home.
Go by yourself.
I don't want to go home.
Will you keep being stubborn?
Jeongyeon!
Gangmo!
This way!
You can go home.
*lit. lady, but in this case a servile
deferential for "young lady of the house"
Agasshi*.
I told you not to
call me that, didn't I?
I need to bring you there,
don't you know?
I'm not going there.
Why would I?
If I don't take you there,
the chairman will beat me to a pulp.
Gangmo! Let me go!
Hey! You blockhead!
~ Manbo Construction 10th Anniversary ~
Thank you for coming,
Commissioner Han.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
By the way...
I wonder if Minwoo
is doing well at work.
What are you saying?
I can only be thankful someone
like Minwoo is part of our company.
What is your son's
position in the company?
His?!
Jeongshik... will soon inherit
the company from his father.
Ahh...
Must be preparing to become the heir?
Well... I guess you could say that?!
I still don't see any chairmen
from the construction committee here?
I hear the chairman
invited them firsthand.
Even if late, they'll soon join us.
At this bidding for
the subway construction,
I hear that only construction
committee members will be allowed to bid.
If Manbo Construction
is to win that bidding,
we need to make sure it's
accepted into the committee.
There is something I need to ask you.
Not content with watching their back,
why did you push me to join
Manbo Construction, despite my reserves?
Is a weak spot the reason behind all this?
Weak spot?
Who, me?
You still don't understand
how the world goes round.
Stop wasting time with that,
and worry about winning the bidding
for that subway construction.
The party has started.
Wear this.
Ahh... Forgot the shoes.
I'll be right back.
Do I really need to wear a dress?
While you're here,
make your father happy for once.
You know how hard he's worked
to protect his company.
You people will drive me crazy...
Anyone out there?
Gangmo...
Lee Gangmo!
Is anyone out there?
Gangmo!
If you're back, help me out.
Gangmo.
Gangmo... Help me with this.
Being the chairman's daughter
is really hard.
I look awkward, right?
How d...
- Who are you?
- It's me... I'm not a molester!
- Don't you recognize me?
- Gangmo!!
Gangmo!
Who are you?
Who?
Long time no see.
I'm Minwoo.
Jo Minwoo.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
I hear the owner is
Baekpa's adoptive daughter.
The kingpin of Myeongdong's
private lenders, that Baekpa?
You're going to 31 Building today, right?
Miju and your brother might be there.
Are you waiting for someone?
My brothers.
It's me, Sotae.
The one who shined shoes
with you in Myeongdong.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com