Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 48
Seonhwa.
Go find out if Minwoo's gone.
Is there a reason
why I shouldn't be here?
Is this all because I was bothering you?
It's not that.
It's cold medicine.
Take it.
We postponed the shoot to tomorrow.
You can go home.
Please, find yourself
another model while you still can.
And why should I give up on
an up and coming star like you?
If that's what you wish,
we can keep all this
strictly business-related.
I'll do everything I can
not to create any unnecessary burden.
Lee Miju.
You know how hard I'm trying
to endure all this in silence?
Do you even realize how painful
it is to just stand here...
without even being able to touch you?
Miju...
Take good care of yourself.
There's a shoot you can't miss tomorrow.
Thirsty, aren't you?
I've heard that people can
only last a week without water.
So I guess you have
about four days left to live?!
The only way you'll get out of here...
is on a stretcher after you're dead,
or if you tell us where that account is.
Park Seonbae...
Go to hell.
- Ohh...
- Sir.
I bet I've made you wait?!
I had this urgent meeting
with some businessmen.
I just arrived myself, Congressman Min.
Drop that "Congressman," please.
Just call me seonbaenim.
Yes.
You know who that is?
Can't really say
I'm familiar with him?!
We can't waste all this time
trying to track Min Honggi alone.
Seongmo won't resist that long.
What do you plan to do?
Whatever he's hiding, we need
to force the cat out of the bag.
You always had an interest
in politics, if I recall correctly?
I've long given up on it.
What are you saying?
People always
get three big chances in life.
You catch one and
it'll pave the way to success.
I'd like to give you
one of those opportunities.
What can I do for you in return?
I'm glad you're
so quick on your feet.
There is someone I'd like
you to discreetly investigate on.
And who is that?
He's this fella called Hwang Taeseop.
He's aware of the secret
fund account's whereabouts.
Are you suggesting that he's
in cahoots with Lee Seongmo?
He had a past on top of a
corporation, so he won't be easy to handle.
Who's there?
A man told me to give this to you...
I have what you're looking for.
If you want that account,
let's meet here in two days, same time.
But you must come alone.
Could this come from Hwang Taeseop?
He's the most cunning snake you could find.
There is no way he would just give me
that account asking nothing in return.
So is he just trying to test me?
I can't say.
Whatever he's plotting... Deploy a
few of your best men here in two days.
Be careful not to be spotted.
All right.
Seonbaenim.
I was curious about something.
What will you use that account for,
once you get your hands on it?
Whether I'll just use it to hit Jo Pilyeon,
or to become the hero
our people are clamoring for,
we'll have to wait and see.
I'm so sorry... I was just...
Are you going already?
Ahh... This...
How much is this book?
Quick.
Park Hoyong.
He's a chief at the Department
of Planning and Coordination.
He's the man who took Chief
Lee to the Seobinggo Bunker.
So we can't trust Min Honggi, either.
Now that we know his true colors,
we'll have to choose
whether to just abandon him,
or use him instead.
Cha Soojeong has missed her shoot once again.
I guess that her cold might be to blame.
They're opening a
shoe store in Gangnam,
and she is there right now.
A shoe store?
She might be trying to
associate her image with this store,
and use it to raise enough funds to
pay back the rest of the money.
Why didn't you tell me?
I... I apologize.
It all happened while
you were busy, so...
I'm only letting this slide because
it won't hurt Soojeong's image.
From now on,
always report to me first.
A... All right.
Crystal's shoes convey
a feeling of happy love.
Right now designer shoes
are being imported from Italy,
but within the next ten years,
Crystal's shoes will have secured
nine-figure export contracts to Italy.
You sure don't lack confidence.
You'd know just by trying them on,
but our shoes are truly
comfortable and pretty.
Cha Soojeong.
We don't really know
anything about you,
are you by any chance experiencing
the same "happy love" these shoes convey?
I'm sorry,
but let's only talk about the shoes for today.
- Crystal Shoes Launching Event -
Chairman. Aren't you going in?
Miju is smiling...
Excuse me?
It's the first time I see
her smile since we broke up.
I tried so hard to make her smile...
If I go inside right now,
Miju won't smile anymore.
Chairman.
Miss Lee called a few times, saying
she'd pay the rest of the money.
Chairman.
You've had enough to drink.
- Why don't you...
- Let her do that.
But the company is incurring
substantial losses because of her.
- Asking for damages...
- Don't do it.
I made a mistake
approaching things this way.
This would have never
changed her mind anyway...
Return all the money
she already paid back.
What?
Even the money she already paid?
All right, Chairman.
What did you find about how
Miju spent the last four years?
They're still investigating.
I think I might have a report
ready for you very soon.
Tell them to hurry up.
If I can find out how
she lived all these years,
it might help me to convince her.
May I ask you just one thing?
Why does it have to be Lee Miju?
Someone like you could
easily find another woman...
Other than Miju,
I have no eyes for anyone else.
What?
Right when I was
wondering why I even existed,
that's when I met her.
She made me fall in love with her,
and gave me a reason to keep living.
Let's stop this.
I was told you called.
Saying you'd pay back
the rest of the money.
Please go back.
There's no need to
pay back that money.
What do you mean by that?
Are you really planning
to ask for damages?
Miju...
Miju!
Let go!
I said let go!
Try to do this again...
And you'll do what?
Will you report me to the police?
Might just do it.
Do you really mean that?
Don't you even
think about your future?
Still better than being
harassed by someone you dislike.
You mean it?
Have you grown such dislike for me?
And why...
You said it wasn't
because of my father, so why?
There's no particular reason why
people just stop liking someone.
I don't want to see you again.
We'll have to stop
investigating Lee Seongmo.
What is that supposed to mean?
And you'd stop with nothing on our hands?
You know how many people give me
stares for tormenting an innocent colleague?
You're working on
behalf of the president here.
Just ignore what other people think of this.
Lee Seongmo is going to
endure this to the very end.
If he ends up dying, who's
going to take responsibility?
- Look, Chief Oh.
- Make up your mind within two days,
or find your evidence before then.
Or else, I'll release him personally.
That...
What is he ever going to
accomplish with so little courage...
Honestly, I don't understand
what you're doing myself.
Now you start as well?
Had I been in Seongmo's shoes,
would you have done the same?
I don't want to suspect him, either.
But he's the only one capable of that.
- Still, Seongmo...
- suspicion...
It often has a life of its own.
Once it manifests itself,
it can only keep growing.
The reason why I keep
pushing this to the end...
is because I want to be
able to trust Seongmo again.
That was really good?!
I've had a great time, Hyungnim!
You think? You stuffed yourself
with all those expensive dishes...
Let's do this more often, shall we?
Aigoo... Whomever ends up marrying
you will have to sweat to handle the missus.
So? Why would you worry about that?
Nothing to report yet.
Yes, Chief Park.
Congressman Min just arrived.
Excuse me... What can I bring you?
I'll have company in a minute.
If you are listening to this tape,
it means you have betrayed us.
Open the doors behind you,
and you'll find a briefcase.
Open that briefcase.
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
You didn't live up to our deal,
so that hit list you were looking for
will now fall into Jo Pilyeon's hands.
Chief Park!
Park Hoyong!
- What is the matter?
- Get your men and go capture Hwang Taeseop!
Now!
- Let's go.
- Yes.
I'll be damned...
Where has Hwang Taeseop gone?
- And you are?
- Where is Hwang Taeseop?!
If you find out, tell us, will you?
I knew his face so I did rent him this office,
but he ran away without paying
the last three months' rent!
Aigoo... See? Told you to get a deposit.
Who imagined things
would turn out this way?
Still, he was a former
chairman so we trusted him...
Look what that got us!
Aigoo... Really...
Find any removal centers in the area... Now!
Yes.
That fella must have done something wrong...
Call us if you find him!
They're gone.
Yes, Chairman. It's me.
Those people looking
for you just came here.
Should anything happen, don't
hesitate and call me right away.
Gangmo, right as you said,
Min Honggi is on a rampage.
This place is under
a manager's name,
so you'll be safe.
How long must I keep staying here?
We can't go on with this for long.
Be careful out there.
If they end up catching
you in this atmosphere,
it might be fatal.
Especially you, Jeongyeon.
Don't worry about me, Dad.
It's tea they sent me from
Mount Jiri. Try it out.
It has a nice scent.
The flavor is delicate as well.
I'm sure you're not
here to praise my tea.
What do I owe this visit to?
Nah... I was passing by so
I just thought I'd pay a visit.
KCIA alumni can smell it a mile away.
The fact that people only say that
when they have something to spy on.
Even if that upsets you,
can't do anything about it.
Since your attitude is
not to my liking either.
Other than this fine tea, did you by
any chance receive anything else?
Thanks for the tea. I'll get going.
I looked into what those ruling
party members were talking about...
when gathering in secret like rats,
and it turns out it was about the account.
The one for the secret
presidential fund, that is.
I did hear about that.
But since nobody has actually seen it,
wouldn't it just be a silly rumor?
You're looking for that
account too, aren't you?
If it does exist, I have to admit
I wouldn't mind finding it.
Nah... You saw it firsthand.
And that's the very reason why you're
trying to approach the opposition party.
Throw such nonsense at me again,
and I won't let it slide.
That account will end up in my hands.
And after that happens,
I plan to deal with traitors first.
Although by now I can more or less
figure out who they might be.
I don't know who will get that account,
but I'm sure it'll spell
the end for someone else.
Min Honggi can't already
be in possession of it, can he?
Seeing how they
stopped those club gatherings,
I'm sure that's not the case.
And if he does have it,
he's not the type to
just do nothing with it.
You didn't live up to our deal,
so that hit list you were looking for
will now fall into Jo Pilyeon's hands.
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
What are you going to do now?
There are only two options on the table.
Taking a step forward firsthand,
or, as Seongmo suggested,
helping the two parties get together.
It would be too dangerous
for us to take the initiative.
And there's no guarantee
the opposition party will trust us.
Still, since Min Honggi betrayed us, we can't
convince the ruling party members, either.
To them, this is a hit list.
If we can't convince them,
we'll have to find another way.
You're not telling me you want to...
Here's a list of opposition party
members you must invite to the event.
They're under strict surveillance.
Not only they're bugged, but
even their mail is being controlled.
Can you do that?
I'll give it a try.
"Direct Presidential Elections for a Democratic Future"
Your support could help
our democratization become reality.
Hi.
- Democratization Fund-raising Exhibition -
- Jang Minjae, 1 million won -
I guess you know
Congressman Jang well?!
We meet here, of all places?!
I'm surprised.
I'm quite close with
opposition party members.
And I help a few of them as well.
I see...
But what brings you here?
An acquaintance from college
asked me to come here.
Is that so?
And tell me, is business going well?
Your credit institution, that is.
I hear you're hosting the upcoming
fund-raising event for the Olympics?
I see you're well informed.
You don't know how much I
blamed myself after hearing that.
We should have done that ourselves,
but I guess we were one step too late.
Send my regards to Director Yoo.
That's Congressman Jang's wife.
Have some cakes.
Thank you.
I never imagined Congressman
Jang had so much talent for this.
This wasn't painted by the congressman,
but by his deceased father.
I see...
It's the last trace of his father he had left...
It must have been disheartening
to part with it.
Still, could it compare with
his passion for democratization?
I will buy this painting.
My... We set a really high price for this...
It's for a good cause.
- Secretary Choi.
- Yes, Director.
We will buy it right away.
Sure.
Here's my business card.
- 88 Seoul Olympics Support Committee -
Commissioner HWANG Jeongyeon
I'll come pay my regards later.
What's that?
I don't know...
Someone sent it to me.
My... Why was this sent here?
Didn't you say it was sold?
I have the business card
of the lady who bought it.
Hwang.... Jeong...yeon?!
There's a message here.
"Hang in there, Congressman Jang.
Our people will always
support the pursuit of justice."
Yes.
I called you earlier on.
Have a seat.
I'm sure you brought
all the necessary paperwork?!
I'd like to tell you something...
I don't need to discuss anything.
I just decide based on your collateral.
What is this?
That is my collateral.
So you'll put no less than
seven-hundred million on the line?
I guess money is not what you're after?
I'd like to work under you, Sir.
Please, take me under your wings.
If it's for your sake, I'll do everything.
With this much money, you
will make a pretty dignified living,
so go find yourself another occupation.
President.
Look, youngster.
I'm a man of great circumspection.
Think I'd let a little money tempt me?
If you want to work in the private lending
business, find yourself another firm.
This is no place for a tenderfoot like you.
I'll be honest, then.
I want to defeat Hwang Jeongyeon.
Hwang Jeongyeon?!
Yoo Gyeongok's daughter?
Yes.
Now that sounds a little more exciting...
Why, did she dump you or something?
Hwang Jeongyeon...
is my half-sister.
Then, are you telling me that your father is...
the founder of Manbo
Construction, Chairman Hwang Taeseop?
That's right.
Fascinating.
I like the fact you're not a mere stranger.
But can you tell me the reason why
you must defeat Hwang Jeongyeon?
Because my mother's death...
was caused by what Hwang
Jeongyeon and Yoo Gyeongok did to her.
I will mercilessly trample on them.
I will force great misery upon them,
and avenge my late mother.
Revenge can be quite
the collateral, at times.
Will you accept me?
Sit down, for starters.
This is what Hwang
Jeongyeon is doing these days.
Her intent is that of
establishing a credit institution.
And of course that is
something we don't exactly approve of.
First, I leave Hwang Jeongyeon to you.
Get in her way.
Would you be up for the job?
I will give it my very best.
What? Cha Soojeong?
And who would that be?
A singer?
We're almost there.
Will take a minute.
What's the matter?
This singer called Cha
Soojeong is asking to meet me.
If it's Cha Soojeong, I've heard
her on the radio a few times myself.
Seems like she's becoming
really popular these days,
- should we ask her to sign...
- Just worry about driving.
All right.
- Congressman JO Pilyeon -
Miss Cha...
So you were Cha Soojeong?
Give this money to Minwoo.
So you two were meeting behind my back.
I told you to live as
if you were dead,
and you become a singer
and pester me instead?
I see you haven't changed.
The reason I'm giving
you this money instead...
is to make sure Minwoo never
shows up before me again.
I suggest you quit your
singing career and move abroad.
Don't delude yourself.
Since I didn't leave Minwoo
because I was afraid of you.
What?
And you know why...
I never told Minwoo
about what you did to me?
Because being disappointed by your
own family would be too much to endure,
since you are the only
people Minwoo can rely on.
If you consider yourself a father...
If you for a single minute could consider that,
then wake up and look at how much
suffering your son is going through.
- Shut that insolent little mouth of yours!
- Watch your language.
Don't force me to seek revenge.
Revenge?!
And you little tramp
would get revenge against me?
Coming here was a grave mistake.
Since you'll soon find out
how scary and cruel life can get.
- Get her out of my face.
- All right.
Yes.
Ohh... Chief Oh.
No, go ahead.
Tell me.
Let's go.
I told you I couldn't care less
whether Lee Seongmo dies or not!
People don't die so easily.
A little torture
won't kill someone like him.
If you insist,
just take a step back.
I said if anyone sets
him free, I'll be the one!
Is that clear?
Those fools...
Lee Seongmo.
I'm sure the number is right.
He's a chief there.
I'm sorry, there
is no such person here.
Hello?
Big Oppa...
What on earth happened to you?
Seongmo Oppa...
So you're going to invite
Cha Soojeong to the event?
Why... Are you a fan, too?
That's surprising?!
You even have a favorite singer...
Cha Soojeong...
is the younger sister
I lost in my childhood.
What?
Then... That kiddo from
back then is Cha Soojeong?!
Yes, I'm Lee Gangmo of
Hangang Construction.
Little Oppa...
Ohh, Miju.
What's wrong with your voice?
Oppa... Can we meet?
Where are you now?
All right.
Will be there in a moment.
Sorry, Jeongyeon.
I'll have to go.
Miju?!
Miju...
Is anything wrong?
Where is Seongmo now?
I guess something urgent
came up in the provinces.
I've heard he might die!
He's being tortured!
You knew it, right?
Where is Seongmo now?
Uh? What is happening to him?
Miju.
Listen well.
Seongmo Oppa...
Get a hold of yourself and listen to me.
Lee Miju!
I will rescue him.
That is what I'm doing now.
So don't you worry, Miju.
Just believe in me.
Got it?
What should I do?
He's in danger, what can I do?
Just... Don't worry about a thing,
and just stay by my side.
Thinking about you
is helping him as well.
Seongmo Oppa...
But how did you find out?
Who told you about him?
I went to meet Minwoo's father,
and I heard him talking about it.
You met Jo Pilyeon?
Is Jo Minwoo bothering you again?
It's all over.
You don't need to worry, Oppa.
Yes...
Yes, Sir!
All right, Sir.
I will do that.
Seongmo...
Seongmo!
I just answered...
Who is behind all this?
I just followed my superior's orders...
Seongmo, are you all right?
Help him out of here.
All right.
Seongmo, let's go.
Careful...
If I knew they'd take you there,
I would have acted a lot earlier.
Forgive me, Seongmo.
It's nothing.
Did you find the account?
Your allegations haven't
been cleared yet.
So until the account shows up,
you'll have to remain confined here.
I see.
Seongmo.
As a condition for setting you free,
I promised it to the ANSP director.
That I would find the account in a week.
Just send me back there.
I don't want you to
face dishonor because of me.
Let me handle this.
Just focus on recovering
and don't worry about it.
Keep him in check,
and there is no need to purposely stop
any contacts with the outside.
Just keep track of everything he does.
Yes, all right.
Gangmo...
Miju...
Are you out of your mind?
Soojeong is a singer!
How can you let her go by herself!
D... Director, I'm really sorry.
Send everyone out to find her.
Now!
Yes!
Miju!
Where have you been?
What have you been doing all this time?
I apologize.
I had something to take care of.
Did you cry?
Let's talk about that later.
We need to go somewhere together.
The fund-raising event
for the Seoul Olympics?!
Did Miju really get invited there?
A who's who of the financial
and political world will be there.
Not to mention the attention
it will get from the press.
You must become the star of the night.
Is that clear?
You must be the queen of
that fund-raising event.
Cha Soojeong!
You really hit the jackpot.
How can they give such an
opportunity to a newcomer like you?
But, where are we going now?
We'll meet with the organizers.
That's impressive.
So you planned all this?
You will come as well, right?
You put my name right on top...
How could I not participate?!
Thank you.
Make sure all the other
congressmen join us as well.
But... These opposition party
members are the issue,
considering the ruling
party members involved.
I thought that it would make
this event a lot more meaningful that way.
What Jeongyeon says is right.
It's right at a time like this
that the two parties should gather,
or else when would they ever meet?
That was my intent as well.
But who is this singer
you invited, Cha Soojeong?
You've come, Congressman Oh.
Director Yoo.
But, who is this lady?
That's quite a beauty.
Introduce yourself.
How are you?
My name is Cha Soojeong.
Cha Soojeong?
Then, that singer who
was invited to this event?
Here's this event's
host, Director Hwang Jeongyeon.
Nice to meet you.
It's a pleasure.
And here's Deputy
Mayor Han Myeongseok.
How are you?
Ahh... Yes...
You really should
be thankful to the deputy.
What?
He was behind all
your recent TV and radio gigs.
What is this?
Was there such a side to you?
Excuse me...
We've known each other for thirty years.
But I've never seem him like this?!
Aren't you going in?
Ahh... Yes... Something
urgent suddenly came up.
Were you looking for me, Deputy?
Right... Drive the
congressman home, will you?
I'll grab a taxi.
Deputy...
Deputy!
By any chance, is Cha Soojeong here?
Is that the reason
he's acting like that?
He's always so fierce no matter what,
but strangely, it all suddenly
changes whenever he sees her.
By any chance, the man who always
sent flowers after every concert...
That's right.
The deputy sent them.
I haven't had so
much fun in a long time.
Miss Soojeong.
You're more fun to hang out
with than I could possibly imagine.
Be careful, Congressman.
Thank you, Soojeong.
I've never seen him
in such a jovial mood before.
Shall we have a drink together?
What?
Yes.
Let's do that.
Can you handle drinks?
A little.
I know you well.
Know me how...
So you're Gangmo's sister?
You know him?
We even met before.
Although you were so little back
then, I doubt you'd remember.
When was that?
Then, should we eat just one?
Go ahead and eat.
They're still warm.
It's all right.
Go ahead.
Aren't you going to?
Yeah... I'll wait for Mommy.
Must feel great.
What?
Having your mother by your side.
Why, don't you have a mother?
I remember!
How is this possible?!
I'm so glad you remember.
So did you find your mother?
You were looking for her back then...
I'm sorry.
I'm so tactless...
It's okay.
Just call me by name, Eonni.
You're friends with Gangmo,
of course you should.
Should I?
All right, Soojeong.
How about a toast?
But, wasn't your name Lee Miju?
That's right.
You even remember that?
I've heard your call earlier today.
My brother Seongmo is in danger.
Gangmo and I are planning something.
It will all go well.
Is there anything I can do to help you?
Even you are helping us...
I'm his sister and there is
nothing I have done to help...
Maybe you can do something after all.
What is it?
If we could only rescue him,
I would do anything.
Come eat at home a
little more often, will you?
See how nice it is to eat all together?
So you're opening a boiler factory?
We will begin the
construction very soon.
What is this?
It's... money?!
It's Minwoo's.
What is that money for?
A certain Cha Soojeong handed it to me.
Who is Cha Soojeong?
And what did you tell her?
She seems full of resentment.
Felt like she was treating
you like a bug to stomp on.
I asked you what you told her.
She's already forgotten you.
- You're the problem.
- You're responsible for that!
Hey... Minwoo!
You're the one who forced that on Miju.
I can't stand the
fact she became a singer.
Since you'd get to see her
every time she shows up on TV.
Dad...
Better to deal with the problem
at the root from the very beginning.
You won't see her on TV from now on.
You just try to bother Miju again.
I'll cut my ties with you once and for all.
H... Hey.... Minwoo!
Minwoo!
The son can never cut such ties.
It's up to the father to abandon his child.
Are all the preparations complete?
It already started.
What is your plan?
Our goal is to gather three
members from each party,
and make them form a six-man committee
supporting the constitutional amendment.
And how are you going to convince
all those ruling party members?
This was sent to you, Congressman.
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
- Park Hongseok -
Hello?
Have you received what I sent you?
Who are you?
A citizen who wants a democratic Korea.
I will soon give you further instructions.
Unless you want the
Blue House to get the original,
I suggest you don't go back on
your word regarding the amendment.
Look... Listen to me!
Yes?
Just answer my question,
Congressman Kang.
Who do you think you
owe that golden badge to?
Of... Of course...
to our people.
Then, do you by any chance know what
our people most wish for right now?
Answer.
Are you referring to
direct presidential elections?
I see you knew.
So you're taking them along
the ride whether they like it or not.
It is all thanks to the
agreement you made them sign.
That's for the ruling party,
but how will you deal
with the opposition members?
With the kind of
surveillance they're dealing with,
even approaching
them won't be easy...
Honey.
Let me introduce her.
She's Director Hwang Jeongyeon.
- Ahh... The one who sent us the painting...
- It's a true honor to finally meet you,
Congressman Jang.
An honor?!
I'm facing so much pressure these days.
- Congressman Choi Hakgil, if I'm not mistaken?
- Yes... That's right.
- And Congressman Oh Sucheol.
- Yes, nice to meet you.
After only seeing you on TV
or newspapers, I finally get to meet you.
I guess sometimes getting
arrested has its positives after all.
I even get to meet
people who recognize me...
Since she's been
proclaimed host of the event,
that's going to greatly
help her approach them.
Jeongyeon is doing great.
I see.
So how are you going
to rescue your brother?
If things go according to plan,
he'll be released
after Jeongyeon's event.
Fishing here has made
me lose track of time.
Now it's time for you
to take a step forward.
- Student Demonstration in
Support of Direct Presidential Elections -
Hey... Aren't you guys hungry?
Should we order some chicken?
I'm fine.
I'll give you the
money, so go get some.
Where did I put my wallet...
What's going on?
Seonbaenim!
Open the door!
Chairman.
The PI sent us all his data
regarding Cha Soojeong.
Isn't that President Lee Gangmo?
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
If we want to use Min Honggi,
he needs a let-out.
Didn't you have a copy of it?
Are you telling me you didn't make one?
Is that true?
Opposition party members said so themselves.
It's legit.
So you get an apartment from Lee Gangmo,
gigs on TV from Han Myeongseok...
Must you really do this to me...
Get out, Lee Gangmo!
If you are the culprit,
I suggest you pull that trigger.
What people call suspicion...
You either let go of it once and for all,
or keep suspecting to the very end.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com