Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ Episode 14 ~
Who are you?
Chairman Park,
you're better than I thought?
What are you people...
We have something to investigate,
so you'll have to follow us.
- What?!
- And you are?
- Proceed!
- What are you doing?
How dare you?
At least tell us the reason!
Who do you think you're dealing with?
What's the matter?
Just performing our duties.
Do you even know who
the VIPs we have here are?
If we interfered with your business,
let me apologize.
They're KCIA agents.
The Central Intelligence Agency?
That's right.
I have nothing to do with this, Dad.
I didn't do it.
Honey... Even the subway issue
concluded in your favor.
Just forgive Jeongshik, will you?
Honey...
You said you wanted to
come back to work, didn't you?
Yes, Dad.
I'll give my very best.
- Gangmo.
- Yes, Chairman.
Jeongshik will work in
Goods & Services with you.
Show him what kind of
trade we're dealing with.
- Goods & Services?!
- Dad...
He needs to taste once and for all
what hard work feels like.
Still, be that as it may,
are you forcing chores on our Jeongshik?
If he doesn't like it, he can
pack his bags and get out of here!
Aigoo... You're really something.
How can you treat your
one and only son like that?
What do you think you're doing?
Who are you people?
I said no!
What is the matter?
Chairman Hwang.
You'll have to follow us and
collaborate with our investigations.
What are you investigating?
I did nothing that would
warrant a KCIA investigation.
Escort him out.
Let go, you fool!
I'll come on my own,
so get your hands off of me!
I hope it wasn't Director
Jo Pilyeon who sent you here?
You'll find out when we get there.
- What is all this about?
- Ajeosshi...
How can you do this to him?
What is all this?
Why would they take you to the KCIA?
What did he ever do wrong?
What's the reason?
Stop acting like a ninny.
Let's go, or we'll wake up
the entire neighborhood.
- Dear...
- Dad.
Just in case, Jeongyeon,
you preside over tomorrow's board meeting.
Dad...
Gangmo.
- Help out Jeongyeon.
- Chairman...
Don't you worry.
I'll be back in no time.
Let's go.
Nothing will happen to him.
That's right, Ma'am.
No matter how serious this is,
he's innocent anyway.
I can't really
figure out what's going on.
Let's just go back in, Jeongshik.
- Come with me.
- Yes, all right.
The chairman?
What is going on?
I'm one step late...
You should be aware of what's going on.
Why did they arrest my father?
Are you telling me Dad is involved
with Chairman Hong's account?
He presided over
the construction committee,
so his name surely
ended up on that account.
Does that mean he might be charged?
First he takes all that money,
and now he has the guts to
blame everything on my father?
Seems like the situation
got a little complicated.
But don't worry too much.
It's the chairman I'm working for,
so nothing serious will happen.
Jeongyeon came here as my woman.
And they say it runs in the family...
Since when did you
start seducing Jo Minwoo?
What?
Minwoo.
Let me give you an advice.
You know, her real mother?!
I don't care whether
you believe me or not.
And that's because I love you.
Nothing will happen.
Tell your family not to worry.
Thank you for your help.
I never imagined Dad would
bribe his way to the top.
It's not something he's proud of,
since he was forced to do it,
for the survival of his company.
I know.
And that only makes me feel worse.
Since Minwoo's father works
for the KCIA, he'll help us out.
Jo Minwoo is not to be trusted.
Director Jo might in fact
be behind all this.
What are you trying to say?
Why would he?
I'll look into it.
KCIA agents searched
Chairman Hong's house?!
Aigoo... As if that would help them...
They turned the damned thing upside down.
So that means they still haven't
found Chairman Hong's account.
They said to call them when they
find it, so I guess that's true.
So how many people were they?
Just his wife... No... Wait...
With the housemaid, that's two in total.
One of them must be carrying that account.
Seemed like they had no idea?!
You come with me, starting tomorrow.
What, again?!
Forget it, you go by yourself.
I'm starving in here...
So you have no problem letting
all your efforts go in vain?
If we don't get our hands
on that account,
forget the subway construction,
it's all over!
So at least let's see
some food on the table.
Let's talk again after he gives me
a decent meal, I'm starving here...
Isn't that right?
Are you out of your mind?
What kind of mess
are you trying to make?
It's just as the report
you received suggests.
As the title suggests,
it's a "national development fund."
Don't you know it's not just me,
but it's closely tied to the president?
Hong Gipyo already made
contacts with the opposition.
What?
Did they already
get a hold of all this?
If the opposition clings onto this,
they'll turn public sentiment
against the president in no time.
So when even keeping quiet is risky,
what would you accomplish
by revealing this to everyone?
There is such a thing as
"sacrificial lambs" in the Bible.
Sacrificial lamb?!
Kill one lamb,
and its blood will atone
for all your sins.
So you're suggesting we
blame all this on a scapegoat?
Think about it.
Isn't Min Honggi the only one who
directly received money from Hong Gipyo?
So, what, let's sacrifice
Director Min at the altar?
Isn't that what politics is all about?
One hand takes you in,
the other brings punishment.
What do you think about this?
The president always mentions our war
on corruption in every single speech.
You really are scary.
I'm only doing this
for our country's sake.
Just ignore all this and leave it to me.
Still, let's keep things clean.
A single slip,
and all our heads will roll.
When all this is said and done, I'll run
for the elections in Min Honggi's place.
Good job, Chanseong.
What do you plan to do with this?
It's easy to guess what
Jo Pilyeon's true motives are.
We can't allow him to
just eliminate Min Honggi...
and turn Hwang Taeseop
into a lackey of his.
Be careful, Seonbaenim.
From the very first moment I joined
the KCIA, I put my life on the line.
But forget that,
I'm thankful for all
the help you've given me.
I told you.
I must avenge my brother, too.
Hyung!
Hyung...
They'll bury me in the state
cemetery like my father, right?
Hyung...
Hyung.
Hyung!
If it weren't for you,
I would have never learned
that my brother died that way.
I'm sorry, Chanseong.
It's not your fault.
I will make Jo Pilyeon pay
for what he did to my brother.
Jo Pilyeon even went as far as
arresting all committee members.
This is not the time for indifference!
What am I supposed to do,
barge in and interfere with KCIA duty?
If that secret account is ever exposed,
it'll be the end for all of us.
Then, take Hong Gipyo in
and investigate on your own.
I'm busy, so I'll have to hang up.
Congressman.
Congressman!
Goddamn...
Who is it?
What is it, now?
It's intel proving how Hong Gipyo's
maternal uncle defected to the north.
So?
As long as it's corruption, it's the
Inspection Department's jurisdiction,
but if it involves espionage, isn't that
a case for our Intelligence Department?
So you're going to corner
Hong Gipyo for espionage?
The director will
assign this case to us.
What's the reason?
I'm asking you why you're helping me.
I'd like to leave the KCIA as well.
Are you implying you'll abandon
Jo Pilyeon and follow me?
Because I feel your path
to success will be much quicker.
Bribes?!
I devote my hard-earned
money to your cause,
and now you just call it bribes?
Forgot who made your business flourish?
Then, arrest everyone
else involved, at least.
Once the account is in my hands,
that is what I plan to do.
Although it will only be
Min Honggi and no one else.
Do you understand now?
All the money you donated has
nothing to do with the government.
You gave it to Min Honggi.
You're nothing but Min Honggi's sponsor.
Spon...
So, now that you're holding the knife,
you play judge, jury and executioner?
Because we need a scapegoat.
And that could be you, Hwang Taeseop.
Director.
Aren't you being excessive?
Let's make things clear.
The first to abandon me
like a pair of worn-out shoes,
Hwang Taeseop,
it was none other than you.
You were talking about
running as an independent,
so if I have to give you my own blood,
we at least need
a good chance of success.
Since when have you been so calculating?
Director...
I will get to the bottom of this.
And you're no exception, Hwang Taeseop.
Director!
What?
Min Honggi?
Here... Let's go.
What do you think you're doing?
We'll have to take
Chairman Hong into custody.
And on whose authority?
He's suspected of espionage.
What? Espionage?!
As you're well aware,
northern propaganda is our jurisdiction.
So you'll have to
step aside, I'm afraid.
You son of a...
Can you see this?
I just got the director's
consent on my way here.
If you have any objection,
go discuss it with him.
Escort him out.
If we lose Hong Gipyo,
then our efforts will go in vain.
We must find that account.
We already looked for it, but...
Even if you have to question his
whole clan and in-laws, just find it!
Here, have some coffee.
You will not be subjected to any more
torture here, so you can rest assured.
If you're going to ask about any account,
just resign yourself.
The only way you and I will survive...
is if you give me that account.
Is that so?
Then, why don't you just kill me?
That will be much quicker.
Here... At least a spoon.
Keep this up and you will really die!
You haven't had
anything to eat all day.
You don't like rice gruel?
Should I mix rice with water, then?
You know where that account is, right?
Wh...What are you talking about?
How could I possibly know that?
No... You know.
It's you...
Right?
The chairman entrusted it to you, right?
I said it's not me.
Without that account,
they said he'll die!
Miju...
Let's bring it to them,
and take the chairman back home, uh?
Ma'am.
If this keeps up,
I'll get a heart attack.
Miju.
They said he'll live,
if we bring that account to them!
That's all a lie.
The chairman said the opposite.
What?
What did you just say?
So you really have it, don't you?
Right?
The chairman told me to
never give that to anyone.
That if we hide the account,
nothing will happen since
they'll have no evidence,
so he told me to hold it at all cost.
And if my husband dies?
What are you going to do, then?
If I give that account to them,
the chairman will be in trouble.
Honey...
I fell asleep.
Go have a rest.
I'll continue questioning him.
Never seen anyone so stubborn before.
I'll go get some shut-eye,
so just keep an eye on him for me.
You can wake up now.
Nothing you try will be of any use,
since I never wrote any account.
Do you know when Shilla
unified the Three Kingdoms?
Find the year when Shilla
unified the Three Kingdoms.
That will tell you the
amount you're looking for.
Remember my voice?
Then...
You are that...
Who are you?
Who are you, to just enter
someone else's property like that?
Are you deaf?
I asked who you are.
Come in.
She's agreed to meet you.
How have you been?
No one inside here
knows of our dealings.
And I will remain the
only one here who can help you.
Is there any way for me
to get out of here alive?
Leave that account to me.
Jo Pilyeon will try everything
to get his hands on that.
Where is that account now?
You must tell us.
Who is keeping that account?
Chairman Hwang was taken in as well.
If the KCIA is looking for that,
neither Chairman Hong nor
Chairman Hwang will be safe.
We don't know.
Ma'am.
She said she doesn't know.
What are we supposed to do,
make things up?
Ma'am.
We're only doing this to help you.
When I find the account I will call you,
so please leave.
I have to clean, so get going.
What are you waiting for?
- Hurry up and leave.
- You little... We're having an important...
Leave.
That housemaid looks suspicious.
The housemaid?!
Ehh... What are you saying?
Think he'd entrust that to a housemaid?
If put in Chairman Hong's shoes,
I would never give it to my family.
That housemaid is the only one
people wouldn't suspect.
Right... Now that I think
about it, makes sense?!
- Take them all in.
- Yes, Sir.
What's wrong with you?
Where are you taking us?
Let me go!
What did we do wrong?
I said let go!
Let's go.
Account or whatever, we're done.
If they even arrested his family,
it's all over, isn't it?
So Director Jo was the one
who arrested my father?
Is your father the one behind all this?
What am I supposed to tell you?
How could he do that to my father?
I think it's a relief, on the contrary?
At least,
I can try to change his mind.
What?
I'm sure there's a reason
why he did all this.
It'll take some time.
Is it because I refused your proposal?
If this is retaliation for that,
isn't it a little crude?
He's not the kind of man who can't
separate business and personal.
Just trust me on this.
I'll take care of this all.
There's nothing...
Nothing at all.
Hey...
The KCIA left empty-handed,
think we would find anything?
Even if it's not the account itself,
there must be some kind of hint.
Search the living room.
I should just steal
everything and run away...
What could possibly be here?
I miss you, my princes.
When we meet, what's the
first thing I should do for you?
Should I sing you a song?
Nah...
I think I'll just let you embrace me
as I abandon myself in tears.
Gangmo.
Quick, come.
Hurry up!
They said they're KCIA.
Where has everyone gone?
The KCIA already took them in.
We're too late.
I see there's more than one
KCIA team working on this?
Don't think you should
be here in the first place?
What were you doing in
someone else's empty house?
I see no reason
why I should answer that.
Getting people to
answer questions is my job.
Should I open your mouth our way?
You're here for the account.
So you're going to use that
to save Hwang Taeseop?
A word of warning.
Get out of this while you still can.
Or you'll walk down a path of no return.
Who really are you?
Who are you helping and why?
Gangmo...
Are you out of your mind?
This is the last warning.
Don't ever cross paths with me again.
Next time we meet,
you will die by my hands.
Hey... Do you know that man?
He's the man who pointed a gun at me.
What... A gun?!
Did he really point a gun at you?
Let's just leave this place.
I'm done with this.
Let's go, hurry up!
I'm leaving.
Write a memo for me.
Where is the account?
I'm just their housemaid.
Would you entrust something
so important to a maid like me?
Where is that account?
What about Hong Gipyo's wife?
She keeps fainting,
so questioning her is hard.
How did it go with Hong Gipyo?
It'll be hard to get anything out of him.
Isn't that all the better?
You never know with torture.
Before he opens his mouth,
we must get our hands on that account.
But I think it would
be wiser to release them.
What are you trying to say?
The moment he learns
you have his family in custody,
Hong Gipyo might start
talking to Director Min.
"I know nothing."
Ohh... Seonbaenim.
How is it going?
I'll be transferred back to
the Inspection Department in no time,
so don't give me the cold shoulder.
How could I?
See you around.
Miju.
Tomorrow morning,
someone will come looking for you.
Give him the account.
Only that can help me get out of here.
Ma'am... You can have this.
At the auction,
you said you wanted that.
Ohh my...
Fits like a glove!
See? What did I tell you?
Told you it would look
great on her, didn't I?
Aigoo... Tell me about it!
It looks tailor-made for you!
I don't need any of this,
so take it back.
Ma'am...
Please, release my husband.
If the director puts in a good word,
he'll be released right away.
As if all that overworking wasn't
already taking a toll on his health...
I hear your daughter rejected
Minwoo's proposal straight away?
What?
She refused his proposal?!
You know? I raised my son
into a very fine young man.
Even when my husband talked
about tying the knot with you,
deep down I was against it.
But what's so great about you people,
to look down on us?
Ma'am...
Anyhow, this is insulting,
so don't ever call me for this again.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
We can certainly reconsider
the marriage issue.
Forget it.
Jeongyeon, she will ruin us all.
That rotten little wench...
It's all your fault.
You dare refuse Minwoo's proposal?
It has nothing to do
with Dad being arrested.
Why wouldn't it?
Do you know what
Director Jo's wife told me?
That this mess all happened
because of you.
You'll force death upon
the father of my child!
- And Minwoo?
- He said he'll be working late.
Have some tea.
Thank you.
Hello?
Ohh... Minwoo.
What?!
Jeongyeon is meeting Dad?
A drink will be better.
Don't you think?
This is the liquor your father
gave to me as a present.
I promised him I'd save it
for a nice occasion.
The aroma is really nice.
Is it something I can put an end to?
I've heard that my father
could be in danger.
If it's a matter
I can solve on my own,
let me know how.
I don't know what they told you, but...
I know that my father refused your offer.
Both funding your elections,
and agreeing to our marriage.
You almost make me sound like
a shameless opportunist.
If what I heard is right, it shouldn't
be too far off from the truth.
Or did I just misunderstand you?
Chairman Hwang made two mistakes.
One was sponsoring a corrupt
official just for his own benefit.
- As for that...
- And another...
was not living up to the code
of loyalty we are bound to.
Forget any business matter,
but when a man betrays your trust,
that's unforgivable.
And whose sake is this "loyalty" for?
I understand.
You're still too young
to understand that concept.
Because you wouldn't possibly know...
that between men,
loyalty is everything.
So what you want to say is that
you won't release my father.
No.
That no self-interest will
interfere with my investigations.
I suggest you go back.
The two mistakes my father committed...
No.
The two conditions you gave him.
I will fulfill them.
We will support your candidacy
until you're elected as congressman.
And as for the other condition,
would marrying your son suffice?
I will.
What's stopping me?
It's just a strategic marriage, anyway.
But you must release
my father immediately.
You can do that, right?
I planned to leave the personal
out of this investigation,
but you force me to
follow my interests again.
I'll consider this
negotiation over, and leave.
I thought I told you
to trust me on this?
You're no match for
someone like my father.
He's the hardest man to please.
I made the right decision coming here.
I finally found out how hard my
father had it with him, all this time.
Feels like I rid myself of that
thick layer which was blinding me.
"So this is what the real world is like!"
Extend my gratitude to your father.
I'll drive you home.
So all you wanted from me
was my father's money?
I wanted to trust you.
But whatever you say
from now on, I won't.
What did you say to Jeongyeon?
She stuck to the
strict necessary and left.
Quite a fierce and clever young lady.
Care for a drink?
There certainly was a way,
without having to resort to this.
All that matters is the quickest way,
everything else means nothing.
She agreed to marry you.
I know you might not like her yet,
but give it a try.
I think I might soon
fall in love with her?!
Love?!
Can't I?
She mentioned the words
"strategic marriage."
"It's just a strategic marriage,
so what's stopping me?"
Don't let sentiments derail
you away from your objectives.
Thank you, Dad.
For going to such lengths
to make my marriage possible.
You're all wet?
You could have called me,
if you had no umbrella.
Come in.
Have you had dinner?
If you didn't, should I
make you some ramen noodles?
Think I'll have to get married.
I'm on my way back from
meeting with Minwoo's father.
I gave it a thought while coming back...
There's no reason why I shouldn't.
I wasn't going to get married anyway.
Because it has no meaning to me.
I'll just think of it as a business deal.
Compared to the bribes my father
handed out during his career,
it's nothing much.
Don't do it.
If that's the kind of marriage
you'll get into, just don't!
I'll help the chairman get out.
There's no need to bow down to people
like them, or let them trample on you!
You just...
Just have faith in me.
Aren't you tired of that?
All you ever do to me is giving.
You never received anything in return.
All I am to you is a burden.
Haven't you had enough of that?
I sure have.
But marrying Jo Minwoo... No way.
Why?
Why would you stop my marriage?
Because I...
don't want you to marry.
You have that account, right?
You have it, right?
Wait a moment.
You're giving him the account?
Read this.
It's the chairman's handwriting, see?
Since he'll be released
if we give them the account,
you don't need to worry.
Honey...
Follow me.
Welcome.
How can I help you?
Where did your housemaid go?
She left for the market this morning.
Is anything the matter?
Have you read the memo we left you?
Memo?
You must have received
a memo from Chairman Hong.
That... She already went
with someone else to take it?
So you gave it to someone
other than our people?
Just as it says here...
Where were they headed?
I don't really know.
Do you know who that man was?
~ National Development Fund ~
Min Honggi
~ Committee Members ~
It was the chairman
who wrote that memo, right?
When are you releasing him?
Can he come out today?
What's wrong?
Must we wait longer?
I'll drive you home.
Seonbaenim.
Follow that car.
Pull aside!
Stop the car!
Stop!
I warned you, didn't I?
That the next time we meet,
you'd die by my hands.
You can't commit murder!
He'll only cause us more
trouble if we let him go.
- Still, murder...
- Let go.
- Seonbaenim... Seonbaenim!
- Out of the way!
My brother was killed unfairly as well!
I beg you, Seonbaenim... Please.
This is a copy of the account.
I'll keep the original.
Hide it somewhere safe, and give it
back to Chairman Hong when he's out.
Then, that man from earlier on...
What happened to him?
The man I gave the account to.
Give it to me!
You finally found it!
You found the account!!
You must never reveal I was
the one who brought you this.
Don't you worry.
Well done!
It's all over now.
Aigoo... How can it be so dirty...
You little, look at you...
Make it shine.
Do you know how much they're worth?
But where's Gangmo gone all day?
Don't ask me...
"Don't ask me"?
That won't do it!
As long as I'm here,
you better get with the program!
Jeongyeon, what brings you here?
Where's Gangmo?
I don't know.
Now that I think about it,
I haven't been able to reach him all day?!
Yes?
Shideok...
Gangmo!
What's wrong with your voice?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Just stop the investigation.
What were you doing while
Min Honggi got hold of the account?
I'm sure there must be
a copy of that account.
Look, Chairman Hong.
If you're just pretending...
You have the account, right?
So what, did you
follow me all the way here?
O...ppa?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com