This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 21 -
I really didn't do anything.
What's wrong with you?
Hyungnim... Blood.
You have hemorrhoids or something?
Hyungnim! A knife.
Who is it?
Who sent you?
G...Gangmo...
It's a misunderstanding.
Was it Jo Minwoo?
Jeongshik?
Who sent you here...
to kill me?
Speak!
J...Jeongshik and...
Jo Minwoo.
Both.
What?
Help me!
Warden! Warden!!
Warden... Warden!
Oppa, you've come?
- Just got back?
- Why didn't you call me?
I had to go to the practice room,
so I'm a little late.
Is it going well?
Oppa.
Listen well and don't be shocked.
I'll soon get my debut song!
Debut song?
Yeah... The composer said he'll
give me the song he's working on now.
Does that mean our Miju
will officially become a singer?
Yeah...
Oppa. He said if I keep working hard,
he'll even let me perform solo.
Wow... You're really something?!
Miju. How about you stop working
as a bus conductor now?
Oppa will take good care of you,
so just focus on singing.
Forget it... As if you didn't spend
enough getting me this house.
It's not like I
have any expenses anyway.
You need to save money
and get married.
I want to see a little nephew soon.
After you and Gangmo get married,
only then I'll follow through.
Ohh... Listen to that.
That's why you're
still single at your age!
Have you visited Gangmo yet?
Couldn't go this week.
I'm too busy to visit him that often,
so at least you do it for me.
All right, Oppa...
Twenty-five.
Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven.
Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine.
And thirty!
Park Sotae.
Visit for you.
I wasn't expecting anyone?!
Young Master...
I can't stay here any longer.
Try to experience it yourself,
this is hell on earth!
Only looking at him gives me chills.
I can't take this anymore.
It's still too early to give up.
Who was it?
Uh?
Even you had visitors?
She's this "Miss Kim,"
from the coffeehouse
in Cheongnyang-Ri.
Ahh... That wench, and I had
even paid my tab already...
Guess that one night
left a lasting impression on her.
Crazy brat...
There are people inside
who can do the job for you.
I'll get them to work for us,
so contact their leader.
Are you Park Sotae?
Yes...
So I guess he called you?
The money?
I'm sure he must have
wired it already, check it out.
Even people like us
follow ironclad rules.
If one of my boys is not involved,
I'm not getting my hands dirty.
I'm aware of that.
Just hold him for me.
I'll take care of finishing him off.
So who are we dealing with?
Lee Gangmo is his name.
He's sharing the same cell with me.
Lee Gangmo?
Yes.
We're past the deadline already.
Have you watched that
on TV yesterday?
Cheonhye Construction's apartment ad
has the same concept as ours.
We must stop the broadcast of our ad
before they air it tomorrow.
And we'll have to postpone the opening
day to after the ad is broadcast.
Who made this mess?
I'm sure it's not anyone from our team.
Seeing how even
the CM song is the same,
it might be someone
from the record company.
They're the only one outside
the company who knew our concept.
Seek legal counsel
and prepare a lawsuit.
All right, Chief.
You'll come with me
to the record company.
We'll have to verify this firsthand.
Drive slowly, why don't you?
If we mess this up,
our sale can end up in failure.
When did you get
your driver's license?
You didn't know how to drive.
Yesterday.
Yesterday?!
You got your license yesterday?!
What's wrong with this?
Jeongyeon...
Start by changing gear,
and turn off the wipers.
- Wait...
- Should I drive?
It's all over... Bring me drinks!
Drinks!
So all the songs Lee Hayoung
released were all copied from yours?
There was even Miju's
debut song among them...
The real problem is our contract
with Manbo Construction.
If they learn it was leaked by
one of our people...
Aigoo... It will be trouble.
I see you understand the situation.
How do you explain this?
We sincerely apologize.
This is not something
a mere apology will solve.
Do you know for how long
we've been preparing this project?
One of our trainees took the songs
and ad plans he worked on,
sold them all and ran away.
Where is she now?
She moved and hid her traces.
I apologize.
I will soon get you another CM song.
We will soon file a lawsuit.
Just so you know.
- Chief...
- Wait! Chief Jo!
Seonsaengnim!
Seonsaengnim, what's wrong?
- Get a hold of yourself.
- Seonsaengnim!
Call an ambulance! Quick!
Yes... Yes.
How did it go?
How is he doing?
They said his blood pressure is high,
so he must not experience any shocks.
How did it go
with Manbo Construction?
There's no talking
to that Chief of Planning.
He refuses to withdraw the lawsuit.
Then, does this mean we'll be ruined?
Miju... How about you
try to reason with them?
What?
Last time, it seemed like their
chairman's son took a liking to you.
You never know, he might withdraw
the lawsuit if you ask him.
If we go bust, you'll have to give up
your dream of becoming a singer.
That's right, Miju.
It's a life-and-death situation,
every little thing can help.
Give it a try.
Or he might even get incarcerated.
Miju...
How about this?
Try it out.
Do I even have to dress up?
I can just dress neatly, and...
Listen to her. How are you going to
convince him if you dress plainly?
What do my clothes have
to do with convincing him?
You've still got a lot
to learn, all right.
But are these all
the cosmetics you have?
Yeah.
This won't do it.
Get up.
Where are you taking me?
Just follow us.
Now that she's all
dressed up, not too bad?!
But have you ever hit on a man?
Not really.
Of course not...
Listen well.
Men can't resist a woman's eyes.
Her eyes?!
Give him this kind of penetrating
stare for a good five seconds.
Seonhwa... I think
I'm not cut out for that.
- Let's just...
- Ehh! You...
If I only had a pretty face,
think I'd have you do it?!
The chairman's son will
fall for this, guaranteed.
Follow after me.
Just tag along.
Can't even do this?
Hey! Here he comes.
Ready to go?
Hey! What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Ohh... What the...
Oh?!
Who's this?
Isn't this country chick?!
How are you...
Wow...
You look completely different?!
But, what brings you here?
Came to see me?
Yes...
I had something to tell you.
To me?
We were heading out for lunch,
care to join us?
Follow me.
Follow him!
Remember the killer stare, all right?
Killer stare!
What are you waiting for?
Yes... I'm coming.
Are you all right?
I'm... fine...
Let's go.
What's this?
Wow... You made all this?
Looks good?!
Where are the manners in bringing food
to a restaurant trying to run a business?
If we pay for our lunch, who cares?
You're right.
Have a taste.
It's really good.
Try it out yourself.
Forget it.
What did you use, to taste so great?
It's nothing all that special,
but it still tastes great?!
Hey...
Over there.
Hey.
Aren't your eyes hurting?
Make her happy and look. Seemed so
busy throwing loving glances at you.
Really?
Now that I think about it,
you really seem to have changed?!
That's right! You need to take the
initiative if you want to make it big.
Jeongshik.
Why do you think she
made this kimbap for you?
Ahh... Right.
We filed a lawsuit against
her workplace, right?
Can't you withdraw that lawsuit?
- Why the hell not, we could surely...
- No way.
I don't remember asking you.
I'm in charge here.
- Still, the chairman's son...
- Minwoo.
Let's just withdraw it, shall we?
If her company goes bust,
she'll have nowhere...
If that's how you want to handle it,
compensate us for the damages.
Or just keep quiet about it.
Ehh... You really...
Embarrass me
in front of her, will you?
You're exactly the
kind of girl I most despise.
Vulgar little bimbos throwing their
bodies around to make life easier.
What?
Do your parents even know
the kind of life you're leading?
Makes me lose appetite, really...
Ehh... Listen to him...
Must you really talk
like that to people?
The kimbap tastes great.
That Chief of Planning
is really an annoying prick.
Miju.
Must we really do this?
It would hurt my pride
too much to bear it.
So stay out of it.
I can handle it by myself.
Did I piss you off?
Fill in the kimbap.
So you're really going to do that?
Young lady, what is all this?
What is this?
This young lady
told me to give it to you.
Where is she now?
- Hyeeun's You Couldn't Possibly Know -
You couldn't possibly know
how much I loved you.
As time goes by,
you'll end up regretting all this.
What's with you?
I was rude to you last time.
I'm counting on you, Chief.
So now there's nothing you
won't do to get what you want.
You've already eaten them all?
I did try to make them tasty...
What are you,
kidding around with me?
You think this will convince me
to withdraw the lawsuit?
Help us out just this once, Chief.
We're all poor people.
We've been struggling so much, and only
now a little hope was on the horizon...
I couldn't care less.
How kind of him...
Fine! Let's see
who gets the last laugh!
I can't just give up now
after what you've done.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
Your reputation precedes you,
Seonsaengnim.
I apologize for not
paying you a visit earlier.
If money is the issue,
a late visit can only be a blessing.
You've got a point.
From what I hear, Manbo Construction
was funding your campaign?!
Money is quite the strange entity.
The more you use it,
the more thirst you get.
And the more you make,
the more you desire.
I hear most of the influential people
in our area are customers of yours.
So it's not money you need,
but my connections?
Of course, if you add money to
the package, it'd truly be a blessing.
I'm not someone who
beats around the bush.
If you extend me your help,
what you'll get in return will make
any interest pale in comparison.
The tea got cold.
Sir.
Why don't you get up?
This discussion has
gotten a bit long-winded.
If he upset you in any way,
allow me to apologize on his behalf.
He never involves
himself with politics.
That's good to hear.
Tell him hearing this lifted
a big weight off my shoulders.
I'm sure he'll understand.
What the hell were you doing while
Cheonhye Construction aired that?
I apologize, Chairman.
Forget the apologies
and find a solution!
Giving up on TV commercials and focusing
our efforts on radio and newspapers...
That's out of the question.
We'll go on with the
commercial as planned.
Seems like it might be
a little too late for that?
All we need to do is match
the sale's start date.
I'll go ahead with it, Chairman.
But if we lose all other
media exposure because of it,
we might even end up
with unsold apartments.
What Chief Jo said is right.
You can't just fight with your back
to the wall whenever you feel like it.
But I think this is
exactly time to do that.
And that's because our apartment
sales will decide the fate...
of our status in the
sector rankings this year.
Be it TV commercials or leaflets,
you better deal with it!
But I don't want to see
any apartment go unsold!
What is leading you to
make such reckless decisions?
I'll take care of it, so stop worrying.
Don't you sleep at night?
Are you going to starve all day?
We have no time, none!
I'll go on without food or sleep.
I started this,
so I'll take it to the end.
Is this because of Gangmo as well?
Are you so obsessed with work
just because of Gangmo?
Because everything I do for Gangmo
is also for my own sake.
What?
You just wait.
By the time Gangmo is released,
nobody in this company will doubt my skills.
I told you, didn't I?
That Lee Gangmo has changed.
I'm no longer your fiance
or anything else.
Still...
I don't want to see
you get hurt any longer.
You've had to go through a lot.
Life hasn't been kind to you.
Give it a rest.
Spare me that kind of talk.
Did you fight again?
How did it go with Lee Gangmo?
Uh?!
Why are there no news whatsoever?
No worries.
I entrusted this to a ruthless man.
He'll get things
done for sure, this time.
Have a nice meal, Hyungnim.
Why?
Think I'd run out of ways
to catch my prey?
Screaming will make no difference.
Thanks to these fellas here,
nobody is around.
You were never destined
to become a decent person.
You still don't get it, do you?
Welcome to your funeral,
you bastard.
They'll only exploit you,
after which you'll be
abandoned like trash.
You miserable twat,
still not having a clue...
Fellas.
Hold this prick for me.
There's no time to waste, hurry up!
What... What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you people?
So you're telling me he
was a childhood friend of yours?
Forget everything else,
but people betraying their friends...
They more than deserve to die.
Ga...Gangmo!
Gangmo!
You sure have little luck...
Of all people you could
ask me to get rid of, him?!
What a shame...
I... I... I'm sorry!
Forgive me just this once!
I let money blind me!
Forgive me, I beg you!
Mom! Mom...
Gangmo! Don't kill me...
Gangmo!
I, Park Sotae!
Have dealt with retards
like you all my life.
I'll set the whole
damned thing on fire!
Forgive me!
Gangmo! Gangmo, please...
Why?
Letting this miserable fool go
just because you were friends?
Exactly because
he's a miserable fool.
Aigoo... You miserable fool.
You at least met a good friend.
Hello.
They're really good, aren't they?
Come have some kimbap.
Go ahead and eat.
But who's bringing kimbap every day?
Ohh... The chief.
What?!
Don't even get us started.
He's spoiling us these days.
- They're so firm.
- Tell me about it. Would never tire of them.
- Wow... They're really great.
- Especially when they offer them to you.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Isn't that her? Country chick.
Hurry up... Here...
All right! Let's go.
She was a conductor?!
Don't tell me...
Stay put and keep your head up.
No need. I'll handle it.
I said stay put.
If I go wash up it'll be fine.
Jeongyeon. Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon.
Jeongyeon. Wake up.
Jeongyeon!
Jeongyeon is still not home?
She spent the night at work
yesterday as well,
how could she be
so obsessed with work?
Ohh Ohh... Really...
Do you ever work late?
Show some dedication
like Jeongyeon, will you?
Mom...
Why are you always bugging me?
- Agasshi!
- Wake up, Agasshi!
Agasshi, what's wrong?
What's this?
What's the matter?
What's wrong with Jeongyeon?
She must have overworked herself.
Are you telling me she fainted?
We just came back from the hospital.
A good night of sleep
and she'll be fine.
Bring her to her room.
I'll take her.
Leave it.
Don't worry.
Ahh... Really...
Aigoo...
Why would young people
like you do this...
She's hell bent on it, all right.
Feeling better?
What happened?
You fainted.
Collapsed right out
of the blue, get it?
It was just a nosebleed, that's all.
Sleep deprivation, malnutrition,
and overexertion to boot.
Don't mind about my business.
If you don't want me to,
then you shouldn't have given me
the chance by making such mistakes.
Shouldn't you have a happy
married life with Lee Gangmo?
But you look even more tired and
unhappy than you've ever been before.
You're mistaken.
I've never been so happy.
Don't come to work tomorrow,
and rest at home.
Gangmo.
You haven't changed, right?
When we meet again, you'll smile
for me like you always did, right?
Gangmo...
What?!
He failed?!
It's probably going to be hard
while he's in prison.
What do we do now?
We can't let him keep
that land for himself.
Ahh... Park Sotae, that useless fool.
Considering the situation,
we'll have to use our last card.
You're telling me there's
another way to get rid of him?
What is it? Uh?
Tell me!
I'm dying of curiosity here!
What is it?
Ahh... Minwoo, you'll have to
help your father's campaign.
Yes... I'll soon
join his campaign camp.
- Right...
- By the way,
it seemed like you've been
wanting to tell me something?
Was I mistaken?
Mom, can you leave us
alone a moment?
What could it be,
if you can't even tell me?
Have a nice day.
I have a favor to ask you.
Is it because of the Gaepo mudflats?
Yes.
Guess Lee Gangmo
must be in your way?
We tried all sorts of things,
but to no avail whatsoever.
Spare some time later this evening.
We need to go somewhere together.
How about it?
You can do that for me, can't you?
If we're dealing
with such despicable scum,
it's only natural he'll need to be
reeducated, for the good of our society.
Thanks.
We're in full election campaign,
so I'm a little busy.
Once the campaign is over,
I'll treat you for real.
Don't mention it, Seonbaenim.
We were struggling
to reach our quota as it is,
so I should be thankful,
on the contrary.
- Here... Have a drink.
- Yes.
How did it go?
Any good news?
Not just Lee Gangmo,
but we'll be able to deal
with Park Sotae as well.
But, if they're sent there,
is it true they'll never come out alive?
Whatever you're imagining,
it's much, much worse.
Is it that bad?
We can forget Lee Gangmo for good.
Is Seongmo doing well?
Yeah... Seems like he can't
find the time to visit you often.
Right... Big Oppa gave me some money,
so I bought you a few things.
So your preparations to
become a singer are going well?
Uh?
You said you might debut soon.
Yeah...
It's going well.
I'm sorry, Miju.
Why?
I should be taking care of you,
but you're the one
who's looking after me.
If you're really sorry, worry about
coming out safe and in good health.
Then, I'll forgive you everything.
It's time.
Miju.
You know what I told you
to keep last time?
That land deed?
Right...
That's really important,
so don't keep it,
just give it to Seongmo.
All right, Oppa.
Don't worry.
All right.
I'll have to go back in.
Just come once a month,
from now on.
Got it?
Oppa...
Take good care of yourself
and don't skip meals.
What am I, a child?
I had a strange dream last night,
a really upsetting one.
You silly.
It's just a nightmare.
Careful on your way back.
Lee Gangmo, Park Sotae.
Follow us.
I'm still not done eating?
There's no time,
so stop eating and just come.
Wait for me.
- Hurry up.
- Yes, coming.
You pricks...
Finally letting me out, I see?
You'll come with me as well.
Wait a moment.
Why him?
He still had a long time
to spend here?!
There's no time.
Yes, sure...
Where are you taking us?
Listen, I can understand taking me,
but doesn't Gangmo
still have a long time left?
What are you sending me there for?
You've been fined twice
for violating curfew.
And how many years ago was that?
Two previous convictions, rank B.
Convictions?!
That's a long record, isn't it?
What?
Rank B.
What are you doing?
Seal it.
I asked you something!
Let go!
Let me go!
Where the hell are they taking us?
If you're releasing us,
Seoul Station would do.
But you're more childish
than I thought?!
You call these drawings?
I could do better with my feet.
Looking at you, people will think
I stole some land deed from you.
- Will you marry me? -
~ Samcheong Re-education Camp ~
Created by the Jeon Duhwan junta in 1980
for gangsters and political dissidents
I have a question!
I was one of the
very first ROK Marines!
How long has it been since I
completed civil defense, what is this...
Starting now,
we'll cleanse you human trash.
Proceed!
You bastards...
- The will to start anew
through educative purification -
How did you end up here?
I wrote this article,
about what happened in Gwangju.
About the military opening fire
on the people of their own country,
shooting and hacking them to death.
And not content with that,
they captured innocent people, and...
What's the point...
Want to get another beating?
But, Gangmo.
I thought you were in prison.
How did you end up in here?
It's likely that Jo Minwoo's
father sent me here.
Minwoo's father?
Former KCIA Jo Pilyeon?
And why would he?
There is something he wants from me.
But I'll never let anyone steal that.
I'm not letting anyone take
anything away from me anymore.
I'll survive this place,
and get back everything that is mine.
To Candidate Jo Pilyeon!
Cheers!
Thank you.
If I win the elections, I won't forget
the hospitality you've shown me.
But Min Honggi seems to have
quite the solid approval rate,
will it be all right?
Min Honggi has no money.
If we take this to the end,
I'm confident I can win.
Baekpa and Congressman
Oh Byeongtak are next door.
Is that so?
Since we're here,
should I pay them my respects?
That's not the problem.
Min Honggi just joined them.
What? Min Honggi?!
Are you telling me Min Honggi
is meeting with Baekpa?
If he's meeting with Baekpa, this...
You needn't worry.
We don't need to worry?!
If Min ever gets
Baekpa's financial support,
it's a fight we will never win.
We would have spent money
in vain, don't you think?
I've already met Baekpa.
Turns out he's not interested
in politics whatsoever.
There's no way he'd help Min Honggi.
I apologize for
introducing myself so late.
I'm Min Honggi.
You must be busy,
why not spend that time
to meet with your electors?
I invited him.
Here... Have a seat.
Listen, Commissioner Han.
You know what Baekpa tends to focus
on as collateral for his dealings?
What can I say...
Wouldn't it be land, after all?
Wrong.
It's people.
He lends money
with people as collateral.
No need to lose ourselves
in empty chatter.
You want me to fund your campaign?
Jo Pilyeon is using money
to influence this election.
If you could only watch my back,
these elections are as good as done.
Give me your help, Sir.
I'll respond on his behalf,
if you don't mind.
We don't get involved
in campaign funding.
Ohh Ohh... Madam Yoon.
We neither accept nor use
any money coming from politics.
That's his ironclad rule.
It used to be.
But I believe things might be
a little different, this time.
What are you trying to say?
If it's not Congressman Min Honggi,
but just Min Honggi the man,
then there's no reason
why I shouldn't help him out.
Sir...
Look...
I told you things were different.
Thank you.
Not as a congressman,
but as Min Honggi the man,
I will serve you to
the best of my abilities.
And when Jo Pilyeon
asked for your support,
you refused right off the bat.
I guess I'll have a
cup of tea before I leave.
I really don't understand
what you're trying to do.
Do you really believe Min Honggi
is any better than Jo Pilyeon?
In all peace and tranquility,
raising a tiger is what you need.
But raising foxes is more
suited to turbulent times.
Now is no time
to raise tigers, but foxes.
So Jo Pilyeon would be the tiger,
and Min Honggi the fox,
by any chance?
- Candidate No. 4 Jo Pilyeon -
"It's no longer about parties, but people!
The people's choice, Jo Pilyeon"
I found him, Seonbaenim.
I found someone who can prove that
Jo Pilyeon's father was a collaborator.
Good job.
But... He's got quite
the few issues himself.
This should more than suffice.
Will you help us out?
Of course!
I can't let the son of a pro-Japanese
collaborator become congressman.
I'll testify for you.
Thank you.
But there is a little problem.
What?
You have a previous conviction.
Still... My father was
an independence activist.
Uh? Aigoo... Really...
What the hell is
happening to this country...
I understand.
However, if you reveal Jo Pilyeon's
past to the press firsthand,
because of your past conviction,
there's a good chance...
they'd just bury it as perjury.
Perjury?!
Even with all this evidence
and someone willing to testify?
Jo Pilyeon is more than capable
of turning all that against you.
Then... What can we do?
Do as I say.
Yes.
So that nobody in the world will know.
The blooming love buried
deep down in my heart.
More colorful than red roses,
is the innocence of a nineteen-year-old.
You sure never give up, isn't it?
Not missing a single day.
Listen.
About withdrawing the lawsuit...
Should I do that for you?
Can you?
I've heard you're
not the one in charge.
Ahh... Really,
what does she take me for?
Tell me, between a salaried chief
and the chairman's son,
who do you think has more power?
That's obv...
Let's go.
Where?
Let's get you some
new clothes, for starters.
How can you go out with me
dressed like that?
Go out where?
The department store.
Anyhow, if you do what I say today,
I'll withdraw the lawsuit.
- Really?
- Sure!
I'll go get the car,
so wait a moment.
Found it.
Do you know how much hard work
it takes to earn this token?
Hurry up... Here.
All right! Let's go.
Come.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Just leave it there.
What are you doing?
Hey... Minwoo!
What's wrong with you?
Hey... Jo Minwoo.
What do you think you're doing?
You!
You little...
Now that he broke up with Jeongyeon,
is his old habit
coming back to haunt him?
Still, I set my eyes on her first,
that little prick...
Where are we going?
Aren't you listening?
Where are you taking me?
Starting from now, you will
have no social status whatsoever.
The Samcheong purification camp...
begins with accepting your sins
and reflecting upon them.
You.
Yes, Sir!
Your offense.
Assault, Sir!
You.
Yes, Sir.
Hit and run, Sir.
You.
Yes, Sir! I...
Did they take you here for no reason?
No, Sir!
I was the worst thug you could meet!
You.
Your offense.
Why? Is it hard to admit
you killed a man?
I...
am not a killer.
Then, if you're not a killer,
what are you?
I fell in love with a woman I
should have never even glanced at.
If I committed any crime,
that is the only one.
Loving the wrong woman.
Stop.
Listen well.
You are no longer people.
You're nothing but criminals.
Repeat after me.
I will follow any and all orders.
Focus.
Discipline.
I refrain from reading newspapers,
listening to the radio or watching TV.
I humbly respect our public institutions,
and refrain from smoking and drinking.
A little more, please.
Away, you prick!
I eat what is given to me.
Five seconds left to eat.
Four... Three... Two... One!
Proceed!
I accept any punishment
that is given to me.
Fine...
Hit me all you want.
I will not run away from...
all the suffering
you're putting me through.
And I will never forget it.
As the payback which awaits you...
will be a hundred,
a thousand times worse.
Seongmo is here.
Send him in.
Have a seat.
Have a drink.
I have a favor to ask you.
A favor?
Just give me any order.
That Lee Gangmo you captured.
He's at the Samcheong
Camp as we speak.
I made it possible.
He's got land.
That is land he can never possess.
What are you trying to tell me?
Get rid of Lee Gangmo.
Kill him.
Do it quietly, without
attracting anyone's attention.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This is a human slaughterhouse,
where undiscriminating violence reigns.
My God...
A woman you couldn't love?
Look at me?
Don't I still love her?
I asked to break off the engagement.
Because I thought I could never
endure married life without love.
Just hang in there for thirty seconds.
When you're struggling and someone
holds your hands, you gain strength.
What are you trying to scheme?
I could tell you,
but then I'd have to kill you.
523. From this moment on,
you'll become 534.
Yes.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com