Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Final Episode
We will now resume our hearing.
Congressman Oh Segwang of the
DLP, you may begin your inquiries.
Witness, you clearly talked
of a secret fund account, right?
Yes.
Fund which would belong
to the former president?
That's correct.
Do you have that account, by any chance?
You're in congress.
A single false statement,
and you'll be accused of
perjury and contempt of congress.
Witness.
I'd like an answer.
I will ask the chairman, if I may.
You saw that account
as well, didn't you?
Answer with a lie, and you
will insult the entire country in the process.
I hope your conscience
will suggest the right answer.
Right as the witness suggested,
I did see that secret fund account.
And it wasn't just the chairman,
but also a few other gentlemen at the
1987 Olympic Support Committee event.
And they're all sitting here today.
Chairman.
Not only because of this secret fund issue,
but to bring to light all of
candidate Jo Pilyeon's past actions,
one day of hearing alone can't suffice.
I motion for an extension.
Ahh... I concur.
I do as well.
What are you waiting for?
Lee Gangmo is doing his
damnedest to find Lee Seongmo!
Whatever it takes,
we must find him before he does!
So, what, am I supposed to
make him appear out of the blue?
You little...
Anyhow,
you must find him whatever it takes.
Did I make myself clear?
I will soon bring you good news,
so just wait.
Right...
I enjoyed the hearing.
I'll call you again soon.
You're not going to
hand Lee Seongmo to him?
We don't even know whether
he will become prime minister,
can't give up such precious goods so easily.
What most matters in a deal...
is none other than timing.
You just wait.
Lee Seongmo will bring us a
huge opportunity on a silver platter.
Please, give him a warm applause.
You could consider Manbo Plaza
the culmination of thirty years...
of evolution and development
shown by Manbo Construction.
If you allow me the bold assertion,
I am confident this will prove to be
an epochal turning point...
in the history of Gangnam's development.
We've heard that the sale
has been completed already.
All buyers will move in starting next month.
That should be all for today.
Our PR reps will show you each floor.
You must be busy,
so allow me once again to
extend you my gratitude, Mayor.
Among the invited I see
many wives of congressmen.
Since they'll become our
department store's first customers.
Yes...
But you completed construction
a lot earlier than expected,
was it by any chance because
of your father's cabinet hearing?
You could think of it as another proof of Manbo Construction's technological supremacy.
If you'll excuse me.
Did you hear that?
Sounded like a piano or something...
I'm sure it's nothing serious.
Gangmo.
Director Go from Sokcho just called me.
Did they find him?
They couldn't, but there are
rumors that he's with Jeongshik.
- You're back, President?
- Yeah.
- Everything in order?
- He's quieter than you'd think.
Need to take good care of him.
We're dealing with precious goods here.
The hell?
A vest...
Hey...
Let's take off that vest.
You look like you
wouldn't be afraid of anything...
This is not real, is it?
Uh?
I said take it off.
President, are you all right?
Ahh... You little...
He sure is strong.
Why, are you hiding
some gold inside that...
Hey.
Take it off of him.
- What?
- Take off the damn vest!
Do it.
Enough.
Open it up.
There's something inside.
What is this?
This!
Is a treasure map!
It's a goldmine... A goldmine!
What are you doing? Stop him!
Take that account from him!
Hyung!
Hey... Stop them!
Hwang Jeongshik!
Park Sotae...
Long time no see!
Long time no see, you prick!
Stop there!
It's me, Hyung.
I'm Gangmo, Hyung!
Look at me...
I'm your brother Gangmo!
Hyung...
Hyung!
I'm sorry, Hyung...
Hyung...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Hyung.
Congressman Hwang Taeseop,
you may begin your inquiry.
Yes.
First, before I go ahead,
I'd like to tell you my story.
Back when Gangnam was moving
its first steps in terms of development,
I was facing financial woes.
I needed money so badly...
that I would have done
practically everything for it.
And that is when a devil approached me,
whispering sweet words in my ears.
He told me to kill my very best
friend with my own hands,
and steal a cargo of smuggled gold bars.
And then I let the
devil lure me into his trap.
I took the gun he gave me,
and went out prepared to kill a man.
Chairman!
Last I checked, this was a cabinet hearing.
Congressman Hwang, you may continue.
To be perfectly honest,
I have no right to be here.
Because it was what I did...
that caused my dear friend's death.
Look, Chairman!
Candidate, you just stay put!
And the person who pulled the
trigger and killed my friend instead...
was none other than...
Jo Pilyeon!
Congressman Hwang!
Don't let him deceive
you, ladies and gentlemen!
He's trying to falsely incriminate
me without a shred of evidence!
This is a travesty against the entire country!
Chairman.
With this cabinet
hearing as my last act of duty,
I resign from congress.
Jo Pilyeon,
you're a cold-blooded killer.
You killed my friend,
and even tried to strangle me to death!
And not satisfied with that!
You went ahead and killed
Congressman Oh Byeongtak as well!
It's a lie! This is a conspiracy against me!
My rights are being trampled on!
It's not a lie!
The only one who is lying...
is Jo Pilyeon.
And the man...
Jo Pilyeon shot to death back then...
was my father.
You...
Shut that goddamned mouth of yours!
And five years ago,
Congressman Oh Byeongtak
was killed by Jo Pilyeon!
What are you waiting for?
Over there!
Get these people out of here!
Quiet!
To destroy any evidence, you even
had their bodies cremated.
However, despite having
meticulously planned all that,
- you made a fatal mistake.
- Don't make me laugh!
There could be no mistake whatsoever,
since my plan was flawless.
So you finally admitted it.
What?!
You've just admitted that
you killed Congressman Oh Byeongtak.
So you'll kill me?!
Since if I do, any
evidence will be buried along with you.
Will killing me really get rid of it?
Who else... Lee Seongmo?
That fool had the guts to
write that secret fund account.
Even if I get rid of him,
who will ever blame me for it?
And this!
Is the secret fund account...
that Jo Pilyeon wrote.
Chairman Jo really built one hell of a place.
Are you the one who
invested in my films all this time?
And what makes you
believe I'd waste my money that way?
Does the film we're featuring
starting today star Cha Soojeong?
Yes. There is a press screening at seven.
I'm sure you added a clause allowing us
to end its theater run in the case of a flop?
Yes, Chairman.
Unless you want to see your film gone,
better focus on improving box office.
Seems like Minwoo has no
feelings left for you whatsoever?!
Then again, it's been so long...
It would be strange if
he was still in love with you.
What's wrong?
And I thought it was a new building...
Go out and see if they
can change the light bulb.
All right.
The hearing should be over by now.
Find out how it went.
All right, Chairman.
Chairman... Chairman!!
Are you all right?
What on earth is happening?
Yes.
Chairman, where are you now?
In the elevator.
What happened?
It's terrible, Chairman!
The building...
The building has collapsed!
What are you trying to say?
The building has collapsed?!
Stay there. We'll send
a rescue squad your way.
Look, Chief Kim.
Chief Kim.
Chief Kim!
Are you saying that
Manbo Plaza has collapsed?
Miju...
Miju is still in the
waiting room of the fifth floor.
Chairman!
Open the door!
Open the damn door!
Open...
Chairman, stop!
If you keep this up,
the elevator will crash down!
Miju is inside.
Miju is still there!
- Chairman...
- Miju.
Open the door!
Careful...
From here on in, Hyung,
you'll live here with me.
All right?
I said be careful.
Ohh... Shideok.
When was Miju's
press screening, again?
Seven.
It's late, we'll have to hurry.
Breaking news.
A new five-storey building in
Gangnam, Manbo Plaza, has collapsed.
What are they saying?
The Manbo Plaza collapsed?!
What you're now seeing is footage
one of our reporters was able...
to shoot on her way to a
press screening for Cha Soojeong's film.
We're at Manbo Plaza,
where Cha Soojeong's new film...
is about to be introduced in a press screening.
Manbo Plaza was...
Thankfully, as the press
screening hadn't started yet,
the number of casualties was low,
but famous singer-cum-movie star
Cha Soojeong is still trapped inside.
The building just collapsed!
I know where Miju was.
I must go inside and rescue her.
It's too dangerous to go inside now.
If we waste more time and the
building completely collapses, then Miju will die!
I'll show you the way, so follow me.
Chairman!
Chairman!!
What did you just say?
It collapsed?!
What collapsed?
The Manbo Plaza Minwoo built...
Why would a building collapse?
How could it?
The aftermath of Manbo Plaza's
collapse feels like a battlefield.
The prosecutors blame the
accident on faulty construction practices,
and will soon summon Chairman Jo Minwoo
and the officials in charge of the project.
An urgent public statement
by the government is expected...
Honey... Minwoo...
What now?
No way.
This is all a conspiracy.
Someone... Someone
orchestrated all this to kill me.
Congressman...
It's Lee Gangmo's fault.
In retaliation for killing his father,
Lee Gangmo committed an act of terror.
The gun...
Where is my gun?
- The gun!
- Congressman!
- Honey! Wake up!
- The gun!
- Congressman!
- Honey!
Miju...
Lee Miju!
Miju.
Miju...
Miju!
It's bleeding, you silly!
It's all right.
Let's go to the hospital, uh?
The hospital, for so little?
Just a band-aid and...
Get on my back.
I said it's nothing, I'm fine.
I live here, put me down!
Is that the problem now?
Blood is gushing out of there!
Gushing?!
I said I'm all right!
Just stay put.
Miju.
I'm her brother.
What are her conditions?
Thankfully, other than a cracked
rib, she suffered no serious injuries.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Doctor.
You shouldn't thank me,
but the man who saved Miss Cha.
If he hadn't found her so quickly,
she could have died due to excessive bleeding.
Miju.
Can you hear me?
It's me.
Oppa...
That's right.
Thank God you made it.
Congressman.
Where are we headed?
We... We must hide.
I don't think hiding
will solve the problem.
If they catch us now, it's all over.
We'll have to rot in the
can for the rest of our days.
But, Congressman...
I can't die.
I can't let them kill me.
There is no way I'm letting them.
Jaechun.
Failure is the mother of success.
We might be on the run right now,
but when we make our return,
the earth will tremble in fear and awe.
Jo Pilyeon will make sure it happens.
How do you think it will go?
There might be a chance
for a reduced sentence, but...
But penal servitude is a given?
Embezzlement of public funds and
professional negligence will still stand.
Chairman.
Creditors have gathered at the office.
So you want Manbo Construction
to be acquired by another company?
With a temporary draft term extension
until the management crisis is resolved,
I think there will be companies interested
in acquiring Manbo Construction.
Any recommendation, Chairman Hwang?
How about President Lee
Gangmo of Hangang Construction?
You're telling us to hand the
company to Hangang Construction?
If we could only leave
management to them, I would approve.
I approve as well.
President Lee Gangmo
can be trusted to deliver.
Chairman...
She's been looking after Seongmo.
Thank you.
Seongmo Oppa.
It's... Miju, Oppa.
It's me...
Don't you recognize me?
I said I'm Miju, Big Oppa...
Seongmo Oppa...
Oppa... What happened to you?
What have they done to you?
Oppa...
Big Oppa...
What is this?
Open it.
It's everything I have left.
Acquire Manbo Construction with it.
Mom...
I closed up shop with this.
You take care of it now, Jeongyeon.
But you worked your entire life for this...
I can't accept it.
I did it all to give it to my daughter.
It was yours from the very start.
We manage to gain control
of Manbo Construction again...
It feels like a dream.
Right... Gangmo will do great.
Dad...
We're going to move down to Jeju.
We have some farmland there.
I only have one thing left to ask you.
To meet a good man and get married.
Mom...
Congressman.
Minwoo is here.
Things must be hard at work, but
I see you still found the time to visit me.
You look much better than I thought.
You pathetic fool.
How the hell did you build
that place, to make it collapse?
Do you even know
who's responsible for that?
That was all...
Get the company back on
its feet before I come back.
It's all over now.
You still don't get it?
It's over for the both of us.
This is Congressman Oh's villa.
As long as I stay
here, nobody will find me.
- Dad...
- And it's not just Congressman Oh.
Congressmen Park, Choi and Hong...
They're all in my pocket,
and the list goes on.
Is that clear?
I'm still alive and well.
Just worry about your end of the bargain.
The company...
is about to be acquired by Hangang Construction.
What...
Lee Gangmo is going to
get his hands on Manbo Group.
What kind of retarded
nonsense are you yapping about?
Turn yourself in.
- Minwoo, you...
- Do it, and accept your punishment.
You son of a...
When are you going to put a
stop to all that ambition of yours?
The day I do that,
it'll only mean my death!
And I won't die!
Please... Stop it, Dad!
Minwoo.
If you let Lee Gangmo take
the company from you, we'll lose.
Our life will become a failure.
Don't you give up.
Life can always be turned around.
And if you're Jo Pilyeon's son,
you must endure it to the very
end and emerge victorious, Minwoo.
You once told me that you wish...
I could be the only
man who beats you, right?
I will help put an end
to that ambition of yours.
Minwoo, you...
What are you thinking?
It is the very last thing....
I could do for my father's sake.
Minwoo?
Mi... Minwoo!
G... Get him...
Go get him! Now!
Have you heard me?
Now.
Now... Go get him now!!
I'm sorry, Congressman.
- Hangang & Manbo
Construction Merger Signing -
And that officially concludes the merger
between Hangang and Manbo Construction.
My father...
is staying there.
Even if he pays for what he did,
I still hope at least you will forgive him.
Jaechun.
You regret meeting me, too?
Thanks to you,
I've had the time of my life.
Really?
Thanks.
I at least wanted to show you
what a winner really looked like...
I apologize.
For not serving you like I should have.
Do I look that miserable and pathetic to you?
You always looked like
a man of great majesty to my eyes.
Majesty?!
Majesty...
Jaechun.
I will take this,
and have one last go at it.
I can never hear that
Lee Gangmo call me a loser.
You just wait, Jaechun.
Lee Gangmo is going to die.
If that's what it takes
to win, I'll have to do it.
Jaechun!
Jaechun...
Providence was on my side all along!
Lee Gangmo came here on his own!
I can't wait.
Come, Lee Gangmo!
Go ahead.
Go ahead and come, Lee Gangmo.
I... I will kill you once and for all.
I'll finish you just like
I did with your father.
That gun...
Now... Give it to me... Do it.
Come on... The gun.
Jaechun.
What...
What did you just do?
Jaechun?
Get up.
He's coming in.
We have no time to waste here.
Get up, Jaechun.
Jaechun!
What's this?
You really think you beat me?
From the very start,
I had no intention of
beating you whatsoever.
Because what I was
fighting against wasn't you.
What?!
Jo Pilyeon.
And the kind of
world run by people like you.
What I was fighting against...
was that ruthless and dirty
world people like you created.
From the very beginning,
you were utterly insignificant to me.
But now I might...
Now I might finally start
to believe in this world again.
Since it forced...
such a miserable downfall on you.
- And Minwoo...
- Right now,
he's on the rooftop.
By any chance,
was he the one who rescued me?
Yes. The chairman did.
And the main investor in all
those films you starred in...
was him.
Despite knowing that Wooju wasn't his son...
Wait a moment.
Minwoo knows about Wooju?
Yes.
He does.
But... Wooju is not Minwoo's son?!
Don't, Minwoo!
You can't die...
Don't do it, Minwoo.
I beg you...
Please, come down.
Come down.
If...
If I'll ever be born again,
then...
I'll be born as your brother.
Since a family never breaks up.
Since I could forever be by your side.
Minwoo...
I'm sorry, Miju.
I'm tired.
I can't take this anymore.
Wooju!
He's your son.
What...
did you just say?
Wooju is... what?
He's your son.
Your father knows about him.
If you die like that,
I'll never be able to look at
Wooju the same way again.
Case file no. 1316.
The defendant Jo Minwoo is sentenced
to two years in prison...
for embezzlement of public funds and
injuries as a result of professional negligence.
- Jo Pilyeon Trial Overturned Again -
Life Sentence Confirmed
What is this place?
Why did you bring me here?
That house.
You told me you'd like to
live in a place like this, right?
With the big dog, the
terrace, and the white piano.
With roses and
lilacs surrounding the place.
Everything you
wanted is inside that place.
How about it?
You like it?
- Hwang Jeongyeon -
I love it.
But...
I think it might
be too big for me alone.
Want to look at
what's in the mailbox?
This notebook...
Back then,
I took it out of the water.
Then....
you've been keeping it all this time?
To me,
it's the most
precious thing in the world.
- Lee Gangmo -
This house...
is a little too big for
you to handle it all by yourself,
so, like...
If it's too hard for you to do it alone...
Fine.
I'll just be honest.
I don't think I'd be able to
live the rest of my life alone.
So will you...
marry me?
- Will You Marry Me? -
I love you, Jeongyeon.
Oppa.
You'll overcome that surgery, right?
I'll be right back, Oppa.
You said you miss Wooju.
I'll go get him,
so you must have
that surgery and get better.
All right?
It's time, let's go.
I'll be back soon, Little Oppa.
Hyung.
Remember what we promised?
To never,
ever live apart again.
You,
Miju and I.
You must overcome this.
Seongmo....
will be more than capable of it.
Don't worry too much, Gangmo.
It's time.
Hyung...
- Two Years Later -
It's the ticket Wooju
bought with his savings.
- Lee Seongmo -
Big Oppa.
You're doing fine up in
heaven with Mom and Dad, right?
Wooju won a
scholarship at an art school.
I miss you, Seongmo Oppa.
I love you...
- 2010 -
Who is it?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for Mister Gangmo Lee.
~ Chairman Lee Gangmo
wins at Global Business Awards ~
If you have the guts,
go ahead and shoot me.
Shouldn't you avenge your father?
Come on.
Do it!
And you want me to stain my hands
with that dirty blood of yours?
If you desire to die that much,
go ahead and jump off.
What?
If the city you always dreamed of
becomes your burial ground,
I'm sure you'll have nothing
to complain about.
Keep this in mind.
All the wicked sins
you people have committed...
will forever be remembered by that city.
You bastard...
Lee Gangmo, you bastard!
You bastard!
Former congressman Jo Pilyeon
committed suicide this evening at nine,
jumping off a building in
Dogok-Dong, Gangnam District.
With a past as winner of
the 12th congressional elections,
Jo was sentenced to life in prison,
and eventually moved to preventive
custody as a result of schizophrenia.
The 4th of this month, Jo had
escaped from the mental institution...
Turn that off.
Things have really changed.
Once the highway from
Seoul to Sokcho is completed,
they say you'll be able to come
back from work on the same day, Chairman.
How far can you see?
I can't see where it ends.
All the land your eyes can see is ours!
Ehh... Liar!
He's right, Miju!
That's our land!
Big Oppa!!
Little Oppa!!
Hurry up and come!
Quick!
Gangmo...
Hyung!
Seongmo Oppa!!
Gangmo Oppa!!
Ohh... Honey.
I'm headed home.
Hurry up.
Your little brother Junmo is here.
- With S2 Presented -
G  I  A  N  T
- Written By -
Jang Youngcheol, Jung Gyeongsun
- Produced by -
Yoo Inshik, Lee Changmin
- Thank You For Walking this Long
Road with Us, and Happy New Year! -
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com