Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 13 ~
So you promised each other you would
meet here at the end of the month?
My sister came here?
If I knew this, I would at least
have asked her phone number.
Aigoo... What now?!
I'm sure Oppa is looking for me.
Will it be Gangmo Oppa,
or Seongmo Oppa?
The sole thought that my family
could be in Seoul makes my heart throb.
You'll come to 31 Building
next time, right?
Oppa...
Good shot... Good shot!
Wow... You're quite good at this.
How long have you
been practicing this?
It's been so long, I don't even
know if I can do this anymore.
Ahh... Dammit.
I wonder why people spend
all that money to play this.
Give it another try.
No.
I'll just think of this as
a nice walk, so let's go ahead.
Ehh... Really...
By now, Hong Gipyo must be losing it.
I bet.
Since all that land he bought from me
for top dollar is not worth a penny now.
The government is planning
to move elite private schools from...
Gangbuk to Gangnam soon.
That's good to hear.
There's nothing like education
to pump up estate prices.
When that happens, we can build
all the apartments we want,
and there will be no problems
selling them at the new subway lot.
Why do you keep following me around?
That one down there is my ball.
What do you think, Chairman Hwang?
Seeing them sit side by side,
they sure look good together.
Yes...
So how about we wrap things up,
since we're here?
I mean regarding Minwoo
and Jeongyeon's marriage.
Chairman.
That's something...
For starters, it would be
best to have an engagement,
what are your thoughts, Jeongyeon?
You'll pardon me, Director.
But this is all news to me.
You didn't even mention it to her?
I didn't get the chance, so...
I trust it's not because you
don't want to become in-laws with me?!
The recommendation
will soon be announced.
Congressman Oh Byeongtak
told me to wait for good news.
And if we manage to get them together,
wouldn't that be the best possible
partnership between finance and politics?
Let's get together with our wives,
and make this official.
Yes, 400,000 won so far.
Anyone wishes to raise?
- 450.
- Yes, 450,000 won to the lady over there.
Any other bids?
- 550.
- Yes, 550,000 won.
- 600.
- 600,000 won!
- 650.
- 650,000 won.
- 700.
- 700,000 won!
Does anyone want to raise that?
- 800.
- Here... 800,000 won.
800... Any other bids?
For 800,000 won, going once...
One million won.
One million.
No other bids?
Congratulations to no. 37, winning
the Python Ruby set for a million won.
Mrs. Jo?
If I knew you wanted it so bad,
I would have just let you buy it cheaper.
A million won is
just pocket money, anyway.
Ahh... Right,
which college did you graduate from?
And why are you asking that?
We have a membership slot
available at our club,
but you need to be a college
graduate to be accepted.
Forget it.
I can't stand getting together with
women and wasting time with gossip.
My... Think people of our status
would bother with gossip?
We just do some charity on our
husbands' behalf, so no need to worry.
I've been raising an orphan,
and do enough charity as it is?!
Then, all the better.
Join our club, I will vouch for you.
I'll see you later, then.
What now, Ma'am?!
You only graduated
from middle school, didn't you?
Shut your mouth! You brat...
Think she doesn't know
I didn't go to college?
That sly old fox...
She goes straight for my weak spot?
What do you think?
About getting engaged with Minwoo.
I don't want to.
This is nothing but
a strategic marriage.
I don't want to become
a mere pawn in your power games.
Still, you didn't say it's
because you don't like Jo Minwoo.
Have a seat.
I'll have to convey to you the bad news.
Jeongyeon...
ended up rejecting your proposal.
You don't want me as your son-in-law?
- It was Jeongyeon who...
- As for Jeongyeon,
I'll make sure she changes her mind.
Would that be enough?
Afraid it won't be that easy.
Jeongyeon's stubbornness is something
even I can't do a thing about.
Then, I will take care of that.
I've heard the news from the chairman.
You knew they were talking
about our marriage, weren't you?
I was the first
to mention it to my father.
That I wanted to marry you.
You said you dreamed of being
kissed by me at the hotel, right?
Do you still think of it as just a dream?
What?
You didn't...
Will you think again...
that this is just a dream, a nightmare?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you know the answer already?
Let go.
Let me go!
You're driving me crazy.
What can I do...
to make you like me?
Do I look like a naive little lamb
waiting to be slaughtered?
Think I don't get that it's all an act
to make your strategic marriage happen?
Don't mention the word marriage
in my presence again.
Gangmo.
Ever loved someone before?
Then again...
I've known you since middle school,
and I've never seen you
date anyone before.
Is it indigestion?
I feel all stuffy inside.
~ Patty Kim's Mist ~
That shadow of yours...
I always cherished.
What would be the point of reminiscing,
When all they are
is nothing but bygones?
But I still so fervently
miss those memories.
Where could that man be?
She's really a good singer.
I'm glad we came here tonight.
Are those two dating now?
What the hell...
I enjoyed the song,
you really look great on the stage.
Thank you.
Let's go, Ma'am.
Is that woman the owner of this place?
Why are you drinking so much?
I feel stuffy.
Feel as if my chest
is just about to burst.
Bring some drinks to that table.
Will you drink in the hall?
If I inherit the company from Dad,
my mother will be glad, right?
I wonder if she's even alive,
living somewhere...
I'm sure she's doing fine.
When she gave birth to me,
she was even younger than I am now.
And she was betrayed by the
man she loved, at that young age.
Will she really be doing fine?
That's what men call "love."
They completely swallow it
when it's sweet,
then spit it out at the
first sign of bitterness.
Marriage?!
I don't need any of that.
I'll only look forward to the day
I can run that company on my own.
Sure tastes nice.
So what's the occasion?
Paying me a visit.
Your sister.
Jeongyeon.
What kind of person is she?
Are you coveting our company?
Think I don't know you?
There's no way you'd be interested
in someone like Jeongyeon.
And why is that?
Her mother...
She was a bar girl,
and that explains
that brat's personality.
Jeongshik.
Watch what you say, will you?
What?
I'm thinking of marrying Jeongyeon.
Wh...What? Marry her?!
Hey, you...
Fine, make her your wife or whatever,
it's none of my business.
But Manbo Construction, that's mine.
Are we clear?
You little...
Did you just laugh at me?
You're not concerned in the
slightest about me, is that it?
You know? It's funny.
You don't concern me one bit,
so why is Lee Gangmo
always getting on my nerves?
You little prick, I just ought to...
Listen, Hwang Jeongshik.
You're my friend.
Do I look like the kind of creep who
would fight with a friend over a company?
Must be out of money, I bet?
When you inherit the company,
then you'll be thankful to me.
Because I'll help our Manbo
Construction to the very top.
I'll get going.
Then again...
Having someone like him
under you is not too bad.
The stairs...
Where are we?
I asked you where...
Be quiet.
You'll wake everyone up.
Gangmo!
Lee Gangmo...
I'm not going anywhere.
Here... Go in.
If you abandon me,
you're dead.
I won't let you get away with it.
If you do that...
You asked me if I ever
loved anyone before, right?
The one I loved...
is none other than you.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
It's the first time I confess it,
but I'm sorry to have done it
while you were sleeping, like a coward.
But one day,
I'll tell you right before you.
I'll say that I love you
with confidence.
Until that day comes...
Until that day,
don't ever let anyone else
take you away from me,
and wait for me.
Think I don't get that it's all an act
to make your strategic marriage happen?
Don't mention the word marriage
in my presence again.
Why are those damned meetings
always so long?
Ohh... Have a seat.
Look, Director Jo.
Yes, Congressman.
I'm afraid you'll have to concede to
Director Min at the upcoming elections.
What are you trying to say?
The party's top brass decided
to push for Director Min.
Thank you.
Congressman!
I'll make a personal effort to guarantee
you're next in line for a recommendation.
And based on what kind of standards
was this recommendation assigned?
Why should we keep
beating around the bush?!
This recommendation was strictly
based upon performance on the field.
Performance?!
If we consider all the money Director Min
donated to the national development fund...
through the construction committee,
your contributions pale in comparison.
Don't let this disappoint you.
You have my support
at the next elections.
Ahh... What is he doing?
Don't mind him.
That's that.
How did the subway matter go?
Yes... Daeryuk Construction is currently
undergoing severe financial pressure.
Barring any unforeseen occurrence,
Manbo Construction
will be put in charge.
Being recommended is
not the end of your worries.
If you truly want to win the elections,
you need to cut your ties with damaged
goods like Hong Gipyo once and for all!
I'm well aware of that, Congressman.
So first they set me loose
on the hunt for their own good,
and now that they don't
need me anymore, I'm abandoned?
I was surprised to hear
you weren't recommended.
Considering the situation,
you'll have to push my candidacy for real.
I'm not taking this lying down.
If that's what it takes, I'll even run
against Min Honggi as an independent.
Director.
That fool sure can't
have solid financial backing,
so even if I have to cover
the four corners in gold,
I'll bring ruin to that prick
once and for all.
I'm a businessman.
And what are you implying with that?
That I can't throw money at a venture
that is not worth investing in.
What did you just say?
I'm not worth investing in?!
To be honest, if you end up
losing at these elections,
wouldn't that spell
the end for the both of us?
Have you already forgotten
who is behind all your success?
Seems like you
misunderstood what I meant.
Rather than wasting money so unwisely,
planning for the future would be...
Chairman Hwang!
So all your day-by-day reservations
about our kids' marriage...
were all because of this?
Seems like you had a drink
too many tonight.
Let's talk again soon.
Let's go.
What?! Cover the four corners in gold?!
What does he think my hard-earned
money is, manure from his latrine?
Will it be all right?
Seems like you riled him up real nice?!
If the republicans don't
vouch for him, it's game over.
How would he possibly...
You're already leaving?
Right.
You'll have to bring
some consolation to your father.
What's the matter, Dad?
Both your marriage and
my recommendation, it's all over!
Honey!
- You're drunk, just...
- Let go!
Minwoo, you!
Act on Daeryuk Construction
behind Chairman Hwang's back.
I want them filing for
bankruptcy in no time!
Director, do you have some kind of plan?
To all the people who plotted against me,
Hong Gipyo is just a time bomb.
If my guess is right,
he must carry some kind of account
listing all their bribes and dealings so far.
So you want to use Chairman Hong's
secret account against them?
I know the type
like the palm of my hands.
Push them into a corner,
and they'll spell their own demise.
But we could bear the grunt as well.
It's the last card on the table for me!
Jaechun, you start spying
on Hong Gipyo's every move!
I will, Director.
Min Honggi, Hwang Taeseop...
Just wait and see
the end that awaits you.
This is serious, Chairman.
Our checks are bouncing.
What?
Someone is purposely spreading rumors
about us among financial circles.
~ Seoul Subway Route Changed ~
Stopping Excessive Speculation the Reason
How about him...
If there is anything you wish
to say, go ahead and tell me.
I just wanted to ask
for your help one more time.
If we manage to
keep the subway contract,
we can get back
on our feet in no time.
Daeryuk Construction's deadline
is at the end of the month.
Look, Miss Yoo...
You know my answer.
That his business policy
is to be a generous lender...
and a very thorough exacter.
Where is he now?
- I'll just have a talk with him, and...
- If you fail to pay interests on time,
you will lose every single square inch
of land you used as collateral.
Can you do this to me?
Have a nice day.
So you really have no
intention of saving that man?
He broke our rules.
But you're still
helping Hwang Taeseop...
Daughters sure can be scary.
I heard you crying
all night by yourself.
Was it Jeongyeon?
If those ties were meant to be broken,
better not linger on.
Those wounds time so painfully
cured might open up again.
Have you been able to reach
Director Min Honggi?
He hasn't been answering our calls.
He really...
We're heading to Namsan right away.
Namsan?!
Are you saying we're going
straight to KCIA headquarters?
KC...IA?
Ahh... You really are something.
How many times do I have to tell you?
If you say it's Daeryuk Construction's
Hong Gipyo, he'll let me in.
Let me get in contact with him!
If you keep this up,
things will get serious.
Until I meet Director Min,
I'm not moving a foot.
Just take him out.
Look...
If you tell him it's
Chairman Hong, he'll know.
Uh? Let me get in touch!
Come on, listen to me!
Director!
Are you out of your mind?
How can you show up here?
Help me out.
If this keeps up,
my company will collapse.
Listen well, Chairman Hong.
I'm in no position to help anyone now.
I myself am walking on
thin ice because of you.
Because of me?!
Do you know why the subway route
was changed so suddenly?
Because you're running amuck
all over the place,
so Director Jo and
Hwang Taeseop put a stop to it.
Is that clear?
So that's supposed to be my fault?
You...
Keep prancing around like this,
and your downfall won't be so pretty.
Are we square?
Let's show some prudence,
that's what I mean.
Also, don't ever come
looking for me again.
Prudence?!
You tell me that?
So should I just quietly go belly up?!
Here's a draft for our apartment ads.
Leave it there.
We have a meeting with a reporter.
You go ahead as you see fit.
By myself?!
All right.
I don't care whether
you believe me or not.
And that's because I love you.
I'm never going to give up on you.
Agasshi.
It's this, right?
Sorry.
I'm so busy with everything,
I even left behind this draft.
But hasn't the reporter arrived yet?
Aigoo... I apologize.
I'm a little late.
No, I just got here myself.
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
It's the draft for our apartment ads.
I see.
Let's take a look.
Seonsaengnim.
It's me, Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo.
You!
Hey!
Lee Gangmo!
I'm so happy to meet you!
Seonsaengnim!
Never been here before, have you?
Have a seat.
I'd heard you became a journalist.
I always felt so guilty, as I thought
you quit at our school because of me.
Never know when they might
fire me here as well.
The higher-ups don't seem
to like the articles I write.
Haven't changed a bit, Seonsaengnim.
Yes, Goryeo Ilbo speaking.
Can I speak to Reporter Yoon Gihoon?
That would be me?!
Who is it?
I'm a businessman in the construction
sector, my name is Hong Gipyo.
Hong Gipyo...
Ahh... Chairman Hong Gipyo
of Daeryuk Construction?
I'd like to have a meeting with you.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
Don't you worry.
I'll see you then.
Sorry.
What did Chairman Hong Gipyo call for?
You know Chairman Hong?
Ahh... You said you work for
Manbo Construction, right?!
Seeing as he wants to meet,
he'll probably give me a good lead or two.
Lead?!
That's that.
How are you doing these days?
I'll return to the Inspection
Department, if you don't mind.
It's still not the time.
Continue sticking to Min Honggi.
We have no more reason
to keep an eye on him.
Are you implying that it's already
game over between him and me?
I bet everyone thinks so.
But this game is still far from over.
The tide will soon turn.
Director.
Hong Gipyo is meeting with
a Goryeo Ilbo reporter.
Goryeo Ilbo?!
Who's the reporter?
Political Editor Yoon Gihoon.
Yoon Gihoon?
He sometimes writes
problematic articles,
so we've had our eyes on him
for a while already.
Bring in that reporter without
letting Hong Gipyo suspect anything.
Yes, Director.
What is the matter?
Know "catching two birds with a stone"?
There are two people who've been
belittling my every move.
Min Honggi and Hwang Taeseop.
The stone I'm about to throw will
make a bloody mess out of those rats.
Go ahead and tell me.
What is this important information
you wanted to disclose?
By any chance,
have you heard of a certain
"national development fund"?
I'll get straight to the point.
During the six years I presided
over the construction committee,
the government received secret funding
from me at the end of every fiscal quarter.
Who made those transactions?
Director Min Honggi of the KCIA.
It's much more serious than I thought.
Is there any evidence
or anyone willing to testify?
I have an account
listing all our dealings.
Once that account
is exposed to the public,
not only those involved, but the
current regime would fall as well.
But you won't be safe, either.
I openly admit I helped those
people corrupt our society,
and I plan to face the
repercussions without reserves.
You must let the
people know about this.
All the people who took money from me.
All those parasites using
authority for their own means.
Our society must be rid of
all those cancers.
Did you bring the account with you?
No.
I'm keeping it in a safe place.
Let's do this.
Even with that account, no article on it
would get through this regime's censorship.
I'll ask the opposition's cooperation,
and see if they can help us.
And that is when I'll publish the news.
Yes.
I know a congressman
from the opposition party.
I'll discuss this with him as well.
Then, we'll exchange
the account here, tomorrow.
All right.
Reporter Yoon, I believe?
And you are?
Take him in.
Who are you? Let me go!
Let go! What are you doing?
Confess.
What did you talk about with Hong Gipyo?
Listen.
I am a reporter.
Being a KCIA agent doesn't give you the
right to oppress innocent people, does it?
What did you say?
Do you have a death wish?
How can you be so rude to a reporter?
Do you recognize me?
If I hadn't seen your photo,
I almost wouldn't have recognized you.
Jo Minwoo's... father?!
I see you remember me.
You were my son's respected teacher,
so I truly feel sorry for
bringing you to such a place.
I think there was some
kind of misunderstanding.
I ask you to let me out of here.
If you cooperate with our investigation,
you'll be free to leave in no time.
I already told them everything I know.
Yoon Seonsaengnim.
No... Reporter Yoon.
I'll ask you again from the beginning.
Did Chairman Hong Gipyo
mention a certain account?
An account?!
Did he, or did he not?
I don't know what you're talking...
Hang him upside down.
If he doesn't confess within an hour,
question him with water,
and if he still refuses,
move onto electroshock.
I guarantee you.
Only a night spent here,
and you'll feel the consequences
for the rest of your days.
Mister Jo!
Mister Jo!!
Mister Jo...
He still hasn't come back?!
That's right.
Seems like they were looking for him
all day at the office, too.
This has never happened before.
Look at me...
Please, come on in.
No.
We'll come again when he's back.
Yes...
Have a good night, then.
Something feels strange.
He said he was going to
meet Chairman Hong today.
They're probably out somewhere, drinking.
Will he recognize me?
Is... Isn't that him?
Right?
If you had confessed earlier,
you wouldn't have forced all this
onto yourself, don't you agree?
It's a relief the boys
didn't mess with your face.
Meet Hong Gipyo as planned, tomorrow.
We'll take care of all the rest.
Did I make myself clear,
Yoon Seonsaengnim?
Seonsaengnim!
Seonsaengnim.
Seonsaengnim...
Bring him inside!
No...
Let's go somewhere else,
I need to take a breather.
I know those were KCIA agents.
It involves Chairman Hong, doesn't it?
What on earth is going on?
Don't try to get involved in this.
Seonsaengnim.
Don't risk your life for nothing!
Is it serious enough that
people might risk their lives?
Please!
Please...
Enough with this.
We've heard Lee Hajeong is about to finalize
her contract with Hyeseong Construction.
Whatever it takes, we must
convince her to change her mind.
She fits the image of
our apartments just right.
Manbo Construction's Chief
of Planning is looking for you.
How bothersome...
Send him packing.
Yes.
How can you come here just like that?
I'll just have a talk with Hajeong.
Ahh... She said no...
- Tell them to come in.
- What?!
So you wanted me to be the
model for your apartment ads?
Yes.
Here... Cheers.
I'm not really much of a drinker.
Chief Jo.
Do you know it's only because of you
that I signed with Manbo Construction?
Is that so?
It's an honor.
Let's drink the night away.
You'll take good care of me
to the very end, won't you?
Of course.
Don't worry and just drink.
Then, will you pour me one?
Here...
So Jo Minwoo knows how to smile?!
"Of course, don't worry and just drink."
Can't you send your colleague home?
I wanted to drink alone with you...
Shall we go somewhere else?
I'm afraid that's out of the question.
That colleague of mine
is the woman I love.
What?
And the only reason
I'm acting so kindly with you...
is because she insisted on
having you as our model.
I could easily do without you.
What did you say?
Guess I ruined the mood.
Should we have a drink by ourselves?
~ National Development Fund ~
Min Honggi
- Committee Members -
Daeryuk Construction: 30 mil. won
Were you looking for me, Chairman?
Have a seat.
Miju.
Yes, Chairman.
You're the only one
who can help me now.
What?
Listen well to what I'm about to say.
You're smart, so you'll understand
what I mean right away.
What is the matter?
You must bear in mind what I told you.
Miju, you can do it, right?
Yes, Chairman.
Don't worry about it.
Have a nice day.
Yes, Hannam-Dong.
The chairman left?
When did he leave?
Just now.
We're one step too late.
We must go and stop Chairman Hong.
Agents from the Inspection
Department might be there already.
If we leave now, we might
stop him before he gets there.
Just who I was looking for.
Let's have lunch together,
for good old times' sake.
I'm a bit late.
You'll have to follow us.
Who are you people?
Escort him out.
What are you doing?
Look!
Reporter Yoon!
What is all this about?
Gangmo...
Tell me everything, now.
What is going on?
I told you, didn't I?
If you get embroiled in all this,
you'll be in danger.
Seonsaengnim!
What's that supposed to mean?
Hong Gipyo was arrested by the KCIA?
A secret account of his dealings
with the committee was found.
Secret account?!
He was keeping one?
Yes, Chairman.
If the committee is involved,
then wouldn't you be in danger as well?
After pocketing all that money,
would they possibly come for us?
Open that briefcase.
Let's first hear the reason
why you're doing all this.
Open it right now, you prick!
What is all this?
Can't you see for yourself?
It's information and prices
regarding the land around the subway.
What?
He was writing a special
on real estate speculation,
and asked me to help him out
with some research data,
so is there anything wrong with that?
Director...
Where's the account?
Account?!
I trust you don't mean
our housekeeping account?!
So you want to play
hard to get, is that it?
Search every inch of this fella's house.
Yes, Director.
What are you doing here?
- Search every corner.
- Yes.
Who are you people?
What are you doing in
someone else's house?
Where is my husband?
Where is he?
Ma'am!
Are you all right, Ma'am?
Seems like it's not here.
Where did you hide that account?
I know nothing about that.
Without that account,
your husband is dead! Got it?
If you want to see him again,
find that account and bring it to us.
My husband...
You didn't harm him, did you?
Unless you want to die here,
I suggest you start talking.
Didn't I tell you...
that there is no account?
Speak!
Where did you hide it?
He fainted.
S...Spare me!
Ever heard of this account before?
Want a taste of that as well,
or will you wake up and confess?
The chairman talked about one
regarding dealings with the government.
And you don't know where he hid it.
I swear to God, I don't know.
- Tie him up.
- Yes.
I really don't know.
Please, don't do this!
Spare me, Director!
Spare me...
Get out of the way!
I was ordered not to let anyone in.
Ordered?!
Who gave that order, you idiot?
I did.
Chairman Hong...
Why did you arrest him?
Exposing acts of corruption is our
Inspection Department's jurisdiction.
Worry about intelligence gathering,
why interfere in our duties?
What's wrong with you?
What do you plan to accomplish,
looking for an account that doesn't exist?
We'll see if it exists or not.
And if it does?
- Don't you know the answer?
- You're out of your mind.
You're digging your own grave.
And we'll see who gets buried
inside that grave, won't we?
Be my guest, then.
We searched his house all over,
but no traces of it.
He might have hidden it
outside somewhere.
Arrest all the committee
members immediately.
What?
All of them, including Hwang Taeseop.
Yes, Sir.
Gangmo, let's go.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com