Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 53
Eonni, have you heard the news?
What news?
According to eye-witness reports,
a blast was heard around 8 pm,
- Huge Fire at Beaute Boilers Yongin Factory -
with fire spreading from
the gas tanks inside the factory.
The Fire Department deployed thirty
fire trucks along with 200 firefighters...
to tame the flames, but strong winds
are currently hampering their efforts.
The police is confronting eye-witness
reports to find the possible causes,
with the possibility of an accidental
fire caused by negligence gaining ground.
What about President Lee...
What's going on?
Sotae!
President...
What happened?
Any casualties?
Thankfully, nobody died,
but employees on night duty
and a few guards were injured.
How about the factory?
Lot A was completely destroyed in the fire.
And a significant part
of Lot B was heavily damaged.
How about total damages incurred?
I'd roughly estimate it at over five billion.
What do we do now, President...
Wait... Wait a moment!
President Lee Gangmo, right?
- What do you think caused this fire?
- Will you be able to release your new boilers now?
This fire might severely impact
the sale of your Suseo apartments,
please give us a comment.
First...
We'll have to take care of the injured.
Here... Now is not the
time, so let's talk later.
Yes.
It's me, Chairman.
We just arrived at
Kimpo International Airport.
The police is investigating
the causes of the fire.
Stay with them until they
board that flight for the States.
Yes, Chairman.
Right...
Gather reporters from all
major dailies by tomorrow morning.
Are you going to have a press conference?
We must end on the 9 o'clock news.
Make sure my interview follows
right after reports of the accident.
I understand, Chairman.
Lee Miju, take a good look.
How your brother, Lee Gangmo,
will be mercilessly trampled on.
Jeongyeo...
Suyeon...
What are you doing here?
I saw you on TV and
got worried, so here I am.
Eonni... Who is that woman?
I'll tell my father, and
find a way to help you.
That won't be necessary.
No, I really want to help you.
Just the thought
gives me great strength.
Are you just leaving?
I've seen Gangmo, so it's okay.
Still, you came all the way here...
Jina.
Starting tomorrow, find
everything you can about this fire.
Everything from total
damages to possible causes.
All right, Eonni.
Once our factory in Osan is complete,
we will begin producing our ondol-based
Korean-style boiler in large quantities.
And with our trend-setting heating system,
our Suseo apartments will prove
once again their quality status.
It looks like you're eying a fierce
competition with Hangang Construction...
over these modern boiler systems,
so how do you feel about
the recent fire at their factory?
A boiler is equipment dealing
with fire and heat on a daily basis.
If what we're dealing with is a fire accident,
wouldn't that prove what kind of
quality you can expect from their products?
How can a news program act like this?
Putting that right after news of the fire...
Seems like the press is
pushing the negligence angle.
It was no accidental fire, this is arson.
So someone purposely
set the factory on fire?
On the day of the accident,
two new guards joined the company.
And now they have
vanished without a trace.
Who could be capable
of something like this?
Whomever would most benefit from
our factory being destroyed in the fire.
And... who is that?
Miju. Have any more side dishes?
All right.
There's a rumor the government
will clamp down on ailing companies.
I know.
So Congressman Oh
Byeongtak is in charge of it?
And one more congressman.
Jo Pilyeon.
My guess was right.
Jo Minwoo is behind this fire.
Even today's news was too deliberate.
As if someone had arranged it
that way to damage us.
Gangmo.
This is a conspiracy to bring you down.
So give that account to me.
Don't start, Hyung.
I'll handle this fight through business means.
But Jo Minwoo is being backed
by his father's political influence.
Hangang Construction
will never endure their assault.
I told you!
That Jo Pilyeon is still suspicious of you.
- This must be solved politically, Gangmo!
- Let me handle it, Hyung.
I cannot tolerate...
putting you in danger again.
So what you're asking for...
is a list of the ailing
companies we will force out?
To people like us, it would
be like finding a vein of gold.
If we move our pawns the right way,
it's only a matter of time before
we turn the stock market into a goldmine.
I bet.
Instead, if our profits go up,
we will generously reward your patronage.
I'd like you to do
something for us, if possible.
Yes, just say the word.
You know about the fire at Hangang
Construction's boiler factory, right?
How long would it take to make toilet
paper out of Hangang Construction's shares?
It's not a huge corporation,
but they've got solid foundations,
so I'm afraid it'll take some effort?!
Then, spare no expense
and do whatever it takes.
The sooner, the better.
All right.
We'll do that.
That's their specialty, all right.
Hangang Construction will soon
be gasping for air at your feet.
If there is anything else you need, just tell me.
I will do everything
in my power to help you.
Once that list is complete,
I'd like to be the first to see it.
We might use that
list to start a few M&As.
So you plan to turn
the company into a group.
Because we can't keep going on
as just a construction company.
It's during turbulent times that heroes emerge.
I'd like you to become the hero
who leads us out of these turbid days.
None other than my son.
Let's go have another
drink at home, for a change.
I'm tired.
I'll get going.
Did you find a place in
the States for that Wooju?
Yes, it will soon be ready.
Rush.
To Minwoo, that's a time-bomb that
could explode any minute.
All right, Congressman.
Let's talk outside a minute.
Come inside.
I remember hearing that
I'd never get to see you again...
The fire at the boiler factory...
Are you behind that?
Tell me!
Did you do that?
Did you really...
It wasn't you, right?
The Minwoo I knew would never do that.
You didn't do that, right?
I guess the Minwoo you
knew would never do that.
But that Jo Minwoo...
was killed by none other than you.
I'm no longer the man you knew.
I know no such thing as a conscience.
That's how I've lived so far,
and how I'll continue to live.
If you try to bring harm to my brother,
how do you think I will react?
Think I'll just sit back
and watch like a retard?
Must I really lose it and stake
my everything to get revenge?
I beg you, Minwoo...
Stop acting like your father,
enough with all those sins.
Stop pretending you care about me.
You know that
this will hurt everyone!
Nothing can hurt me anymore.
Since I've already lost everything.
Minwoo!
Aigoo... I've really had it with you...
Let's start talking now, shall we?
I don't know.
You don't?
I mean it...
Please don't kill me.
Please!
I don't know a thing.
Boys.
Don't do it...
Spare me!
Don't...
Where is your friend hiding?
I said speak, you piece of shit!
I don't know!
Please...
I really don't know!
He's not breathing!
Hey... Wake up!
You fool!
Open those eyes!
Ji Yeonsoo!
Are you going to keep
following me around all day?
That's the daily task I had
the privilege to be entrusted with.
You know that
I've really had it with you?!
So just... think of me as your shadow.
What?!
On your face.
Execute.
Uh?
How dare you talk back?
On your face!
Seonbaenim!
We need to talk.
I'm sorry.
You two are really something!
Are you just going to leave
me out in the cold like this?
What's the matter?
I've heard this from an acquaintance
of mine working for public security.
Turns out that at the
Namyoung-Dong Anti-Communist unit...
a Korea University student died.
Is it torture?
Yes.
All the police top brass
is on high alert as we speak.
It finally happened...
Dig a little deeper.
What do you plan to do?
The police will try to limit damages
and hide what really happened.
We need to tell people the truth.
Seonbaenim.
This would mean betraying the force.
It's our last chance
to get rid of Jo Pilyeon.
The political situation is like gunpowder.
Set the fuse on fire,
and the world as we
know it will forever change.
And then we'll take this opportunity
to reveal the account as well.
- But...
- I know what you fear.
But trust me, Chanseong.
Yes.
Let's take this to the end.
Where is Chief Yoo going?
What have you been
doing in there all this time?
What did you talk
about that I couldn't hear?
Thirty squats. Execute.
Uh?
I can't stand brats
who talk all the time.
Are you going to disobey my orders?
- Still, Chief...
- Execute!
Execute...
One!
Two!
Three!
Thank you for all your help.
Don't mention it, we should
be the ones thanking you.
So when the president comes back
from the US, you'll get us an appointment.
Certainly, Director Hwang.
So you're going to sell 7,000
Hangang Construction shares?
Yes... Yes.
15,000 shares of Hangang Construction?
All right.
I told you already that it's a mess
today because of Hangang Construction.
Is there a problem with
Hangang Construction's shares?
Ahh... That?
These last few days people have been
selling Hangang Construction stocks non-stop.
Selling?!
For the time being, looks like it will
continue reaching the daily permissible low.
If you plan to invest in the stock exchange,
I suggest you don't bother
with Hangang Construction.
You want to sell all your
Hangang Construction shares?
How are our stocks faring right now?
We closed today hitting
the daily permissible low again.
The fire at the factory
can't possibly be the reason.
I'm sure someone is
plotting something against us.
Ohh... A Manbo Construction employment a d?
- Manbo Construction -
Sir.
Why is that there?
How could you let this get posted here?
I apologize, Director Yeom.
I've made you wait, didn't I?
Nah, I just got here.
Did you look into it?
What's the reason?
Who's trying to damage
our share price on purpose?
There were rumors spreading
at the stock exchange.
Rumors?!
That the government is secretly preparing
a list of ailing companies to be ousted.
And you're telling me Hangang
Construction is on that list?
It's pretty much
accepted as fact by now.
Jo Minwoo, that son of a bitch!
Gangmo.
It's already too late to
deal with those rumors.
If this keeps going on
for another few days,
you'll cross a river of no return.
Get all the capital we
have and start buying shares.
What money could we possibly have?
Just a look at the construction
sites will make you lose sleep.
Don't you remember how Jo Minwoo
gained control of Manbo Construction?
Gangmo...
If share prices go any lower,
Jo Minwoo will buy them,
and then he will steal
Hangang Construction from us!
All right.
We'll try to do everything we can.
This is serious.
I think a group of employees
might hand their resignation.
I overheard what they
were saying in the man's room,
and I guess Manbo Construction is
hiring experienced workers or something.
If they start stealing our
employees as well, it's all over!
Immediately gather all employees
ranked section chief and above.
All right.
Manbo Construction.
I see their conditions
are quite favorable.
By any chance,
should anyone be interested
in joining them, I won't stop you.
I'm sure they'll pay you even more.
Particularly considering the
fact they're trying to damage us,
if you say you come
from Hangang Construction,
you will receive even better treatment.
But you can bet on this.
That special treatment is what you'll
receive when you join us again in three years.
If anyone has already written
their resignation or plans to do it,
you're free to hand
them to me right now.
And as for everyone else,
I will listen to any idea on the
boiler that is currently under development.
Those receiving top honors will get
10 million won and a special promotion,
so give it your best.
That would be all.
Is it true that Hangang Construction
has been added to the list of ailing companies?
Please, be honest with us.
Is there such a possibility?
Folks.
In your estimation,
is this Hangang Construction
of ours really an ailing company?
The people Hangang Construction needs...
are men and women
willing to solve problems...
and together sacrifice for
the good of the company!
Collect any resignation
they might hand you.
All right.
Chairman.
He's Director Woo Jaecheol of Bando Insurance.
Come on in.
- Have a seat, please.
- Yes.
I hear you've incurred heavy losses because
of the fire at Hangang Construction's factory?
It's always a possibility in our trade.
So how are you dealing
with the insurance payments?
Once the cause of the fire is officially...
Suggest the possibility of a self-inflicted arson,
and postpone any payments.
What?
I'm sure news reports mentioned
the possibility of an arson?
That's certainly true, but...
Along with Manbo Group, I can
influence the decisions of a few other companies.
Just the right word from you,
and all those companies could
suddenly be convinced to knock at your door.
All I need from you is to postpone
those payments until my further notice.
I'm sure that's not going to
be much of a problem for you?
What is this supposed to mean?
You're insinuating the possibility
that this arson was self-inflicted?
So you came, President Lee.
How can you refuse to pay because of that?
I wasn't suggesting we wouldn't pay,
just to wait until
our investigation is complete.
And when will that be?
I can't really give you
any estimate on that...
Look!
How are you going to compensate us
for our shares hitting the bottom,
while all that remains
of our factory is rubble?
If we don't rebuild that factory right away,
you know what kind of
losses we're going to incur?
The company has already
decided its policy on this case.
I'm sorry, President Lee.
Fine.
Investigate all you want.
But should that investigation reveal
that it wasn't a self-inflicted arson,
you will be held responsible
for every single penny we lose!
What did you want to talk about?
I need investment funds.
How much?
Five bil... no.
The more, the better.
Investment funds for what?
Why aren't you answering me?
Hangang Construction stocks
have been plummeting for days.
I'd like to buy them.
Hangang Construction was added
to the list of ailing companies.
It's still only a rumor.
Are you really sure of that?
Once development for
their new boiler is complete,
their share price will rebound for sure.
- So I thought it could be a good opportunity...
- Wake up!
Director...
There are standards when it comes to investing.
Don't you know that letting personal whims
affect your judgment will only ruin you?
But...
I believe in President Lee.
You were the first to tell me that a company's
greatest collateral is the people who run it.
So if you don't trust President
Lee, at least trust me.
I will act as his collateral.
Are you telling me that
you don't even trust me?
I don't want to lose you over this.
If you really insist on helping President Lee,
you can just leave me.
Since I will never betray my principles.
I apologize.
Ehh... I've really had it with this...
President.
Yeom Gyeongja.
What are you doing here at this hour?
They have no intention
of leaving, how can I?
What?
Are you telling me our
employees are still here?
So you're suggesting we
add a thermostat to the boiler, right?
Yes, so that our customers will be able
to choose the temperature they prefer.
Nice... That's very good!
So we'll take that...
Chief Yoon, how about you?
I'd like to focus on the
boiler's appearance first.
Boilers in the past have only
focused on their functions,
completely ignoring any design issue.
And that is why I thought
we could approach our customers...
with a fresher, more vivid design, while at the
same time conveying a sense of familiarity.
- So you'd like to change the boiler's image.
- Yes.
With people like these,
how could anyone go bust?
What are you doing?
Hey... You...
Are you investigating on that case?
What case?
I know everything already.
- At the Namyoung-Dong...
- Hey.
Will you keep that mouth shut?
I'm warning you,
don't even think of getting in the way.
Is that clear?
But, where is Chief Lee?
The opposition party members
are facing even tighter surveillance.
If this keeps up, I wonder if we'll be able
to secure a quorum before the plenary session.
Look at the bottom.
- College Student Under
Investigation Dies from Shock -
He died as a result of torture.
And of course that article
covered up the facts to limit the damages.
Inside this briefcase you'll
find the truth about this case.
Consult the opposition
and leak this to the press.
- You...
- If you can't reach that agreement politically,
you'll have to ask
the people to help you.
This kind of accident can be
the spark which ignites them.
- Case Report -
Saw them?
Yeah, I did.
Who was that?
Who is my father meeting?
I think he might be quite handsome.
What?!
That's not what I asked you!
Any description or
whether you've ever seen him.
How am I supposed to know that?
Aigoo... I ought to...
Take this,
and while pretending to shoot
the puppy, get him on camera.
What is all this, really?
All right.
I shouldn't even
bother asking that idiot...
It's an appraisal on other
companies we should add to the list.
Hangang Construction?!
So why should Hangang
Construction be ousted?
A look at that and it'll be obvious,
but right now both their share price
and cash flow situation are critical.
I did hear about the
fire at their boiler factory,
but I never really imagined
they'd be facing such issues...
According to reports, they might not
even be able to complete their Suseo apartments.
I think it would be wise to oust them immediately,
and entrust the construction to other companies.
I see it in a different light.
In consideration of the character
shown by Hangang Construction so far,
I'd be more inclined to
give them another chance...
We're not here to
help companies in trouble.
Are you ignoring the president's wish to get
rid of all the black sheep and save the economy?
Look... How about we drop the
act and show some honesty?
Is this what you call saving the economy?
Aren't you just making an example out
of corporations who don't go along for the ride,
trying to downplay the
effects of this lame-duck period?
Watch your language.
Why don't you stop trying to
paper over the president's true motives?
Shouldn't I know what
the purpose of this really is?
Anyhow, Hangang Construction will
be ousted no matter what, just so you know.
Have you had lunch?
So I hear that list has become...
the Holy Grail of the stock
exchange and many a corporation.
I'm sure it has.
So try to explain the reason why
Hangang Construction was mentioned there.
I'm sure you know the
reason a lot better than me?!
If you oust a company just
because of a few difficulties,
how many companies will survive?
You know why Baekpa's private-lending
cartel was torn to shreds?
Because he refused to listen.
He chose the worst possible
target to raise some hackles.
So I guess this worst
possible target would be you.
Let's suppose there are a a
hundred hen inside a hencoop.
It's up to the chef to choose
which ones will be slaughtered for dinner.
They can cry and voice
their grievances all they want,
but those poor hen have no such authority.
Hen in the hencoop...
Sure suits you.
Listen, President Lee.
Why do you think I
agreed to have lunch with you?
I was thinking I could
give you one last chance.
I'm all ears.
If my guess is right,
there was a secret bipartisan agreement
on the constitutional amendment...
at the last Olympics Support Committee event.
Who has that secret fund account?
Don't you think that asking
me that is a bit foolish?
Give me that account.
What I'm proposing is to exchange
the Hangang Construction...
you so dearly cherish with that account.
If you're a businessman with brains,
I think there is no reason why
you would refuse my offer?!
Too bad.
If I knew this,
I would have set business aside
and focused on finding that account.
If that account was in my possession,
this discussion would have been different.
I guess I would have told you this.
"If you think you can do that, be my guest."
"Because I'll roll that account
and stick it down your throat."
Like that?
The secret fund account for that list...
Should be quite the exciting fight.
Of course, that is if I have that account.
I see you're walking down the same
path which led Baekpa to his downfall.
You'll soon find out what kind of misery...
the hen in the hencoop are consigned to.
It's me, Director.
Come in.
How did it go?
Did you find out?
President Noh was pulling the strings
and affecting Hangang Construction's shares.
Noh Gapsoo?!
And it's not just Hangang Construction.
These days President Noh is pouring
huge money into the stock exchange.
It's Jo Pilyeon.
Excuse me?
Noh Gapsoo is acting
under Jo Pilyeon's instructions.
So why focus on the stock exchange...
I guess they'll use the list of ailing
companies to manipulate the market.
Keep looking into it.
Find out which companies he's targeting,
and how much money he's investing.
All right, Director.
- Hangang Construction 1510 Won (per share) -
- I'll be counting on you, then.
- Yes, thank you.
Who is this?
We meet here?!
Here for some investment?
Well...
Was thinking I could give
Hangang Construction a try.
They're pretty much hopeless...
They've been branded as an ailing company,
and their exclusion has
been pretty much confirmed.
Wow... Director Hwang.
You're not as up to speed as I thought?!
I hear you were the
one who spread that rumor?
So I guess I'm up to speed, after all?
I'd watch what I say if I were you...
Don't you know that your word is
everything in the private-lending market?
So that's what you used to
spread such false rumors?
Hey, Hwang Jeongyeon!
I guess you believe your
mother still has any influence,
but Director Yoo is about to go belly up.
She already lost half her capital.
It's all thanks to you.
Thanks to you, they took the IOU list
and the pledge from her,
and the remaining half will
soon meet the same fate.
We'll see if you'll keep prancing
around acting so smug when that happens.
What is he saying?
The director lost half her capital?!
Find out her cash flow situation.
Yes, Eonni.
Anything of note?
The boiler thermostat
might be our best option...
But?
It doesn't have the kind of impact
that would affect customer confidence.
I'd rather choose something
related to the accident...
You call that driving?
Shideok.
Push the horn again.
One more time.
Ahh... I can't eat this anymore, really.
Are we going to keep eating
jjajangmyeon trapped in here?
I told you!
Before that is complete, we're
not going to leave this place.
Ahh... You're obsessed with that, all right.
Hangang Construction will
survive only if we complete that.
Or else we'll have to open a junk shop.
Ehh... Eat yours, will you?
How is everyone?
- Are you having lunch?
- Want me to order some for you as well?
No, go ahead.
Did you add the thermostat?
Yes.
But... President.
Even with that function added,
you won't be able to wash away the stigma
of products of a factory which caught fire.
There's a good possibility that Manbo
Construction will take our share of the market.
Ahh... Here he goes again,
killing my appetite.
So, what? We can work hard all
we want, but it still won't mean squat?
How about we add another function?
Is there anything else to add?
I'd like to add something that would alert
customers when the boiler has a malfunction.
Some kind of alarm system?
The lion's share of customer complaints...
dealt with their worries
about accidents and malfunctions.
Let's offer a way to
prevent such accidents.
Hey... I get this feeling brewing inside...
Sotae, don't you feel the same?
Wait...
In that case, we could use the
fire at the factory in our favor!
A boiler warning against fires, made
by a factory which experienced it firsthand.
Don't you think?
How about it?
Would that be possible?
We'll have to give it a try.
Because if we manage to make it,
it would clearly help us distance
ourselves from Manbo Construction.
Gangmo... Gangmo.
You'll have to come back to the office.
What's the matter?
A shareholder's meeting has been organized.
What are you doing here?
I was invited here,
so show me the way.
Invited?!
How many company
shares have you been buying?
Don't worry.
Since they haven't reached
the price I want yet.
Seems like your shareholders
have plenty of complaints.
Good luck.
President.
Are you aware of the fact that rumors
about the company's impending collapse...
are spreading both at the stock
exchange and in the private-lending sector?
I am.
And they're just rumors.
The same shares worth 2000 won
last week have already lost 500 won.
How do you plan to deal with this?
Once the boiler we're
currently developing is complete,
share prices will rebound.
And when are you
going to rebuild the factory?
Is it true that we will have a
net loss of 4.3 billion this year?
When will they come?
They should be here any minute.
Please calm down, and listen to me.
I perfectly understand your anxiety.
So I will take this opportunity
to make you a promise.
From here on in...
President Lee Gangmo?
What is it?
You'll have to follow us.
What is the matter?
You're under arrest
for business embezzlement.
I'll come on my own two feet.
What's going on?
Why is the police arresting you?
President...
Embezzlement... What goddamned
embezzlement are you talking about?
Have you seen it?
Have you?
Keep acting like this,
and we'll enforce compulsory execution.
No need to worry.
It'll be over in a moment.
Let's go.
You'll soon find out what kind of misery...
the hen in the hencoop are consigned to.
Isn't the police station the other way?
We're heading to our southern branch.
Southern branch?
So, what, you're prosecutors?
It's her retrieval rate
for this fourth quarter.
Most of the Jong-Ro business has
fallen under Noh Gapsoo's control.
And Myeongdong is in no better shape.
What is even more worrying is that
even the clients who decided to stay...
are also dealing with President Noh.
How could she let it get to
this point without saying a word...
The director told me
not to tell you anything.
She was worried this could bring you distress...
Have a seat.
I was about to come pay you a visit.
Shall we have a drink?
No... I wanted to
have a word with you.
You told me you needed
investment funds, right?
So that you could buy
Hangang Construction shares.
I'll take care of that.
Sorry for making you worry about nothing.
First, start with this.
I gathered five billion in a rush.
Director...
If you really want to control
those Hangang Construction shares,
this will make no difference.
You'll soon get an additional
ten billion on top of that.
This is not really neces...
No, just don't do it, Director.
I know what kind of cash
flow issues you're facing.
As you said, a wrong investment done this
way and the whole organization could collapse.
That's right.
I'm putting the entire organization
on the line for this investment.
What?
Once the government publishes
their list of ousted companies,
pandemonium is going
to hit the stock exchange.
Noh Gapsoo is pouring huge sums
into it, as if it was his last resort.
And Hangang Construction is his first bait.
So you're fighting with
your back to the wall as well?
If this keeps up, the rest of the organization
will fall under President Noh's control anyway.
You said you believe in President Lee, right?
So I'll believe in you.
My collateral for this
investment is you, Jeongyeon.
But bear this in mind.
Our destiny depends on this fight.
I will...
I will succeed at all cost.
I will succeed, and
help the people I lo...
And help the people
I like succeed as well.
President Lee was arrested by prosecutors.
Here.
Let's begin.
Did you say it was business embezzlement?
The reason why you arrested me.
You refused to nominate a lawyer.
I didn't commit any crime,
so why would I need legal counsel?
Nobody who comes here
openly confesses his crimes.
Let's start.
Here... What shall we start from?
A tax audit?
Or maybe site supervision?
Right...
A look at special loan benefits
would probably be better.
Ahh... Myeongwol, foolish wench...
And you call this a photo?
Ahh... I have no idea who this is...
Are... Are you done?
Let's go.
They're still following us?!
Don't mind them.
But, where are we going?
Yes.
Did you meet with Congressman Jang?
Yes, just now.
I was feeling nervous as of late,
but he told me to have faith, you know.
It all depends on you, Chairman.
Don't you worry.
I'll call you again.
How long have you been here?
Buy me lunch.
I'm so hungry...
Did you come in to
earn yourself a free meal?
Then, what? There's nothing
else for me to do...
Seonbaenim!
Have you been to this new
tonkatsu place down the street?
It's to die for!
Seonbaenim!
Their investigation
will last 48 hours at worst.
Don't worry, Miju.
And the company?
I've heard that Manbo
Construction could gain control of it.
That's our biggest concern.
We can try to stop
stocks from plummeting,
but if it's added to the list
of ousted companies, it's all over.
So all we need to do is
convince Congressman Oh Byeongtak?
With Jo Pilyeon by his
side, that'll be impossible.
Although I guess postponing
the announcement would do it.
Then, we'll have to try everything
we can to make them postpone it.
Director Yoo met him because of that,
but there was no
convincing Congressman Oh.
Then,
does it mean that there is
no hope for Hangang Construction?
We need to fight to the end.
Let me ask you just one thing.
Congressman Oh and Deputy
Mayor Han Myeongseok looked really close.
Is that true?
Why are you asking?
Tell me, please.
I believe in the word of God,
his wisdom and sense of justice.
By the way...
When did Dad start going to church?
This is all to make a
decent man out of you.
So just pray.
Head to the Myeongdong Cathedral.
Getting the Catholic Priests'
Association for Justice involved...
and using their help to leak
this to the press would be our best option.
In the name of the Father, the
Son, and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
May the grace of the Holy Spirit fill
your heart with light,
so that you may confess your sins with
loving trust and come to know that God is merciful.
A few days ago at the
Namyoung-Dong Anti-Communist unit,
a young college student passed away.
The police treated it as
an unpremeditated homicide,
but in fact,
it was a cruel and
cold-blooded act of murder,
perpetrated by a number
of people while torturing him.
Here are the documents regarding that case.
Refute the claims made by
public power to cover the truth,
and let our people
know what truly happened.
- College Student Under
Investigation Dies from Shock -
Congressman Oh and Deputy Han
are closer than most brothers.
I know what you're worried about.
But trust me just this once.
Would Deputy Han be able
to convince Congressman Oh?
Perhaps.
If there is anyone who can convince him,
that can only be Deputy Han.
So International Group is
going through liquidation?
This is carnage.
Now that we're approaching
the end of this regime,
they're starting to show their teeth.
It must be hard to bear.
It doesn't stop at that.
Not to mention that Jo Pilyeon
is completely obsessed over this...
So what will happen
to Hangang Construction?
If the data Jo Pilyeon sent me is legit,
they'll inevitably have to be ousted.
It's a shame...
It's really a waste to see someone
like President Lee go down this way.
Yes.
Aigoo... Isn't this Cha Soojeong?
What are you doing here, Soojeong?
How have you been, Congressman?
Deputy.
About President Lee Gangmo.
We really can't find anything.
Really?
No signs of tax evasion,
not to mention any trace of illegal loans.
The investigation can
only last 48 hours, right?
Yes, he must be released afterwards.
Then, release him and arrest him again.
We don't have all that time to waste.
I hear you'll soon open your law firm?
Since you're leaving the
prosecutor's office for good,
shouldn't you make a little money on the side?
Let's take a break.
I'm sure that by now,
Congressman Jo Pilyeon will be here.
Tell him to come
see me, while he's here.
If you tell him I have a certain account,
he'll run here drooling like a rabid dog.
Go tell him.
That Lee Gangmo...
has the account he's looking for.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com
Why don't you get out
of this while you still can?
You really think you can beat me?
Gather all the capital you can.
I said find all the money we have left!
I can't see you anymore from now on.
Because I'm not your father.
Why is Jo Pilyeon bothering you?
And what about Jo Minwoo?
Thank you for setting our factory on fire.
You will lose because of that.
There are only three days left, Lee Gangmo.
In three days, that'll be
worth less than toilet paper.
Can you finish our boiler in three days?
I said it must be completed in three days!