Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 39 -
Sir.
Aren't you sleeping yet?
No need to come in.
Go have some rest.
I'm Han Sojin.
- Taeyang Trading CEO-
HAN Sojin
I'm Lee Gangmo.
So you run Hangang Construction?!
But what's your relation with her?
I don't think
that's any of your business?
Ahh... Again being snarky.
- Let me pour you one.
- No thanks.
I need to go.
How much is it?
2,000 won.
Thank you.
I wanted a word with you.
If it's regarding the loan,
you can look for me at the office.
You're still here?
Had a few things to take care of.
All the better.
I need a favor.
Dig into this fella for me.
Han... So...jin...
And who is he?
He's been approaching
Jeongyeon for a while.
What?!
Jeongyeon doesn't really understand men.
If he was a decent man,
I could understand.
But he just strikes me the wrong way.
And if he really is a decent person...
Think that'll make any difference to you?
I'll be counting on you, Shideok.
Ever since you were little,
you always liked fish cake.
You're back, Hyungnim?
Look into this Lee Gangmo.
I have a bad feeling about him.
Yes, Hyungnim.
So according to the doctor,
Baekpa only has three months at best?
Yes.
This should end with a blitzkrieg...
But that Hwang Jeongyeon
is just as bothersome as her mother.
That half-brother of hers.
Was it Hwang Jeongshik?!
Is he gambling at our joint again?
Yes, Hyungnim.
What?!
Has Minwoo really become that arrogant?
Ever since becoming chairman he's been
acting so haughty, I can't take it anymore.
Prick's grown some balls?!
He should remember when he
was groveling at my father's feet.
I really...
Ohh... Bravo!!
See?
If I'm the one calling
Jo Minwoo, he'll come.
Here, a hundred thousand each.
We made a bet!
Let's see my money.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks.
I'll spend them wisely.
Aww... Thank you!
Hey, Hwang Jeongshik.
You said it was important,
what the hell is all this?
Minwoo.
We're best of friends, aren't we?
What?!
Give me some money.
Or if you really don't want to,
you could let me win every penny
you have at the poker table?!
You...
Waste my time with this bullshit again,
and I won't let it fly next time.
And if you won't let it fly, then what?!
You little prick...
You were nothing but a
salaryman until yesterday...
So, what,
you think I'm an idiot?
You better watch out, too.
This prick is no friend of ours.
You might end up in
my same situation, so...
Jeongshik!
Hey, you.
Don't ever gamble with him again,
is that clear?
Let's look where we're going, shall we?
What?
You little...
I apologize.
Hyungnim.
Who could he possibly be...
Jo Minwoo.
Chairman of Manbo Construction.
What?!
So young and he's already chairman?
That's not what matters.
It's the fact that Congressman
Jo Pilyeon is his father that does.
Chairman Jo?
Let me apologize again.
- CHA Bucheol -
What's with you?
You may end up facing some touchy
situations while doing business.
Call me anytime.
Whatever the problem,
I can solve it for you.
Without money, this is useless.
President Lee.
Have you seen today's paper?
What's the matter?
Take a look at this.
- France Beaute Boilers
To Sell Korean Subsidiary -
Looks like those French folks
are selling this?!
It's a gas boiler company?!
From now on, gas boilers
will dominate the market.
If we equip our apartments with
one of these, it's game over.
Why, we don't have the money?
I made a few rough calculations,
- and 12 billion or so would do?!
- Aigoo...
Is 12 billion pocket money?
We can't afford to
invest such figures right now.
This could seriously make a mark...
Then why don't you make one by yourself?
You always brag about
being able to build anything.
Keep prattling, you sorry-ass twat...
I mean, where would
you find 12 billion won?!
Beaute announced that they
will sell their Korean subsidiary.
Are you planning to acquire it?
If we install such gas boilers
in our apartments,
nobody will be able to compete with us.
Chairman.
We had to suffer heavy losses
because of all the aggregate we bought.
If we continue expanding so recklessly,
we'll only bring more losses upon ourselves.
Don't you realize that aggressive
investment is the only way to survive?
Director Moon, form a project team
to decide on our bidding price.
Certainly, Chairman.
Just as the board
of directors suggested,
our cash flow is a
cause for concern indeed.
Get back all the money we loaned
to small and medium-sized firms.
What?!
You're going to take it back already?
It was at zero interest, wasn't it?
There were no repayment terms
listed in the contract.
You must do everything to get that
money back before our Beaute acquisition.
Even the banks have resigned
themselves regarding their debts.
I think the best way to deal with this
would be letting a pro handle it.
A pro?!
How about we entrust it to him?
- CHA Bucheol -
Ehh... That's not the right posture.
Put it down.
Right, don't just push up.
Down, and then up.
That's right.
And now you go back down.
That's right, good.
Looks like that Han Sojin owns quite
the significant share of real estate abroad.
His credit rating is fine,
and Jeongyeon seems to trust him.
Can I have the
installment for Jeongyeon?
Pay back the entire sum.
Oppa...
No need for installments now.
And you can stop conveying to me
news about her as well.
Can I really do that?
That'd be all.
Oppa... Then, come to me. Uh?
I'll make you happy.
I've only had eyes for you all this time.
I never liked anyone other than you.
Gyeongja...
I know...
That it won't work.
Still,
at least once, I wanted to tell you that.
I found Miju!
Where is she now?
An employee at a shoe store in
Hannam-Dong goes by the name Lee Miju.
It's legit.
How do they feel? Do they fit?
- I'll take these.
- Yes.
Come on in.
Do you have anything particular in mind?
Sorry to interrupt,
but I need to ask you something.
Is there a Lee Miju working here?
Don't take that the wrong way,
I'm actually her brother.
There is no Lee Miju here?!
Ahh... I did hear one of our
former employees was a certain Lee Miju.
When did she quit?
It's been quite a while, I think?
And you don't know where she is now?
I'm sorry.
Just a moment.
You can reach me here.
Should you find anything about her,
please give me a call.
Yes...
It's me, Ma'am.
Someone looking for Miju just came.
Looks like she went into hiding again,
knowing we were looking for her?!
Miju...
You really...
I told you not to eat that way, didn't I?
It's frivolous.
Did you really pay any attention
during those etiquette lessons?
There is such a thing as grace,
the most evident example
of which are your table manners.
How many times do I have to tell you
that once you become a star,
your every action will be scrutinized?
I apologize...
I'll have to replace that teacher.
Director...
My teacher didn't do anything wrong.
And didn't I tell you to keep your feelings
to yourself, or any mystery will be lost?
Yes...
Don't laugh for no reason, either.
Nor should you smile.
Are we clear?
Yes...
Do whatever it takes to get that
money back by the end of the month.
You'll be paid after completion.
Just think of this as a test
you'll put me through.
I'd like to meet
Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
He's not the kind of man...
who can spare any time for people like you.
But someone with his ambitions
would surely benefit from my help.
Do it right!
Is that how you treat our esteemed guests?
I apologize, Hyungnim.
Please, try to understand our situation.
It's for you, President Maeng.
Me?
He...Hello?
H...Honey!
I'm scared...
What's the matter?
Strange people came here, and...
Dad!
I'm scared, Dad!
Juhee! Ju...
You goddamned beasts...
What are you doing to my daughter?
If you lay a single finger on her...
You will report us to the police?!
Be my guest!
Then I'll show you what happens
when a rabid dog bites you.
Your colleagues here gave up
their house to save their company,
but you have nothing to your name?!
What you did seem to have was
a pretty decent life insurance.
So if you want to save your family,
at least pay your debts with your life.
Isn't that your duty
as head of the family?
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
President Maeng...
is dead.
What?!
How did it happen?
Yesterday, he was involved
in a car accident.
Ahh... I cursed him
deep down all this time,
but I suddenly feel guilty?!
Now you're screwed.
He'll come after you from
the afterlife, seeking revenge.
Ahh... You fool, someone is dead
and you're in the mood for jokes?
Where is his wake?
You'll soon receive that insurance money.
You know my account number, right?
If you really care about your daughter,
you better wire that money.
And should you
ever tell anyone about us...
You know, right?
President Lee. So you and
President Maeng knew each other?
Yes...
What are you doing here?
We were just business acquaintances.
We really lost a great man...
Never lose courage,
and call me if you need anything.
Got it?
Thank you for coming.
I really don't know what to say.
It's not much, but please accept it.
President Lee.
Are you leaving already?
I'm a little busy.
So I hear you and Hwang Jeongyeon
grew up together?
I see you're quite good
at collecting information.
When it turns out the woman you're
attracted to has male friends,
you can't help but feel nervous.
Can you let me in on
any secret to win her over?
I can't say.
If there is any such thing,
I'd like to hear it as well.
Can I have a word with you?
Good shot.
My name is Cha Bucheol.
Do you remember me?
You know me?
*Yojeong: upscale restaurants,
sort of an evolution of gisaeng parlors
We saw each other at the saloon*
where you met Baekpa.
Is that so?
You don't exactly come to mind?!
Sir, it's me, Bucheol.
I came to pay my respects.
Just leave for tonight.
So what you want from me is money?
I'm sure you know that the
president's term will soon be over,
*1983 bombing of Rangoon's Aung San
Mausoleum, while President Jeon was on visit
and that he's establishing a foundation for
the families of the Aung San bombing* victims.
A few chaebol groups
have already agreed...
What kind of interest rate
are we looking at?
Excuse me?
If you want money from a private lender,
isn't paying interest a given?
Sir...
You dare ask for interests
when the president is involved?
Regardless of their status,
anyone who receives money from me
is nothing but a customer.
Looks like I'm dealing with an old fart
who doesn't know who he's dealing with!
Even when senility knocks at the door,
you better remember this day.
Are we clear?
Sir...
"Foundation" certainly sounds better,
but he's only trying to
create a secret fund.
Still, trying to contend
with Congressman Jo...
Money is power's middle name.
There is no reason why someone
with my money should fear him.
But, tell me.
What do I owe this visit to?
How much do you think
Baekpa's assets amount to?
Let's get to the point.
I'll get my hands on all his money.
Of course, I couldn't do that by myself.
Which is why I'm asking your help.
Sounds fun.
Continue.
I'm sure you know a
certain Hwang Jeongyeon.
She is the daughter of Manbo
Construction's former chairman.
I know her.
I've been instructed by Baekpa
to try to bring her down.
If I manage to succeed,
I'll return under his wings.
So the point is,
if I help you deal with this,
you'll get your hands on Baekpa's fortune?
I'm confident I can do it.
Go back.
Congressman...
Don't think I have any time
to waste watching your back.
When Baekpa dies,
where do you think
all that money will end up?
Couldn't care less.
Get him out of my sight.
All right.
- Let's go.
- That money!
Will all go to Hwang Jeongyeon!
What's that supposed to mean?
Baekpa's money will all
go to Hwang Jeongyeon?!
Baekpa's current heir Yoo Gyeongok...
is Hwang Jeongyeon's birth mother.
The moment Yoo Gyeongok
inherits Baekpa's fortune,
Hwang Jeongyeon will attempt
to reconquer Manbo Construction.
Still no interest?
Looks like we might
need to have a word,
so let's talk elsewhere.
Jeongshik, that useless son of a...
So you're sure he's here, right?
I verified his room firsthand.
Ahh... I ought to just...
Do you know how much your tab amounts to?
Hey... Are you out of your mind?
I risk getting fired because of you!
Let's see that money...
Pay back all the money
you spent in my name!
You little brat, I ought to...
Let this go.
I'm gonna hit you!
Ohh... Now we even
add assault to the list?
Go ahead then, be my guest!
If you have all that
money to waste, go ahead!
Aigoo... You're just
asking for trouble!
Dad...
Just my luck...
Jeongshik!
What are you, Hong Gildong?
Showing up here, while you
should still be in America...
Why is a young man like you
wasting his life this way?
What's there to be surprised about?
I've always been a pathetic loser,
didn't you know?
If you know how pathetic you are,
you should wake up!
Why don't you wake up?
Say what?
After throwing all your eggs in
Jeongyeon's basket and ending up penniless,
now you suddenly feel inclined
to treat me like a son?
You stupid little...
You know?
I have no use for a
penniless father, either.
So, please!
Don't ever show your face
around me, is that clear?
You little fool!
Why did you hit me?
How can you have the nerve to hit me?
Sure, you might hate to see me
in such a pathetic state,
but it's exactly because you're in this
pathetic state that I can't abandon you!
If you'd made something out of your life,
I wouldn't even be here, you fool!
But look at you...
How can seeing what has
become of you not break my heart?
Good to hear.
Because that heart of yours will
suffer a lot more from now on.
Say what?
And you know why?
Because I'll walk straight
into the pits of hell.
Take a good look
at your son's downfall.
Look and cry tears of regret
for the rest of your days!
Is that clear?
Wait!
Jeongshik!
Jeongshik!!
Jo Pilyeon is here.
It would be wise to leave this place.
Go after Jeongshik, will you?
I'm just worried he
might try something stupid.
Just find out where he's going.
All right.
Jo Pilyeon...
It's all because of
that damned Jo Pilyeon...
Fine.
I'll just get rid of that bastard,
and die along with him!
Fine, let's get it over with!
So Baekpa's fortune could
all go to Hwang Jeongyeon?
Since Yoo Gyeongok is her mother,
it's quite a plausible scenario.
Thankfully, someone working for
Baekpa volunteered to help us.
And who is that?
You'll find out in due time.
First, we need to help him
cause Hwang Jeongyeon's downfall.
I'll need your help down
the line, just so you know.
Jo Pilyeon!!
I'll kill you once and for all!
Think you can kill me
with that rock alone?
That's right...
I'll see you in hell!
Congressman!
How dare...
How dare you do this to him!
- Calm down, Seonbaenim.
- Let go!
I'll handle this, so escort him out.
Are you all right?
Hwang Taeseop...
Next time we meet,
consider yourself dead!
Congressman...
Jo Pilyeon!
I will kill you with my own hands!
You're human trash!
What do you think
Jo Pilyeon fears the most?
If you really want to get revenge,
first find a way to destroy
everything he's accomplished so far.
Who really are you?
Despite working for Jo Pilyeon,
why are you trying...
I'm just someone who bears...
as big a grudge against
Jo Pilyeon as you do.
I might not know when it will come,
but one of us will one day
cause Jo Pilyeon's downfall.
Who on earth are you?
You will soon find out.
Jeongshik...
Please, get a hold of yourself!
Where did you get so drunk?
I'll get you some honey water.
Drink it and go to sleep.
I met Dad.
My father...
Your ex-husband.
I met him after four years.
So?
What did your father say?
Is that what you care about?
You're not even asking how he's doing?
What did he tell you?
He was in such good shape
that at first I felt relieved,
which quickly turned into anger.
When he left for the States,
I blamed ourselves for abandoning him.
But seeing him like that,
it rather feels like we were
the ones to be abandoned.
But I'm even angrier at you now.
Why would you?
You abandoned my father,
and only live for that damned bottle!
What other joy left do I have?
My only son spends all day gambling,
and we're about to go broke,
how else can I cope with all this?
Is this what you divorced for?
What?
This is all your fault!
You forced Dad to leave us,
you lost all our money!
It's all because of you!
And you're telling me you
don't know who I did that for?
At least spare me
that "for your sake" excuse!
Jeongshik!
I've had it with you.
You make me sick!
You insolent little...
Jeongshik...
Are you all right?
I'm sorry, Jeongshik...
Forgive me...
Forgive your mother, Jeongshik...
I'm so sorry...
- I'm so...
- Don't touch me!
Jeongshik...
I can't breathe...
It's driving me insane!
Jeongshik... Jeongshik!!
What?!
"You make me sick"?!
You bastard...
You're the only thing I live for...
How can you refuse any loans?
Why are you suddenly acting like that?
I'm sorry.
Please go back.
If that business plan was insufficient,
I'll add whatever is needed.
Your business plan is not the issue.
Is it because of Congressman Jo Pilyeon?
Anyhow, our bank cannot
lend you that money.
President...
President!
Director Han?!
Director Hwang?!
What do you mean, saying Jo Pilyeon
tried to stop them from lending you money?
You know Congressman Jo?
I blocked Director Han's
loan as instructed.
Well done.
Right as I was trying to
acquire a boiler company,
Manbo Construction got in the way.
So that's why Congressman Jo
would interfere with that bank loan.
We were just about to sign...
By gas boilers company,
what are we talking about?
I'm sure you'll be familiar
with France's Beaute.
Over half the boilers used in
apartments come from them.
I understand why Manbo
Construction would be interested.
Do you have enough funds
for the acquisition?
I'm selling my overseas
real estate as we speak.
Once I'm done with that,
I might be able to present
a competitive bidding price.
But the deposit is the real issue.
You need to settle that on
the same day you win the bid,
and now that Congressman Jo froze that money...
How much would that deposit amount to?
Since it's 10 percent of the entire price,
it will be about 1.2 billion.
So...
Would you be able to
lend me just 300 million?
300 million?
It's all I'm missing.
I can use my overseas
real estate as collateral.
300 million is our entire
capital at the moment.
I don't want Manbo Construction to
steal that acquisition under my nose.
Please help me out, Director Hwang.
Birth name, Cha Bucheol.
After working under Baekpa,
he was kicked out for improper conduct.
He also has a past as a
sort of private lender hunter,
and he's got quite the precedents,
both for assault and fraud.
Then, how about that
"Han Sojin" card he gave me?
He's actually an overseas resident.
Cha Bucheol merely forged his documents.
So it was a forgery...
And I was wondering why
I couldn't find a thing...
He's joined forces
with Jo Pilyeon and his son.
What are they after?
Baekpa's fortune.
He set his sights
on Hwang Jeongyeon's money...
so that he could regain
Baekpa's confidence.
If things go our way, we could
use his own trap against him.
Jo Minwoo is trying to
acquire a boiler company.
And should I join that race,
what do you think will happen?
Guess a bidding war will begin.
- But facing Manbo Construction...
- Cha Bucheol...
We will use him.
If it's to help Hwang Jeongyeon,
we have plenty of
alternatives besides this.
We need to get our hands
on that boiler company as well.
If things go as planned,
I'll be able to help Jeongyeon
and our company at the same time.
I'm fully aware of your situation,
but in our position,
300 million is much too...
I'll pay you a generous interest.
And if we manage to acquire Beaute,
I'll soon pay back the principal, too.
What is that fax about?
Ohh... From the revenue office.
I've heard you bear a grudge
against Manbo Construction as well.
Please, help me out.
Instead, I have a condition.
Go ahead and tell me.
I will join your acquisition bid
as a shareholder.
So the money you're giving me...
It won't be a loan, but an investment.
I'm investing in you.
Director!
Thank you!
Thank you, Director Hwang!
When is Beaute's conference again?
It's planned for the day after tomorrow.
I'll see you there, then.
All right.
You won't regret this decision.
Eonni...
What if Baekpa finds out?
Hwang Jeongyeon...
You'll soon be history.
What did you want to meet for?
Just wanted to hear your business plans.
Uh?
Bu...siness... plans?
That... If I had to list all the
investors, it would be a little...
I know that you don't
have a single investor.
I was still waiting
for you to open up first.
All right then, I...
I actually...
have nothing on my plate.
I'm empty-handed.
So I just wanted to
find some desolated backwoods...
and even kill myself once and for all,
but you know,
that so-called flesh and blood...
I still have a daughter, so here I am.
Aigoo, how the mighty have fallen...
What would you like to do?
If only I could be allowed to,
I'd love to give politics a try.
Politics?!
While running my company,
I filled so many politicians'
pockets, you can't imagine.
So I know what they're itching for,
their troubles and what they want.
I know it all.
And I'm not merely
trying to make it big.
Because I lived
without shame for so long,
I know how to handle shameless
pricks like Jo Pilyeon quite well.
If I'll devote the rest of my days
to rid politics of someone like Jo Pilyeon,
it is only for this country's sake.
At least that's what I wish for,
but in this state, I couldn't even
dream of getting into politics...
What is this?
With this much, you'll easily be able
to start a business or get into politics.
Forget it.
How can I accept that money?
I don't deserve to
be Jeongyeon's mother.
So at least you should
make her proud of you.
Gyeongok...
I left a car for you outside.
I don't like men
staying at home all day.
Gyeo...Gyeongok.
I really...
I've made her suffer her entire life...
What did she ever
find in someone like me?
All right.
Forget everything else,
but I'll become a father
Jeongyeon can be proud of.
That's right.
I'm going to succeed at all cost.
Gyeongok...
Yes.
Aigoo! We've got plenty of apartments!
These days in Gangnam you see
a new one pop up every morning,
so come here and take a look...
Oh my... Aigoo! Chairman!
- Aigoo, Director Ju!
- Aigoo!
Chairman!
When did you come back?
So you completely recovered?
Have you been doing fine?
Of course...
These days real estate is
doing well, so we can't complain.
I was planning on
getting myself an office,
can you find a lucky spot for me?
Aigoo, sure!
Why do you think they called him
Jaesu (literally: "luck")?
I'll give you a nice office
in our same building, Chairman.
Lee Gangmo.
How can you do this to me?
Do what?
You entrusted the aggregate sale to me.
So why would you let people
who betrayed us get subcontracts?
Aigoo... Why always bring that up?
You stay out of this!
I told you I could do this, didn't I?
Is it because you can't trust me?
It's not that.
After what happened to
President Maeng, if they end up...
I know!
I know how hard it is to deal with me.
But wasn't that something you
should have at least discussed with me?
Hey... Hey... Sotae!
What's wrong with you today?
Stop it, Hyung!
- You really...
- Hey... Sotae...
Sotae!
That temper...
He must be really angry?
Director Nam.
You said that 12 billion won would be
enough to acquire that gas boiler company?
Yeah... But why?
Why, interested in buying it?
Yes.
But you said we don't have the money.
Even if surrounded by riches,
all that remains of me is an old carcass.
And I guess I will soon
abandon that as well?
In the end, you take nothing with you
on your way to the afterlife.
- Hearing you say that...
- I...
envy the fact you
build houses for a living.
What is a house, after all?
Is it not a precious vessel
sheltering one's beloved family?
And inside this vessel you built,
people will help each other, they will
together dream and share happiness.
How impressive is that?
Don't just work to make money.
Just think of the people who will
live in the houses you built...
even after you're gone.
Then, should you face
even greater difficulties,
you'll always be able to overcome them.
I will always bear it in mind, Sir.
A gas boiler company, you said?
Yes.
The poorer one is, the harder
it becomes to endure winter.
Give it a try.
Thank you, Sir!
- English Conversation -
Director...
You still haven't finished
yesterday's assignment?
Director...
Isn't singing well
all that a singer needs?
What are all these difficult books,
not to mention the make-up,
the clothes, even table manners...
I only have eyes for the very best.
If you can't manage to do this much,
you should just quit.
You can just go back to the shoe store.
I apologize, Director.
- I'll work harder.
- I will work harder, Ma'am!
Told you to stop talking
like a little girl, didn't I?
Yes...
Get prepared, we're going
to record your album.
Album?!
You really...
I apologize.
We found a few nice songs.
They'll suit you.
You're going to leave me anyhow.
It must have finally come,
Time to leave each other.
My heart is telling me to hold onto you.
But after going back and forth
a thousand times,
It is finally time to say goodbye.
I guess it looks as if I'm laughing,
But it hurts so much I feel like dying.
No.
I'm not eating fish.
You need to eat this
if you want to grow taller.
No way.
I said no...
I don't like fish.
Aigoo... Stubborn little rascal...
Who did you take after,
disliking fish so much?
It's so good.
Here, come on.
Ahh... That's so dirty...
How can you use the same chopstick...
You can't eat fish, can you?
See? You haven't touched it once.
Who said I can't eat this?
I just don't like, that's all.
See? You can't!
How can an adult be fussy about fish?
You need to eat it.
Mommy...
Mommy, I don't want to eat fish.
If you don't like it,
you don't need to eat fish.
Instead, while Mommy is at work,
you need to obey Grandma.
Aigoo, my pretty boy.
Right... I've heard someone
came looking for you at the store.
It was your brother.
How much longer will
you keep avoiding them?
I don't know.
I understand you're doing this
because of Wooju,
but you can't keep living apart
for the rest of your days.
If you become famous
and start going on TV,
they'll find out right away.
How are you, President Lee?
We meet often, these days?
But I didn't know you were
interested in boiler companies.
I should be surprised to meet
you two here, on the contrary.
I was convinced by
Director Han to invest in him.
I see.
Unexpected competition as it might be,
may the best man win.
I wish you luck as well.
- Beaute Boilers Korean Subsidiary Sale -
Beaute Societe Francaise,
actuel premier fornisseur de chaudieres,
actuellement possedes presque de
40 pour cent du marche d'Europe.
Our Beaute with
its main French office...
is controlling nearly forty percent
of Europe's entire boiler market.
As a result of the current
reshuffling of the board of directors,
the new executive has decided
to sell its Korean subsidiary.
A secret bidding will be used,
and the highest bidder will win
rights to acquire the subsidiary.
Along with the company, the acquisition
will also include our boiler technology.
Vous avez donc jusqu'a cinq
heures pour soumettre les offres...
The winning bidder will
have until today at five o'clock...
to pay a deposit of ten
percent of the total bid,
and in case they fail to pay on time, the
second highest bidder will be awarded instead.
We hope you understood the criteria,
and wish for a fair bidding process.
Hey, Lee Gangmo.
Aren't we getting a little too ambitious?
Why?
Think I couldn't handle what you can?
Who knows...
After all, it's a money struggle.
Will Hangang Construction
ever be able to contend with us?
I see you still don't know
who our investor is.
Who is he?
Baekpa.
A money struggle?
Shall we give it a try, then?
It went your way last time,
but things will be different.
I'm not losing this bid to you.
That's interesting.
We're not going to give up, either.
Isn't that right, Director Han?
Of course.
This bid is a three-way fight?!
I put my life on the line
for this bid, too.
Better get ready.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Just this once, allow me
to roar one last time.
- And roar against whom?
- Jo Pilyeon.
Who the hell are you to act like that?
This is not something
you're doing on your own.
You're not giving up until I do.
And who the hell is Gangmo?
Is he any different than us,
to treat us like this?
You ungrateful prick.
Doesn't it feel like I might be
the only one left who can save you?
We finalized our bidding price.
It's 12.7 billion.
12.7 billion.
Once Lee Gangmo fails to pay
on time, they will contact us.
I'll have to trust Sotae.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com