Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 29 -
Chief.
Did you look into that James Lee?
It was right as you suggested.
It's the same James Lee as the
owner of those Gaepo-Dong mudflats.
Didn't that land belong
to the late Lee Gangmo?
Good job.
You can go.
Yes, Chief.
James Lee...
Lee Gangmo...
How do you feel about this?
I'd like to accept Hangang
Construction as a new memb...
I'm against it.
It's a medium-sized firm that barely
has a highway project to its name,
and you want us to accept it
into the construction committee?
I might oppose
Chairman Cheon's exclusion,
but I'm a little perplexed
about this recommendation, myself.
I'm against that as well.
Same goes for me.
I'd like a word with you.
Let's talk in private.
Gangmo, you...
Why are you doing this to me?
If you were alive,
you should have come to me first!
Why are you trying to strangle
Manbo Construction behind my back?
Hwang Jeongshik and Jo Minwoo,
just for the sake of getting their
hands on those Gaepo-Dong mudflats,
attempted to kill me.
What?!
Jeongshik and... Minwoo?!
Thanks to them, I learned quite a
few life lessons at the Samcheong camp.
When I'd heard you were
taken to the Samcheong camp,
the thought did cross my mind...
I have no intention...
to forgive the people
who did this to me.
Yeah...
I can understand.
You must be feeling wronged.
You must be livid about it all.
Still, Gangmo.
If only for Jeongyeon's sake and mine,
you must forgive them.
Do you know what
happened to Jeongyeon...
when she heard you'd died?
I'll do everything you ask.
Come back to me, Gangmo.
If you only help Jeongyeon,
Manbo Construction could be...
Right...
Gangmo.
You two get married.
I'll give you my consent.
Wouldn't that be enough?
Gangmo. Uh?!
I've heard Gaepo will soon be announced
as a residential development zone.
I plan to build
apartments on that land.
Sure.
Of course you should.
If you bring that land
and come back to me,
then I'll let you build a new city
in Manbo Construction's name.
I need a construction permit.
And the reason I want
to join the committee...
is exactly that.
Because with the
committee's joint liability,
the City Council will
automatically issue that permit.
So you really want us to part ways?
Didn't giving you that land
make up for all I did to you?
Jeongshik and Minwoo!
I'll make them
repent for what they did.
If you ask me to punish them, I will.
And should that not be enough...
And what will you do to make up...
for killing my father?
What is that supposed to mean?
You fool...
Make up for killing your father?!
And who on earth is your father?
Lee...
Dae...
Soo is his name.
Lee...
Dae...
Lee Daesoo?!
Then, you?!
The man you and Jo Pilyeon
killed a long time ago...
Lee Daesoo...
is my one and only father.
Do you...
finally understand the reason why...
I'll never be able to forgive you?
If you want to stop me,
then why don't you try?
Gangmo was Lee Daesoo's son?!
The same son I spent
so long looking for...
was Lee Gangmo?!
What is the matter?
What happened with James Lee,
to leave you in this state?
Gyeongok...
Looks like I'm getting punished.
For abandoning you,
for my friend...
and what I did...
It is only natural you'd be against
accepting me into the committee.
So let's settle for one condition.
You know better than anyone that,
when you build apartments,
you first need to deal with
the roads surrounding them.
If you accept me into the committee,
I will make sure all
the chairmen present here...
can employ our new method for the
next three years, free of charge.
Visit for you.
Your clout never fails to amaze me.
Allowing me to
walk freely at this time.
I must ask for your forgiveness.
I understand your position.
Min Honggi got the big suits involved,
so there was nothing you could do.
To be really honest, this whole
ordeal really hurt my pride.
Min Honggi was under us
back in the military.
You still have all that data
on politicians, right?
With my past experience at
the KCIA, I'm well aware...
that you're secretly
investigating the entire junta.
Why are you asking?
Give it to me.
Just the data concerning the
big shots currently in office.
And what would you do with that?
I swear,
you won't have to face any
repercussions because of this.
I can't waste an entire year in here.
If nobody is going
to get me out of here,
I'll have to give them
a good reason to do so.
Not to mention the connections
I'll need to deal with Min Honggi later.
Would that data be enough?
I'm sure you know me already,
but I never fail to make it up,
be it debts of gratitude or affronts.
I need to make up for all you did,
and also get revenge against Min Honggi.
Chief, what brings you here?
Ohh... He's a close friend of mine,
and he'll make it big once he's out.
Take good care of him on my behalf.
Yes.
I'll give you what you asked for.
Thanks, Chief Oh.
If you take a look here,
it's the direct opposite.
Ahh...
Done that way, it's much simpler!
You smile?!
Oppa, you're really good
at explaining this.
"Oppa"?!
Chief!
Is he your boss?
No... Actually...
I'm her boyfriend.
Who is he?
He helps me with math
from time to time.
Nice to meet you, I'm a Korea
University student, my name is Choi...
Hurry and get up.
What?
Are you just going
to keep sitting there?
No need to help Miju out anymore.
I'm sorry.
What... "Chief"?!
It just became a habit...
So when did he start
helping you, how and why?
He happened to be sitting
next to me about a week ago,
and seeing how I was
having problems with math...
But did you get angry
just because of that Oppa?
Got used to calling him Oppa
already, haven't you?
Forget how and when...
I mean, why was he
helping you to study, why?
That's just because I'm
not too good at math, so...
But, tell me.
Why do you keep smiling at him?
Uh?
Your lips looked about to burst.
Are you still upset with me?
Why would I?
You're acting like someone who's upset.
When did I ever?
Ever since you came to the library.
Don't smile in
any other man's presence.
What?
You're not jealous, are you?
Hey...
Jealousy... Yeah, right...
I'm not jealous.
I said I'm not!
All right.
Don't even...
talk with another man.
Don't look at them, either.
And don't trust any man other than me.
They're all thieves, got it?
Yes.
I'll do as you say.
I won't talk with any other man,
won't look at them,
and except you,
I won't trust anyone.
Happy now?
What are you doing this weekend?
I need to study.
Come out here at two.
We're going to the library?
On a date!
- Hangang Construction Admission Agreement -
Approved / Rejected
Ahh... Hello?
Lawyer Kim?
I didn't wake you up, did I?
Yes... I needed to
talk about something.
Is he talking with
the Royal Club owner?
You'd like to change your testament?
Is it about the company inheritance?
This must remain between you and me.
Certainly, Chairman.
What is he talking about?
He wants to change his testament?!
What on earth is he thinking?
I'm back.
You're late.
Did you manage to meet
Hangang Construction's James Lee?
He didn't come.
Just forget about them.
There were rumors spreading
on the stock exchange.
It seems Hangang Construction is
looking for a permit to build apartments.
I said stop concerning yourself
with Hangang Construction!
D...Dad...
Did anything happen at
the committee meeting?
Nothing.
Go to sleep.
Did you finish that survey
on the subcontractors?
Here you go.
I only chose the very best
subcontractors in the business.
How about their asking price?
All the people running these companies cut
their teeth on construction sites thanks to me,
back when I'd just kick
them around like rag dolls.
And since I know the estimates
down to the last penny,
they won't be able to bargain with me.
Start meeting with them, then.
And if their asking price fits what
we're looking for, just sign wth them.
Aigoo... You still pay me peanuts
but expect me to work all day like an ox?
What's wrong?
Mister "Founding Director"
of Hangang Construction?!
Just hearing you say that feels nice.
Reporter Yoon is here.
Come on in.
- Ohh... How are you?
- Come on in.
- Bit late, right?
- Not at all.
Here. Have a seat.
Some coffee, please.
Yes!
What are you waiting for? We have
a guest, so let's serve him coffee!
Ehh...
A managing director serving coffee?
Then, should a technical
director like me do it?
I told you to scout Miss Choi
of the Honey Coffeehouse.
While you're there,
give me a cup as well.
The hell am I, Miss Park
of the Gangnam coffeehouse?
Right... Seonsaengnim.
You spread those rumors
at the stock exchange, right?
*Jjirashi: loanword from Japanese chirasu
(scatter); original meaning: propaganda leaflets
Tabloid* pieces about Manbo
Construction are starting to circulate.
Their stock price was
falling as well, today.
This will help you
with your reportage.
Why is our stock price
falling so badly?
We will soon take care of it.
You can rest assured.
Isn't this all because we've decided
on a woman as our future chairman?
And there were rumors at the stock
exchange that Manbo Construction...
and Commissioner Han
Myeongseok are on bad terms,
what is that all about?
It's a groundless rumor
devoid of any truth.
Chief, let Director Hwang
explain by herself!
We're well aware of how they took away
the highway project under your nose.
What are you expecting,
some kind of gift from heaven?
Let's hear it!
Say something!
What do you have to say?
Don't you think all those rumors
are a little too specific?
So you're suggesting that someone
is spreading them on purpose?
Ever met that man called James Lee?
No.
Not yet.
Is it him?
Every obstacle in your way
comes from Hangang Construction.
Seemed like the chairman
knew James Lee quite well.
What was his Korean name, again...
It was all too sudden
to remember it clearly...
Ahh... Right.
He looked a lot like that boyfriend
you once came to the club with.
- By any chance, was his name...
- That is not possible.
Because that man is dead.
Is that so?
Dirty bastard...
Don't misunderstand.
That was for James Lee.
Did you even meet with
Commissioner Han?
Leave me alone.
If you find it too difficult,
I can always meet him.
If anyone ever meets him,
that'll be me.
I thought I told you to leave?!
What's the reason?
What's the reason you try to
leave me out of every important task?
Ever thought that I'm the
only one who can help you?
Look around you!
Who is by your side now?
So you'd help me?
Despite knowing how much I loved him,
the same man who conspired with
Jeongshik and killed Gangmo,
you would help me?
Don't even try to say it was
because you loved me.
Because it is just for your sake,
and to satisfy your father's ambitions,
that you do things like that.
I'll hand you my resignation.
Resignation?!
So, what, are you going
to make it up for killing him...
by simply leaving this company?
What is it that you want?
Want to see me dead?
No.
For the rest of your days, I'll make
you painfully regret killing Gangmo.
And, tell me, will you be able
to do that on your own?
What?
As you said, everything I do,
I'm forced to do it for my father's sake.
But...
you always tried to stop me in some way.
Do you really believe
you can win this fight,
especially knowing that I have
no feelings left for you whatsoever?
What?!
Jeongyeon found out?!
It wasn't me!
I didn't tell her anything!
Hey... Stop worrying.
Even if she found out,
what can she do about it?
Jo Minwoo is one of
Manbo Construction's pillars,
would she go as far as firing you?
Go pay a visit to Hangang
Construction's offices.
Hangang Construction?
Find out who the president really is.
You still believe that
James Lee might be Lee Gangmo?
He could be.
Then...
If it turns out he's
really alive, what should I do?
He was sentenced to
four years in prison.
If he's alive and walking free,
that would only mean jailbreaking.
Jailbr...
You have a point?!
Don't you worry, Minwoo.
I'll find out what that
James Lee is all about.
Are you really going
to make those changes?
Who could this man possibly be,
to have him inherit all this fortune?
Please, don't ask me anything.
All you need to do after I'm dead
is proceeding as this testament states.
This is the last change
this testament will go through.
Here...
You may leave.
It's good, all right.
What are you waiting for?
The closest to the phone picks it up.
Wow... You...
You're as cheap as
this herring, you know?
Yes.
Am I speaking to
Hangang Construction?
That's right, how may I help you?
I'm Chairman Hwang Taeseop
of Manbo Construction.
Gangmo... No...
I'd like to speak with
President Lee Gangmo.
Hey...
It's Chairman Hwang Taeseop?!
What?
He's asking for Gangmo.
But Gangmo went to meet
Commissioner Han Myeongseok?!
Our president right now
is meeting... Han...
Han Something... Commissioner...
Right, he's meeting with this Han Something.
How can you just tell him?
Then, could you convey a memo for me?
Yangsuri...
Next to the public cemetery.
Tomorrow at 1 pm?
I'll probably get to tell him
by the end of the day.
Yes... Yes.
Why is he asking to meet Gangmo
at a public cemetery?
Public...
Got a point?!
Wait a moment.
So huge corporations even get involved
in the grave business, or something?
I was wondering who could be owning
those mudflats in Gaepo-Dong,
and it turns out to be you.
So, what do you
plan to do with that land?
I was thinking of building
apartment complexes there.
The reason I asked to meet you today...
I'm afraid I'll have to
deal with the check tonight.
Hangang Construction doesn't
have the qualifications.
No matter how hard you try to convince me,
I can't issue you that permit.
I will use the construction
committee's joint liability.
Did the committee
agree to give you that?
Should I get that,
would you issue that permit?
You have more business savvy
than I imagined.
Then, how are you going to deal
with your nearly non-existent...
track record with subcontractors?
I'm negotiating with our country's
most efficient subcontractors as we speak.
So can I deal with the check for tonight?
I see you have quite the quick temper.
So, what, do you want me
to make a decision right now?
I'm fully confident I can build
apartments that will be stronger...
and of much better quality than
any of those big corporations.
You have a guest.
I'm Hwang Jeongyeon
of Manbo Construction.
I'm talking with a guest,
send her back.
I won't move a finger
until you agree to meet me.
- Just a moment.
- Yes.
How do you explain
such insulting behavior?
I'm begging for your help, Commissioner.
Look, Miss Jeongyeon...
Save Manbo Construction.
I'm afraid I don't have all that power.
You looked for the wrong person.
Chairman Hwang Taeseop
has been misled into thinking...
you were the first to act
against Manbo Construction.
The one who used Jo Pilyeon
to put me in a difficult spot...
was exactly Chairman Hwang Taeseop.
We never did that.
And if you ask me to stake my life
to prove those accusations wrong,
I will be happy to.
Have you asked yourself who could
be behind this misunderstanding?
The way I see it,
it could very well be the man who
would have most benefited from it,
Hangang Construction's
President James Lee.
Miss Jeongyeon.
I suggest you leave.
Let me clear this misunderstanding.
I will soon contact you.
You may leave now.
President Lee,
I believe you might have
something to tell me?!
I'll be expecting good news
concerning the construction permit.
Bring me that joint
liability you promised.
Although, if Miss Jeongyeon can have
any say in it, it might be difficult.
All right.
Daesoo.
Looks like your son's not coming.
Jeongyeon...
You have matured a lot.
You now know how to drive,
and you've become much stronger...
and more confident than ever.
- Lee Daesoo's Grave -
Hey, Daesoo.
I really wanted your boy
to become my real son.
How could one's destiny
be so wretched...
You've been cursing at me from
up there all along, haven't you?
I... even changed
my testament, you prick.
I decided to give
half my entire assets...
to your son Gangmo.
I know that won't
earn your forgiveness.
Who ever asked you to
forgive me, you silly?
I'm just giving back what was
yours from the very start.
When I come next time,
I'll bring Gangmo with me.
I'm sorry, Daesoo.
Did they go belly-up, already?
How could there be no one
in sight for half a day?
Your palms don't really
suggest this line of work?!
- Oppa.
- Yeah.
Are you really Hangang
Construction's managing director?
Can't you read?
It's written there.
"Managing Director Park Sotae."
So how many employees do you have?
Employees?
Three...
Three minutes wouldn't
be enough to list them!
Who can count all those people?
You're so cool, Oppa...
Hey, Park Sotae.
And why would I run?
Wow...
You sure can be thick-headed.
I wonder what kind of brilliant idea
is behind you coming here looking for me.
What?!
You little twit, have a death wish?
Be my guest. Hit me!
I know Officer Kim down at
the station pretty well.
So hit me!
Actually,
I was here to do a
little negotiating with you.
Give me a break.
Negotiating... Yeah...
Negotiating what?
You like money, don't you?
I can give you money.
Give me land instead, you twat.
Didn't you say I'd get some land
if I got rid of Lee Gangmo?
So... Did Lee Gangmo die?
Of course.
Did he make it, then?
Did you see it?
Have you seen
Lee Gangmo alive and well?
Hey... Hey!
This is just a little appetizer.
If you do as I say,
there'll be more where that came from.
Where is that president of yours?
James Lee.
What is he really about?
I'll bring him to you,
so you can see for yourself.
Really?
Can you do that for me?
I'm Park Sotae...
When am I getting
the rest of the money?
If you bring James Lee to me...
Fine.
Come to the construction
site at midnight.
At... At midnight?!
The president will come
at half past eleven.
You...
If you take that money and run away,
you know it'll get
you killed, don't you?
Am I out of my mind?
Abandoning a stable job for
a pittance and running away.
Let's get going.
You people, really...
What?!
So that is who Hwang Jeongshik was?
I told you.
Because of that prick,
Gangmo was framed for murder,
and was even taken
to the Samcheong camp.
Anyhow, he's the worst thing
that happened to us.
Wow...
That motherless son of a tramp...
So, you'll help us, right?
Let's see the money first.
I told you we'd share it
when it's all said and done!
Fine.
What are you going to do?
What do you think?
Anything that happens
on a construction site...
should be dealt with
the construction-site way.
Construction-site way...
Ahh... Where am I supposed to go?
I can't see a thing in here.
It's here.
Come.
Ehh... You really...
What are you, meeting a spy?
Always acting like trash, aren't you?
Hey... Park Sotae!
Wanna die?
Die?
Who?
Me?!
You bastard...
If you leave me here, you're dead!
You prick!
Action!
Hey... Hey! Park Sotae!
What the hell are you doing?
Hey... Hey... Park Sotae...
Spare me... Spare my life...
Cut!
Said the same thing
many times, deep down.
"Please, spare me."
Sotae... Sotae... Sotae!
Scared, aren't you?
A little angry as well.
But I was a hundred times angrier
and more scared than you.
Action!
Sotae...
Burying you would be a waste of
perfectly good land, you prick.
Sotae...
You fool.
Shouldn't you at least
send me a signal to stop?
Are you really going to bury him?
Please, spare me.
I beg you... Spare me...
He looks like an annoying twat,
just like you said.
Don't cry.
Will that bring back
the love long gone by?
Hand me the rest of my money.
You said you'd give it to me
if I brought you James Lee.
I'm James Lee.
How do you do?
Don't you even understand
"How do you do"?
How do you do.
He's asking how many
yoodoo (nipples) you have.
Uh?
Back where you were.
Quick.
Shall we go?
President James Lee.
Yeah!
Good night to you!
Sotae... Sotae!
- Let's go.
- Sotae!
Sotae!
Get me out of here first!
Nah...
I apologize.
- Why?
- They're so expensive...
How about these?
Our Miju looks like a princess?!
If I'm a princess, what are you?
We're just... your guards, I guess?
If anyone bothers you, just tell us.
We'll scold him for you.
People will be so scared of you,
I'll never get to marry.
Of course!
Whoever it is, better watch out.
If I'm a princess, then I guess
I'll just have to meet my prince.
By any chance...
Are we dating someone?
Uh?!
What's with the surprised look?
You're really dating?
What time is it?
I had to go somewhere...
With whom?
Sorry, I'll get going.
Hey...
Is she really dating, or what?
She had it so hard all this time.
She deserves to do
what everyone else does now.
Minwoo!
Miju!
Are you okay?
It's bleeding, you silly!
It's all right.
Let's go to the hospital, uh?
The hospital, for so little?
Just a band-aid and...
Get on my back.
I said it's nothing, I'm fine.
I live here, put me down!
Is that the problem now?
Blood is gushing out of there!
Gushing?!
I said I'm all right!
Just stay put.
I thought I'd die of
embarrassment in there.
Just a band-aid and that'll do,
need to turn the hospital upside down?
Hey...
There is such a thing as tetanus.
Like you'd have any clue...
You really...
Keep ruining the mood, will you?
Wow! It's a shooting star!
We should make a wish?!
Aren't you?
Doing it right now.
I'm tired.
It's late...
Can't we just go home?
Who was I kidding? Aigoo...
Sure. Let's go.
Go.
This was sent to you by Chief Oh.
Thanks.
- Politicians Movement Report -
Dearest Congressman Park Yongseon.
I always deeply respected you,
but we never had the chance to meet.
What I need now is an ally.
Whether you and I
become allies of a lifetime,
or you refuse to form ties with me
and turn ourselves against each other,
that solely depends on you.
- Min Honggi wins Gangnam By-Elections
by Landslide Margin! -
Thank you, I appreciate it.
Let's have dinner together,
one of these days.
Yes, thank you again.
Congressman.
Congratulations on your victory.
- Congratulations.
- My congratulations.
Congratulations, Congressman.
Yes.
Have a seat.
- Yes.
So the committee is
officially supporting me...
I must thank you all.
But I don't see
Chairman Hwang Taeseop?!
Don't you know how close to
Jo Pilyeon he's always been?
Try to be understanding.
Hwang Taeseop is
still supporting Jo Pilyeon.
Whatever the occasion, you must always
pretend you two are on good terms.
You also should let people believe
Hwang was behind the committee's support.
So we'll create a rift
between him and Jo Pilyeon?
Or if Jo Pilyeon ends up
getting rid of him, all the better.
As long as Hwang Taeseop
keeps going strong,
Jo Pilyeon will always get
a chance to get back on his feet.
Getting rid of our problems
at the very root...
Have any idea how to do it?
Looks like you're busy, these days.
I was about to start feeling disappointed,
always waiting for you in vain?
Forgive me.
But you look good.
There's nothing I
can complain about here.
Your environment is only as bad
as you make it out to be, isn't it?
The construction committee
started supporting Min Honggi.
Is that true?
Even when you're released,
getting back on your feet won't be easy.
Who's behind this?
Was it Hwang Taeseop?
Since Chairman Hwang
leads the committee.
So I see there was a reason why
he kept avoiding me all this time.
Jaechun, you go tell Hwang Taeseop
I want to meet him.
All right.
People only show their true colors
when the going gets rough.
Hwang Taeseop kept betraying me
whenever I faced problems.
If this turns out to be
his latest act of betrayal,
I'm afraid I'll find it hard to
keep forgiving him any longer.
You have a guest.
Who is it?
What brings you here?
Director Jo would like to meet you.
All the better.
I was thinking of
paying him a visit myself.
I'd like a more comfortable setting,
I trust you won't mind?
So the committee decided to pledge
their support for Min Honggi?
Is that so?
Why, you weren't aware?
Don't you think that
was a foregone conclusion?
What?
I'm afraid businessmen like us...
can't afford to wait for
a failure to redeem himself.
Did I just hear "failure"?
Clouds only gather up high.
Same goes for money.
Who would ever invest money
in a losing team?
Look, Chairman Hwang!
I don't have any more money
to throw at you, either.
And that's because it took half my assets
to make up for the sins you made me commit.
What are you talking about?
The sins I made you commit?!
That friend of mine you killed,
Lee Daesoo.
His son has shown up.
So I'll take this opportunity
to atone for all my sins.
That can only mean these wretched ties
of ours will finally have to be cut.
And who is this son
you're talking about?
Why, suspecting a
possible retaliation,
are you by any chance afraid?
I'm asking you who he is.
Or maybe, just like
you did with my friend,
will you get rid of
his son the same way?
Hey... Hwang Taeseop!
Jo Pilyeon.
I see no reason why I should
continue letting you walk all over me!
Past, present or future,
I won't ever kneel down before you,
nor will I lose something
just for your sake.
Are we clear,
Jo Pilyeon?
You're always welcome to try me,
so do as you please.
Ahh...
Also,
allow me to let you in on something.
The fact I could be as
cruel as you, and more.
Cruel?
Even more cruel than me?
Sure...
I'll make you feel what
being cruel really means.
Yes?
Why was it so hard to reach
you these last few days?
I was busy here and there.
Why, anything urgent?
Hwang Taeseop called
several times looking for you.
Said it's important,
so you should call him.
All right.
Yes.
It's me.
Right...
I was waiting for your call.
What is the matter?
I need to go somewhere with you.
You'll also get to meet
a very welcome person.
Who would that be?
Before that, I also need
to give you something,
so I'd like to meet.
Tonight at midnight
by my house would be fine.
Dad.
All right.
We'll meet there, then.
Who called?
It's nothing.
Commissioner Han Myeongseok called.
He wanted to meet you later tonight.
Han Myeongseok? Why?
It'll probably be about
Hangang Construction.
And James Lee as well.
I told you to stop concerning
yourself with Hangang Construction.
Dad.
Postpone my meeting
with him to tomorrow.
I have other plans tonight.
There is nothing more important to us
than meeting Commissioner Han.
Jeongyeon!
You met that James Lee, didn't you?
Who is he?
You can leave.
Dad...
I said leave!
I think that, after letting
Hwang Taeseop take care of it,
it's time we get our
Manbo Construction back.
I'm well aware of what you're implying.
There must be no mistakes.
All right.
Thanks, Jaechun.
Director.
Even when forced into
this pathetic state,
I still feel you're
the only one I can trust.
I'll go take a walk before I come in.
By yourself?!
Let me accompany you.
No need.
I just want to
spend some time alone.
Who are you? Chairman!
Wake up!
Chairman!
Chairman! Wake up...
Chairman... Chairman!!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Jo Pilyeon was behind this.
It wasn't you, right?
And if it was me?
Change the testament as I tell you.
I think you'll get
all the time to do that?
We live in different worlds.
Just marry whomever
your family wants you to.
Is it right that you and Dad
killed Gangmo's father?
Seems that Jo Pilyeon
will be released earlier.
Jo Pilyeon will surely try to get revenge.
Take a good look, Chairman Hwang.
How my son Minwoo
devours Manbo Construction.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com