Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 58
What's wrong, Gangmo?
Why, did anyone throw insults at you?
Nah...
I think I've just
seen Jo Minwoo pass by.
Jo Minwoo?!
And why would Jo Minwoo be here?
How could you let things get to this point?
Was my father really the one
who killed Congressman Oh?
And why... Why?!
Minwoo...
First... First we must get
your father out of trouble.
Seongmo Hyung was there.
What?!
He was there with Lee Gangmo.
He didn't find out, did he?
I don't know.
What's that supposed to mean?
Did he see you or not?
I just told you I have no idea!
Minwoo.
I'll call you again later tonight.
Hello?
Chief Oh.
It's me, Go Jaechun.
Did anyone come visit Congressman Jo?
No.
Does he know about the tape?
He still doesn't.
You...
And you.
Right.
There was one more.
Lee Miju.
I made a mistake.
I should have dealt with
you all from the very beginning...
I sure made a big mistake.
Is that all the soul-searching you
can do? You've left out all the substance.
About all the vile and despicable
things you've done over the...
I know no such thing as soul searching.
And I have never
regretted anything I've done.
I'm just...
disappointed I let this happen.
I wonder if you'll say
the same thing in court.
I can prove every single heinous crime
you committed over the last twenty years.
What do you think he will get, Hyung?
Can't say...
A life sentence is a given,
but we'll have to see if we can
turn that into capital punishment.
See you in court,
Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
You better take
good care of that tape!
Because if you really
want things to go your way,
the evidence needs to be crystal clear.
Play with fire without
a plan, and you'll die for it.
We must find that tape, Hyung.
Gangmo.
Find where Go Jaechun might be hiding.
He must be injured,
so look for hospitals or inns.
How about you?
I need to go somewhere.
See you at Miju's place this evening.
- Letter of Resignation -
You're suggesting we
get rid of Lee Seongmo?
If he finds that tape,
it's all over for the both of us!
This is where Go Jaechun is hiding.
Go meet him.
Seongmo Hyung was there.
He was there with Lee Gangmo.
It's me.
You brought your gun?
Give it to me.
You can't use that.
Then, will you get rid
of Lee Seongmo instead?
It's the only thing that can save us!
Give me that gun.
And Seongmo?
He didn't come?!
Weren't you coming here together?
It's me, Hyung.
Where are you now?
I have a strange presentiment...
that someone might come here tonight.
I'll come there right now.
No.
No need.
Wait for me, Hyung.
I'll be right back, Miju.
Oppa...
Gangmo Oppa!
I was right behind him...
Where on earth did he go?
Give me that tape.
Give it to me, Minwoo.
From the very first moment
you entered our house,
you planned to get revenge
against us, didn't you?
Right as I was treating
you like my own brother,
you were gritting your teeth, waiting
for the day when you'd kill my father.
There is no time.
Give me that tape.
Forget everyone else,
but you knew.
How hard I tried not
to become like my father!
How much I love Miju!
And despite knowing all that,
you still betrayed me?
Give me that tape right now.
Do it!
Shoot if you want.
Since you're not getting anything from me!
Jo Minwoo.
Resent your father instead.
Because all this was caused by him.
Hyung!
Have you ever been sincere
with me even for a single second?
I'm sorry.
Don't move.
Drop that gun.
Do it!
Hands over your head.
Stay put... Don't you dare move!
What happened?
After hearing the gunshots,
the police will be here soon.
I asked you what
happened to Seongmo!
Get out of here right now!
Yes.
Where are you, Hyung?
Everything all right?
Yeah.
I faced a little disturbance,
but now it's all right.
Gangmo.
I found the tape!
Really, Hyung?
That's right.
We won.
Now we can finally avenge our parents.
Hyung...
But why...
do I suddenly feel so tired...
Gangmo... Miju...
Hyung.
What's wrong, Hyung?
Hyung!
Hyung! Answer me!
Answer me, Hyung!
Seongmo Hyung!!
Hyung!!
Minwoo, it's you.
Chief Oh called me.
You took care of Lee
Seongmo's body, I hope?
Jaechun saved me.
Without any evidence they
can use, everything is solved.
Seongmo Hyung...
is nowhere to be found.
What are you trying to say?
I didn't find him inside the car.
Are you telling me you couldn't
verify whether he was dead or not?
Then, the videotape?
Where is that tape?
It disappeared along with him.
What the hell are you saying?
So what you're saying is
that, when you got there,
you only found the car
but Seongmo had disappeared?
Yes.
People living in the surroundings
claim they heard gunshots,
not to mention that we found
bullet holes all over the car as well.
Seems like a shootout took place that night.
So we can only deduce that
someone moved Seongmo elsewhere.
Many hints point at...
- the possibility of murder...
- No way.
My brother is not dead yet.
Here are photos I personally shot.
As you can see, there
are blood stains on this handle.
It's a clear sign that, after being shot,
he tried to get out of the car by himself.
Everyone, gather here.
- Find all witnesses in the area.
- Yes.
Send inquiries to
all nearby hospitals as well.
- Yes, Sir.
- All right.
If he had a gun, there's a good
chance it could be an ANSP agent.
In his last call to me,
he said he had the videotape.
Someone brought harm to
him to destroy that evidence.
So is it Jo Pilyeon, after all?
That Go Jaechun still hasn't been caught.
Be it ANSP or Go Jaechun,
we must hurry up and find my brother.
That's the only way to expose
Jo Pilyeon for his murders.
Then...
You still don't know where he is?
We're still investigating,
but we can't confirm whether he's still alive.
So you're saying that
my brother might be dead?!
All right...
Drink some of this.
Seongmo took that tape and disappeared?!
Does that make any sense?
Find him.
Find Lee Seongmo right now!
Get a hold of yourself, I beg you!
Don't you realize we're being punished?
You and I are finally paying
for everything we did!
The dream I worked my entire life
to fulfill is about to vanish under my eyes,
and that's all you can tell to your father?
You tell me to wake up?
That I'm being punished?!
Find that damn tape.
Find it whatever it takes,
and get rid of the evidence.
Are you happy?
What?
Is living this way making you happy?
Minwoo...
You're the only one I have left.
If you let weakness get the better of you,
then my life will end in failure.
Minwoo.
Once we fulfill all our goals,
then people will only remember us as winners.
"Punishment" is only what people jealous
of winners use to justify their pathetic lives.
So find that tape.
Only then you will win.
Dad...
Dad.
Dad!!
- Congressman Jo Pilyeon
Murder Case Remitted for Rehearing -
- One man's scary tenacity to obtain power -
- Missing -
Lee Seongmo (34, Male)
Hello?
Yes, Dad.
Now?
Yes... All right.
Is anything the matter?
Dad told me to go to his house?
What are you doing...
Jeongyeon should be here soon.
Are you confident?
Are you confident you'll be able
to tell Jeongyeon that you're her mother?
It'll shock her so much...
And what if she doesn't like it...
This won't do it.
Not to mention how awkward
it'll be seeing me like this...
I'll just go get changed.
Jeongyeon...
knows.
Wh.... What are you saying?
Jeongyeon already
knows that you're her mother.
She's been patiently waiting all
this time for you to tell her.
You silly...
Now you cry?
It's because she was
worried you'd react this way.
That it would hurt you,
and make you feel sorry.
Wipe those tears.
Go open the door,
I'll be in my room a moment.
Right... Go wipe your
tears and come out.
Go.
- Come on in.
- Dad.
Ohh... What a nice smell!
Hungry, aren't you?
What is all this?
Chop suey, ribs...
They're all my favorites?
You're not telling me
you made all this, are you?
Director!
Then... Did you make all this?
Go ahead and eat.
Did you cut yourself cooking?
She said she hadn't seen a
chopping board in twenty years.
And she calls herself a woman?
But, what is this feast...
Today...
is the birthday of someone I love
more than anyone else in the world.
It's your birthday, Jeongyeon.
Have some of that seaweed soup.
Excuse me just a moment.
Don't go, Jeongyeon.
If you want to cry,
now you don't need to
hide it anymore, Jeongyeon.
Here...
Do it here in your mother's embrace.
I will, too.
I won't hide it any longer.
I'll cry right in front of you, Jeongyeon.
Mom...
Right.
That's right, my daughter.
My daughter, Jeongyeon.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Mom is sorry.
Jeongyeon... Forgive me.
I'm sorry, Jeongyeon.
Jeongyeon...
Hi, we're looking for a missing person.
How are you?
We're looking for this man,
please call us if you find him.
Give us a call.
Hi.
Hi, we're looking for someone.
Thank you.
His name is Lee Seongmo.
He's an ANSP alumni, so pay
special attention not to be spotted,
- and try to find him as soon as possible.
- Yes.
I'll pay you up-front. There is more where
that comes from if you find him.
They'll do what?!
Are you telling me Jo
Pilyeon will be released?
The prosecutors cited lack of evidence.
Didn't I tell you I would testify in court?
What it means is that
you alone won't cut it.
Jo Pilyeon's lawyer will waste no time and
bring up your rivalry with Manbo Construction.
- And politically speaking...
- Is there really no way?
Is there no way to have
them imprison Jo Pilyeon?
The government is
preparing a major announcement.
So timing is not on your side.
- June 29, 1987. Noh Taewoo, presidential
candidate of the Democratic Justice Party, -
- announces sweeping reforms
including direct presidential elections, -
- which would pave the way for him becoming
the first democratically elected Korean president. -
It's done!
Great job, everyone.
Our people did it!
Congressman.
I feel really proud of you.
Good job.
So you're saying that
you heard Congressman Jo...
confess that he instigated the
murder of Congressman Oh Byeongtak?
Yes, that's correct.
Then, is it true that you recorded it as well?
I said I shot it firsthand!
That tape will soon be revealed.
It's Jo Pilyeon!
Congressman Jo, who is
really telling the truth here?
Lee Gangmo is still claiming that
you instigated Congressman Oh's murder.
The officers investigating this case
already proclaimed that a false testimony.
How much longer will you let a
psychopath mislead you with his delusions?
So if what President Lee said is a
lie, will you sue him for defamation?
That would create too much
clamor, and I can't stand that.
Tell him he can yap all he wants.
I couldn't care less.
I will sue you instead.
You called me a lying psychopath
ring in front of these journalists,
so it's an obvious case of defamation.
I have no time to waste playing with you.
Congressman Jo and I will
soon have a long and fierce fight in court.
Plenty of headlines like the one
you've read are waiting to be published.
I hope you'll cover this extensively.
You were the one saying that your
political career is more important than your own life?
And?
Your political career
is about to slowly crumble.
Oppa...
Have you ever been here?
No.
I've never seen this place before.
So Big Oppa was living
in a place like this?
It's all the money
I saved over the years.
You use it.
You'll have to find yourself
a place to live as well.
Use this to get started.
Thanks, Hyung.
Thanks for what?
You can't avenge our father
all by yourself.
While you take care of Hwang Taeseop,
I will bring forth
Jo Pilyeon's destruction.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to ask me.
If you and I join forces,
there is nothing
that can scare us off.
What if Big Oppa died?
What if he died...
Seongmo Oppa...
He's not dead.
I'll find him at all cost, Miju.
- President Lee Gangmo Keeps Accusing
Congressman Jo Pilyeon of Murder -
Hey... If this is really true, things
are more serious than I thought.
I see you and the
president had a long talk.
Afraid going in will be useless.
What?!
He's quite upset.
He said he doesn't
want to see you again.
There is no way.
The president would never abandon me.
Look, Congressman Jo.
Party administration will soon
file an official request,
but you'll have to
leave the party on your own.
Hey... Min Honggi!
And who would dare kick me out?
None other than the president.
He also said this.
That the ruling party is not going
to recommend you for a seat in congress.
Out of the way!
I must meet the president.
Let's not act this way, Sir.
I must ask you to leave.
Do you even know who I am?
I'm Jo Pilyeon... Jo Pilyeon!!
Do you have a death wish?
Sir!
Are you really going
to abandon me this way?
I worked for you like a dog!
I devoted my entire life!
One more chance...
Give me just one more chance!
Sir!!
Sir...
- 1988 Seoul Olympic Games -
- 1990 3-Party Merger, the
Democratic Liberal Party is born -
- 14th Congressional Elections -
BALLOT COUNTING
Hwang Taeseop of the
Democratic Liberal Party...
beat independent candidate
Jo Pilyeon by a wide margin...
in the Gangnam district elections.
- 1992 -
Hwang Taeseop! Hwang Taeseop! Hwang Taeseop!
- Gangnam District Congressional Elections
Crown DLP's Hwang Taeseop -
- Hangang Construction New City A-Lot Apartments -
- Happy Bank -
Foundation/Chairman Investiture Ceremony
- Lady in the Rain -
Starring Cha Soojeong
Two tickets for Lady in the Rain.
Thank you.
- Cha Soojeong's Lady in the
Rain Continues Sellout Streak -
- Manbo Plaza Project -
Asia's Biggest Multi-complex Building
The Manbo Plaza we're
about to build in Gangnam...
will become the kind of multi-complex building
that Asia has never seen before.
The moment it is completed, I
am confident that it will become...
a mecca of culture and
leisure symbolizing Gangnam.
Not only is the real estate
market suffering from stagnation,
but the entire construction
sector is facing a huge crisis,
so some argue that your
timing could have been better.
Being even more aggressive
in a time of crisis is my business style.
So not only we will build this Manbo Plaza,
but also embark on a project to build
a huge residential area in Hanoi, Vietnam.
Are you aware of the fact that your
biggest rival Hangang Construction...
has entered the bidding for
those Hanoi concessions?
I personally know Chairman Lee Gangmo.
He might have experienced great
success with the New City project as of late,
but I have no plans to
concede a second time.
You're here.
Give us a few comments
on your recent trip to Vietnam.
Is it true that it's a project
worth 5 billion dollars in total?
We will make an official announcement later.
We just returned, so
please let us pass. Excuse me.
Are you aware of the fact that
Jo Minwoo's Manbo Construction...
will join the bid for this Vietnam project?
It feels as if the battle
between your two companies...
will now move abroad...
To cope with the current crisis the sector is facing,
it's only natural that Manbo Construction
would set its sights on the overseas market.
I expect a fair fight, but one
with no concessions or compromises.
Any news of my brother?
We get a few calls
from time to time,
but they never match.
It's been five years, Gangmo.
I think finding your
brother might be difficult now.
Keep looking for him.
Until his conditions are
confirmed, we can't stop searching.
- Asia's Largest Shopping Center -
Manbo Plaza Begins Construction
Yes?
It's me, Gangmo.
Can we meet now?
Jo Pilyeon's recent
behavior is a little suspicious.
He kept quiet for a while
after losing the elections,
but these days he's meeting
with Blue House officials.
What kind of officials, exactly?
According to my sources,
we're dealing with key personnel,
from presidential guards to secretaries.
And his purpose?
We're approaching
the final cabinet reshuffle.
Considering his reputation,
what could he possibly aim for?
So he's trying to become minister?
No.
A little higher than that.
Prime minister?!
Here.... Let me pour
you a drink, Chief Kim.
So...
Have you decided where you'll go
after the president will be out of office?
People like us will never be
able to leave the president's side.
I bet...
And so it should be.
Tell me, what can I help you with?
Aren't you giving
us enough help as it is?
It's just that, like you, I want to be
by his side even after he leaves office.
I know.
This is the last time.
So why don't you put
in a good word for me?
Now that you mention it,
I did talk about that with
Chief Park of the presidential guards.
He holds you in great esteem as well.
When it comes to political
lobbying, he's second to none.
He's building close relations with
most of the president's closest confidants.
Of course, his lobbying
methods haven't changed one bit.
Better yet, maybe I should say
he's becoming even more aggressive?
We can't allow Jo Pilyeon
to gain that position.
How can you stop it,
when it's nominated by the president?
If only we had that secret
fund account, we could try something...
I will find my brother.
If we find him, not only
will we get that account,
but we'll also secure
evidence of Jo Pilyeon's murders.
It certainly would be great, but...
- Chairman of the Korean Policy Development Jo Pilyeon -
Internally Selected as Next Prime Minister
J... Jae.... Jaechun!
Jaechun!
Hurry up and come here.
I finally did it!
Jo Pilyeon did it!
Jaechun!
S... Seongmo, you!
So you... you were alive?
And you thought that
after killing all those people,
I'd let you gain that position so easily?
S... Seongmo...
It's really too bad,
but this is where it ends for you.
Please don't kill me, Seongmo.
It would be too unfair to die this way.
Seongmo...
S... Seongmo...
I... I beg you...
Please, Seongmo!
Die!!
Congressman!
Are you all right?
I guess you had a nightmare.
That Lee Seongmo...
I'm sure he's alive.
We've lost his traces five years ago.
If he was still alive,
why wouldn't he show up?
No...
I have no doubts, he's alive.
He will take the account and that videotape,
and come strangle me with that.
Congressman...
On that day, Ji Yeonsoo
disappeared along with him.
How are you going to explain
the fact that we couldn't find her either?
Find him.
Before Lee Gangmo beats us to it,
we must find him at all cost.
All right, Congressman.
Even if it's the very
last thing I do, I will find him.
Ajeosshi.
I'm back.
Ajeosshi!
It's all right.
You were hurting, right?
How painful was it, if you even cried?
It's me, Yeonsoo.
Ajeosshi.
Will you recognize me
today, for a change?
Do you recognize me? Do you?
I'm Yeonsoo...
Ji Yeonsoo.
Your lackey.
Yes... Say it.
Yeonsoo. Ji Yeonsoo.
Mi...
Mi... Ju.
Miju.
Again with that Miju?
I told you it's not Miju, I'm Yeonsoo.
Let's take off the bulletproof vest today.
I'll give you a bath with warm water.
Ajeosshi...
So you're telling me
he's gradually getting worse?
As you can see, by hitting
the right side of his cranial bone,
it penetrated five centimeters
deep down his left cerebrum.
It's a critical position.
Wouldn't surgery help him recover?
In his conditions, a surgery
could be even more dangerous.
Aigoo... How pretty.
How come you're doing
everything I tell you today?
You even took off the vest.
These two nasty
little rascals are hiding inside your head,
and they're the reason why your
head always hurts, and you can't talk.
But, you know? I'm going to
live with you for a long time.
And I'll help you get better on my own.
And that's because...
Because I like you, and...
I'm sorry, Ajeosshi...
I'm sorry...
Right as you asked, we've restructured
the top floor into a movie theater.
Let's put restaurants right under the theater.
Yes, Chairman.
Minwoo.
Are you busy?
Sir.
I came to have a word with you.
How much more do you need?
I see you read my mind right away.
The cabinet reshuffle
will soon be announced.
I'll have to wedge
the door open this time.
Is that even possible?
If we just end up throwing money at the
wall like during the last elections...
Look, Jaechun.
He's finally become a real businessman.
He's trying to bargain even with his father.
You'll have to succeed this time.
Or else I will refuse to meet you again.
Hand me five big ones.
Fine.
- Chairman...
- There is no time.
Don't make me wait.
Chairman.
We already have given him
a very significant sum.
With the current financial woes we're facing,
just completing Manbo Plaza will be...
When my father becomes prime
minister, everything will be solved.
What?
He'll be able to affect the Hanoi concessions
and the Manbo Plaza construction as well.
I'm telling you that whatever Lee
Gangmo tries, they all will be ours.
But you should be realistic
about our financial situation.
Just think of it as an investment.
It will make it easier to accept it.
Then, how do you
plan to gather those funds?
Would it be difficult to get
another loan from the bank?
I think that route is pretty
much out of the question now.
Yes?
Chairman Jo Minwoo of
Manbo Construction is here.
Escort him in.
Yes, Chairman.
Have a seat, Chairman Jo.
This is awkward, I'll
just drop the formalities.
Fine with me.
I wondered if you could
lend us some money.
So a huge corporation like yours
comes knocking at our doors?! What a honor.
I'd like to start with five billion.
We might need more down the line.
Our biggest strength is quick loans.
But I'm sure you know that our
interest rates are higher than commercial banks?
Five billion?!
I looked into it,
and seems they have outstanding loans
with their main bank for over 10 billion.
I'm sure it's not money
they need for Manbo Plaza.
Then, where would
he spend all that money?
Lobby.
Is there really a chance
he will become prime minister?
It's more than likely.
There's only one
year left until the elections...
That's why Jo Pilyeon's lobbying works.
It's just political spin, anyway.
And if his father obtains that post,
it'll be like giving
wings to Jo Minwoo?
Wouldn't this influence
your business as well?
Why do you think Jo Minwoo
is so eager to help his father?
So he can conspire with him to
gain benefits at his rivals' expense.
And I'll be the target of their little complot.
But if we find my brother,
we can bring an end to all this.
We must find him.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Jo Minwoo.
Have a seat.
Your father seems really proud of you.
I've heard the upcoming cabinet
reshuffle is keeping him on his toes.
Seems like I'll have to take good care
of you on his behalf until then.
You can never be too careful.
It's a secret Swiss bank account.
So how many trips are you going to
make, when it could just take one?
Excuse me?
You and your father
are quite different, after all.
We're a little lacking here.
We're a little lacking,
so give me some more?
I think that it's
what he was suggesting.
Shameless piece of shit...
How would you like to proceed?
What do you think?
Are you going to stop now?
- But the money for Manbo Plaza's...
- Enough with that damned Manbo Plaza, please.
I apologize.
Wow... Who is this?
Minwoo, long time no see.
Where have you been all this time?
Be it you knocking at my
door or the other way around,
we'll soon get to meet.
I'm a bit late, so I'll get going.
You little...
I don't see you in a few years,
and look at what I have to witness.
I apologize for not keeping in touch, Dad.
Well, at least you seem to have
made a decent living in the meantime.
I have a little credit business in Sokcho.
Credit? Private lending, you mean?
Yes.
And where did you find the money?
I entrusted the inheritance my
mother left me to President Noh.
I see...
So, have you made a little money?
I just acquired a department store in Sokcho.
I'm also running a
theater and a restaurant.
You made it big?!
And they say that every dog has its day...
You will need a lot of financial
backing now that you joined politics, right?
I will help you now.
You'll help me?
You little...
And when am I supposed to
find the time to read all these?
Just be glad there's a line
of people wanting to cast you.
There's really nothing to my liking...
Yes, Star Entertainment.
And?
Just a moment.
Soojeong.
- Take it.
- Who is it?
Hello?
You're looking for Lee Seongmo, right?
Why?
Sokcho?!
This fan from Sokcho called me,
and he said he saw Seongmo.
Miju, let's go.
Follow me.
I'll be counting on you.
We'll have to meet over a drink later.
Who was I going to
meet this evening again?
The Assembly speaker?
Someone from a hospital in Sokcho
saw a man with a bullet in his head.
- A bullet in his head?
- Yes.
And the description
resembled Lee Seongmo.
Hurry...
Go down to Sokcho and check it out.
Now.
I'll get going.
Wow... Nice view?!
Once the highway to Chuncheon
is done, it will just be killer.
Should we build here?
If the highway is extended
to Sokcho, it would be even better.
The East Sea is close, too.
Nah... In a place like this,
we should just build a resort.
Chairman... Shall we give that a try?
Where did he see him?
I don't know.
We're going to meet by the terminal.
We must find him.
Then, it'll be all over for Jo Pilyeon.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I will become prime minister.
You said the hearing will last a day, right?
If needed, I will join it.
- Did they find him?
- No, but there are rumors that Jeongshik did.
You want me to extend
my hands to Hwang Taeseop?!
Once I become prime minister,
him and Lee Gangmo
will be the first I trample on.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com