Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 5 ~
If this collapses, it's all over!
I even had to kill to get to this point!
I'm not going to let
a natural disaster ruin me! I won't!
I'm Hwang Taeseop!
I'm afraid of nothing!
Ajeosshi! It's dangerous!
Ajeosshi!
Director!
Help me! Ajeosshi!
What on earth is going on?
What happened?!
Honey!
Dear!
Dear.
How are you feeling?
- Director Hwang.
- Director.
Where am I? Uh?
Don't you remember?
If it weren't for him,
you would have died in that mudslide.
And... the sand?
What happened to all that sand?
Uh?
Aigoo... Our sand!
Honey... The doctor said that
you still haven't fully recovered.
How much is left?
Was it all wasted, and nothing is left?
I'm sorry, Director.
You bastards!
- Honey...
- Dig it all back up!
Find all the sand we lost!
- Honey, please calm down.
- Director, you must relax.
We must get that sand back!
We can't go on without it!
~ Daeryuk (Continental) Construction ~
What? Hwang Taeseop was hospitalized?!
Yes, and all the construction sand
they stocked was washed away by the rain.
And I thought they were holding just fine...
Block all of Manbo
Construction's cash flow,
and also buy all their bonds and
the private loans they signed up for.
I will, Director.
There isn't much time left.
Until our Daeryuk Construction
will use Gangnam as a launchpad...
to reach the top of our trade.
They are refusing any loans?!
All the banks who were on amicable terms
with us and even all private lenders...
are refusing to do any
further business with us.
What is wrong with them?
My head...
I really can't figure out why myself.
I ought to...
Listen, worst comes to worst...
Put the house and the office up for sale,
along with all the land we bought
in Gangnam under the company's name.
Whatever it takes, you must
fill that water surface in Banpo.
That's our only lifeline!
Director Hong of Daeryuk
Construction is waiting outside.
Director Hong?!
Wait... Wait.
Tell him to wait just a moment.
My clothes...
Quick, bring me my clothes. Now.
He said you may come in.
Aigoo...
You must be busy, what brings you here?
The moment I heard you collapsed,
I had to spare a moment and
visit you, no matter how busy.
Collapsed?!
And who said I did?
My head...
Why does my heart hurt so much?
Because of the storm,
I merely was caught by a little mudslide.
You don't know how glad I am
to hear it's nothing serious.
But it seems that as a result of this
calamity, you're facing sand shortage.
Will Manbo Construction
be able to cope with it?
Ahh... Well, we did incur some losses,
but it's nothing to be worried about.
Hearing about this accident
truly saddened me.
Think of the kind of fierce
struggle construction companies...
have been going through to secure sand.
What difficulties could a major
company like yours possibly face?
It's only the trifling little fish
like us that are bearing the grunt.
Are we not all peers fighting
together for the same goals?
If you're facing any difficulties,
don't hesitate to ask for help.
I will be more than happy
to lend you a helping hand.
Should you need my help,
feel free to ask.
I am more than capable of that.
Then, take good care of yourself.
Aigoo... Thank you.
I can't see you out, regrettably.
That prick...
There must be a snake inside
that insidious prick's belly.
He was spotted at the construction
site in Banpo, this morning.
What?
And why are you only telling me now?
Shoe shine!
Shoe sh...
Ajeosshi.
Let me shine your shoes.
- No need.
- I even have socks.
- Next time.
- See you again, then.
Shoe shine.
I finally caught you!
I've been noticing books
were suddenly disappearing,
but it was you, wasn't it?
That has nothing to do with me!
Don't even think that excuses will work.
Let's head to the police station.
Thieving little scoundrels like you
need to be taught a lesson.
I said it wasn't me!
I don't even go to school,
so I would have no use for this anyway.
Would a thief study with this?
He'd just sell it.
Let's go to the station, then.
Let's just go,
and if I turn out to be innocent,
you'll pay me all the money
I lost today because of you.
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead and let's head
to the station right now.
You little runt...
Look at how feisty he is...
Forget it and just go, then.
Keep it.
You said you wanted this.
Here.
What are you,
boasting about being rich?
I can feed all the guys working at
the tent here for days with that money.
You saved my father.
Just think of it as a
reward for your help.
I don't need that.
I'm too busy making money
to worry about studying.
Really?
Not only you're an orphan
and a shoeshine boy,
but also fight every chance you get.
You'll become a gangster
before you make any money.
I only speak the truth.
Wanna bet?
Whether you'll become a gangster or not.
You little brat...
Gangmo!
Hurry up and come.
There's a fight.
The rags boys started asking
for protection money, and beat up...
Wait for me.
There, that one is their boss.
Good job.
Hungry, aren't you?
Let's go eat something.
They'll be quiet at
least a month, after this.
We made decent money by selling socks,
so the rags boys were envious of that.
Go ahead first.
We'll be waiting.
I'll treat you to roasted buns.
Corporal.
How did it go?
It was a total failure.
They didn't show up.
There's a spy among us.
That's the only explanation for
everything that's been happening.
Hampton is suspecting they
might be dealing with a spy.
Michael just came back.
I suspected him for his
involvement with Hampton,
but as the kid said,
this was all a trap to lure us.
Stop with the wiretapping
and get our bug back.
What?
Be it Hampton or us,
all our cards are on the table now.
Now the real fight begins.
Bring that kid who alerted us.
Make sure nobody spots you.
Yes, Sir.
How did you find out
Hampton's plans were a trap?
I can understand a little English.
But both the General and
Captain Michael don't know that.
I hear you'd lost your memory,
but it seems you
were quite well educated.
Do we have a name now?
Your name.
I don't remember.
Don't you want to find out?
There must be a family
waiting for you somewhere.
Think of how strenuously
they must be looking for you.
I want to find them as well.
We're after a secret document
about the Vietnam War.
Just find out where that document is.
I'll take care of
finding your family for you.
All right.
Feeling this chill...
Might be a cold on the way.
You'll soon be discharged, right?
I'll be out in the summer.
Then, will you become a doctor?
Yes.
Your future is guaranteed, then.
So I've heard your father passed away
while rescuing fellow troops during the war?
How did you...
He was truly a remarkable man.
It was thanks to the sacrifice
of men like your father...
that we can live in the Korea
of today, don't you think?
Your pulse and temperature
are both normal.
There is something you must do
for this country, like your father did.
What?
I was appointed here to
fulfill a very important task.
You'll have to help me out.
And how can I...
That boy Hampton brought in.
Watch his every move
and report back to me.
If you really want to find
success after you're discharged,
you must succeed at all cost.
Is that clear?
All we need to do now is to record
Jo's order to steal the document.
Once we have that,
we can arrest him immediately.
Are you back?
Yeah...
By the way, gum is all over these...
American-made gum
doesn't come off easily?
It's... It's me.
Speak.
Good job.
What is the matter?
The kid is carrying a recorder.
What?
Right as I expected.
He's Hampton's double agent.
How are we going to deal with him now?
We must catch him, and find out
where that document is being kept.
Yes, Sir.
So General Hampton thought that
I would fall for such a pathetic trick?
Where did all the strategic marvels
of his Vietnam War tenure go?
Just wait a little longer.
I'll avenge those who killed our father,
and then I'll come back for you.
Think of how long we've
done business together.
Help us out just this once.
I'll head there myself.
President...
Hello?
Hel... Pres...
What's wrong with them all?
It's as if they all got together,
wishing for our company to go belly up.
Hello?
Hwang Taeseop speaking.
Yes.
Sure.
All right.
Go start the car.
Where are you going?
There's this urgent meeting of the
construction committee at City Hall.
I'd need at least something
in my hands to show up and say anything.
Hey, bring me my shoes.
Yes.
Here you go.
There's a hole in your sock?
What?
Ahh... Always this...
They still can't make decent socks?
It's not like they're free...
How can they be so weak?
Ehh... It's so annoying.
Director, here's a pair of new socks.
Give them to me.
I'll go change them in the car.
It's 100 won.
You fool. And how much were
the shoes you ruined worth?
Still, I saved you...
Director! Pay me for the socks!
Even the car is trying to rile me up now?
Director...
If I don't get paid for the socks,
I'll lose a day's worth.
Get out of the way, will you?
Let's just grab a taxi.
Director, just a moment.
If I help you get this out,
you'll pay for the socks.
What are you, kidding with me?
You little...
I just ought to...
I'll get your car out of there,
so you must pay me.
Like that's going to work...
Here. Give it a try.
It's out, it's out indeed.
Director, you have to pay me now.
You have to pay me, Director.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Director, my money.
The money for the socks, Director!
My money!
If this keeps up,
isn't Manbo Construction going bankrupt?
Nuna.
If you fill all that land,
will you be able to save the company?
Why? Want to fill it yourself
so they'll pay you for the socks?
Here's a cadastral map of the lot
we recently bought in Maljukgeori.
You lead Seoul's Construction Bureau,
so I trust you can spot a gem when you see it.
And the cream of the crop was
bought under namesake by Park Hwasang.
You can keep that cadaster.
I must make this
landfill construction succeed.
And I need the help of talented
businessmen such as yourself.
Thank you, Commissioner Han.
- The meeting is starting.
- Yes.
~ South Seoul Surface Water Reclamation
Construction Committee Meeting ~
We're facing great difficulties
in this landfill construction.
So, considering the situation,
the Seoul City Construction Bureau...
decided to withdraw all companies
unable to complete their assignment.
All lots from the companies
which will be withdrawn...
will be reassigned to other
selected companies at our discretion.
The two companies not
present at today's meeting...
have already notified us
of their wish to withdraw.
The companies whose construction
rights will be withdrawn...
are four in total, including them.
Shincheonji Construction.
Your lots in Apgujeong will be
reassigned to Daeryuk Construction.
Do you have any objections?
The last of the four...
is Manbo Construction.
Daeryuk Construction will be
assigned all your lots in Banpo as well.
I can't give my assent.
More construction sand is
coming from Taean as we speak.
Once that arrives,
filling that land will be a non-issue.
Don't you all know?
But what led you to believe that we don't
have what it takes to complete our task?
Are you positive that
you secured enough sand?
If you could only wait a little longer,
you'd find out by yourself!
I'm well aware of the situation in Taean.
There is no way there'd be any sand left.
Look, Director Hong.
I'm saying I can do it right now,
why do you keep arguing otherwise?
All it would take me to find out
is a single phone call.
A... Call?!
And who would you call?
Do it... Go ahead.
*in Chinese mythology,
one of the divine rulers of the sea
Who are you going to call,
the Dragon King of the West Sea*?
Do it!
Here... Let's all calm down.
I will give you four days.
If you can secure enough
sand to fill the Banpo lot,
then you can continue the construction.
If there is no progress
after such deadline,
we will forcibly proceed
in accordance with our decision.
Yes, fine with me.
I will do it.
Even if I have to stake my life to do it,
I will fill all that land whatever it takes!
Listen.
Will you keep this up?
My dealings were done in all fairness.
Fairness, my ass.
What are you yapping about?
Think I don't know you brown-nosed
your way to that decision?
Director Hwang.
This water surface reclamation project
is a crucial stepping stone...
which will decide our
country's future fortunes.
If people use this great enterprise for
their personal gains like you're doing...
and end up compromising the entire
project at our country's expense,
will you be able to bear the consequences?
Great enterprise?!
You bastard, I just ought to...
If I broke a single law,
go ahead and hit me.
Aigoo...
I'm only letting it go because of the law.
Ever heard of business ethics?
Being able to sacrifice
oneself for the greater good.
That's exactly the kind of business ethics
people in our trade should follow.
You!
You barked up the wrong tree!
Remember this!
One day you'll be on
your knees before me,
imploring me to save you.
Before that,
worry about finding that sand.
You got hold of all the loan
certificates Manbo Construction...
signed with private lenders, right?
Yes, Director.
- And the drafts?
- All in our hands, as ordered.
Act on both immediately.
Understood, Director.
Did Manbo Construction's
director come back?
I've heard that's gone belly up?
Did they owe you any money?
What are you doing?
It's worthless anyway,
what do you think?
- Look, the fire's dying down. Hand it to me.
- You...
Don't even think about it.
You better tell everyone.
That if they lay their hands
on this book, they're dead.
You prick...
Did she give it to you?
The daughter of Manbo
Construction's director?
My late mother always told me that pine
caterpillars can only eat pine needles.
Think that those rich kids
consider people like us human beings?
Nuna.
Did the director come as well?
He asked for drinks
the moment he arrived.
I need to go to the post office
before they close.
Director.
There is something I need to tell you.
About that landfill by the Han River.
I know how to fill it.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you having problems
because you don't have sand?
Right...
So what else am I going to use?
Briquette ash.
What?
If you go out, you'll see it
piled up on every alley.
You can use that.
You want me to use
briquette ash to fill that land?
Yes... Do you know how
useful briquette ash is?
You've seen it yourself, earlier on.
After we used it,
the car got out right away.
Get out of my face!
You fool.
You want to fill a place where people
will build their houses with trash?
What's next, sticking out
your tongue at a funeral?
I... I was just trying to help you.
Will you get the hell out or what?
So when will you pay me for the socks?
You little twat, bring it up again...
Who are you?
- Proceed.
- Yes.
Look...
I asked who are you.
We're acting on behalf of the court.
Following court orders, we will now
seize this house and all its valuables.
What is this supposed to mean?
- You're seizing what?!
- Mom!
Aigoo, Honey...
What is all this about?
That is my room, don't go up.
Move.
Who are you people?
Get out of my house immediately,
or I'll call the police.
I said move out of the way.
Director Hwang.
It's trouble.
Checks are starting to bounce.
What are you talking about?
Checks are bouncing?!
I'm on my way back from the bank.
It's a total mess.
Hello?
Yes.
Director, it's your wife.
What's the matter?
Stop weeping and just talk, will you?
Seizure?!
All right.
I said I got it!
*employee
Where did Moon Daeri* go?
He's at the site.
And what did he go there for?
Workers are protesting,
asking for their wages.
~ Go Jaechun ~
Come to the Korean
support warehouse tonight.
Did you find out where
they're keeping that document?
Yes.
You did?!
I did.
I bet.
What are you doing?
Search him.
Did Hampton order this? To record me
as I order them to steal that document?
I'm not on Hampton's side!
What did Hampton promise you,
in exchange for betraying your country?
Did he promise he would take you to
the States, where you'd live in luxury?
- You can't trust me?
- Shut your mouth!
I know what that look
in your eyes means.
You'd be ready to abandon your people
and this country like a worn-out shoe.
Tossing your dead body in the
ditch would be a piece of cake.
Your only chance to survive is
telling us where that document is.
If you don't confess
by the count of three,
I'll shoot each and every single one
of your fingers right in your face.
Once I'm done with all ten fingers,
then your throat will be next.
One.
Press the button!
Two...
Three.
Press that recorder's button!
Do it.
Press play on that recorder.
Did you keep the
document in a safe place?
Don't worry, Sir.
He would never suspect we'd
keep such sensitive material...
in the document storage
section of the war library.
As the Korean proverb says,
the darkest place is under the candlestick.
Keep it there for a few days,
until we move it to the States.
Let him up.
Don't expect any apology from me.
Still, you've gained my trust with this.
You have my word.
I won't have second
thoughts about you again.
Find a way to steal that
document from the library.
I will not accept failure, this time.
Yes, Sir.
Find a way to steal that
document from the library.
I will not accept failure, this time.
Well done.
What will happen now?
Jo Pilyeon will send in his
men to steal the document.
But what we'll have there is not
the Vietnam document that they want.
Then?!
It's a classified blueprint
of an American fighter plane.
Now that we have this recording,
we can charge him for espionage.
Keep this up and they'll kill you.
Think Hampton is even
going to blink once if you die?
You'll die a miserable death.
Why would you waste your life
that way, at your age?
Hyung...
From the very first moment I came here,
I always felt as if you were
a real brother to me.
I'm scared.
Everything that's been happening here...
Be it Hampton or Jo Pilyeon,
they all scare me.
But...
Who scares me the most...
is you.
You're not suffering from amnesia, are you?
Did you pretend from the very beginning?
What's your name?
Lee Seongmo.
Seongmo.
What on earth is your history with them?
What could have possibly
led someone like you...
I'm sorry, Hyung.
I can't tell you anything right now.
Later...
One day, I'll tell you...
all the things that I'm keeping inside.
What did I do to grow fondness
for someone like you?
I'm sorry, Hyung.
I hate this place.
It makes me sick to my stomach.
I wish I could just
get out of here right away.
I don't like it, either.
Later, when you're discharged,
let's leave together.
Forget it, you fool!
About what I found in my uniform...
Thank you.
~ Jo Pilyeon is suspecting you ~
That's my son.
So you're Daesoo's eldest?!
- Look at him!
- Seongmo.
This is Dad's friend,
who runs a business in Seoul.
- That's me!
- How are you?
Daesoo's son can only be
like a son to me.
Uh?!
He sure is handsome.
Come here. Here...
Here you go.
Go ahead and spend it.
Quite a son you have!
Dad's friend...
Aigoo... My wretched luck!
Meet the wrong husband
and you end up on the street!
Think of how hard it was
to buy this house and enjoy this life!
How about my gems and mink coat...
If he only had called us a little earlier,
we would at least have been prepared.
That rotten jerk!
Is that the issue now?
You dreadful little brat.
Leave this house immediately!
The fortune-teller was right about you!
He said you would only
bring bad luck to our family,
but despite raising you
with all our care and affection,
all you do to repay us
is steal and run away?!
Who did you raise with affection?!
Don't you even have a conscience?
What?
Have you ever thought of me as
your real daughter for a single moment?
You... You... Leave!
Go back to your mother!
Leave, get out of my face!
I'd love to do that right away.
But you can forget about me leaving.
What?
Didn't you say I only bring you bad luck?
Then, I'll first witness
your downfall before I leave.
Th...That...
Listen to her!
My head...
- My head!
- Mom.
I can't take it anymore!
Mom...
Where have you gone?
Come and take me with you.
Mom...
You... What are you
waiting outside here for?
Go.
Did you cry?
Mind your business and just go.
Have you had dinner?
What am I, like you, starving all day?
I was just worried about you...
What's with the attitude?
Why would you worry about me?
What are we, friends or something?
Aren't we?!
You worried about me as well.
And even bought me that guide.
Don't get any strange ideas.
I just bought it out of compassion,
since you're out here alone shining shoes.
I'm sorry...
Lee Daesoo...
Forgive me...
Daesoo... Daesoo!
Lee Daesoo...
Didn't you go to school today?
Send me back to my mother.
Again with that?
Haven't you heard about having
to leave the house in a week?
Wouldn't it be better
to have one less mouth to feed?
I'm not going to let that bring me down.
I'll never let my family starve.
I wish you'd just go bankrupt.
If you can't afford to raise me anymore,
you'll send me back to my mother.
You little...
Whatever the case, there is no way.
Dad.
It's cold.
Go back home.
Ehh... Those fools,
they didn't even change the briquette.
What are you doing?
Director! Director...
Find refuge.
After hearing of our bankruptcy,
all the subcontractors headed this way.
Our what?
Director Hwang!
He's over there!
Get him!
Wait a moment!
Catch him!
What you heard is not true! Go back!
Rumors are spreading all over the place,
how dare you lie to us?
The director is not going to con you.
So just go back!
Get out of the way!
Director Hwang!
*lit. countless treasures
Manbo* Construction, my ass!
Manbo?! Manbo?!
The hell with Manbo!
Congratulations!
This is just the beginning.
This Hwang Taeseop and
his Manbo Construction...
are going to reach the very top
of the construction business.
Everyone, we're counting on your help!
Manbo?!
You have the guts to call it that?
Manbo! Manbo?!
Stop it!
Who are you?
Are you Hwang Taeseop's daughter?
Why did my father do wrong?
Because of your father,
we're all about to end up on the street.
Out of the way!
Stop it!
You little brat!
And who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Stop!
Stop there!
Shouldn't you thank people,
in situations like this?
Never asked for your help.
Hey.
Aren't you taking this?
Thank me first.
I'm waiting.
"Daddy's little girl kept putting on airs,
but now it just serves you right!"
If you want to mock me,
go ahead and do it.
Is there anyone who would mock
a friend who's having it hard?
Friend?!
And who would be my friend?
I know, that you don't think of
a shoeshine boy like me as a friend.
But I don't care about that now.
What is this?
As you can see, it's briquette ash.
Are you telling me you want to
use this at the construction site?
Chief, I'm not saying I will...
I was just wondering if you could analyze
whether it would be possible to do so.
Chief.
The entire country is in tumult,
because everyone is lacking sand.
If we could use briquette ash
instead, we'd solve that problem,
while at the same time
deal with waste disposal,
so think how beneficial this
could be for the entire country.
It's a fascinating proposal.
However, whether briquette ash
can replace sand and gravel...
And that is the reason I came to
the research center right away.
Fine.
We will analyze its efficacy.
Chief.
Thank you.
By the way,
how long are we talking about,
until the results will be available?
What can I say...
At the very least,
I think it will probably take five days.
Yes...
Five days.
Chief.
Is there no way to speed up the process?
At the very least, it'll take that long.
I see...
Anyhow, the moment you have the results,
please give me a call.
Shameless bastards.
If I had been here,
this wouldn't have happened.
Jeongyeon.
Where is your father?
I don't know.
Where on earth has he gone,
without saying a word?
It can't be anything
wrong with him, can it?!
A few days ago, the director
of Paldo Construction...
committed suicide after going bankrupt...
Hey!
Don't even say that!
Hello?
Dad...
Jeongyeon.
Listen well.
Go home, and bring me my seal
and the landfill contract.
The people who are after me
might be trailing you,
so you mustn't tell anyone.
Understood?
- Yes.
- Hey... Jeongyeon.
Don't tell your mother, either.
I'll see you later tonight.
Dad!
Dad.
What did he say?
Where is he now?
Dad.
Dad?
I'm here!
Here you are.
What's with him?
I didn't know the way,
so I brought him along.
You little...
You don't need to worry about him.
My seal and the contract.
Also, I won't be able to
come home for the time being,
so tell that to your mother.
By any chance,
do you have any money on you?
I'll bring some tomorrow morning.
Forget it.
If you keep meeting me and
they start smelling us out...
Go back before curfew begins.
Dad.
Don't die.
Don't even think of committing suicide...
I'm sorry, Dad...
I won't make you suffer again.
I'll stop looking for my mother,
and be good to Jeongshik and your wife.
So don't die, Dad...
If you do, I'll kill myself as well.
I'm not dying, you silly.
Why would I leave my daughter behind?
When you're all grown up,
after you get married
and I see my grandchildren,
then I can die.
Why would I die now?
Daddy will be back soon.
It's all right, you silly.
Hwang Taeseop has been nowhere
to be seen the last two days.
We can't just wait without doing a thing.
He brought his seal and contract along,
so we can't force him out.
Then, are you telling me to
just wait as long as it takes?
Let's just give it another two days.
If he still refuses to show up by then,
we'll get a search warrant and find him.
Let me finish!
- You had enough!
- Let's eat some, dammit!
Are you going to stuff yourselves all day?
Are you going to work or what?
What's with all the beggars
straight from the morning?!
What... Beggar?!
You little runt...
Ehh... Little runts...
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
You little runts,
elders have the precedence!
Just wait.
It's ready. Let's eat.
As a sign of friendship
between our two countries,
how about we entertain
our troops with a concert?
We'll steal the document that night.
At the committee meeting tomorrow,
we will be assigned the lot in Banpo.
Are the results ready?
Can we use briquette ash?
If you see Director Hwang,
call me right away.
I'll give you 20,000 won.
About Director Hwang...
Give me a new pair of socks.
I've worn these a few days,
and they smell sour already.
What are you writing?
I'll list every penny you owe me,
so prepare to pay later.
What is this,
do you like me or something?
Do you think you're that pretty?
I only like girls with pretty faces.
I'll be reassigned to the KCIA.
Do you realize what that means?
It's a little country within our country...
Right at the core of power.
Would you like to join me and work there?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com