Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 42 -
Go ahead.
Tell us what this solution of yours is.
First,
to welcome this tax investigation
with the utmost transparency.
We will be hit with significant taxes.
However, the moment we pay them,
we will automatically leave our
shady underworld and gain legitimacy.
It's easy to make such careless statements
when it's not your money, isn't it?
The share of the GDP controlled by our
sector is on a continued downward spiral.
Not to mention all the changes the
market economy will soon go through.
If we don't take urgent steps
to cope with these changes,
our sphere of influence
will continue to shrink.
So what you're suggesting
is to turn our business legal?
Japan is already moving in this direction.
I believe the only way we can survive...
is by paying taxes and creating a new
business model within the law's boundaries.
And how do you plan to
deal with all the repercussions?
Do you know how many
organizations are failing that way?
Sir... There's no need
to listen to that brat.
What this lady said is exactly
what I wanted to tell you all along.
Sir...
Hesitate before a grove
filled with thorns,
and the sun will set on you!
Prepare to pay those taxes.
- Sir...
- Sir!
Sir!
Let's escort him inside.
- Sir!
- Please, don't do this.
Sir... Please.
Sir... How can you just leave?
Sir! Sir!
Please overturn your ruling.
The future of our entire
organization is at stake, Sir!
Try to endure it, Sir.
You can't show them any weakness.
Sir!
How can you suddenly do this to us?
What?! Turn legal?
So you want us to pay all those taxes?
What the hell is wrong with him?
Don't ask me...
Ahh... Really...
You really don't want
to go to the hospital?
I'm fine.
You can go now.
I'll prepare your bed.
Gyeongok...
About Jeongyeon.
She has shown much more disposition
than I ever believed.
Turning this business into a
legitimate credit institution...
was also my longtime dream.
Now that my time has come, I thought
I finally had to give that dream up,
but hearing Jeongyeon say those words,
you can't imagine how happy I felt.
That kiddo, really...
And whose idea was that?
Was it Baekpa's?
It was Hwang Jeongyeon who suggested it.
Hwang Jeongyeon?!
Sure sounds like her.
So, what, did all the members agree
to take her up on those suggestions?
It looks like Baekpa
made the final decision for them.
Taxes is not what I was going after.
How could we let Hwang Jeongyeon
hold us back this way?
If you want me to,
I could get rid of her.
Get rid of Hwang Jeongyeon?
Look...
Think everyone uses your seedy methods?
If the need should arise,
I certainly wouldn't refuse your help.
Dad...
However, that is not the issue now.
How did the members react?
It felt like stirring
a hornet's nest, as you can imagine.
A hornet's nest?
Maybe that could be the very
solution to all our problems.
Thank you... It's Cha Soojeong,
give this a listen.
Thank you... Eonni, spread the word.
Thank you! Cha Soojeong!
Thank you... Thank you.
Here you are.
You bought another?!
I lost the other one.
I see...
I hear that people are requesting
her song on the radio all the time.
Really?
She's determined, like few others.
Let's get going.
We're back.
We're back...
What's that?
Open it.
It's for you, Soojeong.
For me?!
What is this?
Wow... Supplements?!
American-made.
There's even a card.
Read it.
"You always have my support."
Who could have sent it?
Why, isn't it written there?
No.
I don't know who it is,
but looks like we have your first fan.
Aigoo... Feels so good, Cha Soojeong!
Soojeong, congrats.
How nice...
You're back, Director?
What's that?
Yes... A fan sent them, Director.
These days, her popularity is just...
No need to get excited.
She still has a long way to go.
Stop everything else starting today,
and focus on practicing.
You want me to stop
selling albums on the street?
The month is still not up...
You have a few TV appearances.
What?
There isn't much time left.
It's live, so you need to be prepared.
Think of this as your best,
and very last chance.
It's not only live, but also your debut.
Bear in mind that it could make
but also break any newcomer.
Soojeong, congrats!
Congratulations!
Thank you...
Go inside and meet her.
Let's just go.
Why, what's wrong?
You wanted to meet her so bad.
Miju...
had been avoiding us all this time.
I tried to deny
any worst-case scenarios...
But I'll have to check first.
- Thank you for today.
- Ohh... Good night.
- Yes.
- Good job today.
Wooju, Mommy said
she'd be late tonight.
Let's just go to sleep.
Uh?
I'm not sleepy.
Yeah, right.
You can barely keep your eyes open.
Looks like Mommy is here!
I'm back.
Wooju, you're still up?
G... N... D...
L... M...
Are you studying?
He said he learned
those at the kindergarten.
He stayed up this late
to brag about it with you.
Aigoo, what a good boy.
What is it?
Did Mommy do anything wrong?
Miju...
This.
You're the best!
My Wooju is the best.
Mommy is the best, too.
Aww... My pretty boy.
How cute can my baby be?
I'm not a baby.
I'm all grown up now.
What?
All grown up?
Where did he learn that?
Tell me about it?!
So cute...
Let's just call it a night.
I'll have to come alone
early in the morning.
That's great.
You'll come, right?
Of course I will.
But why three tickets?
Who are the other two for?
Want to invite your brothers?
Yes... I'd like to.
Right.
It's a good idea, Miju.
Don't you worry about Wooju.
I'll raise him as my grandson.
That's the reason I insisted on
adding him to my family registry.
Sometimes I get scary feelings.
If Wooju finds out later on in life,
what will he tell me?
He's just as kind and
warm-hearted as you are.
So he'll realize that you sacrificed
everything you had to protect your child.
So...
Don't even think about that,
and hang in there.
Are we clear?
Let's hurry up.
"Rabbit, rabbit, where are you going?"
Careful.
"Jumping here and there,
where are you going?"
Aigoo!
"Jumping here and there,
where are you going?"
I love you, Mommy.
See you later.
I love you, Wooju.
Aww... My boy.
Bye.
Give that baby up.
Give what up?
Please, Miju...
I trust Minwoo.
He will solve everything...
He's more than capable of that!
It's nothing that Minwoo can solve!
If he learns I'm pregnant, Father...
Don't ever call him that!
Never, ever call that
bastard "Father" again.
What's wrong with you two?
Why can't we be together?
Because our father!
Was killed by Jo Pilyeon.
What?
What did you just say?
Miju...
President.
This is serious.
There was another boiler accident.
Again?!
Were there any casualties?
I... guess it was casual, yeah.
Anyhow, Directors Park and Nam
are at the hospital,
so get going.
The... hospital?!
Someone got hurt, all right.
It's a ventilation problem,
what's with all the damned cameras?
There have been a few cases
already this month.
We examined those cases personally,
and there were no defects!
So let us meet the victim, at least!
Haven't you heard what the doctor said?
I told you to get
that camera out of the way...
Hello, everyone.
I just acquired Beaute Boilers.
I'm President Lee Gangmo
of Hangang Construction.
Ahh, is that so?
Then, let me just ask you this.
There are no problems whatsoever in Europe,
so why are Beaute boilers
in Korea going through so many..
We're dealing with the same components,
and the same assemblage as well.
So are you blaming the
customers for their negligence?
We're currently examining the causes.
Should it not turn out
to be a product defect,
I'm sure that hurriedly reporting such
groundless accusations would hurt us both?!
How are you?
We brought you the president.
Ahh... Is that so?
How do you do?
How is your father?
Thankfully, he's all right.
We'd like to examine
your apartment's boiler.
Should it be a product defect,
we will generously compensate you.
Reporter Park, right?
Did your interview go well?
Since there were no serious injuries...
But, who are you again?
It will air on tonight's prime-time news.
How about the victim's side?
We paved the way
for their full cooperation.
Just in case, keep in
constant touch with that reporter.
I've already taken care of him,
so you needn't worry.
We must make Lee Gangmo
dearly regret his acquisition.
Just in case he started believing
he truly could defeat me.
So you're suggesting that it only
comes down to customer negligence?
That's the point, President.
But we can't be 100 percent sure.
Then,
is there any possibility it might
actually be a technical defect?
I couldn't find any defects
with the equipment at my disposal.
If it's neither customer
negligence nor a product defect,
what the hell is it?
I've had it with this
already, so stop asking.
You really...
Who else should I ask that to,
the damned janitor?
Hey... Why are you always
trying to stir up trouble?
Sit... Sit. In other words,
we don't know the cause, that's all.
Fine.
I will give you all the funding you need,
so find that cause before this
issue becomes too big to handle.
All right, President.
Aww... After a meeting
this long, I'm starving.
Shall we all go out for lunch?
We're going back to the factory.
That Technical Director or whatever,
the more we meet, the less I like him.
Still, when it comes to the
boiler sector, he's got credibility.
But Oppa said he was so hungry...
Where did he go?
Gangmo!
Gangmo.
Quick... Turn on the TV.
Hangang Construction
is being mentioned on TV.
Really?! Looks like the president
did something great again?!
- Turn it on.
- Quick.
Just like briquette gas leaks
so common in the 1970s,
quickly dealing with these
accidents is an urgent concern.
Only this month, there have already been
three accidents dealing with gas boilers,
but Hangang Construction,
which recently acquired Beaute Boilers...
- Isn't that the reporter from earlier today?
- And when did he shoot this?!
An even bigger cause for concern...
is that these boilers will be installed
in all Hangang Construction apartments...
built in the Suseo area.
That felt just great!
Facing such accidents the very
moment they acquire that company...
Aigoo... Really.
Are you that happy?
This is all part of the game,
you wouldn't understand the feeling.
And while this holds Lee Gangmo back,
we will develop a
superior gas boiler in-house.
But wouldn't it be hard
to develop such technology?
We're working behind the scenes to
secretly acquire Beaute's boiler technology.
It's only a matter of time before
their core technology is in our hands.
So the factory Lee Gangmo acquired
will become completely useless.
How can a patient who looked
perfectly fine suddenly turn moribund?
Shideok, you go meet the victim's
family and find out what happened.
All right.
There's a good possibility that
all the data leaked to the press...
about the boiler accidents
came from within the factory.
Since there might be a mole
conspiring against us from within.
Sotae, you discreetly dig into it.
All right.
Then, what?
Are you suggesting that we might be
dealing with industrial espionage?
That Technical Director
sure looks suspicious?!
Hey... Hey.
Forget about his personality,
but he really doesn't look
like he'd be capable of that?
Anyhow, I'll find out what sorry-ass
son of a cunt was behind this.
Don't you worry.
He's been looking for you all morning.
Try to convince him.
He refuses to go to the hospital.
Gangmo, is that you?
I plan to retire
to the temple, from now on.
I called you as I wished
you'd bring me there.
If you prefer that over the
hospital, of course I will.
It'll be my pleasure.
President Noh, what do you plan to do?
Will you just pay up
like Baekpa suggested?
I'm not giving them a penny.
This is all because of that brat,
Hwang Jeongyeon or whatever her name is.
What the hell is she all about,
to enjoy all that confidence?
I have very surprising news to convey.
Surprising news?
Baekpa will soon pass away.
What's that supposed to mean?
Is he suffering from
some kind of mortal disease?
I will tell you
all the details on our way.
On our way?
Where?
There is someone I'd like you to meet.
I saw on the news that
there was a boiler accident?
It was nothing serious.
When machines break,
they can always be fixed.
They never betray you like people.
If they learn of my condition,
many of those people will betray me.
It actually might have all started already.
So from what I hear,
you are in love with Jeongyeon?
Is it not the case?
I was in love with her.
There's not much difference, is there?!
I made a very important decision.
Is it anything you can tell me about?
You will soon find out.
Gangmo.
Did you know that Gyeongok
is Jeongyeon's mother?
Yes, I know.
The dreams I could never fulfill
are now on their shoulders.
A huge storm is about to hit these shores.
But leaving two women alone to tame
this hell on earth makes me feel uneasy.
Can you protect them for me?
As someone who spent his life
answering favors for other people,
this is the first and very
last favor I'll ever ask.
Please, protect them.
I will give my all to fulfill
your wishes to the very end.
Thanks, Gangmo.
He's my lawyer.
You said you wanted to
hear about my decision?
They're here.
Let me introduce Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
It's a pleasure to meet you,
I'm Noh Gapsoo.
Pleasure is mine.
I'm Jo Pilyeon.
I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Bang Jushik.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Jang Hopyeong.
I'm Won Gushik.
Nice to meet you.
I'll start recording, Sir.
I, Baekpa Choi Yeol,
will convey my testament through this tape.
First, all the rights concerning the
business ventures I've been involved with...
What I want to know...
is an accurate estimate
of Baekpa's entire assets.
That is something we are not aware of.
I'm sure that's the case.
I've been told your combined assets
make up over half the group's total.
So all I need you to do is write
the portion of your assets...
dealing with the principal
Baekpa invested in you,
and the amount of interests
you've been paying him all this time.
I'm sure...
you are at least aware of that?!
However,
our unwritten laws state that
we are not at liberty to disclose that.
Try to understand our position.
If you refuse to cooperate,
my target will instantly
move from Baekpa to you.
Is that what you want?
What is the reason you're doing this?
To be perfectly honest,
I can't allow Yoo Gyeongok
to inherit Baekpa's fortune.
So the figures you
will write down today...
will become a huge tax bomb
hitting her, after Baekpa's death.
Are you telling us that
we will face no repercussions?
If you need a pledge,
I could write it for you.
Once he finds out in what
ballpark Baekpa's total assets are,
Jo Pilyeon will add
a huge figure on top of it.
So the declared figure will be
a lot higher than it actually is.
That's what this
"underground economy" is all about.
When you know neither
the source nor its flow,
money just ends up becoming
a succession of numbers.
Then, disguising astronomical figures
as a simple inheritance tax...
will be a piece of cake.
I'm sure he's not going to devote
all that money to the National Treasury.
Once all the paperwork for
the revenue office is complete,
he will start negotiations
with Director Yoo.
In the end, what Jo Pilyeon
is aiming for is Baekpa's money.
Seems like he's banking on getting at least
half the money she'll inherit from him.
And if things go according to his plans,
we will find even
more obstacles in our way.
You just wait, Hyung.
Because until the very end,
nobody will be able to predict
who will be the last man standing.
He's even refusing to drink now.
Noh Gapsoo, Bang Jushik,
Jang Hopyeong,
Won Gushik.
Just as you expected,
the group's top brass
has met with Jo Pilyeon.
Seems like it's time
for me to throw my last card.
How about it?
Might only be the estimates we made,
but isn't Baekpa's fortune
truly impressive?
If she really inherits all this much,
taxes alone will be immense.
Once Yoo Gyeongok sees that,
she'll be shocked.
She'll feel like the
tail is wagging the dog.
How much were you
looking for, out of this?
Half the inheritance tax.
I wonder if Director Yoo
will comply with your requests.
She'll be forced to,
since sharing the pie is always better
than letting the National Treasury get it all.
She's Baekpa's heir after all,
think she wouldn't see that far?
It's certainly a brilliant idea,
but I can't really say I like it.
What?!
At the end, isn't it just
fraud and blackmail?
Minwoo, you little...
Baekpa said he will reveal
his testament this evening.
We'll get going, Sir.
Goddess of Mercy.
All the members are starting to arrive.
We can just relax
and wait for it to happen.
Here... Let's all have a drink.
The moment Yoo Gyeongok
inherits all that fortune,
Baekpa's money becomes mine.
We will now reveal
Baekpa's recorded testament.
I, Baekpa Choi Yeol,
will convey my testament
through this tape.
First, all the rights concerning the
business ventures I've been involved with...
will be transferred to Yoo Gyeongok.
The moment this testament is revealed,
all the principal I invested
in the organization...
will be retrieved.
Why is it taking so damn long?
Is it still not over?
I'll go find out.
What are you doing here?
Just thought you'd be curious
about Baekpa's testament.
I see that nothing escapes you.
You're right.
Honestly, I am curious.
Because of all his money. If he wasn't
so rich, I would have never cared.
So Yoo Gyeongok will become his heir?!
That woman's been blessed by good luck.
Serve an old fart for a few years,
and look what you gain.
Baekpa's fortune will be
inherited by someone else.
Someone else?!
Are you telling me
it's not Director Yoo?
And who is it?
Is it you?
Or maybe Hwang Jeongyeon?
Nah... Whomever it is,
it doesn't really matter.
The important thing is
that inheritance anyhow.
*Buddhist maxim by Goryeo
monk, Naonhwasang
"Gongsurae Gongsugeo*," as they say.
"Just as bare as you are at birth,
you are bare in demise."
For all this time, I obsessed over
money with the thirst of a demon.
And now my most fervent wish
is to atone for my foolish ways,
and for all the suffering they
brought upon so many innocent people.
All the money retrieved from
within the organization included,
every single asset in my name
will be returned to society.
Under the consultation of
Yoo Gyeongok and my lawyer,
the money will be divided amongst
various charity and welfare groups.
Gentlemen.
I ask you not to find fault with
this foolish old man's very last decision.
He'll return it all back to society?!
That much money?!
How does it sound, from a
politician's point of view?
Is it not a very respectable decision?
Sure... Remarkable.
A remarkable decision, all right.
Ahh...
He also told me
to convey you these words.
That he's very grateful to you for
helping him make such a good decision.
Did I make myself clear?
You will never take away
a single penny from me!
Baekpa...
Baekpa!!
Congressman Oh Byeongtak is quite
curious about this "secret weapon" of mine.
It's not something that
can be revealed so carelessly.
Congressman Oh might claim
to bear ill-will against Jo Pilyeon...
because of what happened with Baekpa,
but you shouldn't so easily trust
anyone in the political arena.
Not to mention this will completely
turn the balance of power upside down.
It will amount to treason in their eyes.
It's pretty obvious they'll
try to protect themselves.
So you're saying that it
won't be easy to convince them.
Build even stronger ties
with Congressman Oh.
All right, I'll do that.
But, isn't it time you tell me, now?
What on earth happened
between you and Jo Pilyeon...
As for that,
on the day of Jo Pilyeon's downfall,
you will find out.
Beaute Boilers, Another Accident
Accident-prone Beaute Boilers
Unable to Find the Cause
Calls are raining down the factory,
with people asking to return
even boilers that are perfectly fine.
Do you have any guess who it could be?
Ahhh... After what happened,
a single stare and
I start suspecting people.
Starting now, inspect every
apartment using our boilers.
At the first sign of anything even
remotely suspicious, bring them in.
But that'll be no laughing matter?!
We need to prevent
any more articles like this.
And continue looking
for any possible cause.
- Okay.
- All right.
Gangmo.
Let's have a word in private.
Gangmo...
- Lee Miju -
Gangmo Oppa.
You've been curious
about me, haven't you?
Sorry for not getting in touch, Oppa.
I've been busy trying to become a singer.
I knew how worried you were about me,
but I showed you so much
misery that I just wanted...
to finally make you witness me succeed.
Little Oppa...
You'll scold me, right?
Go ahead then, since I
more than deserve it.
I've debuted as a singer
using the name Cha Soojeong.
The tickets I sent you are
for my first live performance.
Come with Big Oppa.
I miss you.
Why should we wait all that time?
Let's just go meet her, Hyung.
She even sent us invites...
- Let's just wait until then.
- Hyung!
You know Miju.
She'll probably want to show
herself at her most beautiful.
Sit.
It's just that I'm worried!
If by any chance...
she gave birth to Jo Minwoo's...
I already looked into it.
Actually, I found her a few days ago.
I saw how busy you were with everything,
so I didn't tell you on purpose.
So what happened to her?
Miju...
didn't give birth, right?
And if she did, think I'd be here
drinking with you now?
Since our youngest
is debuting as a singer,
we must give her our blessing.
That's right, Hyung.
Our Miju...
is really something.
She fulfilled her dream all on her own.
'Course.
Whose sister is she?
- IOU List -
This is a list of the
principal Baekpa lent to you.
- Director Yoo.
- We need to pay taxes right away,
and if you ask us to give back
the principal now, it'll only kill us.
You know who asked for this.
Anyhow, now the decision
solely depends on you.
I will give you a fortnight to settle this.
After which I will begin legal litigation.
Director Yoo...
It's money to be spent for a noble cause,
so don't act as if you were wronged.
Director Yoo!
- Director Yoo...
- Director Yoo!
This decision will strongly
impact their influence.
I'd been feeling we needed to
restructure our organization for a while, too.
Inheriting control of Baekpa's
business might increase your status,
but it'll also bring along
plenty of newfound difficulties.
I know.
Your area of influence will
also be significantly extended.
I'm confident I can do well.
It's as if they're hell-bent on
destroying this organization from within.
We can't just sit
and stare while it happens.
How about we discuss it
with Congressman Jo?
And how could we possibly
trust someone like him?
I'm Bucheol, Sir.
May I come in?
Enter.
I know a way to avoid
giving back Baekpa's principal.
Let's hear it.
Before I tell you that,
I'd like to know, what will you give
me in return if I solve your problems?
You set the conditions.
I will take ten percent of the
amount each of you was supposed to pay.
Hey...
Do you even realize
how much that would be?
Why?
Are you telling me it's way
too much money for someone like me?
- Honestly, with that much money...
- Then!
I'll let you solve it by yourselves.
Hey... Wait.
Speak, what's the plan?
Will you give me that money, or not?
Fine.
If you solve our problems, it's yours.
Couldn't you just get rid of that
IOU list in Yoo Gyeongok's possession?
Hey... Think we never thought of that?
And how do you suppose we do that?
Hwang Jeongyeon...
is Director Yoo's daughter.
If her daughter's life is on the line,
it'll be convincing enough a reason
to part with that list once and for all.
All in.
Call.
May I?
Wait... Wait a moment.
It's a full house.
He's out of the game.
What's wrong with you?
Now that it was starting to get fun...
- Come!
- Hey... Hey! Wait!
Wait...
- Wait... Just a moment...
- I said come!
Don't touch that!
You can do it, right?
If you handle this,
I'll give you more gambling money.
Just do as I told you.
Are we clear?
We have a customer, Director.
Could have called me when
you had your opening party...
I at least would
have sent you a garland.
Look at how she treats customers...
Lend me some money, will you?
I don't deal with gamblers.
But I have quite the collateral...
I can help you meet your birth mother,
how much is that worth?
I know where your mother is.
Want me to help you meet her?
Get out.
I don't believe you.
Really?
Too bad, then.
You're the one who refused,
so don't regret it later.
Didn't look like she'll last too long...
Hey... Hwang Jeongshik...
What is that supposed to mean?
She won't last long?!
Your mother...
is at a hospital.
Wh...What did they
say it was called again?
Anyhow, she's bad enough that
doctors can't help her anymore.
You...
are not just lying to me, are you?
First, you can check for yourself.
Then, if what I said
turns out to be right,
lend me thirty million.
How about it?
I can't wait for long,
so make up your mind.
Eonni...
Are you all right?
Jina...
Bring me a mirror.
What's with them?
Hey...
You're going to meet your mother,
and still bring the stiffs along?
Stay here.
Director.
I'll be right back, so just go back in.
Still...
Haven't you heard me?
But leaving two women alone to tame
this hell on earth makes me feel uneasy.
Can you protect them for me?
As someone who spent his life
answering favors for other people,
this is the first and very
last favor I'll ever ask.
Please, protect them.
Hello?
Yes... It's me.
Is the director in?
Is it President Lee?
Eonni left?!
Really?
Where did she go?
She said she was going
to meet her birth mother.
Her birth mother?!
When?
All right.
Yes?
Director Yoo.
It's me, Lee Gangmo.
Are you meeting with Jeongyeon now?
No.
But, why are you asking?
So it was you?
I'm sure they treated you well enough?!
Who did you do this for?
That's none of your business.
Just stay here quietly, and be glad
if you're sold to a brothel...
I knew it the moment I saw
you punch that sandbag,
but you sure can hit?
If you don't set me free
right this moment,
you will all...
You insolent little bitch...
What are you trying to say?
Jeongyeon went to
meet her birth mother?!
She was abducted.
That's the only...
Hello?
Director Yoo Gyeongok?
That'd be me.
We have your daughter.
Who are you people?
I asked you a question!
What are you asking?
Hello?
Hello?!
Listen well.
Whomever you are,
and whatever you're asking,
it doesn't matter.
Because I...
will kill you all.
You will regret abducting Jeongyeon...
even from six feet under.
Because I'll follow you into
the pits of hell if I have to,
and tear you apart limb from limb!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Without all that money,
our organization will crumble.
- It is Baekpa's last wish.
- Baekpa is already dead!
Give it a rest.
Why don't you give it another try?
There is Cha Bucheol
behind all this, right?
Gangmo!
What is it?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com