Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 2 ~
Who is it you're looking for?
None of your business.
Like I care...
Find some place to sleep nearby.
Go out and do it yourself.
If we sleep here,
we'll freeze to death.
I'm cold!
Same goes for me.
I'll give you a hundred won.
I can just pay for your room
as well, can't I?!
Did they heat this damned room or what?
It's like sleeping in a fridge.
My Jeongyeon...
You must be all grown up by now.
As long as those rich parents
of yours are making you happy...
So I'm supposed to sleep
in a place like this?
Then, go back to the station's lobby.
Are the covers here clean, at least?
Cleaner than those newspapers, I guess.
What kind of jackpot is this?
Aigoo...
Not too bad at all.
That's my spot.
Move.
I said move!
Trying to heat up the floor
with my body alone was so hard.
Leave.
Aigoo... Damned weather.
How could it be so cold?
Hey... It's cold over there.
Come here.
Come sleep here.
And where would we have
any space for her to fit in?
Unless you move out of the way...
I'm fine here.
But there...
It's got to be chilly...
Hyung.
You made it alive, didn't you?
Hyung...
Nothing happened to you, right?
Sir! He's still alive.
Get him up and back to the post.
Where have you been all this time?
Never telling people anything...
Aigoo... I'm beat.
I'm so tired.
Can you prepare me a bath?
Honey...
About Jeongyeon.
What about Jeongyeon?
She'd been throwing
temper tantrums all along,
but she finally took
some money and ran away.
And where could she possibly go?
If I had any idea,
would I be sitting here?
You didn't tell her about
her mother in Daejeon, did you?
Are you out of your mind?
Why would I tell her that?
It's almost curfew time,
where are you going?
Shouldn't I go out and find her?!
Just call the police,
and let's wait here.
When she runs out of money,
I guess she'll be back.
What are you doing all day in here?
You can't even keep a kid in check?
Will good fortune bless me today?
Looks pretty good?!
- Mom!
- Aigoo... My belly...
Mom.
Those guys came
looking for us, last night.
What about your brother,
what happened to him?
Did they catch him?
No...
It was just them.
It couldn't have
been easy to ditch them off...
They said they'd
be looking around here.
I don't think we'll be
able to take the train.
Same goes for the bus terminal...
For the time being,
it might be better to just hide here.
And the money?
This place is quite expensive.
Don't worry.
We have enough money for a few days.
What's wrong?
I'm sure I put it here?!
3,000.
1,500.
2,500.
2,000, and that's my last offer.
Fine.
Instead, give me a thousand up-front.
We have to pay for tonight.
No way.
You'll get it when we find my mother.
Ehh... That's so nasty...
So you're looking for your mother?
Here's her address.
You can find it, can't you?
Wait a moment.
I'll go have a word with my mother.
My wallet!
What is it...
Did you lose something?
What?
N...No...
What are you doing? Let's go.
Mom.
I said I'd pay for
the room later tonight,
so you don't need to worry.
Careful not to let them
notice you, understood?
Yes.
Let's go.
Those bastards will pay
for what they did to us.
You just wait.
Congressman Oh is still at the Blue House,
so I'm not sure when he'll be back.
It's all right.
I'll just wait.
If you'll excuse me,
may I ask who you are?
I already called the Congressman,
so you don't need to worry.
Yes.
Blue House?!
What are you talking about?
Our development projects
in South Seoul have hit a snag?
I'm referring to the Gangnam land we
bought under namesake accounts.
That account list was exposed.
And who got their hands on it?
It has to be either the American embassy,
or the EUSA*'s Intelligence Brigade.
*Eighth United States Army
~ Oh Byeongtak ~
(Republican Party - Chief of Finance)
The Americans?!
Why would they?
Isn't that obvious?
~ Han Myeongseok (Seoul City Commissioner) ~
~ Park Changwoo (KCIA Director) ~
So that they can interfere
with the next elections,
and prohibit the president
from running for another term.
Even the president is not aware
that we bought that land in Gangnam.
If this leaks out,
nobody here will be safe.
So what I was saying is,
why did you let it get to this point?
Why, did we do this for
the sake of personal benefit?
It was to secure political funding,
and show our loyalty to the president
by helping him run for office again.
Anyhow, solving this
is your responsibility.
Listen, Director Park!
The leak of classified intel is the KCIA's
responsibility, why should I deal with that?
Aren't you in charge of our
development projects in South Seoul?
Ohh Ohh... Listen to you!
This is no time to
be fighting each other.
Whatever it takes,
shouldn't we make sure...
those namesake account details
aren't exposed to the public?
Aigoo... My head...
As if we were dealing with the press...
How are you going to stop those
Yankees from revealing everything?
Our hands are not completely tied.
Have any idea?
If a negotiation table is what you want,
you need a card to play against them.
We can get our hands on one of
their classified files, for instance.
So, to buy their silence,
you exchange classified files?
The idea alone is certainly enticing,
but what classified intel
are we going to steal, and how?
I have an American friend who's
working as war reporter in Vietnam.
And?
He said there's a rumor that a top
secret document regarding the Vietnam war...
is being prepared as we speak.
A top secret document?!
And that document's latest revision...
happens to be kept in a safe
at the EUSA headquarters in Korea.
And what is it about?
We don't know the details,
but what is evident is that,
should this document leak to the public,
the American government would fall
into a severe crisis as a result.
A top secret document at the EUSA's HQ?!
~ Eighth United States Army ~
Headquarters
Can you hear me?
These people found you
unconscious, and brought you here.
Where am I?
It's the Eighth Army's headquarters.
Then, is this Seoul?
Sir.
He doesn't have any
serious external injuries,
except for some bruises.
What's your name?
Your name.
Don't you know your name?
I don't.
You don't?!
I can't remember a thing.
Sir.
I think he suffered a head trauma,
which might have affected his memory.
You mean he's got amnesia?
Possibly.
Well...
I want you to keep an eye on him.
Until he recovers his memory.
Yes, Sir.
You're really lucky.
You met the most kind-hearted
American officer in the entire base.
Gangmo...
Miju...
Mother...
Ahh... Don't bother.
So you came all the way
to Seoul just to meet me?
*deferential form of seonbae,
older colleague/fellow college alumni
I had a favor to ask you, Seonbaenim*.
I have enough trouble
on my plate as it is,
so what's with you and favors now?
As you well know, the Defense Ministry
just announced personnel changes.
You've come all the way here,
so let's have a drink.
Help me out.
With your influence, you could
certainly take me under your wings.
Drinks are on me, this time.
What's this?
Go ahead and open it.
So you want me to take this money,
and engage in trafficking of official posts?
Is that not enough?
What do you take me for...
Take it and leave!
I'm not here just for the money!
That money is not for you.
Just funds I'm devoting to our country.
If you wish to maintain power,
you need immense funds.
Aren't you using the Gangnam development
project to gain political funds...
Ehh Ehh! Listen to you!
Careful what you say.
I'll devote this money to the president.
Give me a chance to devote myself
for the sake of this country.
As you said, we need money.
However, we can't just accept any money
without knowing where it comes from.
As God is my witness,
I swear this money is completely clean.
What do you want in return?
I want to join the KCIA.
I don't believe in those who only profess
their loyalty by flapping their tongue.
What can I do to gain your trust?
Let's get up.
We need to go somewhere together.
How about it, Director Park?
I think he's the perfect
candidate for the job?
For starters, you'll be
assigned to the Eighth Army.
There is something you must
do there for the country.
After you succeed,
you will be accepted into the KCIA.
Tell me what task you have in mind.
There's a certain General Hampton
at the EUSA Intelligence Brigade.
He will be in possession of a top secret
document regarding the Vietnam war.
Bring us that document.
I just met them.
Yes.
The kid who witnessed us
fell off the train and died,
and they're looking for
his family as we speak.
Should I tell them to withdraw?
Since there's no witness anymore...
Why would you let free the
possible cause of our downfall?
Trail them all the way.
Understood.
When will we get to the end
of this neighborhood?
Be honest.
You don't know this place
too well, do you?
I never said I live here.
You even fool people?
Let me ask you something.
Where is No. 18 here?
18 is the last house up there?!
Are you looking for someone?
My mother.
Your mother?!
So that woman living next
to the porch is your mother?
Yes, I was told she lives there.
Will be no use going there.
She already took a hike a few days ago.
A hike?!
Why would she run away?
Why do you think?
She must have had her reasons.
Thank you.
Just in case.
If the landlord asks you,
don't tell her it's your mother.
You'll only get in trouble.
Yes.
Anyone in?
You don't seem like
someone she owed money to.
By any chance,
are you her daughter?
What?
I recall her saying she had a
daughter in Seoul or something?
No...
My mother just told us to check
if she was living here.
Aigoo... So she fooled someone
else out of their money.
That brat was just scum.
She had a new man
coming in every night,
and after making a mess, she knocked
at every door begging for money,
and eventually took off
like nothing happened.
I should have guessed it right
when she said she was working at a bar...
Aigoo...
~ 9 - My Daughter's Birthday ~
Mom...
Where have you gone, Mom?
Lodging is a given...
By the way, Eonni.
Is business doing well there?
All right... I get it.
Instead, any tip is mine.
Ohh... I'll come tomorrow.
What's with putting on airs,
for that little rat hole of a bar?
- Are you sure of that?
- Yes.
Having to carry a newborn around,
she won't have gone far.
We're keeping an eye on both
the bus terminal and the station,
so we'll spot her soon.
By any chance,
are you looking for
a woman with three kids?
A newborn, a little girl and a boy.
Where have you seen them?
And she said people were after her...
It's true?!
We're in a rush,
so just tell us where you've seen them.
Ajeosshi, I'm headed for Seoul,
but I'm a little short of money.
Ehh... Just two?!
When I get to Seoul, I don't know
the way, so I'll need a taxi?!
Know the inn down
the turnabout alley?
We spent the night together there.
Even the wallet looks expensive.
And how much is this?
Jeongyeon...
Who are you people?
Where's that woman
with the three kids?
Three kids or whatever,
get out of here!
You even walk in with your shoes on?!
Get the hell out!
I told you I know nothing.
Either pay and check in, or leave!
You don't know?
Are we supposed to believe that?
- She's here, isn't she?
- There's nobody!
- You really are pushing it!
- Look at this Ajumma...
Ajumma?!
I'm the owner here!
Uh?! I own this inn.
Leave!
Out... Get out.
Leave... Out of here.
I said stop interfering
with my business and leave!
Hurry and come out.
I saw her pass by the coffeehouse.
Please, don't cry...
Don't cry.
You can rest assured now.
They're gone,
so it will be safe here.
By the way.
Do you know where that girl
who was here with us has gone?
She... left with my son,
and they went looking
for someone together.
Hey... Aren't you hungry?
I saw a place down there
selling dough buns.
Should I go get some?
Then, let's just go!
My mother is waiting.
Go by yourself.
Then, give me my money.
2,000 won.
You couldn't find my mother.
Give me at least half,
I don't have any money to go back.
Are you listening to me?
Give me my money.
I don't have it.
What?
You don't have what?
I have no money.
They stole my wallet.
Then, my money?
Hey!
Dad...
Seeing it firsthand, it's all much
bigger than I could ever imagine.
So all construction costs
have been settled?
Yes.
Thanks to you,
we overcame this crisis.
Once this construction is complete,
I'll pay you back for
all the help you've given me.
That's your share,
so no need to pay me back.
No.
I will pay it back.
Listen, Director Hwang.
Did you already forget what
you pledged right in my face?
When you said you'd be loyal to me,
whatever it took.
So if I tell you not to do something,
just listen to me.
Is that clear?
From now on, we'll get to see
each other quite often.
I've been appointed to the Eighth Army,
as part of the Korean support unit.
Then, is it a promotion?
I'm a major now, so I guess it is?!
Find a decent place for
my family near the base.
Yes.
I will.
Ohh... You're back?
So, what did the police tell you?
That there's still no news.
I think I'll just have to go myself.
I apologize.
I have some urgent matters
to tend to in Daejeon.
Daejeon?
Actually, it's because
my daughter ran away...
My aide is in Daejeon as we speak.
I'll give him a call,
so if you need any help, feel free.
- It's all right.
- It's not all right with me.
If it involves your family,
it involves me as well.
Are we not family now?
Let's get moving, you brat.
My mother is waiting.
So just go!
My legs hurt so much
I can't walk any longer.
First the cold,
then you're hungry... Whatever!
It's always your fault!
You should have told me
about your wallet!
I thought we would meet my mother.
Get on my back.
You said you have no money
and know nobody here.
So get on my back, you brat.
You don't need to bother.
Just go.
My legs hurt and I'm hungry as well.
Come on.
You... If you don't get on my back
to the count of three,
I'm just leaving.
1...
2...
I knew it when you
started putting on airs...
What's with all the trouble
you're forcing on me?
Still, since I'm on your back,
you're not as cold.
What?
- Does that make any sense?
- I'm hungry, so stop prattling.
You brat...
How can a girl be so heavy?
Stay put.
Stop moving, will you?
- Let me down. Now!
- I said stop moving!
Pay for the room?!
It's paid for already.
What?
My mother shouldn't have any money?
Not your mother,
some other woman paid for her.
Who?
The hell I know, did she prance around
with her ID stamped on her face?
Go in.
She'll take over my spot tonight.
Then, you?
We can take shifts sleeping, can't we?
One hour each.
That woman paid for you as well.
Me as well?!
Yeah.
Gangmo.
Mom.
Hurts again?
Yeah...
Since it's late, seems like
the pain came back to haunt me.
How about medicine?
Have anything left?
Forget that, and go find Miju.
I haven't seen her in a while.
~ Han Myeongsuk's Man with the Yellow Shirt (1961) ~
"I like that man."
"Don't know why,
but I get that feeling."
"Ha! That strange feeling!"
"That feeling I have never felt before."
"Ha! Will he be feeling
the same for me?"
"The man with the yellow shirt,
the silent one over there."
"Don't know why,
but I think I like him."
"I don't know why,
but I just like him."
You'll become a singer!
You're really great.
Do you know any of
Lee Mija's songs?
Of course!
If you do as well as the last one,
I'll give you fifty won.
Really?
"Just a look and my heart throbs."
"Just a thought and my heart throbs."
Oppa!
Follow me.
Now!
Oppa, you're hurting me! Let go!
Who asked you to go there and beg?
What are you, some street beggar?
Uh?
What's wrong with you?
What did I ever do wrong?
You little brat...
Why are you hitting me?
You... Try to beg like that again,
and I'll make you pay. Got it?
Mommy is hurting, what else can I do?
She ran out of medicine,
and she couldn't
eat a thing all day long!
She can't even
breastfeed the baby now.
Think I like doing that?
I hate it myself, it's embarrassing.
But what if even Mommy ends up dying?
Will you take responsibility?
Mommy...
I don't want Mommy to die!
From now on...
I'll do the begging,
if we ever need to.
Dad and Hyung are not with us,
so I'll take care of everything.
So don't do that again.
Oppa...
It's cold.
Let's go back in.
Let's use this and buy some dumplings.
Mommy loves them.
All right.
Let's go.
Ohh... That...
That's the...
Miju...
- Quick!
- Catch them!
Spread out.
Thank y...
Thank you.
She sure has grown into a pretty girl?!
Hey!
It's clear, come out.
Eonni, what's that?
Dumplings.
You said you had no money.
I took the coins you dropped
when you ran away.
Really?
Let's go.
Mom must be hungry.
Mommy!
Mommy's not here?!
This one is just gold-plated...
This is not too bad, but you
won't get much money out of it?!
Not even five thousand won?
Five thousand?!
Ehh... What are you saying?
Take all this back.
Then, whatever you can give me.
Show me that ring.
This one?
If you leave this with me, what the hell...
I'll be generous and give you 3,000 won.
Just endure it a little longer.
Once prices of land in
Apgujeong-Dong start moving,
we'll be able to get our own room.
We'll eat all the pork ribs we want,
send the kids to college,
and live a nice life.
If you don't want to, just go.
Give me that money.
Is there any way I
could get to Seoul from here?
Should we leave a few for your
mother, and eat some first?
No way... I'll eat them with Mommy.
Then, should we eat just one?
Right. Just one each.
Go ahead and eat.
They're still warm.
It's all right.
Go ahead.
Aren't you going to?
Yeah... I'll wait for Mommy.
Must feel great.
What?
Having your mother by your side.
Why, don't you have a mother?
Gangmo.
Mom.
Where have you been?
I was worried.
And Miju?
She's inside.
You keep this money.
Where did you find it?
We'll go to Seoul tomorrow.
Go how?
A truck.
It will pass right here tomorrow,
so sleep early.
Your medicines?
Did you take them?
Wait a moment.
I'll go buy them.
Mom...
I'll never get ill again.
If we can get to Seoul...
I promise I'll never make you go
through all this trouble again.
Her name is Hwang Jeongyeon.
Here she is.
All right.
We'll start searching for her
in the morning.
We don't know where
she might be sleeping tonight.
You'll pardon me,
but I'd rather you started now.
It's almost curfew time.
And I don't even have enough men.
Then, even if my daughter
freezes to death on the street,
you couldn't care less?
What damned police station is this?
Director Hwang...
What's with the attitude?
Attitude?!
I'm rotting inside because
I can't find my daughter,
is staring at trouble from the
other side all that police can do?
Get these people out of my face!
Wait.
And who are you?
You come from the Security Command?
Troublesome as it might be,
start searching for that girl right now.
Yes...
We will start right away.
Get the patrol car ready.
Yes, Chief.
Aww... It's so damn noisy
I can't close an eye!
Take the kid out, at least!
Do something!
Did you rent the entire
damned room or something?
I'm sorry...
Baby... What's wrong?
Mom.
I'll take the baby.
No, it'll be the same
in the other room as well.
Just go to sleep.
I'll put her to sleep,
so you go ahead and sleep.
I said it's all right...
Mommy, I need to pee...
Go by yourself.
No way!
That toilet is too scary.
Mom, I'll take Miju to the toilet,
and then she'll sleep with me.
Hurry up.
Come on in...
Here again?
That room is too cold.
Don't spare the briquettes tonight.
As if I didn't have enough
trouble with all the empty rooms...
You know how much
those briquettes cost?
I can just pay for them.
This much?!
If you don't heat up
those rooms for real,
I'll set the damned place on fire.
You've been warned.
That... That...
Listen to how she talks.
How many briquettes
can I buy with this?!
Mom...
Don't go...
Mom, don't go...
I'll only sleep
next to you for tonight,
and I won't bother you again.
Jeongyeon... You must never
become a despicable person like me.
So... Don't look for me again,
don't say you miss me,
and just pretend
as if I didn't even exist.
I haven't done a single thing for you.
I'm sorry, Jeongyeon...
Don't forgive me.
Jeongyeon...
My pretty daughter...
Should I get the pipe fixed?
What's wrong with the furnace?
Gangmo.
Lee Gangmo.
Get up.
You need to go to school,
you know what time it is?
Are you going somewhere?
To meet your dad.
Dad?!
Daddy asked me out on a date?!
A date?!
We'll go out on a date,
watch a movie, and have a nice lunch.
So you're leaving us behind
and going all by yourselves?
How much longer are you
going to pretend you're a kid?
You have to feed Miju
and keep the house clean.
When will you be back?
Gangmo.
I trust you more
than anyone in the world.
My Gangmo will become a great man.
I'll always be looking at you,
so don't let this bring you down.
You must be strong.
Can you promise me that?
Mom...
Take good care of your siblings,
and whatever happens,
you must never cry.
Understood?
Mom.
I...
I'll trust you on that and go.
Mom...
Jeongyeon...
Jeongyeon... Get up...
Wake up!
Mom!
It's Mommy!
Mommy!
Is this her?
She's not the one we were looking for.
That's a relief.
Oppa... Let go!
Let go! Let me go!
Let me go back to Mommy!
Let me see Mommy!
Listen well.
Mom...
Mom is gone.
She's dead.
So... Stop looking for her.
Liar.
It's for real, you silly!
She's no longer of this world,
is that clear?
No way!
Mommy didn't die!
You're just a liar!
Miju.
Lee Miju!
God.
I'll give you my favorite dolls.
So bring me back my Mommy.
I'll listen to everything she tells me,
and Oppa as well.
And I'll brush my teeth before sleep.
Every weekend, I'll come to church.
God...
Bring my mother back to me.
Uh, God?
Why do you keep acting like a fool?
I told you she's dead.
If she's dead, how can she
come back to you?! You silly fool.
You're even more of a fool!
If she's dead, we must pray
for God to bring her back to us!
What?
Mommy always told me.
That God will always
listen to our prayers!
God...
Please, bring our mother back to us.
Uh, God?
Mommy...
Why did you take her?
Save her.
Why did you even take away our mother?
- Bring her back.
- Oppa...
Bring our poor mother back to us!
Send her back to us!
Why did you take her...
Mom...
I miss you.
- Mommy...
- Mom...
Mom...
Jeongyeon.
Are you feeling better?
Dad...
Right, it's your Daddy.
Now I'm here, so don't
you worry about a thing.
Go get an ambulance ready
to transfer her to Seoul.
All right.
In my dreams...
Someone suddenly woke me up.
She was calling my name,
saying "wake up!"
You little...
So why did you run away
from home like that?
Did you meet your mother?
Do you really want
to meet her that much?
When you get better,
I'll bring you to her.
Really?
Sure.
So you need to hurry up
and get better, you silly.
- How about this patient's guardian?
- Still nobody.
Do you know her?
Uh?!
Is she dead?
I think it'll be hard
for her to survive the night.
You wretched brat...
If luck has completely
turned its back on you,
at least live a long life.
Of all places you could choose,
you want to die right in front of
your daughter, who's dying to meet you?
Ehh... You foolish, vicious brat.
If you were going to die anyway,
at least do it in
your daughter's embrace.
How are you going to rest in peace,
without ever hearing her
call you "mother"?
Ehh... You crooked brat.
Doctor, come over here a moment.
Check her pulse right away,
and stabilize her temperature.
All right.
Jeongyeon...
Close this one.
Yes.
Where are the Korean Army
support quarters?
Yes... Go straight until
the very last building.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Translator/Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
G I A N T
What's the closest oil storage
to the B-side barracks?
Make the oil storage explode.
Who's out there?
We have no place to go now.
We lost our bags, you silly.
Everything we had was in there.
Why don't you follow us
to the orphanage?
Oppa, I don't want to leave the baby.
Let's stay together.
I don't need any of you!
Just leave us alone!
You must find them, even if you have
to ransack every orphanage in town.
What happened to you?
I'll have to do it myself, then.
They call it 3-1 Building.
It's the tallest in Seoul,
with 31 stories.
Big Oppa...
Hurry up and come...
I miss you, Big Oppa!
Did he see your face?
Did he see your face or not?
If he regains his consciousness,
it's all over for us.
Got it?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com