Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
- Episode 24 -
Don't tell me,
they send us to bed on time?!
Hey... No. 534.
So I hear you went to the
commander's barracks today?
What did you do there?
Don't tell me they let
us sleep because of you?
Ahh... really. Did they
spike your drink with cement?
Is that damned trap
going to be stuck all night...
What did you just say?
Accept my conditions.
Go ahead.
Allow enough sleep and nourishment to
everyone who participates in the works.
And?
Many people got injured.
Allow them to be hospitalized
until they fully recover.
And should you fail to finish on time?
If you want me to stake
my life on this, I will.
So let's hear it. How can you make
concrete dry out in two days?
Aigoo... Good girl.
You need to eat to survive.
How can you live without food?
Here... Say "Ahhh."
We brought you some more
side dishes and fruits here,
so don't skip meals and help yourself.
Ma'am.
Aigoo... You're here, Ma'am.
What are you all doing here?
The chairman told us
to take care of her, so...
Leave us alone.
- I...
- Now.
Yes, we'll be going.
Hurry up and come.
- But I need to finish feeding her.
- Hurry up and come!
Finish it all, okay?
So you can hear now?
There soon will be
a shareholders' meeting.
And on that day,
Jeongshik will be proclaimed heir.
You're mute now, so you won't
be able to work anymore.
About your stocks.
Transfer them to me.
Who do you think will take care of you,
when Jeongshik inherits the company?
I'll give you enough to live in
luxury for the rest of your days,
so move abroad.
Did I make myself clear?
You wench, I ought to...
Let me go.
Will you let me go or not?
Sure...
So you're going to act like that?
Just wait until the
shareholders' meeting is over,
so you can find out
what kind of misery awaits you!
What is this?!
Know how much this cost...
I'll be damned, really!
They're really crossing the line here.
Shideok.
A...Agasshi...
You... You can speak?
I need your help.
We just asked Minwoo's father.
To send Gangmo to the Samcheong camp.
Think it was an accident
that killed him?
Minwoo's father paid someone
off to get rid of him.
So... Minwoo's father killed Gangmo
on Minwoo's and your behalf?
Yeah!
You just wait.
You'll never take
the company away from me.
I will avenge Gangmo and
make you pay for killing him.
Agasshi.
Here's the company shares
controlled by the board of directors.
It was really hard to find this out.
Thanks, Shideok.
No need to thank me.
I wanted to get revenge against
those who killed Gangmo myself.
Jeongshik and his mother hold
about 20 percent of the shares,
and it seems like they won over a good
number of minor shareholders as well.
Even if the chairman takes your side,
it won't be easy to turn the tide.
- Yoo Gyeongok -
Who is this?
She controls quite the amount?!
Ahh... This lady.
She's the owner of the Royal Club.
Do you want to give it
a try and convince her?
We must.
Also, Shideok.
You must never tell anyone
I've recovered until the meeting.
Don't you worry.
Gather all the calcium
chloride you have here.
Calcium chloride?!
If you add it to the cement,
it will dry out much faster.
Call unit command and tell them to bring
here all the calcium chloride we have.
- Quick!
- Yes, Sir.
This is Owl.
Eagle, do you copy?
Repeat, this is Owl.
Did it snow somewhere?
Why bring so much calcium chloride,
when they only use it to melt snow?
Aigoo... So heavy...
Here.
Aigoo... Did you buy me
sacks of tonic, or something?
- Next!
- Wretched fool...
Look at the sky.
There'll be showers in no time.
If it starts raining, even Santa
Calcium won't do squat, you fool.
You stay out of this.
I'll tell the drill instructor,
so step aside!
Want to see me get beaten to a pulp?
Hey, Park Sotae...
Spare me the cheap compassion,
and hand me a sack.
It's raining!
Hurry up and cover the cement!
- Gangnam Candidate Jo Pilyeon in Election Scandal -
Climactic Reversal of Fortune Expected
Your approval rate is freefalling.
The supporters' association
is up in arms as well.
They threaten to
immediately halt all funding.
Haven't you found that informer yet?
- If we could only find him...
- Minwoo.
The second most important
thing for me after breathing...
is winning.
Excuse me?
Watch and learn.
How your father will
turn this sinking ship around.
It'll be the perfect opportunity to
learn how to deal with your opponents.
I'm back.
He's the boss of the Maljukgeori gang.
He started working under
Min Honggi for these elections.
He will more than suffice.
Proceed with our plan.
All right.
By now, Min Honggi
must be feeling elated.
That's not too bad
a proposition, either.
Because it's exactly when you let
your guard down that you risk the most.
Thanks, Seongmo.
Your help was truly crucial in
deciding the fate of these elections.
But how did it go with the
favor I asked you last time?
Right... He should have
been here by now already?!
Looks like he just arrived.
- You have a guest.
- Yeah, I know. Let him in.
Sir.
Come on in, Colonel Kim.
- It's been a long time, Seonbaenim.
- Right.
Let me introduce him.
This is my most trusted colleague
from my KCIA days, Lee Seongmo.
This is Colonel Kim Sutak
from the National Security Guard.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
I wish I could stay here with you,
but sadly I have a previous engagement.
Seongmo, this buddy here,
means a lot to me.
Whatever favor he might ask,
help him out for my sake.
Certainly, Seonbaenim.
Right.
So, I'll let you discuss.
See you again.
I'm back.
So, how did it go?
Think it will all dry out before
the division commander arrives?
You little...
You were so sure
you could do it in two days,
so what's with the hesitation now?
I never imagined it could start raining.
Don't even think of using that
as an excuse to save your behind.
If it doesn't dry out by tomorrow,
I might be going to detention camp,
but first I'll be dealing with you.
Is that clear?
Hey... Listen.
Did you give them any condition
in exchange for doing this?
Early release?
But with today's showers,
there's no way in hell
it'll dry out by tomorrow?!
Just pray and hope it will work.
Pray for sunshine.
Who knows what could happen?
If we get a sunny day,
is there a good chance it'll dry out?
Aigoo... And how am I
supposed to know that?
Everyone, wake up!
Gather outside immediately.
Get moving, you pricks!
How do you think it went?
Looks like a really nice day?
You sure are funny. Why ask me
when you can go find out by yourself?
Ten... Hut!
Salute our division commander.
Red hunt!
Starting now, everyone will
go straight to the army bathhouse.
After that,
you have the day off.
Drink and have fun all you want.
Ahh... You twerps.
Never taken a goddamned bath before?
It's so damned noisy I
can't concentrate, you fools.
What's this smell?
I'll just let them cut it off
and live as a cripple.
Hey.
Hold him.
What are you trying to do?
I'm taking no baths.
Now!
I said I'm not going to.
What... What are you doing?
I said leave me alone.
Aww... The smell.
Take off his clothes.
- No...
- Just... Stay put, will you!
I said no...
The hell is that?
What's that, a skin disease?
I told you I won't bathe, didn't I?
Hey!
Carry him.
Aww... That smell...
When we're done bathing,
you'll be transferred to the infirmary.
I told them.
To fix your leg.
Let me go!
Have I ever... Have I
ever asked you to help me?
Uh?
You've been indicted
for murder because of me.
I even let money blind me
and tried to kill you!
I'm that kind of man.
Just human trash.
But why are you
acting like this with me?
Just beat me to a pulp instead.
Kill me with your own hands, you fool!
Even if you die, don't do it here.
Go die outside,
if that's what you want.
Dying while confined...
and doing it outside in all freedom...
are a whole different story.
We're already struggling as it is,
so we should at least be
entitled to a peaceful death.
Gan...Gangmo...
You really...
I what?
What, you fool?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Gangmo...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
Forgive this scumbag
just this once, Gangmo.
I'm sorry, Gangmo...
I'm sorry...
I... I'm sorry, Gangmo!
Gangmo...
I... I'm sorry...
Gangmo.
When my leg recovers...
No.
Even if they cut off both my legs,
and I have to creep my way around,
I'll come back to you.
Even if you refuse to accept me,
or if I die and have to
follow you around as a ghost,
I'll remain by your side.
You sure are something.
So, what, did you stake
your life just to get this?
Did you by any chance learn of
some terminal disease or something?
You take your life that lightly?
Can't see how happy everyone is?
- That's good enough.
- I'll be damned.
If you start acting like that,
what does that make of me?
You're cursing at me
deep down, aren't you?
"You sorry ass twat," and stuff.
I've never been so embarrassed,
even when they caught me
selling off thumbtacks.
But you have this weird talent
for provoking people.
Nam Youngchul.
That's your name, right?
You insolent little son of a...
I ought to just...
How can you just
call an elder by his name...
But how did you find that out?
I had pretty much forgotten it myself?!
My name is Lee Gangmo.
Why, did I ever ask you that?
You will soon meet me again outside.
Really?
Afraid that won't be easy.
Forget how I look here,
but I'm quite the big fish outside.
Unless you make it big enough,
you won't even be able to stare at me?!
Look, Director Park!
Does it make sense that you only
completed 20 percent of that road?
I have no time for your excuses,
so focus on finding a way to
complete that road instead.
Ahh... I really...
What are you doing here?
Why? Am I not welcome here?
Find out who set up this shareholders'
meeting, and what's the reason.
All right.
Ahh... What the hell...
As if we weren't busy enough already,
- what wretched fool set up...
- I did.
Say what?
Here's the summon notice.
And the order of the day
is Jeongshik's succession.
What are you prattling about?
I'm a major shareholder myself.
So I have every right to get
involved in company matters.
Do you even know in what
kind of situation we are?
This is no time to be setting
up any shareholders' meeting.
Rumors about Jeongyeon's health concerns
have spread among shareholders.
What?
I beat the board of directors to it,
so find a solution before they bring it up.
A solution?!
Do I have to spell it out?
Proclaim Jeongshik as your heir
and curb their worries.
With Jeongyeon in that state,
do we really need to go that far?
That's exactly what I'd like to ask you.
Did you really need to
force me into this situation?
Doesn't feel like something
you'd come up with...
So who's behind it?
- Who sent you here...
- You...
have always looked
down on me, haven't you?
But did all this success get
to your head enough to forget...
that I was the very pillar
which made it possible?
Look, Namsuk.
Don't treat me like a fool.
I won't spend the rest of my days
playing the kind and devoted wife.
That brat, really...
How did it go?
The rumors were true.
What?!
That young lady, Hwang Jeongyeon,
is currently hospitalized for aphasia.
A guest is looking for you, Ma'am.
Tell him she's not in.
It was some young lady...
Wait.
A young lady?
Yes. The daughter
of Manbo Construction's...
It's been a long time.
You remember me, right?
Have a seat.
I never imagined you owned
so many of our company's shares.
I heard you were hospitalized?!
So that's the rumor that's
spreading among shareholders.
As you can see, I'm perfectly fine.
I'd like to order something
to drink, will you join me?
You'll come again, right?
Of course! How can I go on
without seeing my Lola?
- You even remember my name!
- Of course. See you.
See you.
See you soon. Bye Bye!
See you...
Hey... Yeom Gyeongja!
What? "Lola?!"
Is this your "shoe factory?"
Who are you again?
- Waiter! A guest here is acting...
- Stop there!
- You're dead!
- Oppa!
Oppa... Let go...
Know how much this cost?
I've heard about the
shareholders' meeting.
Seems like proclaiming
the company heir is at stake.
I'll be honest with you.
My mother...
No...
My stepmother is trying to
position her son as the heir.
Didn't the chairman have you in mind?
While I was hospitalized,
my stepmother won over many shareholders.
And I can't guarantee that my father
will necessarily support me.
I really need your help in this.
I'd like you to support me.
And what would I gain by doing that?
Nothing in life is ever free.
So you'll have to convince me
to offer you my support.
May I ask why you invested
in Manbo Construction?
- That is obviously because...
- If you did it with the company's future in mind,
there is no way you wouldn't
acknowledge what I represent.
And that's because I'm
Manbo Construction's future.
This is the business part of it.
Is there any other aspect
that is not business-related?
I will never let anyone take
this company away from me.
Is that clear?
The future chairman of Manbo Construction
is kneeling before a mere shareholder.
This action has no precedent,
but it will also never repeat itself.
Are you implying that you will
consider me as a lifelong associate?
I prefer the term "family."
It's what has meant the most
to me ever since my childhood.
Including yourself, all the
shareholders who will support me...
will be considered family.
And I believe that is only natural.
Please, get up.
I have no use for things like "family."
All I need from you is to repay
my support with higher dividends.
I will vouch for you at
this shareholders' meeting.
But my support
alone won't turn the tide.
Changing all those shareholders'
minds in the little time you have left...
is only up to you.
I will make sure that happens.
I will succeed.
I'll never lose out to the people
responsible for Gangmo's death.
Minwoo.
They'll probably promote me
to president, this time?
Then, I'll make you
Director of Planning.
Forget it.
Ehh... Hey.
What are friends for?
What's that?
About the road construction?
You're not even running that
project, why waste time on it?
Let's just go out for drinks.
If this project ends up failing,
do you know how it will
affect this year's balance?
Let's hear it.
If you want to become president,
first show some interest in this company.
Hey... With you dealing with it,
why should I bother?
But, Minwoo.
You didn't hear from that
country chick again, did you?
That's girls for you, these days.
When in need they act as
if you're the second coming,
but look at what happens
after withdrawing that lawsuit.
Listen.
Do you have any gum?
Gum?!
Here.
That shows you women can't be trusted.
Need to send them packing
once you've had your fun.
I'll let you work.
You don't have a clue, do you?
When you feel down, nothing beats chewing
gum while riding the bus around town.
I said chew it.
The bus is always half-empty
around this time.
I won't ask you any tickets,
so come anytime.
Don't feel burdened.
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
she's quite ungrateful.
I withdraw the lawsuit, and
suddenly she's nowhere to be seen?!
Here... Come on out. Quick!
Here... Quick.
Thank you.
Everything clear. All right!
Yes?
Yes, that'd be me.
How did it go?
What?
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
What is the matter?
They said they're
releasing my brother Gangmo.
That's great to hear.
Then, you're finally
going to live together now?
Wait... I shouldn't
just keep this to myself.
Seonbaenim...
Wouldn't Miju be at work?
Ahh... You're right...
Let's go out for a drink, instead.
That's exactly what you're
in the mood for, isn't it?
Right, Chanseong.
Let's go out for drinks.
I'm so glad.
Driver.
I found a coin here...
Chief!
What are you doing here?
So, what,
just because I withdrew the lawsuit,
you have no more reason to meet me?
I'm sorry...
These days I'm busy practicing singing.
I couldn't be bothered to tell you,
but you're the one who promised
I'd get a lunchbox every day.
I'll bring you one tomorrow.
But, did you come all
the way here just for that?
Uh?
Looks like I really made you angry.
Seeing how you came this far.
What I hate most are people
who don't keep their word.
I'll bring you kimbap tomorrow,
so don't be angry.
All right?
Why are you staring at me that way?
Is there something on my face?
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Want to eat dinner with me?
But, Chief... I have
no money to buy dinner...
I'll treat you.
Who asked you to pay?
After all you've done for me,
I'd feel sorry letting you pay.
But why are you buying me dinner?
I have no idea, either.
Don't ask that and just come out.
Wait just a moment.
I'll go bring these in
and will be right back.
It's today's total.
Hey...
Come here.
What is it?
Is this all you could make today?
You pocketed some, didn't you?
What?!
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Show me your pockets.
Aigoo, look at this little brat...
What do you call these?
Why were these in my pockets?
Raise your hands and turn around.
Before I call the police, do it!
You little...
Ohh Ohh...
What do I have to see...
Don't turn.
Look straight.
Don't move a finger and just stay put.
Stay put, are we clear?
So we're clear...
What are you trying to do?
- Just stay put...
- Don't!
- I said don't move!
- I didn't pocket anything!
- Don't do this, please!
- Should I just call the police?
You little slut...
I'm innocent.
I didn't steal anything!
Just stay put...
You little...
Chief...
And you are?
Please stop, Chief!
You'll kill him... Stop!
You scumbag...
Thank you, Chief.
For rescuing me.
If it weren't for you, I'd...
Chief.
Thank God.
Nothing happened.
My Miju's a little late?!
Big Oppa...
When did you get here?
Thought I'd grow old waiting for you.
Miju.
You have time tomorrow?
I'll have plenty of time from now on.
I quit my job at the bus company.
Really?
That's really good to hear.
But, why are you asking?
Tomorrow...
Gangmo is coming out!
Really?
Sure... I told you, didn't I?
That I'd soon get him out of there.
Oppa!
We'll leave early in the morning,
so let's go to sleep.
Now we can all live together?
Sure.
Now we won't have to separate again.
Oppa... This feels like a dream.
From now on, I'll make
you dream every day.
Oppa...
Oppa, how do I look?
Did I put on too much make-up?
You look pretty.
Why? Wanted to look
pretty for your brother?
Of course!
How long has it been?!
It's him!
Oppa!
Miju.
Gangmo Oppa!
Oppa...
Hyung.
- Miju, have this.
- Miju, eat some.
Which one are you going to choose?
If you don't choose mine,
I'm not eating.
It's not even cooked well,
just eat mine.
Nah... Nah...
That's all burned.
- What are you saying?
- Here, eat it.
It's so good.
I knew such a happy day would come.
Reminds me of when we were little.
Was it Mom's birthday?
I told them I wanted pork ribs,
and Dad ordered boiled rice.
I remember.
I joked with Dad,
telling him he was a cheapskate.
To save and buy land in Gangnam,
Dad had no money to spend.
If only we hadn't lost those land deeds,
we'd have land and be rich by now.
But we have a lot of land?
Ahh... Right!
You bought some, right?
Hyung, let's finish this and get up.
- Let's go see our land.
- Right.
I'm so excited!
Hurry up and eat, Oppa.
I can't wait to see it.
Out of this huge place,
what is our land?
How far do you think it stretches?
Does our land end here?
No. Go farther ahead.
Is it here?
No. You must continue.
Then, here?
Miju!
Turn around and look!
How far can you see?
I can't see where it ends.
All the land your eyes can see is ours!
Ehh... Liar!
He's right, Miju!
That's our land!
Tell Jeongyeon.
That Lee Gangmo...
was ruthless enough to
choose those mudflats over her.
Forget that woman.
Big Oppa!
Little Oppa!
Hurry up and come!
Quick!
Gangmo...
Hyung!
Seongmo Oppa! Gangmo Oppa!
A construction company?
Yeah.
I plan to start by building
roads in the provinces.
Until your sentence is over,
you won't be able to reclaim your name.
You must keep hiding and
using that alias, James Lee.
I already have a plan.
Once the price of this land goes up,
I'll start fighting with
Manbo Construction for real.
In preparation for that day,
we must build our foundations
through road construction.
It's all the money
I saved over the years.
You use it.
Hyung...
You'll have plenty
of expenses from now on.
You'll have to find yourself
a place to live as well.
Use this to get started.
Thanks, Hyung.
Thanks for what?
You can't avenge our father
all by yourself.
While you take care of Hwang Taeseop,
I will bring forth
Jo Pilyeon's destruction.
If you need anything,
don't hesitate to ask me.
If you and I join forces,
there is nothing
that can scare us off.
Did you look into
those mudflats in Gaepo?
I did try through my
contacts in the States,
but there was no way
to find the owner.
Must we really lose that goldmine
without being able to do a thing?
There is still time until the
development plan is announced.
James Lee, you said?
Yes.
First I'll have to win the elections,
and then get my hands on that land.
The boss of the
Maljukgeori gang contacted us.
When is it?
It's set for tonight.
What are you planning to do?
*"the fox borrows the tiger's roar"
Ever heard of that
"hogahowi*" saying?
When what you lack is power,
then you'll have to ask
a tiger for assistance.
Take this money,
and do us a favor.
If you want me to betray Min Honggi...
- Forget about it.
- Isn't power what you're after, anyway?
- So?
- Min Honggi,
compared to Candidate Jo Pilyeon,
can't hold a candle.
I'll just go next door
and have a drink.
I brought him.
Why, did you have
another guest other than me?
Come on in.
Sit.
Let's start with some introductions.
Over here is my army mate, not to
mention the ANSP Chief of Support.
Who is this man?
He's a gang boss with
seven prior convictions.
A rat bastard wagging
his tail under Min Honggi.
Why bring street thugs here...
I used this back in my KCIA days.
Took a liking to it,
so I couldn't give it back.
It only has a few bullets left.
What's wrong with you?
If I get rid of him in front of you,
you could easily cover it up.
You really!
I get a little trigger-happy when I
see scummy thugs like you prance around.
Human trash oppressing the weak and
getting on all fours with the strong.
What's wrong with you?
If only I wasn't confident I could win
these elections, you'd be dead already.
However, I will win them at all cost.
But don't feel too relieved.
Once I become a congressman,
I'll take human trash like you
off my area's streets right away.
Is that clear?
Whether I win or lose those elections,
you're still a dead man.
Get the hell out of my sight.
What did you subject me to
this pathetic spectacle for?
Two big ones for you.
Once the elections are over,
three more will come your way.
Should be enough to "borrow
your roar," don't you think?
Your temper still hasn't
died quite yet, I see.
Where have you been?
I've been waiting for you.
We never prepared
any memorial for them.
Now that we're all back together,
we need to honor them.
Miju...
Father.
Mother.
You've felt sad all
these years, haven't you?
After all this time...
living away from each other,
we only now got together.
Mom...
Dad...
You must have been hungry,
all this time?
You suffered so much
even while alive...
Now that we could repay you
for all you did...
Forgive me.
It's all my fault, Father.
Forgive me, Father...
It's all because of me, Mother.
I'm sorry...
I miss you both...
I miss you so much.
Be our witness.
All those who brought death upon you,
those who subjected
us to so much suffering,
will never be forgiven.
You just wait.
I will avenge you,
and then succeed.
You said Nam Youngchul, right?
It's all the info I could find.
Right...
You know a man called Baekpa?
Baekpa?!
That lending kingpin from Myeong-Dong?
Yeah...
I need his help to get things started.
Go for another private lender.
I can introduce you to one,
if you want.
I might need the money,
but I also need people like him.
If things go wrong,
he could ruin you.
Anyhow, find out
what you can about him.
His business style,
his eating habits,
hobbies, everything.
You haven't heard about
Manbo Construction, right?
Seems like things are a bit chaotic
over there, because of the heir issue.
Jeongyeon.
There soon will be a
shareholders' meeting.
You must recover before then.
Listen to me.
You must start speaking, understand?
I'm so disheartened,
it's driving me crazy.
I buy used newspapers!
Here! I buy broken radios
and used newspapers!
Used news...
The hell is this?
What's with the car...
Seems a little too early
to sell it off?!
And you said you made it big outside.
I see you run your own business?!
Oh my! Who's this?
No. 534?!
Red hunt!
Eat this... this... this!
See how I grace your walls, you...
Red! Hunt!
Here you go, you pricks.
It's coming.
Congrats on your release.
What son of a
motherless cunt said that?
Ever seen me get...
G...Gangmo!
Gangmo!
There is a way to
reduce construction costs.
And what is that?
Instead of using sand and gravel,
by taking advantage of
that land's existing mud.
You won't use sand and gravel?!
If you do that,
the ground will be too weak,
and will collapse even with
asphalt on it, you fool.
Remember when we used calcium
chloride to tighten the concrete?
If we could only find how
to tighten up that mud,
then it's actually feasible.
Wow... I've always thought that,
but you really are smart.
Isn't that right?
But why did you take damaged
goods along for the ride?
What... Take what?
Who are you calling damaged goods?
Aigoo...
Gangmo, listen.
Do you have enough
money to get started?
I'll have to start finding it.
A customer is looking for you, Sir.
Who?
I've never seen him before.
Seemed like a businessman.
Tell him to come in.
If you will.
Nice to meet you.
Have a seat.
So, what brings you here?
Let's start with the introductions.
My name is James Lee.
James... Lee?!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
It feels so great to
have you by my side.
For the time being,
we'll have to live apart.
I see selling drinks can
make you quite the sum?!
Why don't you get to the point?
I want you to support
Jeongshik as the company heir.
The woman who gave birth to
Jeongyeon was just a bar girl.
I hear someone from within
the ANSP was helping Min Honggi.
And who is that?
Find that out.
From now on in, you stick to Seongmo.
The only way to fight with a huge
player like Manbo Construction...
is by developing a new technology.
Did you develop that new technology?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com