Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 32 -
You were one step
too late, Lee Gangmo.
Jeongyeon asked me to stop you
from obtaining that construction permit.
Get on your knees and
start begging me to save you.
Then, I might even be
inclined to vouch for you.
Let's just say you'll exchange your
pride for Hangang Construction's future.
How about it?
Isn't it worth a second thought?
You never know
when I might change my mind.
Anyone running a business should
be aware that chances like this...
don't come knocking
on your door too often.
So hurry up and get on your knees.
Beg me to save you.
Since we're here,
I'll let you in on something.
You will one day
be forced to kneel before me...
and beg for mercy.
Fine.
We'll see how long that
arrogance of yours can last.
If he had gotten on his knees,
would you have given him your approval?
It was already all said and done
before he even got here.
Hangang Construction will be
assigned the Gaepo apartment project.
So are you saying that you had
already given him your approval?
Back in the can, I had the chance
to read a few history books.
*Yiyi Zhiyi: From San Guo Zhi, "Fight off the
barbarians (enemies) using other barbarians"
Heard of that maxim, Yiyi Jeyi*?
Meaning that you'll use Hangang Construction
to fight off Manbo Construction?
We'll use Lee Gangmo to drive
Hwang Jeongyeon out of the picture.
And in the meantime,
Minwoo will use that opportunity
to gain control of the company.
That's how the tide is
turned in power struggles.
You're really brilliant.
Everything has its due course.
Hangang Construction is still
nothing but a blip on our radar.
Once Minwoo gets his hands
on Manbo Construction,
we can always send them
back where they came from.
Yiyi Jeyi...
Jo Minwoo striking
Hwang Jeongyeon would work, too.
And then, Jo Pilyeon,
your turn will come.
This could come back
to haunt us anytime.
We can't allow things
to stay as they are.
Mom...
Again with that bottle?
Did you look into
the Royal Club's owner?
I hired some private
investigators to dig into her.
So what is she all about?
What's her relationship with your father?
You really...
That temper of yours.
Couldn't find that much about her past.
By any chance, ever heard of Baekpa?
Baekpa?
From Myeongdong's
private-lending market?
Yeah.
She's that old man's adopted daughter.
What?
She's Baekpa's adopted daughter?!
Yeah.
Looks like if her old man goes,
she might inherit his business.
So bank directors and company CEOs
are all groveling at her feet.
Looks like you barked up the wrong tree.
You never know when I might need her help,
once I inherit the company.
Ahh... Enough, shut your mouth.
That's that.
Go get some men.
For what?
So we can get your father
out of there tonight.
Uh?!
What is this?
Where are you trying
to take the chairman?
Are you abducting him?
Will you shut that trap?
Ma'am!
I said keep your mouth shut.
There's no time!
Hurry up and take him out!
- Yes!
- What are you doing?
Chairman! Chairman!
Where are you taking that patient?
To another hospital.
Which one?
None of your business.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Here's your soup.
So what on earth is wrong with Minwoo?
Who said anything is wrong?
He just said he's busy at work,
so he wanted to go live a little closer.
Honey.
Just close an eye.
It's about time he moved out.
He's got a woman, all right.
What?
What kind of woman is she?
I suggest you tell me
before I have to find out by myself.
Ahh... Of all the
women he could choose...
Honey, I'll deal with
them personally, so...
Is he out of his mind, or what?
Honey...
Is this the time to be losing
himself in romantic shenanigans?
Honey, you don't need
to worry about it.
Just leave it to me,
and I'll take care of her.
Where did Minwoo move to?
Director Hwang is
urgently looking for you.
What is the matter?
Hangang Construction was
given a construction permit.
We're discussing a counterplan.
Go meet the director.
I have an appointment.
What?
Director Hwang seems to be
doing perfectly fine without me.
So tell her to handle this by herself.
Chief...
Chief!
I'm only asking you to tell me based on
which standards that permit was given.
Hello?
How about Chief Jo?
Saying he had an appointment, he left.
You may leave.
This is what top executives
drink at luxurious clubs these days,
it's called "bomb drink."
Bomb drink?!
So, what, if you drink that,
your gut explodes?
Wow... There's nothing our Gyeongja
doesn't know or can't do!
Here... This is for Sotae Oppa.
- Youngchul Oppa's.
- Thanks.
And the president's...
Here's yours.
Here, I'll make a toast to
celebrate all your efforts.
To our Hangang Construction's
apartment project!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
One-shot!
Dad.
So your father is hopping from
place to place for your own sake,
and you prance around
dating in all leisure.
I'll keep this short and sweet.
Dump that girl
you're meeting right now.
Dad...
If you can't get rid of her, I will.
But then if something happens to her,
don't try to hold me responsible.
Dad!
If you ever lay a finger on her,
I will die right under your watch.
What?
Die?!
Yes...
I'll kill myself!
Without Miju,
my life would be meaningless anyway.
So you'll kill yourself?!
I made you!
If anyone can decide
when you die, I'm the one!
You'll die?!
You dare say that in
your father's presence?
Who the hell is that wench?
- Die!!
- Please, stop!
Stop it, Sir!
This time...
I'm not going to give up.
Minwoo!
I'll never give Miju up!!
You little bastard!
Die!
You have three days.
If you really can't
wrap things up with that wench,
find something that will convince me.
If you fail to do so,
you won't be the only one I kill.
Minwoo!
Minwoo...
Wake up...
Open your eyes...
I beg you, open your eyes...
Stop crying.
I'm all right...
Who's all right?
Look at all this blood.
I said don't cry.
It's late, so just go.
With you in this state,
how can I just go?
So, what, you'll spend the night here?
I need to make you
breakfast in the morning...
Don't you worry about me.
You're the one who's hurting...
Miju!
Miju, it's me.
Minwoo.
Are you sleeping?
Five minutes...
No.
Just one.
Seeing you go through all that...
because of someone
as insignificant as me...
Stop it.
Thanks to you,
I found happiness for
the first time in my life.
I'll never let you go.
So don't even dream about leaving me.
Minwoo...
To make you mine,
there's nothing I can't do.
Miju.
I came by last night.
Did you sleep at a friend's?
You received an invitation
from Hangang Construction.
I guess they're having
an official launch party.
Chief Moon.
Here.
Isn't that the Songpa area?
That is exactly where
we'll build our apartments, Songpa.
But land prices have already gone up,
so we'd be forced to incur
heavy expenses all on our own.
Let's start by buying land there.
I will inform our
shareholders afterwards.
But... Director.
Don't you know the reason why
we must build apartments there?
It's to lure Gaepo buyers
into choosing us instead.
All right.
When is Hangang Construction's
launch party, again?
This evening.
Make sure that all those who
received invitations participate.
Are you going to go as well?
The real war against Hangang
Construction is about to begin.
Can't let them beat us
right off the bat, can we?
- Hangang Construction
Apartment Project Launch Ceremony -
I extend my sincerest gratitude
to all those who joined us,
to officially celebrate our
Hangang Construction's launch.
We'll pay back
your care and affection...
by building strong
and long-lasting apartments.
Introduce yourself, will you?
- He's one of Hangang Construction's directors.
- Director!
Not to mention my daughter.
We've been raising the president
ever since he was little.
Congratulations, President Lee.
Thank you.
You really should be thankful to me.
If it weren't for me, this event
would have been impossible.
"What did he really want to gain?"
I kept asking myself.
So, did you find any answers?
Manbo Construction.
Since taking down Chairman Hwang
must have been part of the same scheme.
Go around throwing
groundless accusations like that,
and you might get hurt.
And I bet you put us and Manbo
Construction against each other...
for the very same reason.
It seems you still don't
realize who you're talking to.
Wise men never
blow their own trumpets.
You open a little rathole
in a basement,
and the delusions of grandeur
are already getting to your head?
You were prancing around talking
about playing it fair and square,
but seems like our President Lee
is already feeling scared?!
One day,
you will dearly regret
your decision to help me.
Because things
will not go as you wish.
Feel free to act like
a big shot all you want,
but I can still crush you
with these hands of mine.
If you'll excuse me,
I'll have to get going.
I wish you a safe return, Sir.
Hey... Hey, look...
Hwang Jeongshik!
Wow... Lee Gangmo!
You sure turned your fortunes around?!
Congratulations.
Aren't you going to shake my hand?
You were the one who invited me,
but it feels like I'm crashing this party?!
Thank you for coming.
I hope you'll enjoy the party.
You will come to our launch party
for the Songpa apartments, right?
We decided to build right next
to your apartments in Gaepo.
Guess we'll be forced to fight
each other to lure in buyers?
All those buyers...
will desert any sale you try to open.
Before you try to take us down,
I suggest you worry about
protecting your own company.
Minwoo.
I'd like to go home now,
can you drive me there?
Never imagined even I
would get an invitation.
I hope you still don't
bear ill will against me?
It's already all in the past.
I didn't want to come, to be honest.
But I thought I'd take a look and see...
how big our house servant
managed to make it.
Thanks.
Glad you came.
Come to my office, one of these days.
I'll treat you.
What the hell?
Why did you lock the door?
You little...
You taught me a very precious lesson.
That always silently enduring things...
is what only retards do.
You little bastard...
Gangmo... I'm sorry...
Please, don't...
Don't do it..
I'm sorry! Gangmo...
Just buy it and enough with
the prattling, you cheapskate.
Ahh... What do you take me for?
Being cheap is your forte.
- As if you didn't know...
- You sorry-ass little...
Is it locked?
Looks like they've got some
business going on inside.
Why, need to use the men's room?
The cleaning lady just made
a mess, so better not bother.
Use the other room.
I said go elsewhere!
What are you staring at?
My... This is serious, all right.
That'll do it.
I might not forgive you,
but let's just pretend we're even.
For getting away with murder like this,
you should consider yourself lucky.
Right?
Wipe the blood.
You just wait, Lee Gangmo.
When I become chairman
of Manbo Construction,
I'll trample on you
every step of the way.
Ahh... Here is President Lee.
Sorry for making you wait.
I was having a word with a guest,
so I'm a little late.
Is there anything else you need?
Yes.
I hope you didn't misunderstand me.
Misunderstand?!
Even if I hurt your feelings,
can't help it.
It was for the company's sake.
I see you're still looking down on me.
Just a word of warning.
You and Lee Gangmo weren't
the only ones who changed.
I might have danced to your tune today,
but I have no intention of getting
involved in your little love quarrels.
Next time you try
to do anything like that,
I won't just play along.
Love quarrels?!
Chief Moon?
Sorry for calling you at this hour.
It's all right.
But, what do I owe...
Aren't you tired of being just
a department chief at your age?
Excuse me?
- Why... are you suddenly...
- I will give you a chance...
to finally make it big once and for all.
We'll discuss details tomorrow at work.
Lee Gangmo, Hwang Jeongyeon...
So Jo Minwoo is nothing to you?
You just wait...
The last laugh in this fight...
will not be yours, but mine.
I now have a reason
not to let you defeat me.
You have three days.
If you really can't
wrap things up with that wench,
find something that will convince me.
If you fail to do so,
you won't be the only one I kill.
If only for Miju's sake,
I'll never lose to you.
Oppa...
Miju.
What could this... be?!
Wow? A cassette player?
I hear you did well at the test.
Gift from Oppa!
Big Oppa, you rock!
I really wanted one of these...
- Really?
- Yeah.
How does this work...
What is that ring?
Why are you hiding it?
Give me your hand.
Come on.
Wow... Looks great?!
It... It's a fake.
It's glass.
Wanna tell me where you
spent the night last time?
Uh? When?
That night.
I waited for you all night,
and then left in the morning.
At a friend's.
Friend who?
Big Oppa...
I can't tell anyone
about you yet, right?
Why, is there someone
you'd like to tell?
Yeah.
- Actually...
- Miju.
No matter how close you might be,
you still need to keep it secret.
Can't you at least tell me
why I should keep doing that?
It's because of things
Gangmo and I have planned.
You trust me, right?
All right, Oppa.
Let's listen to something.
Here...
What are you doing?
Clap your hands.
"Just a look and my heart throbs."
"Just a thought and my heart throbs."
"Ignore the blooming first love
of an innocent nineteen-year-old."
"So that nobody
in the world will know,"
Our Miju is great!
"And he will remain hidden
at the bottom of my heart."
Oppa...
You're messing up all the beats.
Why...
Didn't I, like, get it right?
Do it right, will you?
Where did you take my father to?
None of your business.
What is it that you're scheming?
Based on his testament,
should your father die,
Jeongshik will inherit
his company shares.
So you did that just because you
feared I would get his testament changed?
Since you're more than capable of that.
So you're not going to let me
meet him until he dies?
Why, can't I?
You people will be punished for this.
Punished?
And who would be punishing us?
I'm afraid that the day
that testament comes into play,
you'll be the one who is punished.
For biting the hand
that fed and raised you.
You're telling me you still
haven't fixed that testament?
It'll soon be complete.
And how "soon" will that be?
I'll call you the moment it's ready.
You know that we don't
have a minute to waste, right?
But, where is the chairman...
I thought I already told you
not to worry about the chairman?
Yes.
Anyhow, I'll be counting on you.
Do right as Madame Oh asked you.
Since as long as Lee Gangmo doesn't
inherit Chairman Hwang's fortune,
everything is fine with me.
All right.
But, about keeping this secret...
I'll take it to my grave,
so you don't need to worry.
Instead,
I'll only bother you once with a
little favor in the near future.
There's something strange at play.
There are no traces of Chairman Hwang,
and those two have been visiting that
lawyer even more frequently as of late.
Keep watching Oh Namsuk
and Hwang Jeongshik.
I'm sure they'll
go meet Chairman Hwang.
All right.
Gyeongok...
I think I'm being punished.
For abandoning you,
and...
for what I did to my friend.
Where are you now?
What are they doing to you?
You miss your family, don't you?
Have you given it a thought?
I'll put my future in your hands.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
You're in charge of the land we bought
around the residential area, right?
Yes.
Transfer it all under a namesake.
A name...sake?!
But it's under company name...
The only people aware of
that land besides us...
are the chairman,
Hwang Jeongyeon and Director Ju.
And they're in no position to be
worrying about that land now.
I'll do as you wish.
In due time, that land...
will all be turned into cash.
Make all preparations.
Yes, Chief.
I'll be counting on you
and will proceed as you wish.
You're my son, all right!
It's a perfect way to get
your hands on Manbo Construction.
Jeongshik will soon inherit the company.
Not Jeongyeon, but Jeongshik?
Jeongshik will be a
much better prey for you.
See, Minwoo?
They don't say "like father,
like son" for nothing.
Your plans and mine are
like a match made in heaven!
Ohh... Come on in.
Any good news to share with us?
We could hear you
laughing from outside.
Is that so?
He's come back to the
Minwoo we all knew.
Ahh... No!
He's come back even stronger.
So it seems like it's your
turn to hear my demands?!
I will marry that woman.
Fine.
I'll allow you two to date.
But you'll only get married when
all our plans come into fruition.
I'll also introduce her
to you before that.
That's natural!
Minwoo...
You were seeing someone?
Don't even start.
That lady completely
took his soul away.
Congrats.
Thanks, Hyung.
We can't not celebrate this
with a drink.
- Here... Let's all drink.
- Yes.
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
A sales war is about to begin.
If we want to defeat
Manbo Construction,
we must find out what our customers want,
and focus our publicity on that.
But, won't publicity cost us money?
Can we ever compete with
Manbo Construction's resources?
Whatever the case,
we must defeat them at all cost.
Money is the problem, all right.
Let's start by using
all that we have left.
I'll see what I can do
about finding ulterior funds.
Make sure our newspaper ads are shown
right alongside Hangang Construction's.
They also must be twice
the size of their ads.
But that'll cost us quite the amount?!
It's not like Hangang Construction
could ever compete with us.
- I don't see any...
- Erase any such indolence from your mind!
We're dealing with the same
product, clients and start date.
Don't you realize we were at war
from the very first moment?
From the smallest newspaper ad
to the final sales,
trample on every single piece of promotion
Hangang Construction comes up with.
Even if you have to
throw money at them,
you must show them what's the price
to pay for trying to challenge us.
Is that clear?
- Yes.
- Yes, we understand.
How's the situation at the site?
Going as planned.
Let's speed up the construction.
We must complete it before
Hangang Construction does.
Our ad is in the newspaper!
How is it?
Does it look good?
You're dying to see it, aren't you?
Better raise your expectations...
- Manbo Construction -
"Neither big nor small,
just the apartment you want."
Wait a moment...
Am I starting to get old here?
I really can't see it.
Where is ours?
This one is just Manbo Construction's.
It's over here.
Here.
We're screwed, all right.
When theirs is so huge,
who's going to look at ours?
It's the same for
every other newspaper.
We should have
just used some leaflets.
After spending all that money,
all we get is...
- Ohh... Reporter Yoon?
- Yes. How are you?
I asked around at every newspaper,
and it seems that Director
Hwang Jeongyeon asked to be put...
side by side with your ads
on every single one of them.
Why don't you forget newspaper ads,
and instead focus on radio and TV?
We're quickly running out of cash.
We must carve our niche with
a unique advertising campaign.
Do you have anything in mind?
Apartments for the working class.
The working class?!
It's exactly what I wanted to build
ever since I cut my teeth on this business.
Done the right way,
it could be quite a hit.
Hangang Construction is
planning a new marketing campaign.
I know.
It's about apartments
for the working class, right?
Let's change our concept
for radio and TV ads to that.
Manbo Construction's brand image...
has always been that of building
luxurious, top-of-the-line apartments.
Couldn't care less.
Don't you realize how
much money it'd take to...
redraw a campaign from scratch,
when production is already complete?
Chief Jo!
What are you, trying to lecture me?
If your superior tells you to change them,
stop arguing and just do it!
What on earth are
you trying to accomplish?
Is it just bringing down
Hangang Construction, or...
Bringing Lee Gangmo down
will lead us to success.
You still don't realize that?
Proceed as instructed right away.
I won't make you
wait for long, Lee Gangmo.
It won't take long.
Hwang Jeongyeon...
You will soon pay a very hefty price...
for looking down on me.
It's the testament revision.
Good job, Mister Kim.
Did you bring the
chairman's original testament?
Yes... Here it is.
I'll deal with this personally.
As you wish.
- If you'll excuse me...
- Yes.
Mom.
Then, am I really becoming
chairman of Manbo Construction?
That's right, my boy!
It's all over now.
Manbo Construction is yours!
You're the best!
But you can't tell anyone, yet.
Got it?
Ehh... What do you take me for?
But, listen...
What if Dad ends up recovering?
Don't you worry.
By the time he does,
you'll already be chairman.
Right...
I'll have to organize
a party with my friends.
Mom, I'll be right back!
Watch what you say.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
Get the car ready.
No, I'll be driving personally.
Oh Namsuk has finally made a move.
Stick to her until you
find out where she's going.
Honey.
I'm here.
Happy to see me?
- Testament -
Know what this is, right?
Your testament.
You thought that leaving
all your fortune to Gangmo,
Jeongyeon would end up
receiving all that, right?
But I'm afraid I
have no more use for this.
I fixed your testament.
Jeongshik will soon
replace you as chairman.
And as for your daughter Jeongyeon,
she'll just end up on the street.
Namsuk...
What is wrong with you?
Feel wronged, I bet?
Think I'm taking things too far?
But you'll resent me even more
for what I'm about to do.
You really think this is all my fault?
No... You're to blame.
Hwang Taeseop, you!
Why...
Why are you staring at me that way?
Did you hate me that much?
Fine, then.
I'll be content with
the life I've lived so far.
I'll just be thankful for that, and go.
Namsuk.
Don't look at me that way.
I'd rather see eyes
filled with resentment.
Curse at me...
Call me a shameless wench,
say one day I will be punished!
Die...
Don't ever think of surviving,
just die.
I found out.
Bribe one of the nurses there,
and keep an eye on him.
What are you planning to do?
You may leave.
If anything is going
to happen to Jeongyeon,
I must get him out of there.
And that's because...
he's my daughter's father.
Because from the very start,
he was mine.
Ohh... Stop!
Wait... Stop it!
Stop it.
What is this?
There's another one.
So you found these relics
at the construction site?
And not just all from the same place.
This area was once a Baekje fortress.
Cover it up.
What?
Just cover up the whole thing,
and go on with the construction.
But if the Cultural Heritage
Administration finds out...
I'll take full responsibility,
so tell your men to keep their mouths shut.
Yes.
As you wish.
Chief Moon.
Nobody in the company
must learn of this.
So you don't even plan
to report it to Director Hwang?
How did it go with
that land I told you about?
Ahh... Yes.
As you instructed me,
I transferred it under a namesake.
I think we might have
to rush with our plans.
Change it into cash.
All right, Chief.
As you can see,
Hangang Construction can't even
compete with our sales record.
Our aggressive marketing campaign
focusing on our brand name...
seems to be making a mark already.
If the situation continues,
we will triumph over Hangang
Construction by a wide margin.
Yes.
President Lee Gangmo?
I'm Hwang Jeongyeon.
Among the things
I've learned from my father...
was the logic behind power.
The fact the small
can never defeat the big.
You'll never defeat me.
The fight is not over yet.
My father also told me this.
That those who acknowledge defeat...
can be much scarier than
someone who never gives up.
You're still not up to the task.
Do you know that?
And all that your father
gained from such wisdom...
was collapsing in the end.
I admit it.
Every time I look at you,
I can barely contain my surprise.
You look like someone
ready to grow into a giant.
But...
what you most resemble...
is your father.
Your father always told me.
That he always ran into the dark
without an end in sight.
My father and I are different.
I pray that's true.
Hand Hangang Construction to me.
Leave the company to me,
and get out of this business.
On the condition you won't
interfere with management,
you'll be generously compensated.
Do you know what my dream is?
And you want to trample on that?
Because...
the sole fact that someone
like you shares my same dream...
is too hard to bear.
I'll be waiting for an answer.
Hope you'll reflect carefully.
Stature alone is not
what makes a giant.
Even the smallest things can defeat
seemingly insurmountable odds.
That's my "logic of power."
What did I tell you?
Didn't I tell you that
providence would be on our side?
That's enough to stop
the construction, right?
Hwang Jeongyeon ventured into
this Songpa apartment campaign...
solely because of Lee Gangmo.
If we manage to stop the construction,
it'll be the end for Hwang Jeongyeon.
Once the press is let in on this,
it will be game over.
I don't want to wait any longer.
Back in the day,
the situation forced me
to get rid of someone,
and I let Hwang Taeseop
get his hands dirty instead.
If you try to personally
bring Hwang Jeongyeon down,
you'll have to deal with the repercussions
even if you gain control of the company.
So you need someone to get
his hands dirty on his behalf?
Lee Gangmo is the man for the job.
Let Lee Gangmo bring forth
Hwang Jeongyeon's destruction.
Only then you will forever turn him
into Manbo Construction's enemy.
Yes.
It's me, Jo Minwoo.
You're having it quite hard
these days, aren't you?
I just wanted to let you in
on a precious bit of information.
Planning to sell trade secrets?
I know what you're scheming.
You want to defeat
Hwang Jeongyeon, don't you?
Yourself included.
You should be receiving a fax by now.
You'll have to go through with it
even if you don't want to.
If you want to survive.
I can't wait...
To see how you'll cause
Hwang Jeongyeon's downfall.
Jeongyeon...
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
What's that supposed to mean?
Your father has disappeared?!
You were the one who hid him
at that nursing home.
What did you do to him?
Seems like some higher-up might
be opposing the construction.
It can only be Lee Gangmo.
I'm actually suspecting someone else.
Tell me.
Did you fix his testament?
Did you?
Let's suppose I did.
What are you going to do about it?
What did you just say?
Miju... and Jo Minwoo?!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com