Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 6 ~
Hello?
It's me. Director Hwang.
Director?! Yeah, right...
So, do we have the results?
What?
You still need three days?
In your opinion,
what is the most likely result?
Is briquette ash worth looking into?
Well...
Until the results come out,
I couldn't really say with certainty.
I see.
Anyhow, I'll be waiting for good news.
Yes.
They sure enjoy
playing with people's nerves.
I can go now, right?
Wait a moment.
Run an errand for me.
Uh?!
I need to go to work.
It will only take a moment.
Forget it.
They're about to kick me
out of the tent, because of you.
What's the matter?
I'm here to meet Major Jo Pilyeon.
Do you have an appointment?
No.
I came on behalf of someone.
No civilians are allowed inside.
Wait.
I'll just go in a minute.
All I need is to convey something
to Major Jo Pilyeon.
Thanks.
Is this all I need to give him?
Yes.
Did you find out?
The file's name?
The name of the file where
that document is being kept.
K-19.
It's in the document storage, section F.
Is Hampton in his office now?
Yes.
From here on in,
only take care of laundry work.
You can't do anything that could
attract Hampton's suspicion.
Yes, Sir.
To prove our wish to bury the hatchet.
You're not going to grow
suspicions again, I hope?
I'll accept it gladly.
Considering the awkward position
this accident put us into,
how about we organize a concert
for our troops, to strengthen our ties?
Sounds like fun.
We will take care of organizing it, then.
Would this Friday be fine with you?
All right.
Then, I will see you at the concert.
This Friday's D-day.
It's the document storage, section F.
File name K-19.
The concert will distract them.
We will steal the document that day.
Yes, Sir.
Major.
A certain Hwang Taeseop sent this.
What kind of mess is he making?
Stop! Stop there!
You little runts...
Elders always come first,
you little runts.
Just wait.
It's ready.
Let's eat.
Is there any rice?
Can you really live off of
potatoes alone day and night?
Pay for the rice and then talk.
Even freeloaders have
the balls to complain...
What? Listen.
Who should you thank for
staying afloat all this time?
That tent of yours,
it's all on Manbo Construction's land.
You went belly up.
I'm still here alive and well,
who went belly up?
Do you know how many creditors are
prancing all over the place all day?
You runts!
Let me make myself perfectly clear.
If you want to continue
doing business there later,
you better treat me well now.
Are we square?
Yes!
Aren't you going to work?
Ahh... Little runt,
he's got guts for sure.
Just my luck...
Ahh... I've really had it with him.
Hey.
Give me another pair of socks,
if you still have one.
Take a look at this.
Aigoo!
Got a hole, again.
Been wearing these a few days,
and they already smell sour.
Give me a new pair.
Ohh... right.
What are you doing?
Ajeosshi.
Nothing here is free.
I'll write everything down to
the last penny, just so you know.
You nasty little runt...
You told the other kids to
keep their mouths shut, didn't you?
Don't worry.
Nobody can learn I'm hiding here.
Are we clear?
I said I got it.
Ahh!
Also,
if anything happens,
report back to me immediately.
All right?
It won't take long, you fool.
If I can only get
the results I'm expecting,
I'll get back on my feet.
I will.
You can try to hide Director Hwang
all you want, but nothing will change.
Didn't I tell you we don't
know where he is, either?
Tell him this when you see him.
That at tomorrow's
committee meeting at City Hall,
the Banpo landfill contract
will be transferred to us.
If Director Hwang participates,
he will be refunded all the money spent so far,
but should he fail to do so,
he will have to give that up as well.
To at least get back enough to go by,
shouldn't his family
show up at the meeting?
Seems like the director took
both the seal and the contract.
If this keeps up, we'll end up in ruins.
You know Manbo Construction's
director, right?
The moment Director Hwang
shows up, call me immediately.
I'll give you 20,000 won
for the trouble.
What?
2...20,000?!
I'm not the kind of man who would
deceive you, so give me a call.
Keep the change.
Sir.
What I was saying is...
Director Hwang...
If we see him, we'll give you a call.
All right, then.
Will be counting on you.
Have a nice day.
Have you heard? If we report
Director Hwang, we'll get 20,000 won!
So?
You fool. Is 20,000 won
your dog's middle name?
Unless you want to
break our partnership,
you better stay put.
He's nothing but a beggar now!
How much longer are you going
to keep feeding and sheltering him?
I said enough!
Is it because of that brat?
Director Hwang's daughter?
Wake up, will you?
Think she cares even the
slightest bit about you?
She's just...
I said enough, didn't I?
What's wrong with you?
Don't try anything funny,
or you'll pay for it.
Ahh... That blockhead.
What?
Hong Gipyo?
Yes. He said that if you
don't show up at the meeting,
your investment won't be reimbursed.
He's just bluffing.
Without me, he can't do a thing.
I already took care of that.
Hand me a few coins, will you?
What?
What for, again?
- Just give it to me.
- So you can drink it all away?
Keep talking back every
chance you get, will you?
Add it to my tab.
The major is waiting.
It's so hot...
As you asked, I pushed to
postpone the meeting a few days.
Thank you.
Actually, I tried
not to get to this point.
Did the results come out?
Yes... They said it will
take another few days.
So why didn't you listen to me, and...
Anyhow, do everything it takes
to keep your company afloat.
When you're back on your feet,
let's talk again.
If I can only save my company, then...
you won't ever order me
around like a mutt again.
Aww... Nice.
Tastes just right.
Hey.
The office is empty.
Dad...
You didn't die, right?
Where on earth are you?
Don't worry.
Your father is safe.
You know where he is, right?
You do, right?
Where is he? Where?
Don't know.
Here.
Get home with this.
What are you doing?
Think I'm a beggar or something?
You walked your way here.
I grabbed a taxi.
So you "grabbed a taxi,"
and your shoes are in that state?
No need for that money.
Since I won't go home
until my father shows up.
By 6, the library will close its doors.
Hide somewhere inside,
and once everyone has left,
infiltrate the document storage room.
Remember.
Section F, file name K-19.
Jo's guy showed up at the library.
As expected.
Well, Sir.
Time to go.
Show's about to begin.
Welcome.
The show just started.
Yeah, looks like the soldiers are
having a really good time here tonight.
Hope you'll enjoy it as well.
Thanks for putting this
special event on, Major Jo.
- Hey, I'm gonna go watch the show.
- Okay.
Thank you!
Where are you going?
I have a phone call,
from my family back in the States.
But I'll be right back.
Freeze!
Drop it!
You're under arrest for espionage.
This is not the document.
I fell asleep inside.
Is borrowing books from
the library considered espionage?
Where's Major Jo?
Sir, he left right after you.
Can't see the laundry boy anywhere.
Did you see the laundry boy?
Where did he go?
He left. He said he'd
run some errands for you.
Call his house, immediately!
He's the orderly of General Hampton.
Open the gates.
I don't even know what I'm doing.
Why did I get involved with Jo Pilyeon...
Let's just forget it.
He promised you'd be
discharged today, instead.
I can forget about
going to the States, now.
I'll search here,
so you check the living room.
I told you we shouldn't have done this.
Past that corner,
a taxi will be waiting for us.
I'll just take that,
and head back home in Daejeon, so...
Hyung!
Dammit...
I knew it... when I saw
my mother in my dreams.
Don't even say that.
I'm a doctor.
There's no hope.
Hyung... I'm not leaving without you.
Leave, now!
You need to find your family.
They'll bury me in the state
cemetery like my father, right?
Hyung...
Hyung!
What?
He got away?!
I want a thorough search of the area.
I want him found!
Major... there!
The document?
The doctor...
is dead.
Good job.
You saved me.
You saved this country.
I said the doctor is dead!
The doctor...
is dead!
And what a relief you aren't.
Everyone dies.
It's just a matter of how and when.
With this in our hands,
he didn't die in vain.
Let's meet again here tomorrow.
For the time being,
you'll live at my house.
You son of a bitch!
Bring him back.
Bring back my father as well...
And all the rest of them!
Bring them back!
Tomorrow we will act.
If we manage to complete this task,
I'll be accepted into the KCIA.
Do you realize what kind of
place we're dealing with?
It's a small country within our country.
The very core of this country's power.
Want to work with me there?
You're still too young to understand,
how having so much power
can change your life.
I have this country's top brass
backing me on this task.
Even if I fail,
nobody inside this country can kill me.
Be it the Americans or Hampton.
That's what power means.
I told you everything I had to say,
so you may go.
Is there anything you want to tell me?
It's a trap, again.
What?!
I just overheard what Hampton said.
What they're keeping in
the storage room is a fake.
The real one...
is inside Captain Michael's quarters.
Fine...
I'll follow you to the pits of hell.
I'll find that other man
responsible for my father's death,
and kill the both of you
with my own hands.
Student.
S-t-u-d-e...
n-t.
Student.
Ahh... Really...
Can't close a damned eye in here.
What are you doing?
Are you studying?
Just sleep.
What are you trying to accomplish?
Just go on shining shoes.
As if studying suited you...
What is he studying?
English.
Aigoo...
He sure doesn't give up...
Seems like nothing can bring him down.
Are you really not going home?
Why are you here?
I don't like bean jam pancakes.
You didn't even have dinner.
I've had so much to eat
I can't take it anymore.
Eat it or leave it, do as you wish.
Why are you lying there?
I won't find anywhere to
sleep under the bridge.
*Confucian tenet: After the age of seven,
men & women shouldn't even share the same room
Hey... Don't you know
about gender separation*?
Why would friends worry about gender?
Lee Gangmo.
Do you like me or something?
Why, you think you're that pretty?
I only like girls with a pretty face.
You little...
You... Get out! Leave!
Mommy!
Seems like it's a black-out.
Doesn't work?!
You can sleep without lights on, right?
I'll go.
Good night.
You said there's nowhere to sleep.
I'll be kind, for once.
Sleep here.
Am I seeing right?!
Why does she look so pretty?
Nah... No.
Must be the hunger.
It's that for sure.
Ajeosshi.
Get up, will you?
Wake up!
Why do I have to hear a kiddo like you
scream in my face at this hour?
Where did my money go?
What?
Where did all the money I put here go?!
And why are you asking me that?
Is there anyone else
who could have stolen it?
You little runt, point fingers
at innocent people, will you?!
You fool. Do I look like
I'd need your petty few pennies?
You'd be more than capable!
You little runt, I ought to just...
Treat me like a thief again,
and I'll just tear that trap...
Got it?
Leave!
Aww... I really can't stand him!
This is all because of you!
What's wrong with him?
Those runts stuffed themselves
enough not to leave a grain of rice?!
So you really didn't steal that money?
If I laid my hands
on that money, I'm your son.
Happy now?
Today the results will come out.
Whatever happens,
this is my last day here.
I'm so hungry I could die.
Go buy something to eat.
I won't steal your money.
It's just that I have to
go to the research center...
Lots of work to do.
Hello?
Daeryuk Construction's
Director Hong, right?
I found out where Director
Hwang Taeseop is staying.
Look... Look at this.
What's the occasion?
Even buying me broth.
You know that it's not free.
Everyone says I'm ruined,
but what if you can't
get your money back?
You're not going to get ruined.
And how do you know that?
Is there anything better
than briquette ash to harden soil?
You take over research, then.
Who are you?
Hong?!
And what are you doing here?
You're still the man
running Manbo Construction...
How could you subject people to this?
Follow me.
Everyone is waiting at City Hall.
Ajeosshi.
What are you doing? Let go!
Let go... I said let go!
You must put your seal
on those documents!
What are you waiting for?
Help him out.
Let... Let me go!
You fools... How dare you!
Let go! I said let go!
They took the director with them.
What?
What is that supposed to mean?
Come with me somewhere.
We have no time to waste, quick!
Where's my father?
Head to City Hall right away.
Go, and tell your father not to sign.
What are you saying?
I'll explain everything later.
Anyhow, tell him to just buy time.
Got it?
We have no time left,
let's go, Ajeosshi.
All right.
- Take Jeongyeon to City Hall.
- Yes.
We will soon begin the audit.
As not all the required
documents are ready,
we're forced to move the transfer
of Manbo Construction's Banpo lot...
to after the audit.
We can solve that right away!
I said let me go!
Let go!
Let me go.
I ought to...
I'm glad you came on time.
Here.
If you don't have your seal with you,
your fingerprint would do.
Go ahead.
I solved the landfill issue.
So you're telling me
you found enough sand?
Yes.
He's just lying.
With his company filing for bankruptcy,
what money could he have?
I found another material to use
instead of construction sand.
That makes no sense!
And what on earth are you going to use?
Go ahead and say it.
What is this replacement
material you're suggesting?
It's... briquette ash.
Briquette ash?!
Yes.
We can use the same briquette ash
you see piling up in every dump.
Briquette ash?!
Listen to that nonsense...
And Director Hwang Taeseop?
He was busy, so we came instead.
How about the results of your research?
Who are you, to ask me that?
I...
He was the one who brought up
the idea of using briquette ash.
You?!
Yes... I told the director.
So we can use it to fill that land, right?
Right?
You could fill land with whatever you want.
The issue is whether you can build over it.
If we can only get past this hurdle,
then we won't have to worry about
construction sand ever again.
Also, since we can even deal with
waste disposal at the same time,
how beneficial would this be
to the entire country?!
Listen, Director Hwang.
I can understand how
difficult your situation is,
but can an entrepreneur
sell his dignity for this?
Sell my dignity?!
I mean, what if you build
housing over briquette ash,
and then the whole thing collapses?
How are you going to deal with
all those casualties?
That is why I told you the result of
that research will be published today!
I think it would be foolish
to go on with this farce.
Have him sign.
By now, the results should be out.
If it truly has no efficacy,
then I'll give everything up,
and sign that document.
All the people gathered here
have busy schedules.
Make some sense, will you?
I can find out with a single phone call.
Go ahead, then.
Hello?
It's the Geological
Research Center, right?
Is the chief in?
What?
He's not?
Wait, I...
I'm in a little bit of a rush here.
If you could only tell me where he is...
Listen!
Someone's life depends on this!
Hello?
He...Hello...
You disappoint me.
I didn't think you'd be
capable of stooping so low.
Just a little...
If you give me just a little more time...
Sign.
Get off of me!
You fools, let go!
Let go!
You little fools...
It hurts! Let go!
Dad!
What are you doing?
What did he ever do wrong?
Jeongyeon?!
What are you doing here?
Dad...
Stop embarrassing yourself,
and just sign that document.
Don't sign it.
He said to endure at all cost.
Who?
Gangmo.
Gangmo?!
The shoeshine boy?
Said to buy time, one way or another.
He did?
There!
Listen to me.
Just an hour.
Wait just one more hour.
I'll get sick,
can't we go a little slower?
No way.
Go faster, faster!
What am I supposed to do, fly there?
It is time.
We can no longer postpone this.
Dad...
Director...
Don't worry about that Banpo lot.
We'll succeed on your behalf as well.
Let's just go.
The results are out.
Chief.
How did it go?
I'm the chief researcher at
the Geological Research Center.
May I borrow the pedestal a moment?
Yes, go ahead.
A few days ago, Director Hwang,
who is here with us,
commissioned a research on whether
briquette ash could be used as landfill.
Since all the construction
committee is present today,
I will take this opportunity
to announce the results to everyone.
Results of our experiments...
indicate that,
compared to sand and gravel,
briquette ash's moisture
absorption rate is remarkably high.
Not to mention in terms of
viscosity and intensity as well.
Briquette ash...
is an excellent alternative
to construction sand.
Then, we no longer need
to worry about sand.
It's done, we're all safe now!
Thank you, Director Hwang.
This is all thanks to you.
He already signed this document.
So our Daeryuk Construction will be
assigned the Banpo lot as expected.
How can you say that?
It clearly has to remain in
Manbo Construction's hands!
Contracts are contracts.
Isn't that right, Commissioner?
What does that
piece of paper matter anyway?
Or just sue him, Director Hwang.
We will all support you,
and testify in court.
- Indeed!
- We will help you in court!
Commissioner Han.
What are you doing?
I'm afraid you'll have to compromise
on this matter, Director Hong.
What?
We have now solved the sand issue,
so we truly owe you a lot.
You may complete the
landfill project in Banpo.
My own home feels unfamiliar...
Honey!
Honey!!
- Honey...
- Daddy.
Aigoo... What is this?
What did you have to go through
to end up in this state?
- Ohh Ohh... Listen to you...
- Let's go inside.
I've prepared your favorite,
beef rib stew.
What are you waiting for?
Come on in.
Yes...
- Come in.
- What is this little beggar doing here?
Ehh... You really...
Come on, follow me.
Come on.
Hey!
Where are you going
without taking a bath?
Here.
Go ahead and eat.
Why are you drinking again?
Have something to eat first.
Aigoo... And I asked him
to get a housemaid...
As if he was some servant,
why bring a boy?!
Enough with that.
I have no intention of
living here as your servant.
Start with settling your tab.
How much is it?
A little over three thousand won.
And if you consider that I
couldn't work because of you,
should make it five thousand
with interests.
No can do.
What?
Dad...
Even the worst of all loan sharks...
wouldn't add so much interest
in a matter of days, you fool.
- Still...
- Instead.
Go to school.
What?
I'll send you to middle school,
so live here with us and study.
Honey!
Are you out of your mind?
It's not like he's your son,
why should we look after him?
Just give him whatever he's asking.
Don't question my decisions.
Honey!
Ohh Ohh! You brat...
Forget it.
I'll earn money for school on my own.
Don't question me, either.
Eat your dinner,
pack your bags and come live here.
Let's go in.
Everyone is waiting for you.
Fella looks quite fierce?!
Who's translating?
He's quite fluent in Korean.
Ohh, is that so?
Hampton.
I'm General Hampton.
I'm Congressman Oh Byeongtak
of the Republican Party.
Well, I trust we can
spare the introductions,
so let's get straight to the point.
Concerning that secret document
we just acquired.
It's quite the shocking material?!
The reality of that Gulf of Tonkin incident
you used to justify deployment in Vietnam...
seems to be a little different
from what was reported by the press?!
That's enough.
Needless to say,
should the world press learn of this,
the American government would be on
the receiving end of severe criticism.
I said that's quite enough!
And when they learn someone distorted
the truth about this Vietnam war,
the Nixon government will
certainly not spare you.
What is it that you want from me?
There must be a reason
why you're doing this to me.
Give us the namesake account list
in your brigade's possesion.
The South Seoul redevelopment plan
is a project our government...
is pouring its heart and soul into.
Whether we buy land under namesakes or not,
it's none of your business.
If you plan to use that list to create
difficulties for us at the upcoming elections,
you better give up, is that clear?
You give me the document,
and I'll give you the list.
Ahh... That's not how
you deal with people.
You'll get it back once
the elections are over.
All you need to do is
keeping quiet until then.
Fine.
Just make sure that no one
knows about this document.
If we're done talking,
you'll probably be busy...
So I won't rob any more of your time.
Good job.
Have a drink.
Meet the KCIA director tomorrow.
He'll have a position ready for you.
*deferential for older colleague
Thank you, Seonbaenim*.
Changing the briquettes when it's needed,
mopping the yard and throwing
away the trash is your job.
Remember to lock the door
before you go to sleep.
You'll have to work hard,
if you want to earn your keep.
Is that clear?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Gangmo.
Forget it.
You dirty little servant...
Why are you seeing things again?
I'm sure I had enough to eat?!
Even had ribs...
Congratulations for being promoted
to Chief of the Inspection Department.
But, what is this Inspection Department?
It's the scariest place in the KCIA.
Oh my! Then...
Is it dangerous, or something?
You don't need to know.
- Here, have a drink yourself.
- Yes.
- I'm back.
- Minwoo, it's you?
Ahh... Right. He will share
the second floor with you...
What was your name again?
Lee Seongmo.
Right, Lee Seongmo.
Treat him like a brother, understood?
Yes, Dad.
Nice to meet you.
I'll go study now.
All right.
I said I don't want to!
I don't want to!
Miju.
You have a mom and dad now.
You'll get to eat tasty food
and they'll even send you to school.
I said no!
You don't like us?
My brothers will come for me!
Brothers?!
Where are your brothers?
Director...
Please, find my brothers.
Uh?
Let me stay together with my brothers.
Director...
Oppa...
Where have you gone?
Where have you gone, Oppa?
Oppa...
Hey! Want to be late on your first day?
All right.
- All right!
- Wait... Wait a moment!
Quick!
All right.
We made it.
Jeongyeon, are you okay?
Girls with no prudence...
What?
What did you just say?
Girls without what?!
When you wear a skirt,
you should be careful.
I bet all the boys here saw your panties.
You saw them too, didn't you?
Seeing you get all red, must be right.
You.
If you don't want a beating,
keep your mouth shut.
A beating from who, you?
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
Aren't you Min Honggi?!
You worked under me a decade ago, right?
Whether your superior will shake
your hand or not, it's up to him.
You're dead last!
If you don't end up within the
school's top ten, you'll have to quit.
Director Min will put you
through a few tests.
You must pass them to enter the KCIA.
Are you interested in Jo Minwoo?
Then, try to beat Jo Minwoo
at the next midterms.
I'll go with you to the movies.
You son of a bitch!
What are you, some gangster?
Chief Jo, do you know him?
No. Not really.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com