Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 54
Minister Kwon had a lot to say about you.
I'll make sure we can
meet over dinner soon.
Yes. Take care.
You as well.
Chief Prosecutor.
Why, is anything the matter?
Lee Gangmo is asking
to meet Congressman Jo.
Me?
What are you, crazy?
- How can you agree to that...
- No need to blame him.
He looks like a newcomer.
I'll get going.
He claimed he has a certain account.
An account?
What is that supposed to mean?
You can leave us alone.
Quite daring.
Trying to blackmail me in a place like this.
Thought it wouldn't be too bad
a burial spot for the both of us.
I'm sure this will create some
headaches, but I won't die over it.
Even if this had been the Blue House.
So you have an account?
Then, must we start
negotiations from scratch?
Your company for that account.
Did he tell you I
had that account on me?
I called you here to find
out who did this to me...
You never betray
my expectations, do you?
But unless you give me that account,
whatever those expectations
might be, I will be sure to defy them.
Even if I was in possession of
that account, I'd never use it for this.
I'd keep it safe, and only use it
once the company goes bankrupt.
Wouldn't that make for
much more effective blackmail?
Sure.
Blackmail would need to benefit you.
Go ahead.
I might be curious,
but I'll first worry about making
Hangang Construction go belly up.
But if you do try,
I suggest you take this to the very end.
Because should you leave
even a single spoon behind,
I'll use that to go at your throat.
So you used to laugh
a lot before joining politics?
I sure did.
I'd always prance around
laughing for no apparent reason,
so people called me Smile Mask.
So I guess I found your
elixir of eternal youth.
Really? And what would that be?
Getting kicked out of congress.
What? Kicked out?!
That's right.
Quitting politics would
sure help me live longer!
Let me pour you a drink, Deputy.
Ahh... Y.... Yes...
I'm going there as we speak.
Who did you see?
I'll be there in a moment.
Better be careful
about that Cha Soojeong.
You saw how she
was acting a little different today.
I'm sure she was
approaching you on purpose.
And why... Why would Soojeong
approach an old fart like me?
So that's why it's strange.
How naive... What's wrong with you?
You and I are on the same
boat for the rest of our days.
So if Miss Soojeong was approaching
you with ulterior motives,
neither of us will have
anything to gain from that.
Couldn't believe my eyes...
It's you, all right.
Did you drink?
Yes...
With whom?
It's the very last favor I'll ask you.
Please, stop this.
What are you talking about?
Leave my brother's company alone.
Afraid it's a little too late for that.
If you really want me to stop...
I've heard they banned you from TV.
If you want, I could help you with that.
No, thanks.
I don't need your help.
I'm the only one who
can defeat my father.
Is that really the case?
Try to gain even more
power than your father, then.
What are you trying to imply?
Gain even more power?
Just as you've heard.
Ohh... Soojeong.
Aigoo.... Chairman Jo.
We see each other
quite often these days.
I'll treat you to a drink later.
I have company tonight.
Sure.
We'll have to get going as well.
Deputy...
Yes.
Actually, I can't handle liquor too well.
Yes...
I kind of suspected that myself.
Buy me soju.
What?
Of course I would have,
like, no reason to refuse...
Why are you always so kind to me?
I get flowers after every concert,
you send me supplements,
help me get invited to TV shows.
Why do you do that?
So I was asking the same question.
To who?
The mirror.
What did it answer?
This is what it said.
"Ehh... You fool."
That was it.
I'm just a foolish man, I guess.
Would that answer be enough?
Here...
So now it's your turn to tell me.
If we count all the people I've shaken
hands and spent time with in this line of work,
it'd probably be enough to make a small city.
I'm sure you had something to ask me.
Don't you?
Ohh... Are you... about to cry?
Ahh... Nevermind, then.
I'll stop asking.
No crying, please.
I apologize.
I didn't mean to do this...
But I see you don't like it.
You hate seeing women cry, right?
Yes... Because when women cry,
you must always grant their wishes.
So that's why I told you not to cry.
I'm not going to listen to
wishes I might not be able to grant you.
Now...
I can find my way home by myself.
Thank you for today.
Are you just going to
go home empty-handed?
You looked different tonight.
Just like someone who
gave up on herself.
You will have to be convincing.
Because depending on what you say,
I might decide not to see you again.
I must have really disappointed you.
I apologize.
Why does Jo Pilyeon...
keep bothering you?
So he got you banned from TV,
and what else? Tell me
what he's been doing to you.
And what about Jo Minwoo?
Is he the man you love,
or just a despicable
lowlife I should punish?
Tell me, Soojeong.
I'm sorry.
I know how much
you hate seeing me cry...
Be it a single teardrop or an entire bucket,
you're still shedding tears before me.
Cry all you want.
Cry until you don't have a single tear left,
and then tell me the truth.
I'll grant all your wishes.
- Hangang Construction 915 -
- Manbo Construction 2150 -
Yes.
Selling 12,000 Hangang shares?
Yes... Certainly.
Yes... Hangang Construction is
hitting the daily permissible low,
since they're just
selling shares left and right.
You're selling again?
We're a half hour before the closing bell,
but everyone is selling in droves.
Yes, Chairman.
Well... I don't think there
is anything else to see here.
And of course, they reached
the daily permissible low again.
I guess by next week they'll
be worth less than toilet paper.
That's when we'll buy them.
Go ahead.
Shall we begin?
Yes, Taeyang Securities.
What? You're going to buy
Hangang Construction shares?
15,000 Hangang
Construction shares, then.
20,000 shares?
Hangang Construction, right?
- Hangang Construction 995 -
Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
- Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
Here you are, Director.
We stopped shares from getting suspended,
and brought them back to the 1000 won mark.
Order something to eat for those people.
All right.
What is this?
It's 100 won higher than yesterday!
With twenty minutes before the closing bell,
people just started buying shares nonstop.
So someone must be scheming against us.
What?
President Lee is being investigated by prosecutors,
who would possibly buy those shares...
Find out who bought those
Hangang Construction shares.
All right, Chairman.
- Hangang Construction 1058 (from 964) -
- International Group -
- Left (Ailing Companies) Right (Viable Companies) -
- Hangang Construction -
(Ailing Companies)
I guess we're pretty much done
selecting the list of ailing companies.
Thousands of lives are on the line here.
How about we give this data another read?
Have you forgotten that our deadline for
reporting this to the president is around the corner?
But about Hangang Construction.
Their boiler is still under development.
Should the results defy all expectations,
wouldn't it be unfair?
So, what, are you going to make the president
wait just because of Hangang Construction?
I wasn't necessarily suggesting that.
Thank you for your hard work.
The classification is done,
so leave the rest to me.
Jaechun!
Were you looking for me, Congressman?
Take this to my office.
I'm telling you just in case.
When this list is published,
there will be pandemonium
in the financial world.
Through mergers and acquisitions,
some will go bankrupt,
others will grow into huge dinosaurs.
And?
I set my sights on two players.
The private lending market,
and Manbo Construction.
Should any of them use
this list to gain an unfair advantage,
I will be forced to accuse you of
accumulating wealth through illicit means.
That overzealous solicitude of
yours seems to be getting quite serious.
Was just going on
record for your own sake.
Don't take it the wrong way.
What are you waiting
for? Take this box!
Yes, Sir.
Jaechun.
I can't stand that old fart any longer.
I can only pray he'll live a long life,
so that when the time comes, I can
trample on him every step of the way.
Suyeon...
It was hard, wasn't it?
How did you find
out I'd be released now?
I didn't.
I didn't, so I've
been waiting all day here.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Let's go have something to eat.
There he is.
Don't stop.
Just go, Jina.
She's really something...
Why does she keep hanging around him?
My father was really worried about you.
I see.
Is Chairman Cheon doing well?
He's a bit disappointed
because you never call him.
Won't you come by our
house, one of these days?
It would make my father really happy.
Let me ask you something.
By any chance, did you...
Did I what?
Go ahead and say it.
Did you buy those Hangang
Construction shares?
Shares?
I'm not really into that stuff.
If you don't have any appetite,
shall we just go for a drink?
I know this great place...
No, I think I'll have
to go back to my office.
You're just going?
I'm sorry, Suyeon.
I have something to do.
- Hangang Construction 1100 -
- Current Price 1320 won -
- Hangang Construction 1430 -
Yes... Yes.
All right.
Gangmo...
They were suspended...
Our shares were suspended
for excessive gains!
This is strange.
We haven't even finished our boiler,
why is this happening?
Why do you think?
Rumors that we'd make a
killer boiler started spreading.
Did you find out who's
been buying our shares?
That... There were too many
buyers to track them down.
Unless someone made a concerted effort
to help us, this wouldn't have happened.
Keep looking into it.
Yes, I will, President.
I knew it... My guess was right.
You know, only big shots
would be capable of something like this.
You seem to be investing in the
stock exchange quite significantly as of late.
Ahh... So that's why you jumped on board?
But of all companies, Hangang Construction?
Isn't letting pride and competitive spirit
become your only reward a bit naive?
When the target is someone
like you, any reward is fine.
To be really honest, I never
really thought of you as an ally,
but neither did I ever consider you a foe.
I'd at least have to feel a little
intimidated for that to be the case.
I see we have different views.
You've really made a name for yourself.
And I can't stand that.
A loan shark who would grovel
at Baekpa's feet for pocket money...
is now acting like a businessman.
It just feels phony to me.
Stop giving me that haughty
crap and listen well.
You choosing to bring this
fight to the stock exchange...
is like a monkey
trying to eat with a fork.
Am I making myself clear?
It's the very last chance I'll give you.
Leave me the rest of the
areas under your control,
and get out of this business.
I'll promise you right here.
I will make sure you can call it quits
sooner than you can imagine.
Better remember
my words, Noh Gapsoo.
I guess the stock market
will be a good place for you to get buried.
These companies have been confirmed.
The list will be published in a week.
So start putting all those
M&As in motion before then.
So I can stop worrying
about Hangang Construction.
Don't let your guard down until
the official announcement is made.
That Lee Gangmo is backed by big names.
That's from the kindergarten Wooju frequents.
Turn around.
What?
Take me to Wooju.
Yes, Chairman.
Daddy!
Have you been well?
I missed you, Daddy.
What do you want to do today?
I want to go to the toy shop.
Again?
Wow! I won!
Wooju!
Come and get me!
Wooju.
Time to go now.
Daddy...
Come see me again tomorrow.
I can't come anymore.
Why?
Because I...
am not your father.
Take him inside.
Yes.
Wooju... Let's go.
Daddy... Don't... go...
Daddy...
Don't go...
This is serious, Congressman.
Serious?
It finally happened.
- Agents Involved with Death
by Torture Case Arrested -
- On January 14, 1987, SNU student and
democratic activist Park Jongcheol... -
- passed away after going through
electroshock and drowning torture, -
- which proved to be the spark igniting
the June (87) Democracy Movement, -
- with students raising against
the Jeon Duhwan junta's claims that... -
- direct presidential
elections were unconstitutional. -
- This led to Korea's first ever direct
elections, and to the end of the 5th Republic. -
Hey... Will you stop typing?
I'm all done.
I'll go get this report examined,
so don't you even think of running away.
Is there anything problematic
in the reports she's writing?
I took a look the other day, and it
was just basic daily itinerary and stuff.
That torture accident is
going to seriously ignite the situation.
When do you plan to reveal the account?
We'll first observe how
the situation evolves.
What's for sure...
is that this regime is
surviving on borrowed time.
And Jo Pilyeon's fortunes...
will face the very same fate.
That's it.
That's how you write a report.
Good job.
You can go.
See you tomorrow.
Ahh... I'll work even harder.
You organized all the reports
she's been writing, right?
Yes, Chief.
This is starting to smell.
I'm sure something is up.
Does that torture case
have anything to do with you?
From what I hear, the first informer
came from the ruling party.
Is this the time to be worrying about that?
Shouldn't we know what's going
on between you and the opposition?
You don't need to know now.
I don't?!
You just wait.
The direct elections that congress
could not bring into fruition...
will likely be achieved by our people themselves.
So?
First you send out the
hounds on a hunting spree,
and with the hare in your
hands, no need for them anymore?
Didn't you just answer the call
of duty from the very start?
This wouldn't have been
possible without your efforts.
If I only could, I'd go out on
the street and throw rocks as well.
Our candidate would like to see you.
I'm sure he's busy preparing
the presidential elections...
All the more reason why he'd
need people like you by his side.
What are you trying to say?
At the next general elections,
we'd like to recommend
you for a seat in congress.
Ahh... I see...
Help us out, Chairman Hwang.
Shouldn't we obtain those direct elections...
and put an end to this dictatorship?
I will be happy to devote my
insignificant life for this great cause.
"Did he really hit the
desk and suddenly die?"
What the hell are you people about?
How could you let this happen?
You shouldn't blame it all on us.
Think you politicians' hands are clean?
Look, Chief Oh...
I have no time to waste arguing with you.
What is this?
The reports from the mole
we sent to Lee Seongmo's office.
You know Yoo Chanseong, right?
According to those reports,
this Yoo Chanseong once
wrote a report about the torture case.
Of course, we never ordered him to do so.
Then, Lee Seongmo has to be behind this.
Are you suspecting him again?
Yoo Chanseong is like
Lee Seongmo's alter ego.
There is no way he could
have plotted this on his own.
Still, how can we just punish him
for having written a mere report?
- Jaechun.
- Yes, Congressman.
Follow Chief Oh, and get
Yoo Chanseong's full records.
All right.
I'll finally start to get a hold of
who this invisible thorn in my side really is.
- Hangang Construction 1710 -
I see you're still
holding the fort, Lee Gangmo.
I forgot the Hwang Jeongyeon card.
Then... The one who's
been buying our shares...
I should have dealt with her first...
Still, it's not like the end
result will be any different.
Thanks for setting my factory on fire.
Listen well.
That is what will lead
you to your downfall.
Work hard on that boiler of yours.
You have only three
days left, Lee Gangmo.
In three days, that...
will be worth less than toilet paper.
Hey... Shouldn't we really
thank Jeongyeon for this?
To be honest, if it weren't for
her we would have gone belly up.
What is the matter?
This is serious, Gangmo.
What happened?
It's a top secret from the
Ministry of Finance I just got a hold of,
suggesting that in three
days, the list of ousted companies...
including Hangang Construction will be announced.
In three days?!
That quick?
If you don't do something before then,
it will be over for any
company that is mentioned.
Start the car.
So should there be any
danger of a gas leak or a fire,
this mechanism will sound the alarm?
Yes... I tried to explain this to
Sotae a hundred times to no avail,
but I guess having a brain
helped you get it right away?!
Once this boiler is developed, it
will really change the sector's landscape.
Tell me about it.
We should have bought shares earlier...
Jeongyeon.
Gangmo.
You're here?
What's going on, these days
you always come here?!
These two ladies asking questions
nonstop are driving me insane.
Oh... Really?!
I'm the one answering all questions,
so why would that drive you insane?
Congrats, Gangmo.
Looks like your boiler
will really be something.
Can you complete development
within the next three days?
Three days?!
What's that supposed
to mean, all of a sudden?
We must do it.
We're not dealing
with briquette gas here...
I said we must complete it in three days!
Gangmo...
In three days, that's impossible.
Then, how long will it take?
No matter how fast we go,
at least a week... No...
It will take at least ten days.
Gangmo...
The list you gave us
was of great help.
Right... So what did you invest in?
First, 30 billion will be headed
Manbo Construction's way.
I see you're sparing no expense.
We carefully analyzed those ailing companies,
and went through a very thorough selection.
Unless that list suddenly changes,
I assure you it will
be worth the investment.
That list is not going to be
altered, so just trust me, President Noh.
Isn't that the reason why
I'm investing my entire fortune?
If you want to look after me,
you'll have to make a lot of money.
I will.
Shouldn't you go for the
highest seat, sooner or later?
Don't you go around mentioning that.
But, when do you plan to sell
those Hangang Construction shares?
We'll start the assault tomorrow.
So it'll be downhill for them starting tomorrow.
Once the list is announced in three days,
it'll be all over for
Hangang Construction's shares.
Here... Let's drink.
It's you?
I have something to tell you.
We know.
So the list will be announced in three days?
Yes.
Will they manage to
complete their boiler on time?
To be honest... It looks unlikely.
Any way to revive the
company's fortunes before then?
Other than telling
you I will give my best...
So shouldn't you start selling all the
Hangang Construction shares you have?
Tell me what you're thinking.
How would you like to proceed?
I still have faith in Gangmo.
Gangmo will succeed.
He's not going to go down this way.
Jeongyeon...
I know what you're feeling...
- But the reality of things...
- So?
I'd like to fight with him to the end.
The decision is obviously up to you,
but that's the way I see it.
When it comes to being so
reckless, she just takes after me.
Just pretend you didn't hear that.
I'm in the mood for a drink, too.
Can I join in?
Excuse me, can I have a glass?
Yes.
The Hangang Construction shares you have...
must be sold, Jeongyeon.
I don't really think I would endure...
seeing you in difficulty because of this.
Back then, when
I lost Manbo Construction...
Remember?
This is what you told me back then.
"You might abandon it, but
do it with your head held up high."
"Don't show them a single tear."
You can fail once and lose it all, Gangmo.
There are more people who
failed than those who succeeded.
And even more people got back
on their feet after experiencing failure.
Still, even if you do fail,
I don't want to see you lose.
Particularly if whom you're fighting
with are Jo Pilyeon and his son.
Even if you lose the company,
you must remain strong and
fight to the very end.
Thanks, Jeongyeon.
Having you by my side...
gives me great strength.
- Have a drink.
- Sure.
So is it this weekend?
What?
Ahh... That?
It still hasn't been signed
by the president, right?
I was going to go to
the Blue House tomorrow.
But why do you
keep bugging me about it?
I was just wondering if you could
delay that announcement a little.
After the torture scandal,
public sentiment is already heated as it is,
so must you really make such
an announcement at a time like this?
You do have a point,
but how can I not respect a
deadline made by the president?
You could still try to convince him.
What's the reason you're asking me this?
I don't believe this list
was selected in all fairness.
Of course it wasn't.
Since it was born out
of pure bias to begin with.
So let me be perfectly honest.
I'd like you to take Hangang
Construction off that list.
Or if you can't do that,
at least delay the announcement,
and give them another chance.
I don't want to test the
president's patience over that.
I've dealt with construction
companies for two decades.
I've occasionally experienced things that
made my heart swell with pride,
but also enough corruption
to grow tired of it.
Of course I couldn't possibly
claim I'm completely clean.
So?
President Lee Gangmo is one of the few
competent and honest men I've met in this trade.
So seeing that kind of man be
sacrificed at the altar of corrupt politics...
before he can even spread his wings...
is something that, as someone
who's spent twenty years in this trade,
I couldn't possibly allow to happen.
And should I refuse, what would you do?
I think I might be convinced
not to see you again.
How can you so easily tell me that,
considering all we've gone through?
In all our years of friendship,
I have never asked you a single favor.
I know.
And that even disappointed me, at times.
This is my very first, and last favor.
Please delay that announcement.
Look what having a
friend like you gets me...
I would have waited even
longer to tell me, if I were you...
You should have come to me first.
Anyhow, your help was crucial.
I'll go out a moment and greet him.
Right, go.
Ohh... I was wondering where you went.
Don't worry.
I think it will go just as you hoped.
I really envy President Lee?!
He really has a clever little sister.
Thank you, Deputy...
I'll never forget what you did for us.
Thank you so much.
- Current Price 940 won -
Why don't you get out of this
while you still can, Director Yoo?
You'll soon realize that
there's a glass ceiling above you.
You really think you can
beat my financial resources?
Gather all the capital you can find.
- Director...
- Didn't you hear me?
I said get all the money we have left!
All right.
I'm sorry, Director.
We couldn't possibly stop
Noh Gapsoo's assault with that money.
And we pretty much used
all the funds we had.
This is all I have left.
Director...
Use this and resist to the end.
But...
If we use all this money...
I'll let you in on a good news.
The announcement set for
tomorrow has been canceled.
It will be rescheduled to ten days from now.
You must complete that boiler before then.
Thank you, Director.
That money is an investment.
So I will see profits, right?
Yes, Director.
You can go now.
Whatever the case,
aren't you going too far?
It's not like they completed that boiler...
How much do you think
Jeongyeon is worth to me?
Even all the money in the world...
wouldn't mean as much
to me as she does.
I can certainly understand that, but...
The reason Jeongyeon is doing that...
is because of Lee Gangmo.
Because she loves him.
Putting everything on the
line for someone you love...
I think that's the noblest
investment anyone could make in life.
Isn't my daughter wonderful?
So that's why I'm investing
everything I have in her.
Because she's my daughter, the person
I most cherish and love in this world.
Aigoo...
It's here!
It's tomorrow's evening paper.
Give it her.
Ahh... Come on!
You watch.
No, you do it.
I'm so worried I might see that list,
my heart's going to explode.
Just give it here.
Where did my spectacles go?
Ahh... Really, give me a break.
Give it to me.
What's the matter, President?
There's no article about the announcement.
None?
Did you bring yesterday's paper?
Think I'm that stupid?
What's going on here?
Didn't they say it would be today?
The announcement has been postponed.
It's ten days from now.
You can complete
the boiler by then, right?
What's wrong with you two?
In public and all...
What are you doing?
There's no time to waste.
Let's finish this!
Oh... Congressman Jo, come on in.
What did you just do?
What did I do?
Why did you postpone that announcement?
The president's attention is
focused on the demonstrations.
Take a look outside.
People are on the verge of
storming towards the Blue House.
So?
So I told the president.
Now wasn't the time to
make that announcement.
Guess he had it with this himself.
He just said "All right, so just go."
But is there any particular reason
why you must make that announcement?
What I was saying...
Congressman Jo seems so
hell-bent on making this announcement...
Look, what are you trying to imply?
I would never allow him to gain
personal benefits out of this,
think Congressman Jo wouldn't be aware of that?
Your turn.
Odds.
Congressman.
Jaechun...
I can't let Oh Byeongtak get away with this.
What?
I want to kill that bastard.
Congressman, calm down...
and take a look at this.
And what is that?
It's the data regarding Lee
Seongmo's underling, Yoo Chanseong.
And?!
Yoo Chanseong's older brother was
a doctor for the Eighth US Army.
So, why the hell
would I care about that?
Don't you remember?
That doctor who died back
when we stole that secret Vietnam file.
Hyung!
I said the doctor is dead!
The doctor...
is dead!
That's right.
I remember.
The doctor died back then.
So Yoo Chanseong would be his brother?
Yes, there is no doubt.
So he must be thinking his
brother died because of me.
Which is why he's doing all this to avenge him.
Everything that's been
happening was plotted by him.
Really?
Then, before he brings harm to me,
I'll have to get rid of him first.
What is she waiting for?
Kids her age are all like that.
The hell does she takes me for...
Ji Yeonsoo!
So...
Are you ready?
So, let's get started.
Chief!
Are you out of your mind?
Ohh... I'm so sorry.
Thought it was taekwondo today...
I'm sorry, Chief...
Are you all right?
What now... That's got to hurt.
Breathe...
Good job, everyone.
So Manbo Construction's
boiler is finally complete.
Would you like to take a look, Chairman?
No.
Not now.
When is the boiler's presentation again?
At 2 pm.
With the announcement being postponed,
we'll inevitably have to face
off against Hangang Construction.
Are you confident?
Of course we are.
Call the press.
Lee Gangmo is still
resisting at the stock exchange,
so we need to bring this to an end.
President.
But, we didn't have time,
so we couldn't do
sufficient performance tests.
We did our best.
Now Hangang Construction's destiny...
depends on this boiler.
You haven't heard anything
about Manbo Construction?
They keep a tight lid on development, so...
Let's go for it.
We're at the edge of the cliff.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
This could severely
impact Manbo Construction and Noh Gapsoo.
It could even destroy them for good.
Where did Hangang Construction
and the rest of those ten companies go?
Watch what you say, Jo Pilyeon!!
That account... give it to me.
Congressman Oh says
he's got something for us.
Seems like it's a secret
report about Jo Pilyeon.
This is all because of Oh Byeongtak.
How do you plan to deal with this?
We must get rid of him.
Go for Hwang Taeseop.
I'm sure Lee Gangmo's name will surface.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com