Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 33 -
Yes.
It's me, Jo Minwoo.
You're having it quite hard
these days, aren't you?
I just wanted to let you in
on a precious bit of information.
You should be receiving a fax by now.
You'll have to go through with it
even if you don't want to.
If you want to survive.
I can't wait...
To see how you'll cause
Hwang Jeongyeon's downfall.
Jeongyeon...
I hope you won't
disappoint me, Lee Gangmo.
As while you worry about
bringing Hwang Jeongyeon down,
I'll be getting my hands
on Manbo Construction.
What is he scheming?!
Jo Minwoo!
- No Trespassing -
Hey... Guess it's not the right place.
There... Try digging over there.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Not there, you fool.
Farther back!
Here.
You do it then, dammit!
Excuse me?
What did I just hear?
We're getting a little sassy, aren't we?
This... This...
It must be a caveman's bone, I bet?
Wow... What an epochal
discovery I've just made!
Hey... Guess someone around here
had some dog soup?
It's a dog bone?
Ehh...
Move out the way.
Wow...
You do look like a tomb raider?!
I ought to...
That!
Jo Minwoo was right...
Gangmo.
What do we do now?
What do you think?
If we let the press in on this,
Manbo Construction will be forced
to halt the construction. Then what?
All the buyers will
come our way, what else?
If we got these out of
a few hours of digging,
think of how many more
will be buried in there.
Good job.
You and Sotae can go to sleep.
Can we?
Let's go get a drink
and then call it a night.
If you're treating,
I sure could give it a thought?
All right...
I'm treating, you pay.
Jo Minwoo might be trying to
gain control of Manbo Construction.
What?!
Who's Jo Minwoo's closest
confidant within the company?
Wouldn't go so far
as to call him confidant,
but Chief Moon Seongjoong
is always around him, so...
Then, stick to him for now.
All right.
But, Gangmo...
Are you really all right?
And if I'm not?
Are you really going to keep
fighting with Jeongyeon to the end?
You still haven't left?
Why is the president
refusing to meet me?
You still can't realize why?
There is no bank in Korea willing
to lend money to Hangang Construction.
Were you the one who
was stopping our bank loan?
Who else did you think it could be?
I suggest you stop trying
to interfere in my business.
This is a warning.
We're in a fight that can
only end with your foe's demise,
and you "warn" me?
I see you've still
got time to waste doing that.
You might believe that refusing the
acquisition proposal I made is your last stand,
but let's pretend I never mentioned it.
Since the situation has now changed.
You will end up on a street.
And that's because I will
destroy Hangang Construction.
Here you are.
How have you been, President?
Please, come on in.
Gangmo...
If you can't do it because of her,
let me.
If anyone does it, I will.
Gangmo...
Enough.
You know...
that I wouldn't bear to
see you get ruined, don't you?
Do you know why a scumbag like me
has been sticking to you all this time?
Think it was just to make it big?
Gangmo, it's...
because I wanted to see you succeed.
Because I wanted to
see your dreams come true.
Leave all the dirty work to me.
As if it's for Lee Gangmo's sake,
I'm even prepared to die.
Go ahead first.
I'll drop by the newspaper
on my way to the office.
I said I'll do it.
What's this?
How much does your loan to
Manbo Construction amount to?
And why are you...
I was just asking
out of concern for you.
What are you trying to say?
These are Baekje relics found
on Manbo Construction's site.
Should the press get a hold of this,
the construction will have
to be stopped immediately.
Get out of the way!
Start digging... Now!
Move out of the way.
Director!
Director...
What are you going to do?
Hand the report to the press.
- Baekje Relics Found on Site -
Complications Brewing for Manbo Construction
Handled quite neatly, I see.
Manbo Construction's stock price
will soon begin to fall.
And I'm sure you've been preparing
the capital to buy those shares?!
Certainly.
You will soon be able to get
your hands on Manbo Construction.
Yes?
Go ahead.
The chairman has regained his speech.
That's great to hear.
Oh Namsuk still doesn't know this, right?
No.
She must never be told.
You understand what I'm saying, right?
Ohh... Miss Kim.
Hello? Miss Kim?
The chairman's condition
is still the same, right?
Yes.
I'll have to hang up.
His wife is here.
How have you been, Dear?
Dreamed that you would get back
on your feet last night.
You can't imagine how startled I was.
I even changed the testament now,
you can't do that to me...
Isn't that right, Honey?
Know what this is?
- Petition for Adjudication of Incompetence -
I filed for an incompetence adjudication.
The court will soon announce the verdict.
With that,
even without having
to wait for your death,
Jeongshik will be able to
become the new chairman.
Namsuk...
Why have you suddenly
become so scary?
Are you the same Oh Namsuk I knew?
What are you, reflecting on
all the years you spent ignoring me?
Or is it just plain resentment?
If you were capable of
throwing puppy eyes at me,
you should have tried
while you still could.
None of this would
have happened, then.
Miss Kim, don't you want
to earn some easy money?
Excuse me?
Help me out just this once,
and you'll get your hands on the kind of
money a lifetime of work wouldn't give you.
Write down your account number.
Don't you worry and just write it down.
It won't be all that hard
for someone like you.
This is home.
Let's go in.
They'll be waiting for us.
How do I look?
Is the make-up looking all right?
You're pretty.
Let's get going.
Minwoo...
What should I tell them?
Just let me handle it.
They already gave us their consent,
what's there to worry about?
Come on, let's go in.
Come on in.
How are you?
Honey, serve us some tea, please.
Have a seat.
Our Minwoo got himself
quite the radiant beauty, I see.
Thank you.
So your parents passed away?
Yes...
Must have been hard, all these years.
Any other family...
Brothers or sisters?
- That...
- She has no family.
She's alone.
So I hear you passed your
GED test with flying colors?
I'd love to see you graduate
from college, while we're at it?
I was already planning to send her.
Must be busy.
Worrying about work and finding
the time to look after students...
I will pay my tuition.
And how do you plan to do that?
That's cute.
You have quite the
independent spirit as well.
I can understand how Minwoo
could fall head over heels for you.
I think marrying as soon
as possible would be best.
Minwoo...
You...
Men need to have a strong foundation
behind them to make it big.
We'll leave our Minwoo to your care.
*-in-law
Yes... F...ather*...
Your father seems
like such a nice person.
Think he liked you.
But... How did you
manage to convince him?
Told you, didn't I?
That I could do anything for you.
You've heard him say he wants to
get married right away, didn't you?
I told you to leave Minwoo to me.
And if he starts refusing to
break up with her later, then what?
No need to stir up a hornet's nest.
Just let him do as he pleases for now.
I need to go out,
so make all the arrangements.
How are things going for Jeongyeon?
If I tell you, you'll only feel worse.
Just say it.
At today's shareholders' meeting,
they might actually
kick her out of the company.
- Construction Halted, Stock Crashes -
Formerly the Sector's Kingpin, now an Also-Ran
Wake up, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Nobody can help you now.
If you lose out to the shareholders today,
it is over for Manbo Construction.
I can't ruin what my father
worked a lifetime to build...
just because of Lee Gangmo.
The shareholders are coming.
Hello there.
You're one of our major
shareholders after all...
My behavior was inexcusable.
Allow me to apologize.
No need to apologize,
it's all in the past.
I see you still haven't forgiven me?
My... You sure know
how to hold grudges.
That wench is going to keep up
with the attitude to the end!
Still, remaining calm
was the wisest move.
She's Baekpa's adopted daughter...
If it weren't for that,
I'd already be all over...
Let's go in.
What is going on with
the apartment construction?
The Cultural Heritage Administration
announced a major excavation,
how are you going to deal with that?
Have you seen how we're doing
at the stock exchange?
Our stocks are plummeting!
Here... Everyone!
If you want an answer, please be quiet.
At the end of the day,
we won't have to stop the construction.
I'll assume full responsibility, and...
Do you even have what it takes
to assume responsibility?
Shouldn't you face the repercussions
for causing all this in the first place?
I'm rather curious how Director Hwang
will overcome this crisis.
Moments of crisis always go
hand in hand with management.
Which is why, on the contrary,
this might turn out to be the
perfect proving ground for her.
And if letting her take her
first baby steps as a leader...
ends up putting the entire
company at risk, what will you do?
Well said!
What if she fails?
What would you like me to do?
Would you be prepared to renounce
all your company holdings if you fail?
Ahh... Seems like that would be ideal.
Weren't you the first to force this project
on us, promising you'd take responsibility?
Fine, then.
Should this construction
have to be halted,
I'll relinquish all the
company shares in my possession.
So what do you need to understand,
in order to sign a contract?
Let's respect the line, shall we?
If you don't...
Ehhh! Ajumma!
Stay in line, you're
messing up the whole thing!
Aigoo... All right.
All right, Ajeosshi.
How many times do I
have to tell you... Gangmo!
We hit the jackpot!
They're all going crazy,
asking to sign with us. Take a look.
- Gangmo.
- Gangmo!
What are you doing, Mom?
You think you can buy an
apartment with this kind of money?
Why... Is it not enough?
But we brought everything
we have down to the last penny?!
You can stop dreaming with this much.
Couldn't you inform yourself
before coming here?
I will buy an apartment for you...
Mother.
Mother?!
Who's this fella?
Isn't he the one who scolded
us for not staying in line?
I apologize for earlier on,
I'm a director here at Hangang
Construction, Park Sotae.
Dir...Director?!
Our Shideok is a director, too?
But, will you really
buy us an apartment?
Yes... When I've made
enough money later on.
Aigoo... Really...
Isn't there anything
we can get with this much?
Even if it's small...
Aigoo... And we saved a little money
to buy ourselves an apartment.
Just let them sign
for whatever they have.
Really?
Gangmo...
This is not even half the price.
They looked after Miju and me,
when we were little.
I always wanted to repay you
for your generosity.
Let's wrap up the contract, Gyeongja.
All right, Oppa...
Seal here, Dad.
Your seal.
But I could have bought you one later...
Gangmo, we're so thankful...
Only people who've gone through
hardships could understand.
Despite all the work
we've done for them,
Jeongyeon's family never gave us
enough to get ourselves our own place.
I'm so thankful, Gangmo...
- Aigoo... Thank you...
- The hell are you crying for? Are we in mourning?
I'm just thankful...
Please help us out, Commissioner.
Aigoo, really...
We can't just halt
the construction like this.
If you were aware something
like this had happened,
you should have come to me
before the press got a hold of it.
I only found out later myself.
It is all my fault.
Yes.
Ahh... How have you been,
Commissioner Han?
What brings you here, all of a sudden?
I see you're here as well.
What is going on with Manbo
Construction's apartment project?
The higher-ups still
haven't made any decision.
Not only Songpa,
but also Jamshil and Pungnap-Dong
have been proposed as historical sites.
If we went by the book all the way,
who would ever build anything there?
Yes... You certainly have a point.
Then, are you telling me you could
help us continue the construction?
You should come to our rescue
in situations like this.
I am indeed trying everything
in my power to help you out,
but it seems that someone from above
is purposely delaying things.
Then, I'll have to put in a good
word where it counts, I suppose?
I think even the higher-ups believe
that development is necessary,
if we are to successfully host the
1988 Olympics and 1986 Asian Games.
I'll see what I can do,
so don't you worry too much,
and focus on your company instead.
Thank you.
If I think of how far back
Chairman Hwang and I go,
this is nothing
compared to what I owe him.
We have no more time to waste.
Send the chairman to a
better place by tomorrow.
I'll be counting on you, Miss Kim.
Mom!
What did you just say?
To a better place?!
What is that supposed to mean?
Your father will spend the rest of his
life in a vegetative state, anyway.
Mom!
Be that as it may...
How could you do this to him...
I married your father out of love.
And it was that same sentiment
which gave birth to you.
Think I'm enjoying all this?
This is all for your sake.
Haven't you had it with
being ignored all your life?
Mom...
Must you really go this far?
The hell do you know, anyway?
Do you even realize how it feels?
What could you possibly know?
Just pretend you didn't hear this.
I'll take care of everything else.
How could this happen?
Why did things have
to get to this point?
Jeongshik...
Jeongshik!
That man's life is over, anyway.
He's merely leaving us a little earlier.
He can do that much for us, can't he?
Yes?
All right.
I'll come there myself.
Oh Namsuk...
So you plan to go all the way...
Dad.
This has nothing to do with me.
I've always been nothing but a fool...
You always scolded me
for that same reason.
I'm just a wretched, useless fool...
That's all I am...
So I didn't even realize
she could go this far, Dad...
No way...
I can't let her do this to my father.
Don't worry.
They're just supplements.
Dad...
Dad!
Nurse!
Nurse!!
What did you just say?
Your father disappeared?!
How about that nurse?
What?!
She quit?!
All right.
I'll head there right away.
What is it?
She said the chairman disappeared,
where are you going?
Uh? The chairman disappeared?
If the construction is halted,
we'll be the only ones to lose money!
Please have faith in us.
That is never going to happen.
The Cultural Heritage Administration...
Hey... Think it's the first time
I go through something like this?
Please, don't do this...
Just calm down, and...
Forget that, and tell
your chairman to come out!
If he doesn't compensate us
for our damages right away...
Let go!
You dare...
lay your hands on one of my customers?
Get up.
Ahh... My back...
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
I apologize.
Give me back my money!
Everyone, keep quiet!
Here is a new contract.
A few clauses have been added which will
protect you from incurring any losses.
So what's the reason
you wanted us to meet?
I have no intention of
sitting here staring at your face,
so get to the point.
If you want to protect your company,
first try to find out what
Jo Minwoo is going after.
And do you have any evidence
to support such accusations?
The fact that the man who alerted me
to those relics was exactly him.
Really...
If my guess is right,
Jo Minwoo is trying to oust you and
gain control of Manbo Construction.
And of course Jo Pilyeon is behind him.
How about you, then?
If your "guess" is right,
then you let Jo Minwoo manipulate you.
After letting the puppeteer
move you around freely,
what do you plan to accomplish
by telling me that?
It's because...
I don't want to see Manbo Construction
fall because of anyone that isn't me.
Right...
as expected, Lee Gangmo.
It went right as Minwoo predicted.
He told me.
That you'd come looking for me,
and try to frame him
and his father for all this.
Ahh!
He also said this.
That Park Sotae came to our
construction site to dig up those relics.
The only people who are helping me now...
are Jo Minwoo and his father.
So you want me to cut my ties with them?
You know...
The mere thought that I
once loved a man like you...
just makes me feel ashamed.
Marriage?!
So you're going to marry Chief Jo?
Yeah.
Think I might.
Eonni...
What have we been doing while
she was winning the lottery?
Did his parents
give you their consent?
Yeah.
Minwoo's father is really nice.
Then, how about singing?
Even after I'm married,
I won't give up my dream.
Minwoo said he'll help me.
Made me lose all my appetite...
What's wrong with you?
I did my best to make it tasty...
Don't say that, and have some.
What's wrong with her now?
Miju... Are you all right?
Don't know what did this to me,
but it's been this way for a while?
Aigoo...
You're the only committee member
who refused to give a penny.
I apologize.
We've had our difficulties
here and there, so...
Give me a little more time
to find the money.
Our friend at the Blue House
is not enjoying this, you know?
I'm losing face just
because of you, is that clear?
A little more time is all I ask.
One way or another,
I'll get you that money.
That money Jo Pilyeon is gathering...
will end up in the
president's Swiss bank account.
Then, being put in charge
of the consultation panel...
Just a way to legitimize
his need for capital.
Jo Pilyeon turned
that post in his favor.
He's got an innate talent for
ingratiating himself with powerful figures.
We can't let him get away with this.
And how do you suppose we proceed?
You need to put
a stop to him, Seonbaenim.
If Jo Pilyeon continues to gain
power in the construction sector,
we'll all be wallowing in
quicksands soon enough.
Don't you know what kind of
money we're dealing with?
You want me to bother a sacred cow?
Gangnam's development rush
is about to fire up,
but it's already shrouded in shadows.
I wonder if that city can
ever truly develop in peace.
How much land have
you managed to sell so far?
We'll get the rest of our
money in a matter of days.
First, transfer what you have to me,
and spare no effort to get
your hands on all the rest.
All right, Chief.
Gangmo.
I finally caught them red-handed.
Take a look at this.
Chief Moon is selling that land
behind everyone's back.
But this land belongs
to Manbo Construction.
Shouldn't you let Jeongyeon know?
They took advantage of what
happened to Chairman Hwang.
And that's because they can
get out of any trouble...
by simply claiming
the chairman ordered this.
But... What is Jo Minwoo trying
to accomplish with this money?
Find out where Jo Minwoo is.
Why...
Want to meet him?
I'll have to meet him firsthand,
and find out whether my guess is right.
I'm happy that you
found someone you like.
Want to meet her right now?
Now?!
I'm sure she's at my apartment.
Let's just go home
and have a drink there.
Don't know about that...
I am a little curious, I'll admit.
But what kind of woman
are we dealing with?
My...
Do you like her enough to act like
that any time someone mentions her?
She's like a blessing to me.
So who is this woman?
Her dream is a tad
out of the ordinary.
She sings well, so...
We need to talk.
I'll leave you two alone.
Just sit, Hyung.
Let's not ruin the mood because of him.
Thanks to you,
my job has gotten much easier.
Don't enjoy this too much.
I have no intention of letting you
gain control of Manbo Construction.
I'm sure you know who got that
dying company out of trouble?!
I know what you're plotting.
While Jeongyeon and I fight each other,
you'll make sure
company shares hit rock bottom,
and then get your hands
on them on the cheap.
Smarts as always, aren't you?
But...
How do you plan to stop me?
Last time I checked, you allowed me
to manipulate you like a puppet.
Jo Minwoo,
all the hell you put me through...
is exactly what you're going
to experience from now on.
Let's go, Hyung.
Right...
You've arrested him once,
if I recall correctly?
Will you keep an eye on him for me?
Never know when he might
go back to his old ways.
Take good care of him.
He's like a brother to me.
He ended up ruining the mood, all right.
Let's go to my place, Hyung.
Will have to meet
your girlfriend next time.
You're not coming?
I have something to do.
Introduce her to me next time.
Jo Minwoo is preparing a secret fund
to gain control of Manbo Construction.
I'll have to get
my hands on that money.
Looks like you might need my help?
Moon Seongjoong.
He's a department chief
at Manbo Construction,
and was put in charge
of the secret fund.
I know it won't be easy,
but we must stop
Jo Pilyeon's secret fund.
Let's give it a try.
We need to.
When did you arrive?
Still haven't had dinner, have you?
Just sleep.
I had dinner.
Then, I'll sleep a little while more.
I see you've cheered up our Minwoo.
Looks like you're our good-luck charm.
Don't you like meat?
Why are you only eating salad?
What?
She loves meat.
Should I cut it for you, then?
No...
I can handle it.
Miju!
Really...
Suits her just right...
Awww... I can't stand her.
Wait a moment...
She can't be...
Miju, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Still dealing with that indigestion?
Pregnant?!
Seeing how she only eats salad,
and suffering from nausea like that.
She might be pregnant indeed.
What if she really is?
Leave it to me.
I'll take care of everything.
I'm so sorry.
I've been dealing with an
indigestion the last few days.
Can you eat anything?
I do feel bad about it...
But I'm afraid I can't.
I apologize, Father.
An old friend of mine
runs a traditional clinic,
let's go together.
We'll have to get you some tonic.
Tonic?
You don't need to bother.
If you want to become
my daughter-in-law,
I want a healthy lady by my son's side.
Let's go there.
Consider yourself lucky.
He's never done that for me before.
Thank you... Father.
We'll prepare some tonic for you,
so come get it next week.
You can go ahead first.
Yes...
Have a nice day.
Yes, you as well.
So, is she pregnant?
There is no doubt.
Tonight at 7?
Yes, Moon Seongjoong and Jo Minwoo
are set to meet at a night club.
How about the password?
Looks like it might be Manbo
Construction's founding day.
0316.
Good job, Chanseong.
So is it my turn now?
It won't be easy to get both
account book and seal from him.
Don't worry.
I have something in mind already.
It's me, Lee Seongmo.
How about a drink later tonight?
Yes... It's been a while,
so thought I'd ask.
Yes.
Then, we'll go to the usual place.
Yes, all right.
This has all the
deposit money we encashed.
It's thirty percent of the total sum.
Gather the remaining seventy
percent all in the same account.
All right, Chief.
Minwoo.
Hyung!
What are you doing here?
I came here to have
a drink with Director Jo.
The owner said you were here.
Ahh... Say hi.
He's like a brother to me.
- I'm Moon Seongjoong.
- Pleasure to meet you.
All the better, then.
When Director Jo arrives,
we can all have a drink together.
I'll get going.
As you prefer.
Yes.
Almost ran out of drinks here?
Order some more.
Here...
Let's first empty this one.
To our Minwoo's...
happy marriage!
Cheers!
Remember, Hyung?
The first night you
took me out for drinks.
You said I was piss drunk that night...
You puked all over my
one and only suit, you fool...
Hyung...
I'm so happy these days...
You do look happy.
Did I miss all the fun?
You're here?
- Dad...
- Ohh...
Looks like Minwoo is already drunk?!
Yes... I'm a little drunk.
Seongmo is perfectly fine...
How can you let him
outdrink you like that?
Ohh Ohh... Look at him.
He said he's really happy these days.
Is that so?
Forget him, and let's
have a drink by ourselves.
Yes.
- I'll pour you one, Sir.
- Sure.
Here...
- Cheers.
Have you found the nurse
who took away my father?
She already erased her traces.
I asked everyone at the hospital,
and nobody knew a thing.
Director Ju... File a
missing report with the police.
That's out of the question.
My father is nowhere to be found.
We won't gain a thing by
letting everyone in on this.
And why is that?
What did you do to him behind my back?
Watch your mouth.
I did what?
You were the one who hid him
at that nursing home.
What could you possibly be afraid of?
If people learn of this,
what will happen to the company
you're running into the ground?
You'd only fuel the fire, got it?
Until we find him, forget the police.
Shouldn't you be smart
enough to understand that?
She does have a point.
We'll look for him again tomorrow.
Jaechun, can you really drive?
Yes... Had a little sleep earlier on,
and that sobered me up.
Seongmo, come sleep at my place.
Was going to ask myself.
Minwoo, that fool needs to be taught
how to handle his alcohol.
Here...
I've really had it
with my father, Hyung.
Want me to do it?
Why did I have to be born his son?
I've never seen you act
like that with your father.
Do you really want to
become a film director that bad?
My father will never
give me his consent.
And I'll never
manage to convince him.
Thanks, Hyung.
You ended up getting a beating as well.
When you get him angry,
he just swings at everything in his way.
But why do you work
under someone like him?
Forget that and let's deal
with these bruises first.
A grown-ass man like you...
Does this even hurt?
Let me do it.
Hyung.
Shall we go somewhere
and take a photo?
Looking like this?
Why not?
Let's go, uh?
How nice it could have been,
if we hadn't met like this.
Is Minwoo still sleeping?
I tried to wake him up, to no avail.
Shall I give it a try?
We need to have breakfast,
so go wake him up.
Yes.
Just let him sleep.
He'll come down eventually.
All right.
How are you?
- I'd like to transfer some funds.
- Yes.
Yes, just a moment.
It's quite the amount?
Please, follow me.
Jo Minwoo.
Take a good look.
Dad...
Have you seen my account book?
Account book?!
What account is it?
It's important.
You didn't...
Hyung.
What happened last night at the bar?
You were drunk,
so we helped you get here.
Maybe it fell down in your room?
I looked everywhere,
but I couldn't find it.
Maybe you dropped it in the car?
Go take a look.
Minwoo...
Here's the key.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
I can't let you meet Minwoo any longer.
What's wrong with you two?
Why can't I?
Because our father!
Was killed by Jo Pilyeon.
Without Miju,
my life would be meaningless...
My stepmother did it.
To oust me from my heir position.
If the chairman doesn't show up
at the shareholders' meeting...
The testament will be presented.
I'd like you to
remain inside this room.
If Lee Gangmo ends up
seizing that money,
it only means that
there's a traitor among us.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com