Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
Gangnam.
South of the Han River.
These very brooklets,
once brimming with the sounds of calves,
became the prelude to an unprecedented
time of development, the likes of which...
the entire world still marvels at.
~ WITH S2 Presents ~
G I A N T
~ Episode 1 ~
In a mere forty-year span,
the value of Gangnam's land...
soared several hundreds
of a thousand-fold,
the battle to gain supremacy
in this golden land of opportunity...
more ruthless and wretched
than any war man had ever fought.
~ Chairman Lee Gangmo
wins at Global Business Awards ~
~ First Ever Korean
Awarded CEO of the Year ~
~ Hangang Construction Stocks
Continue to Rise ~
Chairman Lee!
Congratulations on winning the GBA!
They call this the Oscar
of the business sector,
can you give us your impressions?
Pundits argue that this award will improve
Hangang Construction's status internationally.
Give us a comment, Chairman Lee!
Can you comment on your feelings?
I merely gave my best to build
strong and reliable buildings.
And with that, I wish you a safe return.
Mister Chairman, just one more comment!
Mister Chairman.
We've been informed that Jo Pilyeon
escaped from the mental institution.
Ehh... Stubborn old fart.
As if he had that long to live...
He's not going to come
looking for you, is he?
Send home all employees
left in the building.
What?
It's been a long time.
Care for a drink?
Did you believe my downfall
would come so easily?
I'm Jo Pilyeon!
I'm not dead yet!
That...
That land they call Gangnam...
It is my creation.
I, Jo Pilyeon!
I sacrificed my own blood and tears
for the sake of our country's development.
And you stole all that from me.
You stole all my
achievements of a lifetime,
and the world I created!
If it weren't for you,
this city would have been
a much better place to live in.
What?
You people ruined it all.
While constantly yapping about
development and growth,
greed has blinded you all.
Shut your mouth!
You can act superior all you want,
but a bullet is all it'll take to silence you.
Kneel down and beg for survival.
I should have given your father
a chance to beg as well.
Had he begged me on that day,
I might have even spared him.
But it was all over in one shot,
blood spurting out of his chest.
You should have seen him.
Fine...
Go ahead and kill me.
Do it!
A finger is all it will take to make the man
who killed your father taste payback.
Pull that trigger.
Do it!
You can't kill me.
You don't have the courage to do so.
Murder is not for anyone.
If you have the guts,
go ahead and shoot me.
Shouldn't you avenge your father?
Come on.
Go ahead.
Do it!
And you want me to stain my hands
with that dirty blood of yours?
If you desire to die that much,
go ahead and jump off.
What?
If the city you always dreamed of
becomes your burial ground,
I'm sure you'll have nothing
to complain about.
Keep this in mind.
All the wicked sins
you people have committed...
will forever be remembered by that city.
You bastard...
You bastard!
"Just a look and my heart throbs."
~ "Pure 19" by Lee Mija ~
"Just a thought and my heart throbs."
"Ignore the blooming first love
of an innocent nineteen-year-old."
"So that nobody in the world will know."
Come here!
~ 1970, Busan ~
Where are you running to?
Hyung... Hyung.
Hyung, I didn't touch your piggy bank.
I swear.
Everyone knows you stole it.
- You little...
- Why are you hitting me?
Miju and I had been saving that money
to buy a birthday present for Mom.
Give it back.
Give it back!
Ahh... I said it wasn't me!
All right.
Awww... You're so nasty.
The hell will you buy with this?
Who's nastier here, you or us?
It hurts.
- Miju.
- Mommy!
Gangmo.
What did you do this time,
getting scolded again?
Mommy, Mommy...
Little Oppa took the piggy bank, and...
Gangmo.
Where are you going, again?
It's cold.
- Good job.
- Yes... See you tomorrow.
- See you.
- Yes, we're going.
If Lee is driving, should be all right?
He's honest and has a good reputation,
so it should be fine.
Right, that's that.
But you're sure the gold bars
are coming in this weekend, right?
Stop worrying.
When we're done with this,
no more smuggling.
- It's all done.
- Good job.
Bring these supplies
to the army base, and come back.
Yes, certainly.
Ahh... Right.
You know that we have more supplies
coming this weekend, right?
We're counting on you for that.
Aigoo... No need to mention it.
- Dad.
- Ahh... What the hell...
When did you jump in?
You little scoundrel, you came
to steal chocolate again, right?
Those fellas from earlier on,
they're smugglers.
What kind of nonsense
are you talking about?
I heard it all while hiding here,
and they talked about
smuggling gold bars this weekend.
Smuggling gold bars?
Are you sure they said gold bars?
Yes.
Thought I'd come and tell you right away,
since it's under your jurisdiction.
~ Chief of Security JO Pilyeon ~
You did the right thing.
We had been gathering evidence on
a smuggling ring within the base.
And now it's not just flour
or saccharine, but gold bars?
Let's deal with it ourselves without
getting the police or the military involved.
That's right.
What did you say your name was?
Lee Gangmo, Sir.
Right, Gangmo.
We really appreciate what you did today.
This is not much,
but here's your reward.
It's all right.
It was our duty to report that.
No.
With our country facing
such economic difficulties,
what he did will really help us.
Here, take it.
Thank you.
Mommy, over there.
Take a look.
They sure are pretty.
Ohh... I'm doing fine.
How about you?
~ Director HWANG Taeseop ~
Yeah, things are going fine here,
so stop worrying.
I told you to wait just a little.
All the land in Gangnam you bought...
will turn into gold in no time.
Yeah...
Okay, I'll see you around.
How did it go?
The bank said they will not
lend us any more money.
Tell them we'll pay double
the interest rate!
We promised we'd foot the rest
of the bill by the end of the month.
If we keep leaning onto the bank,
we might lose all
the building lots we have.
How did it go?
What did Park from Wangshim-Ri say?
Don't get me started.
The moment I mentioned money,
I was kicked out of the door.
And Director Choi?
Choi from Myeongdong.
He even refuses to meet me.
I'll be damned.
~ Manbo Construction ~
What are you looking at?
There isn't a single one I like.
You're hungry, aren't you?
What should we get?
Let's go.
- Four gukbap*.
- Yes.
*boiled rice with soup
We're five,
why are you ordering only four?
Miju can't finish a serving by herself.
Just ask for another bowl of rice.
No way! I'm going to finish
one serving all by myself!
Have one with me,
I can't finish it all.
Still, it's your birthday.
Dad, let's go for some meat.
I want pork ribs.
They serve beef soup here as well.
Your belly will fill up anyway,
so just be quiet and eat.
Mommy, happy birthday.
What is this?
Oh my...
It's a silver ring?!
Did you buy this?
Not Little Oppa, just Big Oppa and me.
My... And what money
could you possibly have?
Happy birthday, Mom.
Thanks.
It's so pretty...
Give me that ring.
Come on.
This ring doesn't suit you.
Dad...
Daddy!
Dad is right.
It's too damn corny.
You be quiet.
Dad, we bought it for her.
It doesn't even suit her,
why even bother wasting money?
You're such a cheapskate.
Like that Scrooge fella.
I told you we'd move to Seoul, right?
So don't even think
about wasting money like that.
Your father is right.
It'd be much better to buy a
few sacks of barley with that money.
Go get your refund.
Here's your gukbap.
Here... I'm hungry. Let's eat!
But, that friend of yours, Hwang Taeseop.
Are you sure he's trustworthy?
I told you!
He's a friend from my hometown,
and we found refuge together during the war.
Why, do you trust
all your hometown friends?
Ehh Ehh! Did you meet today
for the first time, or something?
Let's see some smiles, shall we?
Ehh Ehh...
Who asked you to cry? Smile!
Hyung. Give me that hat.
There... Nice, nice!
We're set...
Here... I'm shooting.
1... 2... 3!
The Defense Ministry just
announced their personnel changes.
Aren't they going too far?
Considering results or any other criteria,
a promotion was a no-brainer,
but they appoint you to
Samcheok's outskirts out of the blue?
If you end up leaving,
I'll hang up my boots.
Jaechun.
How about we stake our careers
to really make it big, for once?
What?
If you want to succeed in this field,
you need to establish connections
with the central agency,
and to achieve that you need money.
Which is why people with neither
money nor connections like us...
are destined to play second fiddle in
the countryside for the rest of our careers.
But where would we find the money?
Gold bars.
What?
The gold bars which
are about to be smuggled.
With that gold in our hands,
be it the Blue House,
the Defense Ministry or the KCIA*,
*Korean Central Intelligence Agency
any important post could be ours.
But, Chief...
What if something happens?
Of course we can't do this firsthand.
We need someone to get
his hands dirty on our behalf.
I still haven't been able to.
You want me to come down to Busan?
Because the situation here is urgent...
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
Of all people to send there,
why call me again?
Honey.
Going somewhere?
Jeongyeon, you came, too?
Dad, I came as well.
Just sit.
Honey, come here and have some.
They're sweet potatoes.
You can't imagine how tasty they are.
Jeongyeon.
Have one yourself.
You said you had this friend, right?
The wife of Dongyang Dyes' Director Hwang.
Think she could manage
to lend me some money right away?
Her? She got divorced last year
after having an affair.
Have some of this.
Here.
Think I have time
to eat potatoes, you brat?
Ahh... You scared me to death.
I was just offering you some potatoes,
why scream at me?!
Aigoo... Really!
How can a little brat
always be so hungry?
- Jeongshik.
- Ohh, Mom.
What's that, were you staring at me?
Where is my mother?
She's here, where else?
Didn't ask for my stepmother.
What?
Stepmother?!
I mean my birth mother.
You little brat, I just ought to...
You kicked my mother out
and took her place.
I don't care if your mouth got all warped,
but let's speak the truth.
I didn't kick her out,
she just gave birth to you outside
and you were brought in.
Mom, I want more.
Ohh... Sure.
Here you go.
If you really want to meet your mother,
go to Daejeon and find her yourself.
I bet after abandoning you
she'll be ecstatic to meet again.
It's driving me crazy as well.
If I don't settle my back payments
by the end of the month...
That doesn't concern me.
Give me my money back
and pay the penalty.
Chief...
I invested everything I had and more,
because you gave me your word.
Think that you can get away
with making me lose money?
If we manage to overcome this crisis,
you'll make ten times... no...
a few dozen times your initial investment.
Then overcome that crisis,
even if you have to sell your heart to do it.
If I could only do so,
I'd sell my every organ.
There could be one way...
To find all that money?
Go ahead and tell me.
If I can finish this construction,
I'll do everything.
Smuggled gold bars will
soon reach the harbor here.
If we arrest those smugglers,
the bars will be seized as state property.
But if we close an eye,
then they can be ours.
So are you suggesting
we steal those gold bars?
It's not like...
we'd be forced to report them.
So first come, first served, isn't it?
But... How can we?
I'll watch your back, so you do it.
Me?!
You need to survive
through this, don't you?
How about it?
Want to stake your life for it?
Is it...
something I can do?
In life,
there is nothing people can't do,
when they set their hearts on it.
The truck driver will
transport the gold bars.
Kill him, and seize those bars.
Must I really go this far?!
Are you asking me to kill someone?
Why do things always
end up so messed up?!
Hey...
Taeseop.
What brings you here so suddenly?
It's you?
Here...
Have a drink.
Is something going on?
It's just that nothing
ever seems to go right...
I really...
Listen to him.
Think of how we survived
that battlefield, will you?
Just the fact we crossed
the 38th buck naked...
and made it all the
way here is remarkable.
You sure could call it that.
Killing and being killed...
That's no big deal.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Daesoo.
Whatever it takes, I'm going to succeed.
Can't we just make money working like dogs,
and spend it like kings?
I can do it.
I, Hwang Taeseop,
can do that.
You trust me, don't you?
You know that I can do anything
if I really want to,
don't you?
Of course!
I don't really know what's going on,
but if it's something
even Hwang Taeseop can't do,
then nobody can.
Right...
Thanks.
You're the only one I can count on.
Bean curd!
Do you really have to go at this hour?
I knew something was up last night...
Honey, have a seat.
Thanks.
Ever since you met me,
you haven't had anything tasty,
and had to wear shabby clothes,
but you never complained even once.
You did all the hard work...
Just endure it a little longer.
Once prices of land in
Apgujeong-Dong start moving,
we'll be able to get our own room.
We'll eat all the pork ribs we want,
send the kids to college,
and live a nice life.
Ahh... How nasty...
You make people cry
right from the morning?
This must be expensive,
where did you find all that money?
Ahh... I shouldn't tell you this.
Actually, it was Gangmo who bought this.
Ehh... And where would
Gangmo find that money?
Because he did something to
help our economy, he was rewarded.
What are you talking about?
Let's just leave it at that,
I'll tell you later.
Dad, let's go.
I told you to stay home.
I heard it from Gangmo,
about you and the smugg...
Heard what?
It's nothing.
We'll get going.
I'll be late.
I'll make your favorite, kimchi jjigae.
Since we're there,
how about a bottle of soju?
You beat me, this time.
We'll get going.
See you tonight.
Aigoo...
My belly...
Follow us.
Yes.
What if they find out we
reported them and try to hurt us?
If people were afraid of doing that much,
then nobody would ever try
to do the right thing.
Seongmo.
You're the eldest.
Uh?!
When Dad gets old,
you'll become the head of our family.
And you know what's
the most important thing?
It's courage.
Courage.
The courage to protect your family.
To feed and support them.
The courage to sacrifice for them.
You need courage to lead your family.
Always bear that in mind, uh?
Yes.
Mommy, don't die!
Push! Do it!
Aigoo... you brat!
You're making more noise than her! Get out.
Water... Water.
Aigoo... Are you out of your mind?
Go fetch some cold water.
Cold?
Aigoo...
Where the hell is your father?
Push...
Move them!
Stay inside and don't come out.
What's this?
Hey...
Lee Daesoo!
What are you doing here?
So you were sent by the Security Command?
Ahh... Really...
We can save the details for later,
so let's take all this down.
Hey... You!
Of all people, why you?
Of all the people who could be here,
why did it have to be you?
What's wrong with you?
Listen well.
They're not investigating
a smuggling case.
They're just trying to steal that!
You understand what I'm saying?
Hey.
Take your family
and go to Seoul right now.
I'll take care of things here,
so get going.
Now!
Then... You were in
on all this from the start?
I... need money.
We're about to lose all that land
you bought in Gangnam, you fool.
Go! We have no time, you fool!
I'm going to bring this
to the police right away.
Hey!
Lee Daesoo!
Even if that makes me a beggar,
I have no intention of becoming
a father my sons can't respect.
Aigoo... You fool!
Why don't you listen to me?
Keep it up and you'll die!
Hey... They're here...
Hey!
Hey... Listen...
Taeseop.
Run...
Run away!
I can't kill you with my own hands.
Hey... I beg you...
Run away, you fool!
Who's there?
Get him.
See? Before you forced me to,
you should have shot him.
You saw me kill him,
so I can't allow you to survive.
Why can't you be a little more honest?
Just say that, from the very start,
you planned to use me
and then get rid of me.
Isn't that right?
But... You barked up the wrong tree.
I'm not going to die
as easily as that fella.
I'm not going to die that way!
Really?
Then...
Shall we find out?
Look...
It'd just be a waste to kill me this way.
With a businessman
like me by your side...
That... Those gold bars...
will be nothing compared
to the money you can make.
I'm a very ambitious man.
Can you satisfy all those ambitions?
If you spare me...
Whatever I'll end up doing,
I will always be loyal to you.
So... Please...
Don't kill me.
From now on, we're partners.
Make sure our construction
business in Gangnam flourishes.
That is, I want to see
money pouring down on me.
Is that clear, Director Hwang?
I apologize.
He must have seen us for sure.
By any chance,
do you have anyone in mind?
I really have no idea.
I'll take care of things here,
so go back to Seoul.
Prepare to leave.
Yes.
Dad...
What brings you here?
My father...
Your father what?
got drunk...
He got drunk,
and beat up your mother?
Yes...
So, like... You want us
to go and stop them from arguing?
We're too busy now,
so why don't you
ask a neighbor to do that?
- Then, I'll get going.
- Why don't you join me for lunch?
No. Let's do it next time.
~ Jo Pilyeon ~
This is someone
we must arrest at all cost.
- So we ask you to spare no effort.
- Ahh... Of course!
You needn't even mention it.
- I'll be counting on you, then.
- Yes.
Hyung.
Oppa...
Where's your father?
Dead?!
Your father is dead?
Aigoo... I ought to just...
And you expect us to believe that?
Fine... Let's suppose he really did.
Who killed him?
If he died, someone must have killed him.
Jo Pilyeon.
What?
Jo Pilyeon?
He's some high-ranking officer for sure,
and his name is Jo Pilyeon.
What is this?
Chief of Security Jo Pilyeon?!
Are you sure it was Jo Pilyeon?
If that wasn't the case,
how would I know his name?
Tell me.
Where is your father,
and who were those people?
I said speak to me!
Where is your father?
He passed away.
What?
Dad...
is dead.
- Mom... Mom...
- Mommy!
- Mom...
- Mom!
- Mom, wake up!
Mom!
What brings you here?
We won't beat around the bush.
Let's split those goods.
You stole smuggled goods,
so we are no different.
And if we do split,
my share?
It's the four of us and you,
so one-fifth each.
One-fifth each...
I'm thankful.
But...
There is something
you don't seem to understand.
I didn't steal the goods you smuggled,
but merely confiscated them.
What are you waiting for?
Arrest them for smuggling!
Yes, Chief.
On your knees, you pricks.
I said on your knees!
Don't think you can fool me
and get away with it.
A word from me is all it takes
for your life to end in misery.
We will give you half those gold bars.
Half?
Take them away,
and report to our superiors.
Yes, Chief.
Tell us the amount you want.
We will give you whatever you ask.
What is it that you want?
To never see human trash like you...
stink up the society our president
worked so hard to bring us.
What are you waiting for?
Get up, you pricks!
We will give it all to you.
Without a single condition,
we will give everything to you.
So spare us.
I'll decide for you.
80 to 20.
Eighty for me, twenty for you.
If you think of it as
the price for your survival,
I'm sure you won't feel cheated.
But who's the man who saw me,
from inside the truck?
What?
Wasn't it one of you?
Did you tell them?
Yes.
We can't stay here any longer.
Mom...
Pack up a few clothes.
What's wrong, Mom?
Didn't you say both the smugglers,
those people and the Chief of Police
are on the same boat?
There's no time.
Get moving! Now!
Of all people who could see us, his son?!
Don't worry.
They'll catch him soon.
And when they do, then what?
You must get rid of him.
You must get rid of everyone
who saw me kill him, is that clear?
Seems like they already ran away?
To the station!
~ Seoul  Busan ~
Over there!
Step out!
Pull yourselves up.
We're going to Seoul.
With the land Daddy bought in Gangnam,
we will have no problem making a living.
Even without him,
I'll send you all to college,
and marry you off.
You don't need to worry.
And Dad?
How about his body?
Can we just run away by ourselves?
We can just...
come back for it later.
Later...
We'll find those people
and make them pay for what they did,
and after that,
we can take care of him.
Hey...
If I knew it'd be you, you fool...
I wouldn't even have gone there.
You know that I mean it, right?
Of all people...
Of all people, why did you show up?
You died because of me.
It's my fault you died.
Because of this stupid fool,
you ended up dying.
So?
So what, you prick?
You...
You are already dead!
Fine...
Forget the dead,
as the living must go on.
I even had to get you killed
for this opportunity.
I, Hwang Taeseop!
Will succeed at all cost!
All the money in this world...
will end up in my hands.
Hey... Buddy.
Even if from down there,
you must take a good look.
Uh?!
How I succeed...
And how I hold the world
in the palm of my hands!
Open your eyes
and take a good look, you fool!
Hey...
Daesoo.
Lee Daesoo!
Why don't you answer me?
Answer me...
Don't cry.
I said don't cry.
~ Daejeon Station ~
The current stop is Daejeon Station.
Gangmo.
Get up.
Mom!
- Mom.
- Mom...
- Mom, wake up.
- They're here.
Take this. Come on.
Gangmo.
Listen well.
The moment the train starts again,
you and Mom step out.
- Understood?
- Hyung...
Seongmo, and you?
If we all do it, they'll catch us.
I'll buy time luring them
on the opposite side,
so go ahead first
and take Mom to Seoul.
Then, how are we going to meet?
At the end of this month,
let's meet on top of
Seoul's tallest building.
Got it?
There's no time, go!
Seongmo...
We'll meet again soon.
Hey!
Ohh? That...
Mom, stay here a moment with Miju.
Hyung!
Go!
Don't forget our promise, Hyung!
We must meet again!
Hyung!
Jo Pilyeon is the one
who took the gold bars.
Why are you going after us?
You just shouldn't have
witnessed your father's death.
So...
is that why you want us dead?
But...
Where's the rest of your family?
That...
Go tell Jo Pilyeon.
That one day I will come back
to avenge my father.
That crazy fool...
- Mommy...
- Mom!
Oppa, Mommy is burning.
~ Inn ~
Ajumma.
Give us a room.
We only have two large ones here.
One for women, the other for men.
Mom, go in first.
- You have enough money?
- Yeah.
Miju...
How much is it?
It's 200 won each,
so that'll be 800 for all of you.
That expensive?!
Then go somewhere else.
When the last train goes,
there'll be no empty rooms anywhere.
By the way...
Why is it 800 won?
We're only three, so it should be 600.
What about what she's embracing?
Even the baby needs to pay?
If the baby wakes up and starts crying,
what if all the other
customers start leaving?
I even give you a room out of courtesy...
So are you staying or what?
Three women only.
And you're not staying?
The train for Busan will soon depart,
so we encourage all passengers
to head for the appropriate exit.
The train for Busan will soon depart,
so we encourage all passengers
to head for the appropriate exit.
They must be around here for sure.
Let's ransack the whole place tomorrow.
What could have happened to him?
When you have a death wish,
anything is possible.
Crazy fool...
Jumping off a moving train...
Go away.
Now!
This is the women's room.
You're the one who should leave.
You're a pickpocket, aren't you?
What?
If you go around here stealing,
you must be familiar with this place?!
I'm looking for someone,
but I've never been here before.
Will you help me out?
You don't even have
a place to sleep, anyway.
Looks like you need money,
so I'll give you a thousand won.
You little brat...
1,500.
Can't go higher than that.
I don't need any of that,
so get out of my face.
Really?
Too bad, then.
Ajeosshi! There's a...
Who are you touching
with those dirty hands?
You thief...
I'm not a thief.
Then, what are you?
Lee Gangmo.
The name my father gave me...
is Lee Gangmo.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
Translator/Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editing/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com