Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 47
Chief Yoon.
Don't tell me you don't know.
Chief Lee is just a workaholic,
it's all he has eyes for.
So what is this thing
only you are aware of?
There is no such thing.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Hey... Yoo Chanseong!
Think about it.
He could have been using you.
Don't you think you're
crossing the line here?
I mean... How can you accuse him of
being a spy after all you've gone through?
Lee Seongmo is going through
a polygraph test as we speak.
A polygraph test?!
I know how close you two are.
So hide even the smallest detail, and...
Do as you damn please!
Have you bugged
Yoo Chanseong's phone?
Yes.
Yoo Chanseong just left.
Stick to him.
Are you ready?
Let's begin with a little warm-up.
Name, Lee Seongmo.
Yes.
Working for the ANSP.
Do you pride yourself on having given
your very best for the sake of your country?
I suddenly get the feeling that
it all might have been in vain.
You know Congressman Min
Honggi quite well, don't you?
You know that he worked here.
I hear Congressman Min has formed a
faction of sorts among fellow party members.
Have you heard
of his mountaineering club?
Yes.
You know who the members are?
More or less.
List them.
Congressman Lee Gilbok.
Congressman Lee Changmin.
Congressman Jang Youngcheol.
Congressman Kang Soonhwi.
Congressman Kwon Haeryong.
Congressman Kim Suhwe.
Congressman Yoo Inshik.
It's me.
Ahh... Chief Lee.
I'm heading to the
police station right now.
Hello?
Yoo Chanseong.
That man you have there in custody...
is the chairman of a top labor union.
Hold him until I get there.
I will do the questioning.
All right.
Are you going to meet?
Seems like they're trailing him.
Or maybe he's been bugged.
Then, you can't meet?
Weren't you going to ask
for news of your brother?
I'll have to head to the police station.
Help me out.
How many times do I have to tell you?
This prick here suddenly started hitting me.
You were the first who started
bitching that I was eating too much!
Then you could just stop stuffing
yourself like a goddamned pig.
Wh... What? Pig?
You little rat, I ought to just...
Sure... Go ahead.
Hit me? Guess you've made
enough money to cover for this?
The hell is this, your living room?
Mister Detective, why
don't you check his records?
Look at this mug, will you?
There's "jailbird" written all over it.
You son of a cunt...
The hell is this?
What is all this list? He's even
been to the Samcheong camp?!
See?
Told you he was a jailbird.
Excuse me.
Come on in.
I'll be questioning him,
so don't let anyone in.
But he was the one who reported them?
He's a suspect I had been trailing.
Follow me.
- What the hell?
- I'm so sorry.
Allow me to apologize.
Ahh... No...
It was all my fault.
I will press no charges.
We'll just consider this settled and go.
Shall we go?
The hell is wrong with them?
Hey!
Right as recorded,
he entered the police station.
Keep checking on him.
Have you ever engaged
in activities against national interest?
Never.
What do you think about
direct presidential elections?
I oppose them.
We recently planned a wiretap mission
at Jeil Hotel's Chinese restaurant.
They knew already, right?
Let me rephrase it.
Did you leak details
of this mission to anyone?
Answer!
I never did such thing.
You were involved in missions dealing
with that secret fund, right?
I'd like a more specific question.
We already know everything.
Then I'm sure you're also aware
of whom that secret fund belongs to.
Hey... Lee Seongmo!
Let me ask you just one thing.
Is the director aware of this?
Or was Chief Oh behind this?
Look... I ask the questions.
There are things you
can't say even at gunpoint!
So if you really want to hear about
that, bring me the director first.
Bear this in mind.
The moment I reveal any
detail about this secret fund,
anyone who ordered
you to investigate on this...
will have to pay a
hefty price for what they did.
A polygraph?!
Are you telling me they're
forcing a polygraph test on him?
You don't need to worry about that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Is your name Lee Seongmo?
Yes.
Do you have any family?
No.
The polygraph checks for any minute
alteration in breathing, skin responses,
pulse and blood pressure
occurring right as you lie.
Any way to neutralize it?
When forced by the situation to lie,
KGB and CIA agents reply while
thinking of times tables and the like.
So they avoid any such alteration
by thinking of something else.
- Is that it?
- That's right.
Or else they stimulate a
meridian point under their feet...
to deliberately lower their blood pressure.
Let's give it another try, then.
Do you want to get
revenge against Jo Pilyeon?
I don't.
I trained him extensively,
so most polygraph tests won't work.
Entrusting the account to me was a good move.
Without any material evidence on
their hands, they can't do anything to him.
Who is behind all this?
It has to be Jo Pilyeon.
I saw Go Jaechun in the
hallway of the ANSP offices.
Give me that account.
That's out of the question.
If Jo Pilyeon is suspecting him,
my brother won't get out so easily.
Not to mention that if they
even bugged your phones...
Do anything reckless and
you could get hurt as well.
The account is in a safe place,
so don't worry.
Should anything happen to
my brother, call me right away.
You saw wrong.
It wasn't Lee Seongmo.
I'll just release him.
Nah.
You must get a confession out of him.
Even if all the allegations we
throw at him are unfounded?
He's way too good at this.
It almost feels as if someone
trained him on how to deceive polygraphs.
Seongmo is an agent with years
of specialized training under his belt.
Even if they brought him up north,
he wouldn't start talking so easily.
You do have a point,
but to be really honest,
this secret fund account is
way too big an issue for me to handle.
Lee Seongmo earned the
respect of most ANSP agents.
If people learn of this, we would
have to deal with plenty of headaches.
What's wrong, Chief Oh?
This is a tug o' war.
Are you already letting Lee
Seongmo gain the advantage?
But should our guesses be wrong...
At times, intuition can beat reason.
This is like fishing.
It's a fight requiring time and patience.
- Manbo Construction Boiler Factory -
Here is where Manbo Construction's
boiler factory will be built.
Our negotiations with
subcontractors are proceeding smoothly.
The most evident flaw of
ondol-based Korean-style boilers...
is their inter-floor water pressure gap.
Should water reach boiling
point between two floors,
it would make the pipes expand, which
is one of the problems we must deal with.
We already solved that problem.
Because of the height of inter-floor
space in Korean apartments,
we developed a mechanism enabling
us to keep water at a uniform pressure.
All we need to do is adding
an expansion tank to be used...
whenever water reaches the boiling point.
That's impressive.
That's all good,
but you should also research
some kind of mechanism...
set up like a sprinkler,
activating itself in case of gas leaks.
All right, Chairman.
Manbo Construction already found
a building lot for their boiler factory.
What?!
If they're already at that stage,
doesn't it mean they're proceeding
at a much faster pace than us?
Like it would be that easy?!
Even someone like Director Yang is
having trouble finding a solution.
But if they stole our core
technology, it is more than likely.
If only Factory Manager
Lee Seonggu was still with us...
Why look for someone who stole
our own technology on his way out?
I ought to just beat
that sorry-ass cunt to a pulp...
Did Lee Seonggu join Manbo Construction?
I think he is still unemployed
to avoid any suspicion.
Aren't you being excessive now?
How many times do I have to
tell you to wait until the factory is complete?
I already spent all the money
you gave me for my son's surgery.
If you could only help me out
with the rest of his hospital bills...
Hello?
Where have you been?
Why?
Someone came earlier on, and
settled all hospital bills for this month.
Who was that?
He just said you know him well...
That's right.
Now that's more like it.
Manbo Construction
would never abandon me.
- Cha Soojeong Earrings/Necklaces -
- Cha Soojeong -
Open it.
Wow... Almost looks real.
Even if a fake, it's still pretty.
Don't you even know what a man
giving you a ring means?
I don't think I can accept it.
Give me your hand.
Are you telling me you're just going to
forsake your parents because of me?
Minwoo...
See? Why force it...
That's a real diamond.
What?!
Why are you only telling me now?
Have you lost something?
Stay away!
Please, don't come here.
Hey... Is a diamond
more important than...
I found it!
If I lost it,
I don't know what I'd have done...
So you chose Soojeong
as model for your new opening?
Yes.
Here are the conditions we can offer.
When will the final decision be made?
With your consent, we'll have a board
meeting and decide by the end of the week.
So you will give me ten percent of proceeds?
Yes.
When the final decision is made,
I'd like to be paid sixty
million won upfront...
Would that be possible?
Yes, I'm sure there will be no problems.
Then I will sign.
Thank you.
We will inform you
once the final decision is made.
This is great, Miju.
Only a week, and you'll be able
to pay Manbo Construction.
I'm so happy.
These days,
you're hitting the jackpot.
We owe all this to you.
Excuse me, you are...
Di... Di... Director Moon...
I am Moon Seongjoong
of Manbo Construction.
What brings you here?
We have a meeting to
discuss concepts for our ad,
and we require your presence as well.
I've already paid part of the signing fee.
But because the contract
hasn't been resolved yet,
you will have to fulfill our requests.
I will pay you the rest in a week.
- If you could only wait...
- Soon...
Our sale will begin,
and should we incur
any losses because of you,
you will not only have to pay the signing fee,
but you will also be sued for damages.
This is all because of you.
Why did you hear their name
wrong and caused all this?
Soojeong, I'm sorry.
Even if this gets me fired, I'll just...
Nevermind, that won't be necessary.
Can I come right now?
If what I said sounded
intimidating, allow me to apologize.
If meeting the chairman personally
is too much of a burden,
he told me you won't be
forced to abide by that clause.
He sincerely wants to help you.
As someone who's been serving
under him for years, Miss Soojeong...
No...
I hope you will try to
understand that, Miss Lee Miju.
Chairman.
I brought Miss Cha.
I'd like to have a word with you.
Director Moon, have you explained everything?
Yes.
So I'm sure we have
nothing else to talk about.
Let's go.
The concept of this ad is
emphasizing the major strengths...
of our ondol gas
boilers under development.
After coming in, Cha Soojeong
will remove the thick coat she's wearing,
to reveal light clothing instead.
Then she will look at the camera and say,
"This is how you want
to dress at home, right?"
And with that comment,
the ad will conclude.
Chairman, these were
the concepts we prepared.
They all have merit.
Miss Cha.
Which one do you prefer?
I apologize.
I...
don't really know much about ads.
This ad will only be
effective if it suits your image.
So there's no need to make it
complicated, just speak your mind.
I liked Mister Seo's concept the most.
Director Moon.
Add snow to Mister Seo's concept.
It would be better to add traces
of snow to Miss Cha's hair and clothes.
All right, Chairman.
Ahh... Director Moon,
please drive Miss Cha home.
Certainly, Chairman.
That won't be necessary.
Fine, then.
Here, let's wrap this up.
Good job, everyone.
Director Moon.
Could you find out how Lee Miju
has been living the last four years?
Her manager doesn't seem to know much,
but I'll hire a pro to dig into this.
I'll be counting on you.
Yes, Chairman.
Soojeong!
How did it go?
When is the shoot?
This weekend.
What now...
We won't be able to
pay all the rest by then.
Forget that, how about you
tell this to your brother Gangmo?
I don't want him
to get involved in this.
I'll just have to find
a way to delay that shoot.
How is Lee Seongmo?
He's just looking for you.
Seongmo.
Congressman.
I just heard the news.
I asked to see you.
I'd like to have a
word with him in private,
don't tell me you
don't trust me either?!
I'll take full responsibility.
I really can't figure this out.
Why is the ANSP trying to dig
into the secret presidential fund?
Seems like opposition party
members have talked about its existence.
Wasn't it a well known rumor by now?
The problem is that they talked of
an account regarding that fund.
An account?!
Is there such a thing?
Was anyone other than
me involved in the fund-raising?
No.
No one.
It was just you and I.
This has to be some kind of conspiracy.
Is that what you think?
Unless that wasn't the case,
how could such an account even exist?
Were there any witnesses?
Seongmo.
How about you
just give us that account?
So you're suspecting me.
Anyone could write an account.
Not to mention the fact that for someone
who's been spending so long in this trade,
writing one would be a habit by now.
Congressman.
Unless that account is found,
they won't let you get out of here.
Am I making myself clear?
Only if that account comes
out will all this pass us by,
and you'll be able
to safely walk out of here.
Don't tell me that you showed
that account to someone else?!
For instance, someone like Min Honggi.
Should this rumor reach the president,
you would be the one
most affected by this all.
It is all a complot by someone
who is trying to bring you harm.
Should we fail to find him,
I will take all the blame instead.
That would be much wiser.
Just say I was the one
who wrote that account.
Seongmo.
I know what you're feeling.
However, how could I let you sacrifice
yourself just for my sake?
Conspiracy or not,
the culprit will soon be caught.
And I will be the
one who catches him.
If you need any help,
don't hesitate to call me.
Chief Oh gave us his consent.
Sitting face to face like
that is not going to work.
Change the cards.
What's that supposed to mean?
There's that certain
something you folks are good at.
You want me to torture Lee Seongmo?
If psychological coercion doesn't work,
you need to get physical.
Don't you know in what kind
of atmosphere we work these days?
If things go wrong,
I'll be blamed for everything.
I'll talk to Director Kim.
I can introduce you to a team
that can handle Lee Seongmo.
The Seobinggo Anti-Communist
unit is perfect. They're pro's at this.
Look, Chief Oh.
It's not for me that you're
working, but for the president's sake.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity for you.
Here.
You'll have to give
these fellas special treatment.
Is that clear?
Don't you worry, President.
We should be the ones treating you...
Aigoo... Don't even say that.
I've found myself such esteemed
new customers, so I should be the one.
Director Yoo, what brings you here?
So President Noh was the reason
why you refuse to deal with us again?
It is thanks to the late Baekpa's
money that you made it this big!
How can you end a twenty year
long partnership in a matter of...
Why do people call it "currency"?!
Because it can change course
depending on the tide, don't you think?
These gentlemen are now my clients.
Is that how you're going to fight me off?
I'm just running a business here.
I hear you've been hit
by some heavy taxes...
So should you need any assistance,
I'd be more than glad to help you.
I would never ignore your pleas.
Ohh... I guess we ruined the mood.
Here... Let's have a drink.
Find anything you
can about that Noh Gapsoo.
All right, Oppa.
I said just lie down.
It's just a little fatigue, I'm all right.
Ehh Ehh... You really.
Come here, I'll massage your shoulders.
I said I'm all right.
I said come here.
I know all the hardships you're going
through because of your business.
You've brought me back to life,
but this is all I can do for you...
This is more than enough for me.
Director.
It's me.
Director, are you sleeping?
Co... Come on in.
Dad...
What are you doing here so early?
Ohh... I... well... had something
to talk about with her.
What brings you here?
Have a seat.
I will host the upcoming
Olympic Games event in Seoul.
- Business Plan -
88 Seoul Olympics Funding Committee's
"A Night for Blue Seoul"
I thought this was a really important event?!
So they entrusted this to you?
Yes.
A who's who of our
country's financial world will be there.
Will politicians be there as well?
I'd like to,
but Deputy Mayor Han
Myeongseok is against it.
Considering how delicate
the political situation is as of late...
To establish your credit institution,
securing a clientele is paramount.
Which is why I plan to use this
event to raise at least five billion.
You haven't had lunch yet, right?
There's this fine traditional
restaurant down the street...
Let's go there.
Let's have lunch together.
I'm hungry, Dad.
Jeong...shik...
You must live...
a better life than Jeongyeon.
Don't you ever let
them look down on you,
and live a much
better life than Jeongyeon.
You smile?!
After causing my mother's death,
you have the courage to smile?
I will make you pay for forcing
my mother to cry on her last moments.
Only then she will be
able to smile in the afterlife.
Where are you taking me?
I told you.
Chief Oh said he wants
to have a drink with you.
Spare me all this, Park Seonbae.
I might not be the
sharpest knife in the drawer,
but I can certainly
sense when things smell fishy.
Chief Lee, why don't you quietly follow us?
Before you force us to carry you there.
Don't act all haughty with me, you prick!
Who said you could order me around?
Don't make a scene and cooperate.
Don't resent us.
We didn't want this, either.
If they can't prove anything, then I'm
afraid I'll ignore the fact you're my colleague.
All the top fifty corporations
in our country will be invited.
And Hangang Construction will be top of the list.
Can you really do that?
We probably won't even make the Top 100?
I'm the host, so I decide.
You will be the first to be invited.
And I bet you'll cast aside some
very prominent people...
and end up sitting right in front?!
That's an honor?!
Just our being invited
there will be of great help to us.
So now I paid it back, just a little.
The debt I had with you.
Gangmo.
Hurry up and call this number.
What is it?
It's Chanseong.
It seemed really urgent.
Can I use the phone?
Things have taken
a turn for the worse.
The chief was taken to
the Seobinggo underground bunker.
Tell me what happened.
Where is that account?
Tell me.
If we don't do anything,
my brother could die!
The 1st Yeongdeungpo subway line,
safety box number 14.
And the key?
All right.
I'll call again if I need your help.
Your brother might die?!
What's that supposed to mean?
There is no time.
See you later.
Gangmo!
Are you going to save
your brother with those?
Gangmo...
If we were dealing with gangsters,
we could have helped you.
But I don't think this is going to work.
I mean... I'm not saying we
should ignore your brother's situation.
Still, there are things you just can't do...
You just worry about the company.
I'll handle this.
How can you say that?
We're in this together.
Why don't we
give this to some politician?
- Wouldn't they handle it...
- Then, my brother will die!
So how about it...
Do we finally remember
where that account has gone?
Aren't you a pro yourself?
So let's not waste
each other's time, shall we?
You will give up before I do.
And I will remember...
all your faces.
Let me help you.
Just tell me what I can do.
Have you been listening?
I told you it's dangerous.
But you're still planning to do it.
- Jeongyeon...
- If we're dealing with Jo Pilyeon,
then I just can't ignore this.
You're mistaken.
This is not Jo Pilyeon's doing.
What's that supposed to mean?
Wasn't that money connected to him?
That secret fund...
belongs to the most
powerful man in this country.
And a complicated web
of political connections is behind it.
Not to mention the fact that
anyone involved with it might die.
- So, all the more reason why...
- Knowing it could kill you,
you still came to my rescue.
When they were holding me hostage,
you put your life on the
line and still came there.
If whom you're dealing
with is as scary as you say,
then I don't want
you to fight by yourself.
I'll never allow that.
You still can't.
Not this time.
- 88 Seoul Olympics Support Committee -
Didn't we agree we
wouldn't invite politicians?
This entire event is my responsibility.
So if you entrusted it to me,
I'd like you to let me decide on my own.
I mean,
these days the strife between ruling
and opposition party is reaching the limit.
Haven't you entertained the
thought that inviting them here...
could have an adverse
effect on the entire event?
I'll take full responsibility for that.
Let me hear why you're
insisting to do this, then.
You need flowers to attract butterflies.
Without powerful politicians participating,
a good number of businessmen
might not show up at all.
I think the pivotal point of
this event is public acceptance.
We must increase the scope of our
funding committee as much as possible.
There is even a singer on the list?!
I thought we could invite Jo Yongpil.
A top singer like him suits
this kind of event perfectly.
About the singer to invite...
Could you leave that decision to me?
Do you happen to be familiar
with a certain Cha Soojeong?
Cha... Soojeong?
Yes...
You know, she's one of the
hottest newcomers these days.
I actually think someone like
her would fit our event a lot more.
Then, you'll let me invite
politicians as well, right?
Well... Let's give it a try.
There is a way to save my brother?!
I will invite members of both
parties at this fund-raising event I'm hosting.
I will have to leave concrete plans to you,
but wouldn't that help?
It's me.
Go ahead.
Was Min Honggi the politician
who was helping my brother?
It's not him.
It was Chairman Hwang Taeseop.
Why would he join forces with Chairman Hwang?
It would be better for you not to know.
Keep informing me of any new development.
We'll have to find another
way to get in touch.
Many of our mountaineering club
members are becoming agitated.
There are even rumors that the ruling party is
trying to find all sympathizers of the amendment.
Isn't that the reason I asked to meet you?
- Let's begin by calming them down...
- Why don't we just forget all this?
What's wrong with
you, Congressman Park?
In this atmosphere, I'm not going
to approve any amendment, either.
Congressman Kang!
The longer your tail, the easier to find you.
How about we just
break up this club altogether...
What did I miss?
I... I better go.
These days, whenever you see
groups of two-three people talking,
they always seem to
criticize the government.
I'm sure ruling party members
aren't joining in on the fun?!
Forget everyone else, but if I
have any complaints, I don't hide them!
Need to mention it...
Seems like Lee Seongmo is
being investigated by the ANSP.
For what?
Certain ruling party members
have tried approaching the opposition.
And looks like Seongmo
found that out from someone.
It's too late for me to help him.
Seongmo is at the Seobinggo
bunker as we speak.
As you well know, once you enter
that place, there are only two options.
Either you confess, or come out crippled.
I'm betting on the former.
As if he was some kind of patriot,
why resist when your flesh is burning?
And why would you tell me that?
Because I thought you could
be the one who gave him the tip.
Hey... Jo Pilyeon!!
[*From Han Dynasty poem Junzi Xing]
Don't fix your shoes in a melon field or
tidy your hat under plum trees*, they say.
And that means you shouldn't
do anything that would arouse suspicion.
Is that clear?
What are you trying to say?
You want me to give up on them?
Just give me the account
and those signatures instead.
And why?
With that in my hands, I could
at least try to change their mind.
I can't do that.
Chairman Hwang!
Don't you realize in
what kind of situation we are?
Our deal was that I would give it
to you if you convinced them to cooperate.
Lee Seongmo has been taken
to the Seobinggo underground bunker.
What?
Seeing how surprised you
are, I must have guessed right.
So Lee Seongmo is the
source of that account, right?
And he must have been the one who
informed you of what the ANSP planned.
Well... Believe whatever you want.
If Lee Seongmo can't resist
and ends up confessing,
you will be the first
to pay the consequences.
So hurry up and give me that account.
It is the only way we can survive!
By the way, weren't
you and Min Honggi close?
I don't trust Congressman Min.
I've seen enough over the years
to convince me not to.
I said give me that
account, Chairman Hwang!
It's not in my possession.
It's not?!
Then, who has it?
I'll have to get going.
Chairman Hwang!
How did it go?
Did you find out?
I couldn't reach him.
Something happened to Lee
Seongmo right as Min Honggi suggested.
If I knew this would happen,
I would have kept that account for myself.
If they get it from Lee Seongmo,
we're as good as dead.
Shouldn't we run away?
If the ANSP starts looking for us...
Who is it?
Gangmo.
What are you doing here?
I had something to talk about.
Here... Have a seat.
Aren't you busy?
I might have had all the time in the past,
but things have become a little complicated.
I'm sure they're not just complicated.
Since your life is at stake.
And perhaps not only a few lives,
but our country's future as well.
Gangmo, you...
How much do you know about this?
All I care about is one man's life.
Lee Seongmo.
How can you know...
Because he's the older brother
I lost in my childhood.
What?!
Lee Seongmo...
That's my son.
So you're Daesoo's eldest?!
- Look at him!
- Seongmo.
This is Dad's friend,
who runs a business in Seoul.
- That's me!
- How are you?
Daesoo's son can only be
like a son to me.
He sure is handsome.
Here you go.
Go ahead and spend it.
Quite a son you have!
Right... That's him.
I saw him once.
Lee Seongmo...
was that boy?!
Pull him out.
The situation is critical.
All the ruling party members
who pledged their support...
have suddenly started
hesitating and pulling out of this.
Was Min Honggi really behind all this?
That's indeed the case,
but it didn't feel like
Seongmo really trusted him.
To help out my brother, we first need
to find out what Min Honggi is all about.
Aren't you being excessive?
Ever since Baekpa passed away,
you practically stopped coming.
So didn't we answer your
call and came right away?
Let's have a drink for
good old times' sake, then.
Is anything the matter?
The moment Baekpa passed away,
many core members
sided with Jo Pilyeon.
Are you telling me the cartel
is falling into Jo Pilyeon's hands?
Yes.
And Jo is using their money to
find out all opposition party members...
who approve of the constitutional amendment.
That Jo Pilyeon is quite resourceful, all right.
Director Yoo.
I'd like a word in
private with Congressman Oh,
will you leave us alone just a moment?
Certainly, go ahead.
When you're done
talking, come tell me.
Congressman.
I have something to discuss with you.
Didn't I warn you on
more than one occasion?
You knew already?
Know how long I've been in congress?
Jo Pilyeon might be suspecting you,
but without any evidence,
there is nothing he can do.
So break up that club as soon
as possible, and forget all this.
But forget that... Were you aware of the existence
of an account for the secret presidential fund?
Look, Congressman Min.
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Congressman Oh!
With that account in our hands,
there's nothing we can't do!
Keep it up, will you?
Change the subject, this is no fun.
Min Honggi's obsession over that
account makes me feel a little uneasy.
Scene 1, take 2.
This is how you want to...
Cut.
I apologize.
It's all right.
Soojeong, don't be nervous.
Let's do it again.
This is how you want
to dress at home, right?
Cut.
- That's not bad?!
- I don't like her expression.
Let's do it again.
This is how you want
to dress at home, right?
Miss Cha.
You don't look comfortable at all now.
Let's take a break.
All right.
Let's have a 30 minute break.
30 minutes, everyone.
- Why are you trembling?
- I kind of feel cold...
Did you catch a cold or something?
She's got fever.
It's all right.
All right?! How can you say that?
It's hot water.
At least have that.
The shoe company hasn't called yet, right?
They're still a few days
away from making that decision.
All those NG's are
on purpose, isn't it?
You're trying to delay things.
So that's why you even caught a cold.
I'll find someone who
can give you cold medicine.
Or if we can't find
it, I'll go buy it myself.
Seonhwa.
Go find out if Minwoo's gone.
Is there a reason
why I shouldn't be here?
Open your eyes... Open them!
Open those damned eyes, you prick!
Speak.
Where did you hide that account?
I said speak, you bastard!
If I do, will you let me live?
'Course...
So go ahead and tell us.
That account...
That's right.
Where is that account?
It's under...
your wife's skirt.
Get him out of here.
Even if you have to kill him,
you must find that account.
All right.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Who do you think is responsible
for that golden badge you're wearing?
You know what our people wish for?
Who is behind all this?
Seongmo, are you all right?
You said it wasn't
because of my father, so why?
There is no reason
why people stop liking someone.
Please, take me under your wings.
I want to defeat Hwang Jeongyeon.
I will mercilessly trample on all of them.
Where is Seongmo Oppa?
What is happening to him?
I received all the
data about Cha Soojeong.
Isn't this President Lee Gangmo?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com