Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional -
Nice to meet you.
- Episode 25 -
Have a seat.
So, what brings you here?
Let's start with the introductions.
My name is James Lee.
James... Lee?!
A look at the eyes of people coming here,
and you'll usually witness two feelings.
One of frantic, pressing concern,
or just plain despair.
But you seem to be a
little different, young fella?
I'm well aware of
your business method.
Is that so?
So what do people say about me?
To never let my guard down.
Or, at the first sign of weakness,
you'd either squeeze money out of me,
completely run me dry,
or even bring forth my collapse.
- That's insulting.
- Nah.
Money means survival,
and if he came here to stake
his entire life on this deal,
that much insight is a given.
Let's begin by seeing your collateral.
I hear that, based on the collateral,
your interest rates might vary.
Shall we take a look
at the contract, then?
Show it to him.
May I write down the interest rate
that would best suit me?
Look...
What do you take him for?
Write it down.
But, Sir...
So you won't give me
a penny for the trouble?
I guess it's time
to see the collateral, then.
- High Efficiency Cement Business Plan -
Here is my business plan.
I'm in the money-lending
business, I'm no investor!
All this time, you've been making
money while hiding in the shadows.
Whereas I want to earn my living
in the most transparent way.
Shady or transparent,
money has always the same color.
The moment it's brought into play,
it brings forth great struggle and
gives you immense power no matter what.
I appreciate your confidence,
but your collateral is not to my liking.
You may leave.
Would this satisfy you, then?
And what is this?
A land deed for my mudflats in Gaepo.
- Sir, this land...
- I'm sure you know...
what will soon become of that land.
How much are you looking for?
Sir.
Please read my business plan.
What I really wish for right now
is not a huge sum of money,
but a moment of your time,
to be devoted to reading that plan.
How did it go?
You didn't leave the
land deed with him, did you?
We agreed to meet again
after I develop our new technology.
So you're telling me he agreed to
lend you money without any collateral?
If things go according to plan,
he might become our Hangang
Construction's very first investor.
I can't believe it.
There's a good reason why people
in his trade call him "vampire"...
Are you really planning to
lend him money without a collateral?
I don't know.
I haven't made up my mind, yet.
I've never seen
you confused before, Sir.
Was it James... Lee?
What most confuses me...
is the realization that there is
someone who could confuse me.
So now you're even ignoring me,
just because you can't talk?
I don't need your shares any longer.
I secured more than enough
holdings to win a majority vote.
So you should have listened
to me while you still could.
Why risk it all by doggedly
trying to contend with me?
When Jeongshik
inherits the company,
we could just take away all
your shares for incompetence,
and trap you inside a hospital
room for the rest of your days.
But if you give up your shares now,
I'll pay you generously for the trouble,
and allow you to live overseas.
It is my very last act of generosity,
merely for my husband's sake.
You have until the
shareholders' meeting to decide.
If you let that day pass,
then no excuse is ever going to work.
What do we owe your
kind invitation to, Miss Yoo?
I wanted to discuss the Manbo
Construction succession matter,
as fellow shareholders.
Didn't we all agree to push for
Hwang Jeongshik as the heir?
I see this issue in a different way.
Considering performance on the field,
I believe Hwang Jeongyeon
would be much more fit for the job.
Don't even joke about such nonsense!
Forget anything else, but how can you
let a woman run a construction business?
Are you against it merely
because she's a woman?
Is there anyone here willing to invest
in a construction company run by a woman?
Have you seen, Miss Yoo?
Not a single one of them.
And it's not the first time I see
a woman ruin a company that way.
But, Miss Yoo... Don't you know that
Hwang Jeongyeon is suffering from aphasia?
- That...
- There is no need to argue this!
How can you let a woman
with poor health run a business?
Let's just stop talking
about this, Miss Yoo.
It's obvious how it'll end,
no matter how you put it.
I'm late, right?
Where are all the shareholders?
It would be wise
not to meet them now.
What?
Let's have a word.
Are you suggesting that there's
no way to convince them?
Whatever the case,
I'll just face them.
Giving up now would be...
They're opposing your
candidacy for two reasons.
The fact you're a woman,
and because you suffer from aphasia.
Suffering from aphasia
is a non-issue, already.
But the crux of the matter is
that they refuse to acknowledge you,
because you're a woman.
If you can manage to
overcome those weaknesses,
then you still have a chance.
So you want me to turn a crisis
into an opportunity?
Ma'am, a guest is waiting for you.
Who is it?
The wife of Manbo
Construction's chairman.
Keep in mind what I told you.
Successfully turning a crisis into an
opportunity only depends on your timing.
Always a beauty, Miss Yoo.
Ahh... Let me introduce my mother.
I've heard a lot about you.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
What brings you here?
You've invested quite
the sum in our company...
I see even selling drinks for
a living can be profitable?!
Oh my...
I meant it as a compliment.
I hope there was
no misunderstanding?!
Why don't you get to the point?
I have very important
guests to deal with.
I'd like you to support Jeongshik
at the next shareholders' meeting.
Of course it's already
a foregone conclusion,
but I still hope you
could give us your help.
You're aware of
Hwang Jeongyeon's situation, right?
About her catching aphasia, and all.
I thought Jeongyeon
was your daughter as well,
what's the reason you're doing this?
It's a family matter, so there's no
doubt I'll be treading murky waters,
but since you're a major shareholder,
I'll be honest with you.
Jeongyeon's birth mother...
was just a bar girl.
Think about it.
If the world learns that the
daughter of a lowly bar girl...
is running Manbo Construction,
how will people react?
Let alone ruining the company's image,
wouldn't it also impact
our shares on the stock exchange?
I suppose.
Then, I'll consider that
as your stamp of approval.
Seems like we're done talking,
so if you'll excuse me,
I'll have to leave.
Go ahead.
Whenever we get the chance,
let's have a drink together.
I'll be happy to treat you, then.
Meeting outside the confines of my business
relationships is against my principles.
How can a wench running
a club be so haughty?
Mom!
You've seen it yourself!
Her treating me like a pushover.
Think all money is the same?
She'll hear you, stop it!
Did anything happen inside?
Agasshi.
Shideok.
You've been collecting
company data, right?
Bring it all to the hospital.
What?
Both reports of all our
current construction projects,
along with our accounting
records, all of them.
Yes.
It feels so good
to have you both by my side.
You remember?
When we lived in Busan,
the five of us all
slept in the same room.
When Dad came back
after a night out drinking,
he'd snore so loudly.
I miss that sound so much.
Don't you?
Don't worry about that.
Gangmo and I will snore
all night for you instead.
Little Oppa used to even
grind his teeth.
Are you still doing that?
Miju.
For the time being,
I think we'll have to live apart.
What's that supposed to mean?
We just got back together.
I need to go down to the provinces.
And I've got work to do there.
No way! Don't go.
Miju.
Until his sentence is over,
Gangmo must keep hiding.
Try to be understanding.
Right, Miju.
Once my sentence is over,
then we'll never
have to separate again.
You must never tell anyone
you have brothers, yet.
Is that clear, Miju?
Instead, call often.
Sure.
Every now and then,
I'll even come pay you a visit.
Ahh... This is so hard.
Push, will you?
And what else am I doing now?
- As if you weren't an old fart...
- What? Old fart?!
Did you just call me an old fart?
I sure did. Going to Samcheong at that age,
what else should I call you,
- a fresh young breeze?
- Still better than damaged goods, you fool.
Give me a break,
how can that be worse?
- Stop prattling and start pushing!
- That's what I'm doing!
- Aigoo... Let's pull a little harder!
- But why the hell is this so heavy?
Ohh... It's so hard!
Aigoo! So hard.
- Are you faking it?
- I said I'm pushing!
Gangmo.
Gangmo, when did you get here?
You don't look like you pushed at all!
I said I did!
Here...
Hold it.
This way?
Done!
- Hangang Construction -
Hurrah! Hurrah!
- Manbo Construction -
Daejeon-Busan Highway
If we manage not to use
sand and gravel,
by how much would
construction costs be reduced?
I'd say a good
30-40 percent, at least?
Wow... That's huge.
But if there was such a way,
why would everyone else
waste time with gravel?
If we're going to compete with
big players like Manbo Construction,
developing a new technology
is the only way.
How about it?
Would it be possible?
What the hell...
Let's just give it a try.
Uh? All we have to show for
is a pair of balls, anyway.
I really envy you.
What with only having
one to risk, and all.
Ohh... So you know
that I only have one?
How did you find out,
that it's swinging solo down there?
Want me to show you?
Be my guest, here you go.
Seen it? Have you seen
whether it's only one?
Have you? So, what,
you have three instead?
Ahh... What are you doing?
Give it here.
Looks pretty solid to me?
Hey, damaged goods.
Come here a moment.
Ahh... The hell am I,
the mutt down the street?
What?
Just jump inside.
Did this dry out?
Can't you see for yourself?
You're sure I'm not going to fall, right?
These are new shoes, fresh new.
You fool, a truck can stand on this!
If we manage to succeed with this,
the entire road construction
sector will be in our hands.
Really?
Give me a sec.
See?
Told you it wouldn't work.
Ehh...
Let's just start from scratch.
They're as good as gone now.
You shameless sons of a
smelly slave cunt with rabies.
- New Road Construction
Technology Diary -
- Manbo Construction Sales Report -
- Business Performance
and Construction Report -
Hwang Jeongshik.
Someone like you will never
take that company away from me.
Ahh... Oppa!
Then, are you going to become
Manbo Construction's next chairman?
Why? Want your own place?
So we can go at it for real this time?
Aww... Listen to you!
- Orabeoni!
- Ehh... You sly fox!
- "Parade for Him" (one of the Gwangju
Movement's most popular folk protest songs) -
With no love, name or honor,
That promise which followed
them around all their lives.
- We're people too,
give us a place to live in -
You have nowhere to go,
all you can do is wave that flag.
- Removal -
Until a new day comes,
let's not give up and fall back.
As time goes by, nature will know.
Are you ready to act?
Yes.
I already took care of all the
redevelopment companies in the area.
And you?
Whenever you're ready,
just give us the order.
Take your boys and
join the developers' side.
You want me to
help the removal efforts?
That's right.
Jaechun will be giving you all
further instructions.
All you need to do
is act on the right day.
All right.
Right... About that informer
from the last stumping session.
Min Honggi was behind that, right?
Yes, that's right.
Who helped him?
Excuse me?
There must have been someone
in charge of putting all that together.
It has to be someone from
the ANSP, in all likelihood.
What?! The ANSP?
Yes... I hear Min Honggi has a
really close acquaintance there.
And who's that?
I never saw him personally.
If it's a Min Honggi
supporter from the ANSP,
that limits the number of suspects
down to a few people, doesn't it?
- Ohh...
- Chief Oh is here.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
Here...
I can't stay here for long.
So what is it?
How is Lee Seongmo doing,
these days?
He's very popular in the agency for
being meticulous in all his dealings.
Ever felt there could be
some kind of collusion going on...
between him and Min Honggi?
What are you implying with that?
I'm just wondering whether he might
be helping Min behind the scenes.
Never received any
such report, I'm afraid.
Right...
While Min Honggi was
having dinner with the director,
I did hear him asking the director
to take good care of Lee Seongmo.
Is that true?
What did he call him...
a "trusted colleague" or something?!
Back in his KCIA days,
wasn't he working under Min?
If he goes as far as saying that
during unofficial meetings,
wouldn't the two be very close?
I have a previous engagement,
so I'll have to go.
Let me do it, Sir.
I can't even imagine the possibility.
Seongmo betraying you?!
There must be a mistake.
There is no way something
like that would happen!
The impossible becoming reality
is what people are all about.
Are you suspecting Seongmo?
These days, Jo Pilyeon is visiting
clearance areas under his jurisdiction.
Clearance areas?! Why?
He's just paying close attention,
without any particular move.
I'm sure he's
scheming something there.
- Keep watching him.
- Yes.
Right.
I've heard this from
a Support Department agent,
but it seems like the chief there
asked about you and Min Honggi?!
Chief Oh?
Yes.
Look, Director Park.
Do you believe only completing 20 percent
of the highway construction makes sense?
We've been facing quite
a few problems as of late.
Especially in regards to tightening
the soil before pouring cement.
I don't need your excuses!
Chief Jo.
Take over the highway
construction project.
Chairman.
Chief Jo will soon be promoted
to Director of Planning.
I'll do this with the future success
of this highway construction in mind,
so don't disappoint me.
Certainly, Chairman.
You're really impressive, Chief.
By showing interest in
the highway project as of late,
were you already
expecting this would happen?
Yes.
How did it go?
A job there in accounting?!
Sure... Thanks.
What, something
going on between us?!
I'm just helping her out
of compassion, that's all.
All right, fine.
Thank you, Chief.
For rescuing me.
If it weren't for you, I'd...
Chief...
Thank God.
Nothing happened.
Why did I say that?
What brings you here?
Is Lee Miju here?
You came to see Miju?
Where is she now?
You'll find her on the rooftop.
How. Are. You?
It's so hot...
I'm Lee Miju, I just came back
from my tour of Southeast Asia.
Everyone, I love you!
*Hyeeun megahit. "(Eodeureo) Gamsugwang"
is Jeju dialect for "where are you going?"
I'll now sing you
my hit song, "Where*."
Windy Jeju is full of rocks,
But also of kindhearted
and gentle young ladies.
Where...
Where are you going,
and how about me,
You pitiful little thing.
I will let you go this once,
so hurry up and co...
Who is there?
I asked who's there.
Chief!
Hey... Can someone who dreams of
becoming a singer actually sing so bad?
I'm bad at it so I keep practicing.
But, what are you doing here?
You're back on the employed list.
What?
I found you a job.
You got me a job, personally?
Don't ever work at places
like that bus company again.
Thank you, Chief.
I was looking for a job myself.
You know how to
write a resume, right?
Resume?!
Chief...
What?
Should I really list my
academic background as well?
Write down every little thing.
- Preparing for GED Examination -
- Other Family Members -
You must never tell anyone
you have brothers, yet.
Is that clear, Miju?
- Orphan -
- Introduction -
It's done.
But where should I present this?
Give it here.
What?
No way.
I said give it here.
I'll just deal with it myself.
- Orphan -
I'll take care of this,
so don't worry.
Give it here... I'll do it!
Do you know what kind
of company this is?
Think you could just get in
with such lousy credentials?
Just do as I say,
don't argue with me.
Give me a call tomorrow.
What?
Don't make me waste time looking
for you for something so trivial.
Here.
Chief.
Thank you.
I've never been treated
with such kindness before.
I'm really thankful for all
you're doing for me, Chief.
Don't get any strange idea.
I just felt sad you lost your job
because of me, so that's why.
Almost fell for it again.
So why are you feeling like that?
What's the matter?
Don't get me started.
This motherless old cunt...
I'll be damned...
He just got up in arms
saying nothing will work.
He just suddenly turned everything
upside down, cursing a storm,
not to mention getting piss drunk.
The end.
But, the way I see it,
I don't think calcium
chloride will ever work.
If it was such a simple matter,
everyone would be going for it already.
So let's just give up road construction,
get ourselves some laborers and...
Get rid of those damaged goods...
Get rid of what? You, shut up!
Ahh... Did he shove
the bottle up his ass?
Swearing every ch...
How can a construction
company's stairs look like this?
This seems tight enough.
Not bad?!
Gangmo, what's wrong?
Wake up! Quick!
Get up.
Aigoo, what's the matter...
Here... What did they use
to make this brick?
What do you think?
Can't you see for yourself?
They made it with mud.
So why are you asking, if you know?
But why is it so stiff?
Because it's a brick, what else?
Can't we just tighten up
the mud the same way?
Tell me.
What do they use to tighten up bricks?
Hardener.
If you mix this hardener with the mud,
it becomes as hard as rocks.
Why couldn't I think of that?
This.. this... Nam Youngchul
has lost it already.
Let's try it out right away.
I'm sure we'll be able
to do the same with roads.
So, what, you're going to
spread bricks on the highway?
Shut that trap and
go get us that hardener.
Get moving!
- Hardener?
- Yeah. Hardener.
- Hard... Aigoo!
- Hardener?!
- Just go.
Yes.
That's me.
What can I do for you?
There's a get-together
at the Royal Club tonight.
You know Congressman
Oh Byeongtak, right?
He'd like to meet you.
No need to feel burdened,
just come introduce yourself
and it'll be the end of things.
Getting acquainted with someone
like him surely won't hurt.
I'll leave right now,
so hurry up and come.
So I'll just come in a moment
and introduce myself.
Lee Seongmo just left
the ANSP building.
Where was he headed?
I put some of our men on his trail,
but we still don't know
his destination.
Where's Min Honggi now?
We got word he's at the Royal Club.
Let's head there right now.
Get the car.
All right.
That car behind us. Doesn't it
feel like they've been trailing us?
Really?
Why would anyone trail us?
You said Chief Oh asked
about me and Min Honggi?
Yes. But what would
that have to do...
Chief Oh and Jo Pilyeon
are really close.
Then...
Are you suggesting that Jo Pilyeon
might be suspecting you?
Take the next alley
and go around the block.
Yes.
Seems like he still hasn't arrived.
It can't be Seongmo.
No matter how you put it,
he'd have no reason to betray you.
And if it indeed turns out he did?
What?
If Seongmo really betrayed me
and is helping Min Honggi,
what will you do?
We'd obviously have to...
Get rid of him.
Gaining my trust is not that easy.
However, once I trust someone,
I'm never the first to betray them.
If it really turns out
Seongmo betrayed me,
I will not forgive him.
I can only pray he won't
show up here tonight.
It's obvious they're trailing us.
This won't do it,
let's return to the office.
Go to the Royal Club.
Seonbaenim.
I must meet Min Honggi.
Don't you know that'll mean
falling right into their trap?
Jo Pilyeon is already suspecting me.
If I don't deal with this face to face,
I'll never get out
of Jo Pilyeon's shadows.
But...
Let's go!
After all, Lee Seongmo was a traitor.
What are you trying to do?
Seongmo was like a son to me!
And that same man betrayed me!
- But, now is not...
- Let me go!
So the man who was helping you
is this Lee Seongmo?
Yes.
Both in terms of
skills and disposition,
he's a brilliant young fella
who could make it big in politics.
They say there's nothing
like trustworthy disciples...
Seems like you hit the jackpot
when it comes to that.
This bodes well for
the upcoming elections.
My congratulations,
Congressman Min Honggi.
"Congressman" Min Honggi...
Rolls off the tongue, doesn't it?
You're embarrassing me, come on...
Here... Let's drink.
What's the matter?
I was told to give you this,
Candidate Min.
Forgive me for what I'm about to do.
What is it about?
What's with you?
How dare you come here?
You little...
So I'd be your "right-hand man?"
Is that the kind of rumor
you spread to...
drive a rift between
me and Jo Pilyeon?
Stop it.
You better listen well.
Seems like you'll try every trick
in the book to win these elections,
but you'll never win.
I'll never let you, is that clear?
Seongmo!
Take Seongmo out. Now.
What is this?
What the hell
are you people doing?
My apologies.
But that buddy
can't tolerate injustice.
What, injustice?!
I'll soon take the opportunity
to formally apologize to you,
but in the meantime, I ask
for your kind understanding.
Hey, Jo Pilyeon!
Just consider yourself lucky.
If it weren't for me,
he would have beaten you to a pulp.
Isn't that the Lee Seongmo
Candidate Min was talking about?
Seongmo, you'll have to keep
that temper of yours in check.
Forgive me.
I never imagined Min Honggi
could stab me in the back like that.
But, what were you
doing at the Royal Club?
Actually, I'd heard people referring
to you as Min Honggi's right-hand man.
I'll just be honest with you.
For an ever so brief moment,
I suspected you.
Seongmo.
And Jaechun.
Yes.
I might look like a vile,
ruthless opportunist,
but I don't solely live for
the sake of my personal gain.
You and I will walk
together to the very end.
I'll never forget all your efforts.
Just endure these hardships
a little longer.
It's on that new realm
of ours in Gangnam...
that our kingdom will be built.
Here...
Did it work?
Just touch it and find out.
Ehh Ehh... You wretched twat.
Will bring bad luck!
I, Nam Youngchul!
Put my thirty years of
public works at stake for this.
If this doesn't work,
I'll just cut my hair,
and retire to a temple for meditation.
Why, have any hair left to cut?
Ahh... You son of an anal wart,
you'll bring bad luck!
My knee...
I'll break my damned leg this way.
We did it!
It's done... We did it!
What did you do with my hair?
Shut your mouth!
You work at a club and still
have the guts to complain?
Still, you cut my hair?
It's all because of you!
Will you shut that trap or not?
If I had any scissors handy, your ears
would be on the floor, your brat!
Go ahead then! Who's stopping you?
Ohh... Really! Come here!
Stop it!
Are there no side dishes?
Anything to chew on...
Is that what you worry about?
Aigoo! I can't take it anymore!
Yes.
Agasshi?!
Agasshi?
Jeongyeon?
'Course not.
Yes.
Yes, yes... Certainly.
The shareholders' meeting
will soon start.
Shouldn't you go get Jeongyeon?
I think it just wasn't in
Jeongyeon's destiny to become my heir.
Hurry up, Agasshi!
You'll be late for the meeting!
- What is the matter?
- What?
I didn't say anything.
Patients absent without leave...
It's not "leave," but discharge.
Thank you for everything.
Have a nice day.
You go ahead first.
Whatever results
today's meeting will bring,
don't resent me.
The verdict has already been
decided beyond my control.
You must give your support
to Jeongyeon no matter what.
Seems like you're still not
fully aware of the situation.
Oh my! You're here?
Nice to meet you.
You give quite a different
vibe outside that club?
Have you two met before?
We sure did!
Think I wouldn't know the
owner of the Royal Club?
She's a company shareholder.
Shall we enter?
It's really too bad for Jeongyeon.
And after going through all that abuse,
I can't even get a chance?
You just wait.
This shareholders' meeting will mark
the very last time my father ignores me.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Why would you even come here?
Just because it's
a shareholders' meeting?
And what would you do here?
You'll wiggle that trap
like a roach and then leave?
Give it a rest.
Are you feeling better?
Oh well... All the better.
You at least can
clap your hands, right?
When they announce me as the heir,
you can join in and give me
an applause like everyone else.
Where are you trying to go?
And I hope it'll also be the very
last time you act like a pompous prick.
So, what, still banking on
that last thread of hope?
Sure... Be my guest.
I'll embarrass you in front of
everyone and have them kick you out.
We will now start today's
shareholders' meeting...
to decide Manbo Construction's heir.
Every shareholder is entitled
to exercise their voting rights...
based on their holding rate.
Before the voting, a Q&A session with
the two candidates will take place.
We already know
everything there is to know.
What's the point of
going through all that?
That's right.
Let's not waste our precious time
and just start voting right away.
Let's do that.
Let's vote.
Then, if there are no objections,
we will vote right away.
I will ask a question, if I may.
Birds of the same
feather flock together.
Please, go ahead.
First, I'll ask Hwang Jeongshik.
What is the current
financial state of the company,
and how much can shareholders
expect in dividends this year?
That...
Manbo Construction's
current financial situation...
is quite positive.
So it's only natural that you will be
satisfied with your dividends this year.
Very satisfied.
I'll ask the same question
to Miss Jeongyeon as well.
Go ahead and tell us.
Just in case anyone
is not aware as of yet,
- she's suffering from aphasia...
- If I may speak!
Manbo Construction's current assets
total 473 billion won,
with 162.7 billion won in liabilities.
This year's predicted total
revenues are 126 billion won,
with profits of 47.4 billion won.
Park Gidong Seonsaengnim?
You own 100,000 of our shares,
if I recall correctly?
That'd be right.
You will then receive 550 million
won in dividends this year.
That's a 350 million-won
growth year-on-year.
Choi Taeseop Seonsaengnim?
You own 50,000 shares, right?
Yes... That's... right.
Your dividend growth will
be 175 million year-on-year.
Congratulations.
I think we need to verify whether
Miss Hwang Jeongyeon's claims are true.
Chief Jo Minwoo?
I kindly ask you to confirm to the shareholders
whether my calculations were right.
It is right as Hwang Jeongyeon said.
As a fellow candidate,
I'd like to ask Director
Hwang Jeongshik a question.
I'd like you to tell us about the difficulties
our highway construction is facing,
along with any possible
solutions to the matter.
Hey... Minwoo...
Road construction is truly a
crucial sector for our company.
But it's going perfectly fine,
if you must necessarily
find a problem with it...
A construction that should have
gone past 40-percent completion...
barely went past half that figure,
but you're still suggesting
everything is "going perfectly fine?"
We will now begin the voting.
Sorry about that.
I had to finish watering my pots.
Have a seat.
So, did you develop this new
technology for road construction?
I just came back from filing
a public works patent request.
I will announce the results.
By a margin of 68 to 32 percent,
the new heir of Manbo Construction...
will be Miss Hwang Jeongyeon.
Mom...
What's wrong with you?
Get a hold of yourself.
Whether you'll choose
this land deed as collateral,
or my business plan instead,
I leave the decision to you.
How much are you looking for?
I'd like to borrow
five hundred million.
Listen to that.
Not a penny of interest,
and 500 million?
If I choose your
business plan as collateral?
You'd eventually be rewarded with
immense dividends down the line.
And if I choose
the land deed instead?
I no longer need you.
Choose one of the two.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Chief Jo Minwoo.
Take these and follow me.
Are you telling me
he met with Go Jaechun?
You just wait.
While everyone bets on my downfall,
I'll shock them all and turn this around.
- I'd like to go out with you.
- I already have a boyfriend.
He works for Manbo Construction,
and is already a chief there.
It's my letter of resignation,
giving up my rights as heir.
If this project fails, I will
present this letter to the chairman.
We will use this new technology
to fight off those corporations.
Do you mean Manbo Construction?
Dig into this Hangang
Construction right away.
Find out who runs that company!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com