Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 46
Jo Minwoo.
I hear you're facing quite the
headaches with those boilers.
It's all been solved.
Really?
That's not what I've heard?!
Is our factory manager doing fine?
Seeing how he stole our core technology,
I guess you're looking to
develop a new boiler as well.
The factory you acquired
is nothing but an empty shell.
I'm sure you'll soon come to realize it.
Can you really develop a
proper boiler with stolen technology?
What a shame...
Now you treat me like a thief
without a shred of evidence?!
You sure didn't betray my expectations.
It's just like your father said.
He might steal from you, but he is
honest enough to do it in your face.
No...
Maybe "daring" would fit him better.
The results will tell the story.
Because justice doesn't bring you success.
It's success that brings you justice.
I'll keep those words in mind.
Because you will be defeated,
and be scorned at for your cowardice.
The same which led
you to say those words.
What is this?
I came here to meet an advertiser.
Please, leave.
Sit.
Minwoo!
I am the advertiser you were waiting for.
I ordered steak,
knowing how much you like it.
Is that fine with you?
How do you explain all this?
- My manager talked of a Suyoung Construction?
- I guess he heard wrong.
Sit.
Among the clauses in that contract...
was the fact that
you'd accept all our requests.
If you truly have no feelings left for me,
then there is no reason why
you'd avoid meeting me for business.
On the contrary, it's a huge
opportunity for a newcomer like you,
so you should just go for it.
What should I do to terminate that contract?
You could just read it
and find out by yourself,
but all you need to do is
pay three times the signing fee.
Aren't you being shameless?
You're the one who
forced me into this state,
and pushed me to go through
all this just to see you smile.
So blame yourself.
Your order is ready, Sir.
Sit.
Before I do something even worse.
What's the matter?
Thought I saw someone.
Who?
I'm sure it wasn't her.
Let's eat.
What?
Can't you cut it into smaller pieces?
Then you lose all the taste.
I know how much I disappointed you.
Since I couldn't
protect you from my father.
I told you that wasn't the issue, didn't I?
If it's not,
then why on earth
are you acting like this?
The more you meet me,
the worse you'll feel.
So please, stop.
I don't know how I could let go of you.
I can't erase you from my mind.
Then... I guess there's only one solution left.
I'll have to force you to hate me instead.
If you think you can, be my guest.
What have you been
doing these last four years?
Must I really tell you?
From now on, we'll dine
together when I ask you to.
Another clause of that
contract, you can check it.
Did you just use that to buy me?
For now.
Want something
else other than that steak?
Thank you for the dinner.
I'll drive you home.
Is that another one of your clauses?
Buying me dinner and driving me home.
Tomorrow we will go back
to that riverbank we've been to.
I'll come to get you.
Why didn't you tell me it
was a Manbo Construction CF?
What are you talking about?
It was a Manbo Construction CF?!
Ohh... That?
Turns out I heard it wrong.
Does that make any sense?
What's the big deal?
If it's a huge corporation like
Manbo Construction, all the better...
And how about the contractual terms?
Were you aware of any
additional clauses besides the usual?
I was too busy to read all the fine print...
I just thought it would be all right,
considering who we were dealing with.
Why, is anything wrong?
The contract is at the office, right?
I'll have to check that out first.
But I don't think your
schedule would allow that...
That's more urgent to me!
Let's hurry up.
Miju?
Miss Cha Soojeong!
Oppa...
Here, take it.
You can't imagine how much he's
been pestering me to come see you.
Like you didn't want to...
Aww... I'm hungry.
But, aren't you two getting married?
Uh?!
Aren't you seeing anyone?
He's not too popular with women.
Like you are.
Me?
Of course I am.
I'm so popular,
I can't take it anymore.
Really?
Big Oppa, is that really true?
No comment.
Be right back.
Make him confess.
You never dated
even once, have you?
Miju.
By any chance,
is Jo Minwoo bothering you?
You don't need to worry.
Good to hear, then.
It's hard, isn't it?
Nah... With you by
my side, why would it be?
Just say the word.
I will help you every step of the way.
Got it?
All right.
You two...
Talked behind my
back all this time, didn't you?
Wow... How did he guess?
You can't fool him.
My ears were burning.
All our top business acquaintances
have turned their backs on us?
That's right.
So Noh Gapsoo is
finally declaring war against me.
And it doesn't stop at that,
as he's trying to make all stocks of
companies we invested in hit the bottom.
Director.
It's Miss Jeongyeon.
Jeongyeon must not learn of this.
All right.
Come on in.
Have you completed that business plan?
Yes.
To obtain our permit for the credit institution,
we will have to go through
very complex legal procedures.
That's right.
And we will need a start-up capital
of at least thirty billion won.
Any concrete plans on
how to secure that capital?
I'm weighing the options on...
So you came to me
with an incomplete plan?
Or you really believed I would
invest that much money all on my own?
- No.. I never implied...
- This is unacceptable.
Leave.
I'll come again and bring
you a more concrete plan.
I don't want you
to disappoint me again.
All right.
- A Night for the 88 Olympic Games -
Businessmen Gather in Seoul
Eonni...
You'll pierce a hole
through that newspaper.
How could the director tell you to
find those thirty billion all on your own?!
She had no reason not to.
Jina.
Find out whether Deputy Mayor Han
Myeongseok is in charge of this event.
Why are you asking?
So you want to help with the event?
Yes.
Your father has been backing
quite a few congressmen as of late, too.
Is this all to help your
father's entry into politics?
Since it's you, I'll be honest.
I'm planning to open a credit institution.
Is that so?
And I need investors.
So by helping the event I'm supervising,
you will muster the
financial backing you need.
Yes.
Help me out, Deputy.
It would surely help my cause as well.
Here... Let's help each other.
Thank you.
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
Did you bring the account as well?
Once I can convince enough ruling
party members to reach the quorum,
I will approach the opposition as well.
They must never find out
the source of this account.
I know.
I will keep the list and account.
Because if anything happens, we
must get rid of all material evidence.
We'll get going, then.
I will handle this.
I've heard rumors that Chief Oh and
Jo Pilyeon are meeting frequently as of late.
You do that.
Mountaineering this,
study group that...
There are way too many outside
groups forming among ruling party members.
With the country in this state, is this
the time to be worrying about their hobbies?
You really think those people gather
simply to share their hobbies?
So that's why I'm telling you.
No need to look elsewhere.
The way I see it,
these are bonafide factions.
And that's exactly what we
were focusing our attention on.
Any good news to tell me?
There is a lot of clamor over the constitutional
amendment among ruling party members.
And who would they be?
I don't need any conclusive evidence.
Who are we dealing with?
You're dealing with congressmen here.
Ruling party members at that.
We can't use a few complaints bandied
about over a drink to inculpate them.
Look, Chief Oh.
Any crime they commit
won't be an accidental misstep.
Because the moment they show their
approval for the constitutional amendment,
they'll be guilty of treason.
So even if we don't
have any clear evidence,
you must do everything
in your power to create some.
Aren't you listening to me?
I said you're dealing
with ruling party members!
Seems like I'm
not making myself clear.
Fine.
Who do you think is
most likely to be the culprit?
I finally realized it
thanks to mountaineering.
The steeper the mountain,
the more people
you'll need by your side.
More people you can rely on,
and reach the summit with.
We'll go for Mount Jiri next month,
and our numbers will triple.
Is everyone confident?
It has to be done.
It must.
What are you doing at
a mountaineering gathering?
How have you been, Congressman Kang?
Congressman Park...
I see Congressman Kwon as well.
If you're really that
interested, join our club.
More than the mountains,
I find the company
here a lot more enticing.
What's that supposed to mean?
I recall someone saying this.
That nobody was as enlightened as
the ruling party's mountaineering club members.
Seeing the talent on display, it does
seem as if those weren't unfounded rumors.
It's indeed a remarkable
collection of great minds.
You're spoiling the mood.
If you didn't come here
to have a drink, just...
I believe that this country needs a
constitutional amendment to survive.
However, the amendment I was thinking
about differs from what has been mentioned.
Even if we have to fix
the constitution to allow it,
we must move to a parliamentary cabinet system.
Parliamentary cabinet?!
Are you suggesting we
nominate a prime minister?
And who would be entrusted this task?
Need to ask?
It obviously will be the president.
That can only mean an unlimited rule...
And why not?
Don't you know what the
people are asking for right now?
It is only a statistically
insignificant minority.
Everyone else just follows their village
headman's decision like a loyal mutt.
Get out of here!
Spare me all that nonsense
and get out of my face!
But when that "nonsense" becomes reality,
history will be written anew.
While you enjoy your mountain-climbing,
I suggest you bear that in mind.
Don't let that intimidate you.
Swaying off our path will only mean defeat.
So you think they're the ones who
approve of the constitutional amendment?
I still am not sure.
But all I need is one of them
betraying everyone else.
Because one of them coming to
me is all I need to expose them all.
Gangmo.
Manbo Construction is
having a press conference.
About what?
They said it's about their boiler branch.
Boiler?!
Why would they suddenly
enter the boiler business?!
There is no doubt now.
They stole our technology for sure.
- Manbo Construction, Ondol-Based
Korean-Style Boiler Development Conference -
We will install boilers in every Suseo
apartment under construction.
Are you going to cooperate
with Hangang Construction and...
use the boilers from their
recently acquired Beaute?
To my knowledge, Beaute still
hasn't resolved their gas leak issues.
So what you're suggesting is that you
found a company that solved those issues?
Yes. We did.
And which company would that be?
None other than Manbo Construction.
Manbo Construction
developed its own gas boiler?
To be precise,
it's under development as we speak.
So tell us about your solution
to avoid any further accident.
That is something I'm
not at liberty to reveal.
What I can tell you is that
the boiler we're developing...
will not only deal with all the
inherent flaws of existing boilers,
but also be based on our Korean-born
ondol culture instead of radiators.
It was a huge success, Chairman.
All the reporters looked really shocked.
More than the reporters, I'm curious
how Lee Gangmo reacted.
Isn't that obvious?
I will have dinner with
Cha Soojeong this evening.
Make a reservation with the hotel.
Ahh... That...
Tonight she has a radio broadcast, so...
Director Moon.
How long has this been going on?
I apologize, Chairman.
There seems to
be no convincing her, so...
Still, it's not like we could demand
the signing fee for breach of contract.
Do it.
What?
If she breached our contract, she must pay.
All right, Chairman.
No... Nevermind.
I'll tell her myself.
Check her schedule and set up
an appointment as soon as possible.
Yes, Chairman.
Miju.
If you keep this up,
you'll only force me
to retaliate even more.
- Manbo Construction Chairman Jo Minwoo
Solves Fatal Flaw of Beaute Gas Boilers -
What is so interesting?
Look... Give this a read.
Wow! The department store
is having a bargain sale!
Ahh... Not that, this one over here.
Why are you acting all angry with me?
Ahh... Really, sorry-ass cunt.
Sorry-as...
Gyeongja... Gyeongja!
I didn't mean you...
But I'm really curious what this
solution they found really is?!
Jo Minwoo, sorry-ass son of a cunt.
Guess he's trying to completely bring
us down at the next apartment sale?
I brought him, President.
Come on in.
You've read the
newspaper, haven't you?
Yes.
We are now sure that
our core technology was stolen.
Now the battle will
be fought on pure skills.
So you want us to develop
an ondol-based boiler of our own?
And it must be much
more efficient than theirs.
But they're already developing
their technology as we speak?
From now on, you'll be in
charge of the boiler factory.
You're telling me to act as factory manager?
Yes.
You will be in charge of the whole process.
We will provide all the resources you need.
Youngchul Hyungnim, you take care
of providing factory resources.
All right, fine.
You can do it, right?
Then,
I'll put my 30 year career
on the line and give it a try.
What now?
Soojeong, what do we do now?
Chairman Jo said it's a breach
of contract, and sent you this.
What?
I told you not to rile him up, didn't I?
Do you even have the money
to pay that signing fee?
Chairman.
Cha Soojeong is on the phone.
Put her on.
Yes.
I'd like to meet,
would that be possible?
I'm a little busy now.
See you at the Hangang
Hotel, eight o'clock.
Wooju!
Mommy...
You missed me, didn't you?
Come on in.
By the way, can you just
go around like that?
There are only a few people
recognizing me on the street.
So Wooju's father chose you
as model for his apartments?
Yes.
Actually, that's the reason why I came.
I think I'll have to use all my savings.
Do I have a father?
Where is he? Daddy.
Wooju, that's not what she meant...
We'll have to be
careful when he's around.
I think so, too.
I want to see my daddy...
Sorry, Wooju.
Your father is up in heaven.
In heaven?
Yeah.
How much do you need?
I need to pay 150 million won,
so if we add the fifty million
for my model contracts,
the thirty million
for my contract as a singer,
and the ten million I've been saving,
I'm still sixty million short.
I think I could help you with that.
No way, Mom.
Forget it.
Miju...
That money was left
to you by the chairman,
I could never use it for me.
So just make a lot of
money and pay me back.
That'll do it.
First, I'll try to find it on my own.
Since you're here, have a seat.
Don't just stand there as if
you were looking at a monster.
Sorry for sending you that certification.
- Tomorrow, I'll...
- No need to apologize.
I couldn't find the entire sum.
I will pay the rest as soon as possible.
Is this really necessary?
That's exactly what I wanted to ask you.
How can you be so cruel to me?
Let go of my hand.
I don't want to hurt you, either.
- So let's get this over with.
- It might be over for you,
but it's not to me.
Because I had lost all the will to live,
and only regained it thanks to you.
So no matter how much you hurt me,
it will never be as painful as all the
time I spent living without you!
Just go for tonight.
I'll let you go.
That money...
is all we have left.
Mom...
J... Just... Just this once.
If I can only make enough
to open a store somewhere,
I'll never gamble again, Mom.
I mean it, Mom.
I swear to God.
It's not something I wanted to do,
but we can't live with this money alone.
We can't do a thing with this little.
Don't you worry, Mom.
I had this great dream last night.
A hundred million.
If I can only make that much,
we'll use that to start a business,
and it'll be the end of our worries.
Got it?
So don't worry, Mom.
It's because you're so clueless that you
let Jeongyeon's mother steal Dad from you!
You...
What did you just say?
Jeongyeon's mother?!
Yoo Gyeongok, that woman...
is Jeongyeon's birth mother.
Dad has been deceiving us all along.
So how can I not feel sorry for you?
Call.
- I'm dead.
- Full house.
I'll have to take this.
- Call.
- Flush.
Just a moment.
This, this, and this!
Flush.
Thank you.
This, and I raise another five million.
I'm dead.
Five million,
and ten more.
Ten, and I raise another twenty.
Twenty, and thirty more.
You'll forgive me,
but I put my life on the line here.
So it's all in.
Call.
Ace full house.
Mom... I did it!
I did it!
Mom...
Wait... Wait.
Wait a moment.
We're a little impatient, aren't we?
I'm sorry.
Hey! You cheated, right?
Let me go!
No way... You changed that card!
That is my money...
Give it back!
My money!
I'll never forgive you.
You dare make my life so miserable?
And you think I'd just
let you get away with it?
After you've turned me into this state.
Dream on.
I'll kill you and then
get it over with myself!
Only that...
can bring me some consolation.
Only then...
I won't feel so stupid.
Mom...
What do we do now?
What do we do...
Mom.
Mom, are you sleeping?
Yes...
That's right.
What?!
Mom.
Mom!
Mom...
Mom.
Mom!
She's not dead, is she?
Right?
She can't be dead!
- She lost her consciousness.
- So wake her up!
Surgery... She needs
to go through surgery.
- Do it! Now!
- Please, don't act like this.
She regained her consciousness.
Mom.
Can you hear me?
Mom!
Open your eyes, Mom!
Mom...
Jeong...shik...
Mom.
I'm here.
Your son is here.
Ohh... Tell me.
What is it?
What do you want me to do?
Tell me, Mom.
My son...
Mom...
- My poor boy...
- Mom...
You must live...
a better life than Jeongyeon.
Don't you ever let
them look down on you,
and gain people's praise...
Promise you will...
live a much better life than Jeongyeon.
Yeah... Mom... I promise.
I will succeed at all cost, Mom.
My poor boy...
Mom.
O... Open your eyes, Mom.
What's wrong with you...
You're scaring me!
Mom! Mom...
Open your eyes... Mom...
Mom...
What's wrong with you, Mom...
Mom!
- Is this Oh Namsuk's...
- We accept no mourners.
- Are you Hwang Jeongshik?
- I don't want to see anyone. Please leave.
I'm a lawyer.
This is the inheritance Oh Namsuk left
behind after selling her house and land.
What is that supposed to mean?
But if you tie all this up,
how will you make a living?
I ruined my son's life.
I am the first reason why that happened,
and the second is money.
If Jeongshik can only get a hold of himself,
no matter how difficult life
will be, it won't be in vain.
But, Ma'am...
Once my son finally wakes
up, I'll give him that money.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Mom.
Forgive me, Mom...
I'm sorry...
Namsuk.
Was it all for this?
If this was the end that awaited you,
why did you live that way?
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have met you in the first place,
and ignored you for so many years.
Still...
What is this?
You foolish brat...
Yoo Gyeongok is now like a decaying tree.
It's only a matter of
time before she collapses.
But she's still supporting Hwang Taeseop.
And I can't let that happen.
I will bear that in mind, Congressman.
How are the opposition
party members reacting?
I did hear a strange rumor.
About what?
I can't speak with certainty,
but it's about a certain ruling
party member organizing a...
secret meeting with key
opposition party members.
And you don't know who
this ruling party member is?
You know you can never
be sure with political rumors.
It could just be a false alarm,
but considering the situation...
A secret meeting with
key opposition members...
I have a bad feeling about this.
Yes.
All right.
Sure.
We set up a date.
When is it?
This Saturday,
at the Shanghai Restaurant in Myeongdong.
They couldn't have been
informed of the account, right?
I'm sure he didn't tell them explicitly,
but he likely suggested that
something like that might exist.
Or else, he would have had
a hard time organizing all this.
You were right.
Who is this ruling party member?
I'm sure that day he will be revealed.
We will find out for what, why
and by whom all this was organized.
Wiretap?
When you need material
evidence, nothing beats the wire.
I can't smell any tear gas here.
That's how the world should be...
I told you his sniping
skills are second to none.
Wow... I'm so envious.
- It's a gift.
- Thank you.
How could he be so good?!
Hey... Why is it so hard to see
your superior these days?
Chief Hong is really busy as of late.
Is his wife giving birth this month?
It's not because of that.
He's in charge of politicians, these days.
Politicians who?
I don't really know for sure,
but you know that Chinese
restaurant, the Shanghai?
I hear they're bugging
the place or something.
Ahh... Shanghai?
At the Jeil Hotel?
Yes, that's the one.
Get ready.
Yes.
It's me.
Is Congressman Min with you?
He is.
Just listen.
The ANSP learned of all this.
Cancel today's meeting.
They did what?
You said that the opposition party
members know about the account, right?
They bugged the place, so
you must stop them from mentioning it.
What?
They bugged it?!
What is the matter?
We're heading that way,
so turn the car around.
All right.
We'll do that.
Turn the car around.
Turn around?!
What's the matter, Chairman Hwang?
I think they might have
found out about our meeting.
What?
We're almost there.
The agents must be
waiting by the main entrance.
Let's take the underground parking lot.
All right.
They're late.
But, should we really believe that?
I can't say.
Seeing as they called us
first, it shouldn't be a lie?!
So they talked of an account
for the secret presidential fund?
That's what I've heard.
If that is indeed the truth...
Yes.
The place has been bugged.
You must leave immediately.
You failed?
Details of our mission might
have been leaked beforehand.
Does that make any sense?
How could they possibly
find out about an ANSP mission?
There's an even bigger problem than that.
And what is that supposed to mean?
This is what the opposition
party members talked about.
But, should we really believe that?
I can't say.
Seeing as they called us first,
it shouldn't be a lie.
So they talked of an account
for the secret presidential fund?
That's what I've heard.
If that is indeed the truth....
This is where it ended.
An account for the
secret presidential fund?!
Have you ever written any
account while handling that fund?
Look, Chief Oh!
I would never do anything other
than what the president ordered me to.
But they did mention
the existence of such an account.
- If it wasn't you, who...
- Wait.
I wasn't the only one
handling that secret fund.
Lee Seongmo.
Chief Lee Seongmo?
That's right.
The only one in possession of enough
detailed information to write that account...
is Lee Seongmo.
Then, it can only be him.
I know how fond of him you are.
I don't want to believe this,
but how do you think the opposition
party members learned of this wiretap?
Capture Lee Seongmo
and get him to confess.
Still, nobody can learn of this.
You understand what I mean?
Should the president learn of this account,
I will lose everything
I have accomplished so far.
All his confidence in
me will vanish in a moment.
All right.
If Lee Seongmo betrayed me as you say,
then report back to me.
As I will deal with him firsthand.
What do you think you're doing?
Chief, what are you doing here?
Where is Lee Seongmo?
- What is this about...
- Where is he, you prick?
I plan to quit my job at the
ANSP within the next three years.
I'll just hand my resignation and run
an orchard in the outskirts of Seoul.
Grapes should do it.
Miju loves them, and we could
make wine out of that.
Hyung.
Just be honest and tell me everything.
Tell you what?
Saying that you'll quit in three years,
that can only suggest
you'll destroy Jo Pilyeon before that.
Better be careful what I say to you...
What have you planned?
Gangmo.
Leave this to me.
You're my brother!
Later... In due time,
I'll tell you everything.
Must you really
hide it from me as well?
That's what we
planned from the start.
We promised that you'd worry about
your company, and I'd handle this.
Let me make a call.
It's me, Chanseong.
Right as you were worrying,
I think they heard them talk about the account.
They even came to your
office and looked everywhere.
I suggest you find refuge somewhere.
Listen well, Chanseong.
As long as they don't find the
account, everything will be all right.
Without material evidence,
they can't do anything.
So don't worry about me and
take good care of that account.
No... Running away won't solve a thing!
I will handle this, so
you just worry about the...
What is that all about?
Running away?!
And what about this account?
Gangmo.
Who did you just talk with?
No way, Hyung!
Don't go.
If I don't, I'll have to hide
for the rest of my days.
And all our plans will be ruined.
But if they find
that account, you'll die!
- They won't.
- You think they won't make you confess?
You know who you're dealing with!
I'll just resist.
I will endure it to the end.
Hyung!
Gangmo...
I'd never leave you
and Miju behind and die.
I can't.
Give me that account.
What?
I'll expose it.
Let me do it.
Then, nothing will happen to you.
I told you to leave this to me!
So don't go there!
Or you could have
done it before I found out.
How can I let you go there?
Gangmo, I swear.
I won't die.
I promise, I won't.
Trust me.
Until I see Jo Pilyeon dead,
I'm never going to die first.
What is it?
You came out for me?
Chief Oh is waiting for you.
Were you looking for me?
Don't make a scene!
If you cooperate,
this will end quickly.
Follow me.
Starting now, I'm not your older
colleague, but just the man questioning you.
I ask the questions,
and you'll only speak to answer them.
And let's start by fixing that posture.
- Park Seonbae...
- Avoid all titles.
First tell me the reason I'm here.
Being treated like a criminal at my
workplace without knowing the reason...
is just insufferable.
There is a traitor within our ranks.
Then, I will catch him for you.
Hey... Lee Seongmo.
Park Seonbae!
You're close with the chairman
of Daeyang Chemicals, right?
Why did you take classified
department of defense files...
and met Chairman Song in secret?
Wh... What?!
That is exactly what you call betrayal.
Should I list all the
other "traitors" besides you?
You really...
I'm sure you're not the
one who suspects me, Chief Oh.
It is clear that outside pressures are to blame.
Who is it?
Who is calling me a traitor?
Let's make this clear.
If you can't prove any of your allegations,
then whomever is responsible for
this, be that from the inside or out,
will pay for what he did.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Is Min Honggi the one who's helping you?
If Lee Seongmo ends up confessing,
you will be the first to pay with your life.
So give me that account, Chairman Hwang!
It's too dangerous for
us to take a step forward.
- This is it.
- Against politicians?
We just received data
regarding Cha Soojeong.
Isn't this President Lee Gangmo?
If you still call yourself a father,
at least try to understand the
suffering your own son is going through.
You'll soon find out how scary
and cruel the world can be.
I told you I don't care whether
Lee Seongmo is killed or not!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com