Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 56
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
I think we'll have to stop a moment.
Really? So pull over.
What?! Isn't that Jo Pilyeon?
Hang tight.
Go faster!
They're a little late?
Hello.
Chanseong, where are you?
I...
I can't see...
What?
- Jo Pilyeon...
- Chanseong, where are you?
Jo Pilyeon!
Chanseong!
Chanseong, where... Hello?
He...
What's the matter, Hyung?
I think something might
have happened to Chanseong.
Wait there a moment, will be right back.
What's wrong with you?
Wake up.
If you stop here,
Jo Pilyeon will kill us!
Step on it!
Listen to me!
Do you want me
to go down and check?
If anyone sees us,
it'll only bring trouble.
Just leave.
All right.
Chanseong... Chanseong!!
Chanseong!
Chanseong.
Chanseong, are you all right?
Open your eyes!
Chanseong!
Chanseong.
Can you see me?
Hyung...
Don't talk.
Chanseong...
- Congressman Oh Byeongtak
Dies in Car Accident -
You really want to run an orchard?
That would be the plan, I guess.
But I don't really know
how much that would cost me.
And would you happen to have
a job for me, if I came there?
Why, want to quit as well?
Honestly, I've had
it with all this myself.
So hand your resignation
and come right away.
You can always raise pigs next to me.
I really will!
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Chanseong...
Chanseong was murdered.
In his last call to me, he
mentioned the name Jo Pilyeon.
There is no doubt, Gangmo.
It was Jo Pilyeon.
He was the one who killed
Chanseong and Congressman Oh.
If what you say is right,
then they shouldn't
have cremated their bodies.
All this was a stratagem by
Jo Pilyeon to avoid any autopsy.
Congressman Oh Byeongtak wrote it.
Hyung, this...
He wrote in detail about
the connection between...
Manbo Construction, Jo Pilyeon
and the private lending cartel.
According to reports
written by that Ji Yeonsoo,
the report Yoo Chanseong
wrote dealt with the torture case.
And the Catholic Priests' Association
for Justice got their hands on it.
While Hwang Taeseop played the messenger.
- That's what we can speculate.
- Arrest and put the squeeze on him.
That's the quickest way.
We can't do that anymore.
If we arrest someone without evidence,
we'll only get into trouble.
You know how much the president
agonized over that torture case?
Go take a look on the street.
Seditious individuals are about to riot.
I see we got a little cocky
ever since Congressman Oh died.
What do you mean by that?
Be honest, didn't that benefit you?
And it will become the opportunity
of a lifetime for you as well.
I know how to draw a line
between allies and foes.
Seongmo.
Don't you think you're
neglecting me a little these days?
A colleague of mine passed away,
so I couldn't spare the time.
Yoo Chanseong was actually
bearing a grudge against me.
All that has happened to us at
the ANSP was plotted by him.
And you were unfairly
accused because of him.
I see.
Is that the reason
why you killed Chanseong?
- Hey... Seongmo!
- I was just asking.
Because if Yoo Chanseong was
indeed a traitor, he had it coming.
Well said.
He deserved to die.
But...
It's too bad that he died in an accident...
before I could deal with him firsthand.
Come by my house one of these evenings.
My wife is really
disappointed that you never visit.
Do you still suspect
Seongmo, by any chance?
He lied to me twice.
What are you trying to say?
First he told me Lee Gangmo
died at the Samcheong camp,
and then he lied about
that Miju getting an abortion.
Yes... Now that I think
about it, it's strange.
If Yoo Chanseong was the
one who leaked the account,
then there is no doubt
that Lee Seongmo wrote it.
So don't you ever let your guard down.
All right, Congressman.
So this has something to
do with Congressman Oh's death?
The corrupt connections
involving Jo Pilyeon are two.
With a certain Noh Gapsoo
and his private lending operation,
and Manbo Construction.
Congressman Oh tried to bring
an end to Jo's political career by revealing that.
There is no doubt that this
would be a formidable scoop,
but the fact we're dealing
with Jo Pilyeon bothers me.
Because of press guidelines
they are forcing on us,
every article has to go through
an examination before it can be published.
Then, is there no way
to publish that article?
Congressman Oh's death
wasn't a simple car accident.
It was a first degree murder
plotted by a partnership...
between corrupt
politicians and the underworld.
There might be a way after all...
We'd go straight to printing
without passing through the editor's room.
Is that possible?
Reporter Yoon,
what are you doing here?
I came to see you, what else?
It's going to take some
money to convince me?!
At least a nice bottle of makgeolli...
Let's go, that will be my pleasure.
But, this fella?
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Lee Gangmo.
Ahh... You're a president?!
I suddenly feel the
urge to eat samgyeopsal?!
Here... We'll go for makgeolli
and samgyeopsal, then.
What are you saying?
So you want to change that
article and publish it that way?
Here you go.
- The Menage a Trois between Congressman
Jo Pilyeon, Private Lending and Manbo Construction -
Seeing this, looks like you're
trying to scold a few bad apples...
We're counting on you.
I have three kids in college.
Of course two of them were imprisoned
after joining the demonstrations,
but if I publish this and get fired,
how is my family going to survive?
- Mister Park.
- How many years left until you retire?
I'm about there?!
But, why are you asking?
If you end up getting fired,
Hangang Construction will scout you.
S....cout?!
We also will pay you
double your current salary.
And of course we'll employ you for
much longer than your retirement age.
Let's suppose I do it,
but how about you?
You'd be fired even
before they worry about me?!
I...
have already written
my letter of resignation.
Seonsaengnim.
Don't worry, Gangmo.
A few other dismissed reporters have
started a monthly current affairs magazine,
so I can just join them.
I need to go back to work,
so let's have another drink and leave.
Yes, sure.
- The Menage a Trois between Congressman
Jo Pilyeon, Private Lending and Manbo Construction -
Yes, Chairman.
Have you seen the paper?
What?
The paper?
Gather all the top executives
for an emergency meeting.
Right now.
Who the hell published this?
That article was written
by a certain Yoon Gihoon.
Yoon Gihoon?!
That Reporter Yoon was
Lee Gangmo's middle school teacher.
Then, are you telling me
that Lee Gangmo is behind this?
According to our
investigation, that's right.
Arrest him immediately
and question him... Right now!!
The entire country
has set its sights on this!
How can we avoid all
those arrows coming our way?
So? Are you just going
to let him walk free?
It's already spilt milk.
Shouldn't you worry
about putting off your own fire?
Yes.
Yes, Sir.
I will, Sir.
Who called?
The Blue House summoned you.
I am mortified, Mister President.
Now they even call
you to a meeting like this...
I see joining Congressman
Noh's camp helped your career.
He's soon going to announce
his candidacy for the next elections.
As if I wasn't busy enough already,
now I even have to deal
with your dirty laundry.
Are we getting sarcastic?
Congressman Oh was my political mentor.
And I plan to get to the bottom of this.
Have you forgotten that the president
just asked us to handle this quietly?
If you end up having the
slightest involvement in that case,
I'm sure the president is
not going to forgive you.
Give us a comment on
Congressman Jo's suspected connections.
Did you see the list of ailing
companies before it was published?
And how do you feel about the insinuations
of politics and finance as corrupt bedfellows?
I'm sorry, please free the way.
Several shareholders are
requesting a meeting with you.
Send them back.
What?
But, you should at least
say something to reassure them...
Other than finding a solution,
why should I waste time on any of that?
All right, Chairman.
Ahh.... Thank you.
Thank you.
How about it? Does it look good?
Wow... Miss Cha is really great?!
I think we'll have really cool ads.
Oppa.
Good job.
When is the shoot for the commercial?
This Friday.
Once the newspaper ad
and the commercial are out,
we've got this sale covered.
I'll be there to promote the sale as well.
Really?
If you can do that for us,
we'll just hit the jackpot!
Of course.
It's Cha Soojeong, after all.
Yes...
Anyhow, leave no stone unturned
and thoroughly investigate everything.
Yes.
Come on in, Chief Lee.
I see you're busy.
Manbo Construction is soon going
to be hit with a massive tax audit.
Have anything that could
help us, by any chance?
Nothing concrete.
It's not going to be easy,
if Jo Pilyeon is the target.
He's not the type to
leave any evidence behind.
How about the prosecutors' side?
I've already hit that route.
He will soon be summoned.
They won't be able to
get much out of him, either.
They'll stop at mere formalities.
And that is why we
need stronger evidence.
Would you be able to allow
the ANSP to investigate on him?
You mean letting you
take over the investigation?
Because I'm the only one who
knows Jo Pilyeon well enough to do it.
You do have a point.
I will bring it up with Director Kim.
Thank you, Congressman Min.
Who are you people?
What are you doing here?
Look!
Hey!
What is going on?
We're from the National Tax Service.
Proceed.
Who are you people?
We come from the ANSP.
The ANSP?!
So not the prosecutor's
office, but you are here?
You'll have to forgive me,
but I must ask you to follow us.
Chief Oh is smarter than I thought.
I was just thinking that
this would be much better for me.
- Jaechun, give Chief Oh a call.
- All right, Congressman.
Yeah...
All right.
Sure.
Director Kim told me he hopes
that there are no seedy connections...
between you and Jo Pilyeon.
You can take a short leave
of absence if you want, Chief Oh.
Seongmo, you came out to see me?
What is this?
I'm sorry.
I'm forced to
follow my superior's orders.
Where did Chief Oh go?
He's away on an assignment in the provinces.
Who did this?
Director Kim?
Who ordered you to arrest me?
There are plenty of eyes on us.
If you don't collaborate,
this might take long.
Lee Seongmo.
Now you're starting as well?
Don't tell me you're suspecting
that I killed Yoo Chanseong?!
I once heard this from you.
That suspecting someone
with the intent of saving him...
or just to kill him are
two entirely different things.
But what I see in your eyes...
is nothing but suspicion with
the intent of killing someone?!
I'm surely...
seeing wrong, isn't it?!
I will start.
You once told me that Yoo Chanseong
was bearing a grudge against you.
Explain why he would bear
such feelings against you.
Seongmo, I thought you were clever.
- Guess I was wrong.
- Please answer.
Be it intentional or not,
you're making a big mistake.
I'll ask again.
Is it true that you killed
Yoo Chanseong's older brother?
Right...
Why would I blame
it on someone like you?
Only one man is capable of
plotting something like this against me.
Min Honggi!
Stop forcing Seongmo to do
your dirty work and come forward.
This is not going
to kill me, I'm afraid.
The moment I get out of this room,
you'll find out firsthand
how big a mistake all this was.
I'll take responsibility,
so let's go all the way.
Is that true?
An impregnable fortress like Jo
Pilyeon was arrested by the ANSP?!
Congressman Min Honggi
was convinced that...
Jo Pilyeon was behind Congressman Oh's death.
He joined Congressman Noh's camp,
and now he's firing on all cylinders.
Well... Since barring any last minute change,
Congressman Noh is going
to become the next president.
Then, does it mean that Jo
Pilyeon's political career is over?
Timing is the problem.
No matter if it's Congressman Min,
he won't be able to hold
Jo Pilyeon for much longer.
If he doesn't find any concrete evidence,
all this will have been in vain...
What's wrong with you?
Uh?!
I'm a colleague of yours.
Aren't you taking this too far?
Hey... Seongmo!
What were you waiting for, man...
Take all these off of me.
Go Seonbae.
Yeah, Seongmo.
How many people
have you killed so far?
Did anyone instigate you to
commit these last two murders?
Or did you order someone else to do it?
The congressman was right...
I still wanted to believe
you to the very end...
Answer my question.
The congressman!
Always treated you like a son.
Why did you do it?
Why?
What is the reason?
Chief!
Chief! You're going to kill him!
Out of the way.
Chief!!
My mother died because of you.
I've been waiting for
this day ever since, Go Jaechun...
Chief!
- My Home, The Most Comfortable Place on Earth -
Hangang Construction
The moment the sale was opened,
hordes of people filed applications
for Hangang Construction's apartments.
I think we should follow
suit before it's too late.
You only start a fight when
you're 100 percent sure to win it.
And now is not the time.
- Still, just sitting back and watching...
- Just wait.
I'm thinking of a counterplan as we speak.
Watch the line, folks.
Soojeong's help made a big difference.
Hey... We'll have to
open another sales office.
Do that.
- Shideok, look into it.
- All right.
But we're so damn busy, why are
those two not coming back from the UK?
Hey... The way I see it,
Sotae made a move on her.
I knew it the moment I
saw how he was staring at Gyeongja.
What is that supposed to mean?
Shouldn't his brother-in-law know better?!
Don't even say that!
Thank you.
Yes.
What's the matter, Mom?
What on earth are you saying?
Dad was arrested by the ANSP?!
I'll look into it,
so don't worry too much.
All right, I get it!
What happened, Chairman?
Chief...
Aren't you having lunch?
You didn't even eat breakfast...
Should I go out
and buy you something?
Yes.
It's me, Hyung.
What's going on with my father?
It's nothing serious.
Just a formality.
All right.
No need to worry.
Still, I'm glad you're there.
Need to go.
I'm busy now.
I've gathered all executives.
Starting now, we're going to
accept applications for our apartments.
As you're well aware,
Hangang Construction is...
performing much better than
us in the Suseo apartment sale.
So to turn the tide in our favor,
we will follow a new strategy.
First,
we will focus on upscale
buyers with higher prices.
This will not only show that the
rumors about us are unfounded,
but also help us differentiate
our offer from that of our competitor.
During sales season, you often
see "birds of passage" trying to get their fill,
real estate speculators
trying to drive up prices.
We could use those middlemen
to spread rumors about...
the price of our apartments going up
threefold a few years after buying them.
Encouraging real estate speculation is
the best form of marketing we can undertake.
We will hire a few hundred people
to stand in line at our sales offices,
to make people buy into the idea
that our apartments are selling really well.
And using TV exposure to our
advantage is another must.
All right then, let's join forces.
There's nothing as effective as TV...
in convincing the same banking sector
which has been ignoring us.
The bank is giving anyone
who applies for their apartments...
loans at very low interest rates.
- Manbo's Suseo Sale About to Reach the 60 Percent -
According to our investigation,
it seems like they're
using real estate speculators.
Speculators?
Aren't they manipulating the market, then?
Should we go at it as well?
No.
No need to give people the image
that we're wrestling against each other.
We'll just go at it our own way.
How about the CF shoot?
You saw, right?
It was just awesome.
They're going to start
airing it from next week.
Spare no expense
and market it aggressively.
- Yes, we will, President!
- Yes, Sir!
I think Jo Pilyeon
will have to be released.
The investigation is not over yet.
He'll be released in the afternoon.
Asking Director Kim will be useless,
since there have been
complaints from political circles.
I feel just like you,
but what else can we do?
We'll have to find another way.
I'm sure Jo Pilyeon
will resent you for this.
Be careful out there.
Chairman.
Dad.
So even Seongmo
Hyung couldn't expose him.
First, we'll have to go to the hospital.
I'm... just fine, Congressman.
Who the hell did this to you?
Lee Seongmo...
Are you telling me Lee
Seongmo personally tortured you?
It was as if he wanted to kill me.
Even if still upset over
Yoo Chanseong's death,
there is no way he
would do something like this.
I may not know the reason,
but this is betrayal for sure.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
If it was for your sake,
Seongmo Hyung would do anything.
I don't really like the fact you're
suspecting him without a single hesitation.
There are things you don't know.
We must find his true colors at all cost.
Leave me alone a moment.
Uh?
I said get the hell out!
Y...es, Chief.
- 0830, Chief Lee Seongmo Arrives at the Office
- 0915, Morning Meeting (Director's Office)
- 1100, 2nd Division Meeting (Torture Case)
Open this.
- What?
- Hurry up and open it!
- Ji Yeonsoo Files -
- 1000, Chief Yoo Chanseong
Interrogates Student Demonstrator -
- 1000, Chief Yoo Chanseong Writes
Report (Namyoung-Dong Torture Case)
What's the matter, Chief?
Who's in charge of examining
the new recruits' reports?
These days, Chief Yoon does it.
I knew this would happen.
You like your new phone?
What's the matter?
You don't like the phone?
How could I possibly blame it on you?!
Like you'd know what was going on...
Chief...
- Isn't that Cha Soojeong?
- It's her, Eonni!
- Cha Soojeong, how are you?
- Hi.
Hi.
You're so pretty!
Thank you.
Will you sign this?
I like your songs so much.
What's with him?
He looked at you and just left?!
Seonhwa, let's just go.
Thank you.
Birthday?!
Do you know what giving a man
a necktie pin really means?
The way I've heard it,
it's what women give to men
when they confess to them?!
Really?
I just bought it without knowing?!
Keep it for the rest of your days.
If you ever take it off, you're dead.
Gangmo!
Are you still busy at this hour?
Aren't you leaving?
We're soon getting our permit,
so I was checking data
for the last screening.
Really?
Can I help you with anything?
Nah...
So, what should we start from?
Here.
See if the calculations are right.
Okay.
Jeongyeon.
Later... In what kind of
house would you like to live?
What kind of house?!
Just...
You know...
The kind of house people in their
40s or 50s dream of, and stuff.
I really have no ideal house?
Still...
Tell me.
Let's see...
I never really thought about it...
Ohh... I'd like to
have a really big dog.
A dog?
Yeah... A white one.
My stepmother hated dogs,
so I could never have one.
If you want a big dog,
you'll also need a very large yard.
Right?
With large front doors...
and a tiny gate.
What else?
I'll want to play the
piano every now and then,
so the living room
should be really wide.
Which color for the piano?
White, of course.
A Grand piano.
Ahh... Grand.
I'd like very large windows, and...
Right.
A terrace where I could drink
coffee in the morning would be nice, too.
Right where the sun shines.
As for the roof...
Red would be nice.
And I'd put roses all
across the fence. Lilacs, too.
That's my favorite sce....
I really have no big expectations...
So if you really want to take care of all that,
I don't think you'll be able to live alone?
Go back in.
After I see you go.
It's cold, just go.
Thanks for helping me, Gangmo.
Drive safely.
Right.
Just wait, Jeongyeon.
I'll build you that house for sure.
Yes?
Hyung.
It's you?
Why did you drink so much?
Because if I don't,
I might just go crazy.
We still have a chance.
Don't let anxiety
get the better of you, Hyung.
Gangmo.
If... And that's just a if.
If I ended up dying, you'd
still be living happily with Miju, right?
What do you mean by that?
I can't take this anymore.
I just want to put a bullet through
Jo Pilyeon's head and kill myself.
Get a hold of yourself, Hyung!
I mean it, Gangmo.
I might even kill that bastard tonight.
Hyung, you're the head of our family!
If you die like that, think our
parents will welcome you with open hands?
Chanseong died because of me.
While I was letting Jo Pilyeon fool me...
While I was acting
so foolishly, I got him killed.
Tell me what happened.
Jo Pilyeon sent a spy to our office.
Neither the killed...
nor the killer knew anything about it.
Jo Pilyeon plotted
all that from the beginning.
He made sure a colleague would kill him!
It's my fault.
I let him fool me.
He died because of me!
I know, Hyung.
I know what you're feeling.
But revenge is all we need.
We can just all join forces, Hyung.
But don't you ever
tell me you'll die, Hyung.
We need to find Junmo
and live together happily, Hyung.
Did he have that much to drink?
There's nothing wrong with him, right?
No need to worry.
Just prepare him some
hangover soup tomorrow.
He should get married, so that
someone can take care of him.
Are you feeling better, Hyung?
Where am I?
Miju's bedroom.
And how did I end up here?
I don't remember a thing.
About that spy you
talked about yesterday.
She still doesn't know she's
being used to spy on you, does she?
She's a naive girl.
And kind.
I think we might actually
use her to ruin Jo Pilyeon.
Since all we need is proof
that he killed Oh Byeongtak.
So now you've been cleared of
any suspicion of murder?
They've got nothing on their hands,
what could they possibly do?
I almost risked getting
involved in all this because of you.
This was a good opportunity to learn.
Better yet,
to recall things I've been
forgetting for much too long.
The fact that offense is
the best form of defense.
Who's the target?
Min Honggi will be the first.
And the second?
That bastard...
That is...
The one who's been going at
my throat from behind my back.
Yoo Chanseong is already dead,
so is it still Lee Seongmo?
So, what kind of offense
are you going to start with?
No need to hesitate any longer.
If we put the squeeze on Hwang
Taeseop, everything will be solved.
Think about it.
Min Honggi might have been
benefiting from his connections,
but he was a sympathizer of
the amendment just a few months ago.
That's just an allegation.
Isn't that the reason why we
should catch Hwang Taeseop?
He holds all the keys.
All we need is for him to speak.
I see...
Same goes for Lee Seongmo.
If the man who got in touch with
Yoo Chanseong is Hwang Taeseop,
I'm sure Lee Seongmo's
name will pop up as well.
Yes... All right.
I'll be by your side, Sir.
Yes.
Ahh... I can't take this anymore.
- Forgot it's your turn?
- All right.
What's the matter?
Looks like the direct elections that
congress couldn't bring to fruition...
will be dragged into the streets.
Are you going to participate as well?
After all we've gone
through to get to this point,
why would I possibly hesitate?
Unless I'm given a second life,
I'll have to take this to the end.
Who are you people?
Mister Hwang Taeseop?
You'll have to follow us.
Follow you where?
You... What are you people?
Ju Youngguk... Take him as well.
- Yes.
- You really...
Where are you taking him?
Dad! Dad!!
I told you to take a few days off,
what are you doing here?
I'm all right, Sir.
If not me, who would be by your side?
What is all this?
Why was my father arrested?
Isn't that what you wanted?
You asked me for information
from the opposition party,
we never talked of arresting my father.
What will happen to him?
Don't worry.
If he tells us what we need,
he'll be released in no time.
And how are you going to
get that confession out of him?
Will you torture him?
Now that his father is in danger,
seems like the prodigal son finally woke up?!
This is not the kind of revenge I wished for.
Release him.
I couldn't care less what you wish for.
What I need is intel,
so if you want your father
to be released, bring it to me.
I do have a photo.
A photo?!
It wasn't shot properly,
so it won't be of much help.
You have it on you?
It's the man who's been
meeting in secret with my father.
Isn't this...
Lee Seongmo?
Yes...
It does look like him.
Sorry for treating
you that way all this time.
Don't say that...
You must be having it really hard,
and I'm not doing anything to help...
I should apologize.
Once your tenure as recruit is over,
where would you like to be assigned to?
I'll work under you for sure.
You'll take me, right?
If you want to choose your
assignment, you need to win points.
Are you working hard on those reports?
Don't you worry! I can write
reports like the best of them.
Take it.
I'm Lee Gangmo.
Just a moment.
It's a certain Lee Gangmo.
Yes, go ahead.
So you have found clear evidence?
Write this down.
Tell me time and place, please.
This week.
Wednesday night, at nine.
Have you written it down?
Be there on time.
All right.
Was that spy fella next to him?
It's a woman.
A woman?
You'll have to help
me with that, Shideok.
All right.
Don't worry, Gangmo.
Take good care of that memo.
Yes, Chief.
Yes.
It's me, Seongmo.
Where are you now?
I sometimes come here alone,
whenever my head hurts.
Seongmo.
I still like you.
Do you know that?
Since we're here,
I guess I should agree.
I know that things aren't what
they used to be anymore.
I can't really figure out when
things started going downhill.
Did you kill Chanseong?
Right...
That's right.
I think misunderstandings
like this were to blame.
If you didn't do it,
then that's all I need to know.
I'll believe you, from now on.
Seeing these autumn leaves,
I get the feeling that growing
old is not that bad after all.
I guess it's newfound
passion for one's final days.
Right...
Well said.
Then, they fall to the ground.
And die.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com