Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
- Episode 38 -
- Gangmo...
- Let go!
- You've lost all reason!
- You bet I did.
There's no stopping me now.
Gangmo...
That's the piece of shit
who ruined our Miju!
And now he's trying to ruin me as well!
And in conclusion, you've become
chairman at such a young age,
can you tell us your future aspirations?
I have a keen interest in the
social role corporations can play.
Profits are certainly important,
but they always pale in comparison
with the contribution your...
What is President Lee Gangmo of
Hangang Construction doing here?
There's a limit to my patience!
So, what?
Are you gonna hit me?
Think I couldn't?
If you want your face on every
major newspaper's front page...
Be my guest.
You don't have the guts to do that.
Know why?
Because you can act tough all you want,
but you still remain a weakling.
A joint syndicate?!
Know why you were swept away
like leaves under the autumn wind?
Because you're weak.
And a bunch of cowards.
So that's why you'll never make it.
You'll only be bait for the big fish.
Gangmo...
Weakling?
Coward?!
I told you, didn't I?
That any time I see pompous fools
trying to act like big fish,
I get the urge to devour them!
Stop!
Chairman...
Chairman!
Gangmo!
Director Moon...
Report him to the police immediately.
Right away.
You caught it all on film, right?
Are you all right?
Thanks, Hyung.
- Happy Credit -
Good morning.
Eonni...
Can't we just get this out of the way?
Aww... It's such a nuisance.
We might need it as collateral,
so keep it here.
Construction Firm President Assaults
Manbo Construction Chairman Jo Minwoo
Currently Hospitalized for Treatment,
Chairman Jo Receives 4-week Prognosis
- Gangmo.
- This way.
Gangmo, what is all this about?
Your face is all over
this morning's newspapers.
I'm sorry to all of you.
No need to feel sorry!
Hey... You did well.
If anyone deserves to be
behind bars, that's Jo Minwoo.
What did you ever do wrong?
That's right...
He's the one who should be
punished by the law.
While you were at it,
why not rough him up for good?
For the time being, you two
take care of the construction site.
- All right...
- All right, don't you worry.
You handle things at the office, Shideok.
All right.
Even without me,
it must be business as usual.
Is that clear?
President...
What now...
Aigoo... Here they are.
Minwoo, are you all right?
I only let them hospitalize me
to play up the press,
so no need to worry.
So what happened?
I underestimated him.
I never imagined Lee Gangmo would
hit me before all those cameras.
In business and politics,
your image is the most important thing.
This will negatively affect you as well.
And what did Minwoo ever do wrong?
The blame is all on who hit him.
If you don't know what you're
talking about, just keep quiet.
All the government funding which
was promised to Hangang Construction...
has been canceled.
Walk all over Lee Gangmo,
so that he won't get a chance to recover.
If I only stopped at
paying him back for this,
that wouldn't be much of a revenge.
Just hang in there a little longer.
They'll soon release you on probation.
Sorry, Hyung.
But I don't regret this.
If I hadn't done that,
it would have driven me crazy.
I know what you mean.
The Ministry of Construction
decided to cut your funding after all.
Won't you have to halt
the construction now?
Nah.
I'm not giving up.
I'll take this to the end.
What Jo Pilyeon wants...
is for you to put all your eggs in
this one basket and end up ruined.
I'll handle those company matters, Hyung.
That's that,
but still no news from Miju?
All the choreographers and singing trainers
are sparing no compliments about her.
Lee Miju, you said?
Yes.
But do you really plan to
groom her into a top attraction?
It would be a waste
to limit her to our stage.
Th...Then...
Where do you live?
Hannam-Dong.
Family?
I live... alone.
If you really wish to succeed,
you must put everything on the line.
And even if you do, nobody
can guarantee you'll make it.
I really want to
become a successful singer.
Everyone starts
with your same intentions,
but real success comes very rarely.
And that's because not only
you won't make it without effort,
even effort alone can never be enough.
Practice will be very severe.
If you don't think you can
handle that, better give up now.
No, Director...
I'm confident I can make it.
I'm back...
Did you just finish?
Yes...
My legs are killing me.
Still, see how far you've come?
Getting opportunities like this.
You're right.
But, how about Wooju?
Don't know what upset him today,
but after making a fuss all evening,
he fell asleep only now.
Mommy...
Come here.
Here...
Sleep.
Sleep well, my Wooju.
In the garden and over the hills,
Even birds and lambs are asleep.
As the moonlight
shines through the window.
Sleep well, my baby.
In the garden and over the hills,
Even birds and lambs are asleep.
Wooju.
Mommy will succeed,
and make your every dream come true.
So grow up into a healthy boy.
Are we clear?
Here's his registration number
directly from the States.
So that Han Sojin does
own real estate overseas?!
He looked so young...
Must be really rich.
Have a nice day.
They're not calling?!
Did they smell a rat?
They'll call soon.
Since I forged my ID using
a real landowner living overseas.
There is no way
Hwang Jeongyeon could find out.
See, you fool?
Told you they'd call.
Yes...
Han Sojin? Happy Credit here.
Ohh... Yes! Director Hwang.
Our background check is complete.
You can just bring us
a copy of your account book.
Yes, I'll bring it tomorrow.
Yes...
Bait is taken!
What brings you here?
Found a way to target Hwang Jeongyeon?
Sure.
I can get my hands on
all her money in a month.
Quite confident.
Anything I snitch will be mine...
I should give my best.
You don't have much time.
Success or failure,
you only have one month.
Is Baekpa doing well?
He is.
And you as well.
Yes, I'm fine.
Ohh... Good to hear.
I had this fine ginseng I got
from an acquaintance of mine...
I'll just send it your way.
No need.
Once you're done,
contact the Royal Club.
Fine.
If she didn't get in the way,
I would have never had to live this way.
What?
Her place was mine.
She took it away from me.
Yoo Gyeongok...
Don't act all important.
Think I don't know that
Hwang Jeongyeon is your daughter?
That daughter of yours will pay back
for everything you did to me.
- Jong-Ro Police Department -
Gangmo.
Shall we go for a drink, Sir?
I need to go to the construction site.
I've left it unattended for far too long.
Ehh... How nasty, wanted
to get piss drunk with you...
Sorry, Hyung.
Let's do that another time.
Ahh... Yes, certainly, President!
Aigoo, as you wish!
At this rate, how long will it
take to remove all the rock bed?
How long is not the issue.
It's whether we'll be still in business
by the time we finish laying foundations.
Wonder if they've heard about
the government cutting our funding,
but the subcontractors
are starting to get restless.
How about our finances?
Pretty serious.
Looks like we might
soon need another loan.
Gangmo...
Before we go belly up,
let's just drop out of this.
He's right, Gangmo.
It's nothing we can solve on our own.
This construction is not the issue!
If we're excluded from
the New City concessions,
we'll never rise above third-rate status.
Let's give it all we've got.
If we endure this to the end,
we'll find a way.
The fight now will be
fought with raw materials.
What are our most pressing needs?
Aggregate*.
*slag, crushed stone, and all other
material used to reinforce composite
There's a war raging between competitors
to secure aggregate in the Suseo area.
Even if you have to pay
double, secure it at all cost.
But the other committee
members would protest that.
It doesn't matter.
We might be allies when it
comes to committee issues,
but out on the construction site,
we're all enemies.
I will proceed as instructed, then.
Right...
Has Hangang Construction not given up yet?
Despite facing the impending
prospect of running out of funds,
they're proceeding with
the construction as we speak.
Call the International Bank and
set up a meeting with the president.
Why would you suddenly...
Just in case, we need to cut all
possible escape routes they might look for.
All right, Chairman.
Manbo Construction is hoarding
aggregate as if there's no tomorrow.
And prices have risen twofold already.
Ehh... Motherless twats.
We don't even have money
to finish laying foundations...
If this keeps up, will we even
get a look at that aggregate?
- Manbo Construction -
Let's just go.
Aren't you going to meet Jeongyeon?
If she sees me in this state,
it'll only make her
feel more responsible.
Unless I first gain
some kind of foothold,
there's nothing that
will give her peace.
That...
Jo Pilyeon!
I ought to just...
Calm down.
Look at him!
Look at how he parades around!
He's prancing around as if he owns the
place I shed blood and tears to build!
And what would going at him
possibly accomplish?
I'll be damned...
I did hear he became a congressman...
Sure got himself some influence.
"President Jeon Duhwan condemned
these student demonstrations..."
"as illegal acts of vandalism that can
only damage our country's reputation..."
"in the international community's eyes,
as we prepare to host the 1988 Olympic Games."
This country is really
getting out of control.
If left to my discretion,
I could deal with those fools
in no more than three months.
Yes?
Yes, Sir!
Turn that off.
Yes, I'm listening, Sir!
Yes, Sir!
Yes, Sir. Certainly.
I will come there
right away, Mister President.
Jaechun, get the car.
What is the matter?
I need to head to the Blue House.
What are you waiting for?
All right.
How did it go earlier?
The Ministry of Construction will soon
announce a declaration dealing with the North.
Why would the Ministry of
Construction deal with North Korea?
To interfere with the Olympic Games,
the North is building an
immense dam in Mount Geumgang.
They plan to fill it with water
and release it all at once.
Then... What will happen to us?
The flood will submerge the capital
all the way to 63 Building.
Those bastards...
We were already well
aware of such plans...
True or not, it doesn't matter.
We will build a similar structure
up Bukhan River to contend with them.
So that's why the Ministry
of Construction got involved.
A huge amount of money will be
poured into the dam construction sector.
Easy money, as they call it.
Thank you for the precious information.
We will devise a plan.
That is why economy and politics
always go hand in hand.
Hello?
Isn't our president there?
He's not there?
Why isn't he coming?
We don't have a minute to waste.
Gangmo...
This is serious.
Head to the construction site right away.
Why, what's the matter?
The subcontractors are threatening
to abandon the construction.
What?!
Where are you going?
Didn't they cut all your funding?
And who said that?
We have plenty of options
left on the table.
Then, shall we start
by settling our advances?
Here, folks... Don't act like this.
Let's just finish working, uh?
Shouldn't you finish working if you
want us to get the money to pay you?
Anyhow, if you don't pay us,
we're not going to work.
Here... Let's all go.
Fine... As you wish.
Let's do this.
You've been working hard all this time,
so I'll give you a week off.
Then, will everything
be settled in a week?
Of course.
So there will be no interruption,
but just a temporary break.
You know that once the week is up,
you'll have to come back to work, right?
Since you're there, enjoy a good rest.
Because after that, there will be no
days off until the construction is complete.
Are we clear?
Guess we'll see each other in a week.
Gangmo...
Is there a way to get us
out of trouble in a week?
There's none.
None?!
If there's none,
then why give them time off?
So that things will
quiet down for a week.
We'll have to find a way before then.
Ehh Ehh... Look what
nonsense he gets us into...
Go back to the office.
For the next week, I'll remain here.
If you stay, let us join you!
Let's just go.
It's best to leave him alone
when he acts like that.
- Let go, you twat...
- I said come!
The "Peace Dam"?!
It's what they'll call it when
the official announcement is out.
I have my doubts
about this project as well.
If you want, I could help you get
involved with the dam construction.
But, is it really true?
Will Seoul really be flooded if the North
makes their Mt. Geumgang dam explode?
Just worry about building that dam.
If it's a lie, I want
no part in this, Hyung.
It's a fraud.
I have no intention of making
dirty money by joining a fraud...
perpetrated against our people.
Then, are you going to go on
with this construction?
I have a week.
I'm sure I can find a way.
I feel so sorry for Gangmo Oppa,
it's killing me...
How much money does he need?
It's not just a few pennies.
So why even bother building there...
But looks like it's all
because of Manbo Construction.
It was Jo Minwoo
who broke up the syndicate,
and he even had a hand in
the bank refusing us loans.
Jo Minwoo... What a bastard.
Eonni, why did you
break up with Gangmo Oppa?
I really can't figure you two out.
If you like each other, just say it.
What's wrong with you?
Did Gangmo...
say he likes me?
So you didn't know?!
Know why I came to you
for those installments?
That is all because Gangmo Oppa
was wondering how you were doing.
That poor fool...
If he accepted me, I'd be good to him...
We regretfully have to refuse.
The Ministry's funding...
was already given to
Manbo Construction.
If you ever close up shop, blame me.
I'm just a coward!
A son of a bitch!
Be my guest!
I'm not falling down this way!
I'm never,
ever going to be defeated!
Even if I have to build those
damned apartments this way!
I'm not...
I'm never going to give up!
Never!
Never...
Never.
I'll never be defeated!
If that's what it takes...
If that's what it takes,
I'll build them here.
Those apartments...
Lee Gangmo...
will never lose!
Ever!
It can turn a rock this big
into gravel in a moment.
We developed this.
- Manbo Construction
Suspected of Hoarding Aggregate -
So what did you want to meet for?
How is your company doing, these days?
Unless you agree to lend us money,
don't bother asking.
Can you use this
over rock beds as well?
With a large hydraulic breaker,
it certainly could work.
We'll give you a loan.
Interest will be at normal bank rates.
What?
Wait... Bank... rates?!
Are you really going to
lend us money on the cheap?
Instead, I have a condition.
Have you heard
of Hangang Construction?
Hangang Construction?
Haven't really heard of them,
but why are you asking?
That damned temper of yours...
Aww... Look at these hands, you fool!
- Get moving!
- Is it that heavy, you twat?
Wow... This...
Wow, Gangmo here must have croaked.
Ahh... Really, listen to that.
Gangmo.
Gangmo, wake up.
What's that?
Ohh... Someone sent this to you.
To be specific, this is
called a "hydraulic breaker."
They use it to break rocks.
Really?
"Really?"
Who sent this?
Well, guess they sent it
to advertise their company?!
With this on that rock bed,
it'll take a hundred years longer.
So why did you bring this along?
The hell you know?
Take a look at this paper,
and what... What's this?
These were inside the package.
Look.
- Manbo Construction
Suspected of Hoarding Aggregate -
What's that?
Why, what's so new about
construction sites lacking aggregate?
Take this and follow me.
Now!
- Hey... Take it.
- You take it, this time!
Go stop him, will you?
Gangmo!
Gangmo, please! Give it a rest!
Hey... Gangmo!
Hey... Call an ambulance.
Hyungnim, can you see this?
Can you?!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
It's a rock, you fool!
This is gold!
We found a goldmine!
Hey, Gangmo...
It'll take you a damned century
to deal with this rock bed using that!
Shideok. Give it here.
And if it was this big?
What's that?
Was there one this big?
Hey... If it's a
hydraulic breaker this big...
It will speed up things exponentially?!
Forget getting rid of it, if we
start fragmenting this huge rock bed...
Gangmo!
This rock bed is a goldmine!
It's a goldmine!
Right?!
Ahh... really, you people!
What damned goldmine?
It's a bunch of rocks!
Aggregate!
What?
Ag...Aggregate?
That's right, you fool!
If we fragment this all and sell it,
this is all money!
We're saved!
We made it!
Gangmo, you're a genius!
Call them right away.
But... But... But, can you really
crush all that rock with this?
Aigoo, you foolish twat!
You crush rock beds with explosives,
while you'd use that equipment
to fragment the rocks.
You could have just told me,
why always twat this and twat that?!
'Cause you are one.
What it means is, that rock bed will be
enough to cover aggregate for all Suseo.
Not to mention reducing the costs
of removing all that rock bed,
and bringing us a ton of money
if we sell that aggregate.
What? Wow!
They're not answering?!
This won't do it.
Let's head to the factory.
- Right.
- That...
was developed by us.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Go Cheolsu.
How many hydraulic breakers
do you have right now?
How many do you need?
I'd like to buy them all.
All of them?!
Instead, you must give us a discount.
You saved us as well.
Of course we will!
But, how did you find out
we were in this situation?
I read it in the newspaper.
Thank you.
The sample you sent gave me courage.
Ahh... Yes...
We looked into it, and turns out you
borrowed over 500 million from the bank?
We can only give you about 30 million.
That little?!
I'd easily get fifty elsewhere?!
Then, go ask them.
All right.
At least interest is cheaper here.
I'll take that.
Come this way.
Hwang Jeongyeon...
She's more meticulous than I thought?!
Until I order you to stop,
pay the installments on time.
Yes, Hyungnim.
She's taken the bait,
so now the struggle begins.
Keep pulling the rod, and
she'll soon take a wrong step.
A mistake that will cost her dearly.
Eonni.
Let's go.
Isn't this Director Hwang?!
We meet again?!
So you like working out?
In business or anything else,
strength is everything.
Director Hwang...
Ever hit one of these?
Ehh... You're always
carrying cash with you.
Shouldn't you learn
how to protect yourself?
I always wanted to learn self-defense?!
Here, I'll give you a quick lesson,
so give it a try.
Here... Let's go.
Harder.
That's right! Harder.
Our president always
lives up to his word.
Sit down.
Did you enjoy your time off?
Yes!
This gentleman wearing the hat here,
Technical Director Nam Youngchul,
must have explained already?!
You're really something.
How did you manage to turn useless
rock into aggregate?! You're brilliant.
I'll only request two things from you.
First, we will pay all that is due
to you after selling the aggregate.
May we do that?
- Yes!
- Sure.
Also, we will keep all the aggregate
in a tent and conserve it.
Until we actually start selling it,
please maintain secrecy.
That is all.
Gangmo.
But, why keep the fact that
we're selling aggregate secret?
Right! We should spread
the word right away!
Manbo Construction keeps
hoarding aggregate at high rates.
So, what...
"Let's force Minwoo to eat his own crap?"
That?!
It was Jo Minwoo who started this fight.
That's a Hangang Construction truck?!
Jo Minwoo.
I see you're hard at work.
Crushing that rock bed,
and throwing it all away.
I hear you're busy hoarding
aggregate, these days?
If you want to buy any,
you'll have to pay it on the double.
You shouldn't laugh in the
face of business ethics like that.
Business ethics?!
Know business ethics
that can't be topped?
Selling quality apartments
at the right price.
There's a way to sell quality
apartment at cheap prices, too.
Wish you luck.
Looks like he still has no intention
of giving up the construction.
He's always been a blockhead.
And that's what
will ruin him in the end.
Because of Manbo Construction,
aggregate is twice more expensive.
Isn't this excessive, Chairman Jo?
Are you implying that it's my fault?
Listen, Chairman Jo.
Isn't that happening because
you're hoarding it all for yourself?
Let's not do this to
each other, Chairman Jo.
You disappoint me.
What?
I thought at least you could distinguish
between cooperation and competition.
Listen, Chairman Jo...
We might be fellow committee members,
but do I really have to witness someone
who could be my son lecture me?
It sounds to me like you're looking
down on me for being young?!
Ahh... What...
What did you say?
Let me be clear.
I didn't come here to
grovel at your feet in deference.
If you have any qualms about me,
file an official complaint.
You...
You really...
My!
What brings you here?
Nothing that should
concern you, so keep going.
So you still haven't
given up the construction?
You know me.
I don't give up so easily.
I sure do.
But, can you really handle it?
You should be running
out of money by now...
How about you call it
quits while you still can?
If you think money can only come out of
a bank's vault, you're sorely mistaken.
What?
Sometimes it can come out of this.
And even out of here.
Why...
Going to sue him for assault again?
He's so good at this, might
get himself a three-week prognosis.
Hey, Lee Gangmo...
Seems like you still haven't
quite figured me out yet...
I sure have.
I know that you're
weaker than the weak,
and more afraid
than the biggest cowards.
What?
Because using power and money
to walk over weak people...
is something that only the weakest,
most miserable coward would resort to.
Have you noticed anything
strange about them as of late?
I can't say...
Other than the fact that they're
going ahead with the construction...
He's got no respect.
Tell me about it!
Look at how he uses his father's
influence to indulge his arrogance.
But the real issue is
our lack of aggregate.
Can't be helped.
If Manbo Construction is paying twice
the price, we'll have to do the same.
You don't need to.
President Lee,
what are you doing here?
I will sell you the aggregate
for your apartment construction.
On the condition that you won't
give me a penny over market value.
What is that supposed to mean?
Are you telling me Hangang
Construction is selling aggregate?
Yes.
You won't face any more difficulties
because of aggregate shortages.
Can we really trust you on this?
Yes.
The sister you were loo...
Chanseong, still haven't gone home?
No need to hide it from me as well.
I know what is in that account.
Chanseong.
I'm against this.
Because not only Jo Pilyeon,
but you will risk your life as well.
I already have a plan in mind.
Seonbaenim...
I'm not suggesting I'll do
anything with this right away.
Under the current regime,
it would be useless.
But things will change for sure.
We will soon live in a world where
Jo Pilyeon can no longer dominate.
I'm sorry, Chanseong.
The only reason I'm hiding it from you,
is that in case they find out...
I jumped on the same boat with you.
I have no intention of taking the
easy way out, if this can kill you.
But, what were you trying
to tell me on your way in?
Ahh... Right...
I can't really speak with certainty,
but someone claims to
have seen Miju in Seoul.
Where is that?
I think they said Hannam-Dong?!
Hannam-Dong?!
In this case, matching these
with your clothes won't be easy.
So how about these?
They look all right?!
- Try them on.
- Yes.
Excuse me?
Yes.
Just a moment.
- Can I try these?
- Please sit here and take off your shoes.
I guess you live alone?
What?
I apologize.
By any chance,
have we ever met before?
What?
I don't think you ever came here?
They fit just right.
How do they feel?
Quite comfortable.
I'll take these.
I'll wrap them up for you.
Deputy Mayor.
You'll be late for your meeting.
Is it time already?
Can you keep these for me?
I'll come buy them later.
Yes.
Deputy Mayor?!
- Excuse me?
- Yes.
- Turning a Crisis into an Opportunity -
Minwoo, you!
I told you not to let
your guard down, didn't I?
You can't even handle Lee Gangmo?
I'm sure you're not implying
that you're afraid of Lee Gangmo.
Aren't you taking
that a little too seriously?
What?
If he saw you in this state,
Lee Gangmo would dance in jubilation.
Minwoo, you little...
I'm not going to
make any more mistakes.
Isn't destroying him
all that I need to do?
I'll have to teach Minwoo a lesson.
Let him be.
That verve of his only reassures me.
What?
Lee Gangmo is the scariest
man I've ever seen.
If he's going to face
someone like him,
that's how he should act.
Lee Gangmo...
Lee Gangmo!!
We appreciate your prompt payment.
Here is your receipt.
Thank you, President Lee.
Thanks to you, our company has
signed export contracts overseas.
I should be the one saying that.
Thank you.
Actually,
you should extend your
gratitude to someone else.
Excuse me?
I didn't send you that sample.
Then, who...
It was Director Hwang Jeongyeon.
She asked me not to tell you,
but she was the one who
sent me your way as well.
You really have a nice friend.
Aigoo... I envy you, President Lee.
Gangmo...
Where did you go buy that chicken?
All the way to the...
Gyeongok, it's you?
I asked Director Ju to buy me a...
And you...
Hey... What do you think you're doing?
Let her go!
What is this...
Did you two move in together?
Hey!
Oh Namsuk, you...
What are you doing?
How did you find this place?
How long has this been going on?
How long?!
How miserable...
I should have smelled something was up...
You must love the fact we got divorced?!
No need to hide it from me now.
It's my house.
Get out of here.
Sure!
I'm sure it is.
And he must be your partner.
Ahh!
Don't tell me you're
Jeongyeon's mother?!
You really!
Because if such wasn't the case,
I can't really figure out why you'd stick
to someone who was as good as dead.
Think everyone is like you?
You have no right to act like this!
Get out!
Why would I have no right?
You're Jeongshik's father.
You're the father of my child!
Do you even know in
what state your son is?
Why...
What's wrong with Jeongshik?
I'm well aware...
that I'm the first to blame
for spoiling him so much.
But you ruined him just as much...
No, even worse than me!
What on earth could have
possibly happened to him?
Jeongshik...
has completely lost all
reason, gambling all day.
He gave up on himself, my Jeongshik!
Say what?!
Honey...
I beg you, make him stop...
You know that
I can't live without him!
Honey... Honey...
I beg you, help my Jeongshik...
He's your son as well!
Honey...
Help our poor son out...
Call.
Bounty.
Flush.
Sorry, man...
Another round.
Two million.
Two and raise another five.
Hey... here you go, full!
- Let's hear it.
- Plate is mine.
Already lost everything?
You seemed to be in good form today.
Hey, tail.
Did you ask for me?
Hit me with another ten million.
But it doesn't really look like your day?
- Why don't you stop for today?
- Just do it!
Let's go ahead.
Here...
You know this is a private loan, right?
Seal here.
Just a moment.
You said he's Hwang Jeongyeon's
half-brother, right?
Yes, Hyungnim.
Bring me another ten million.
While we're at it, let's deal
with all the Hwangs in one strike.
Things are getting
even more interesting...
Why don't we go for a snack?
I'll go meet my friends,
so I'll be late.
Don't be too late,
and don't get drunk.
All right.
You must be back before the last bus.
I said all right.
What will you go for?
Chicken feet and soju?
- Come on in.
- Good evening.
- Some noodle soup, please.
- Yes.
- You have noodle soup?
- Yes, sure.
I hear you opened a business?
Going well?
Yeah...
Not too bad.
And you?
I've been busy.
Enjoy your meal.
Come on in.
Noodle soup, please.
Having dinner now?
Thanks to you, everything went well.
I'll come pay back
the principal tomorrow.
No need to come firsthand.
Just wire it to my account.
No, I'll be in the neighborhood anyway.
Right...
Are you free in the afternoon?
This friend from the States
brought me a few gifts,
but it's all stuff for women, so...
Ever since you were little,
you always liked fish cake.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
They're selling this from France?!
It's a gas boiler company.
If we sell these with our
apartments, it's game over.
Go ahead.
I'll show you what dealing
with a rabid dog feels like.
If we manage to acquire Beaute,
I'll generously reward you.
I have a condition.
I will join this acquisition
as a shareholder.
We're the only ones
who know the bidding price.
It must remain secret.
Let's hear the bidding price.
Show me the money first.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com