Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 52
Ga... Gangmo.
This will save us.
With this, we can
develop a great boiler, Gangmo.
With the new technology I brought you,
you won't have to worry about
being excluded from the New City project.
Actually, when combined with
Beaute's existing technology,
you might even improve upon the original.
Will you be all right?
I certainly appreciate all this help,
but what you just committed was a crime.
To be perfectly honest...
I was too embarrassed to face my own son.
You practically saved Minsoo's life,
and I just couldn't ignore all the
difficulties you were going through.
It was as big a crime as stealing Beaute's
core technology and bringing it to them.
I am solely responsible for all
this, so you needn't feel guilty.
Let's do this.
We'll make even cheaper and better
boilers with the technology you brought us.
I think that the benefit
people will gain from this...
will help you forgive
yourself for what you did.
I can only thank you for
being so understanding, President.
Wooju.
Ajeosshi!
Has our Wooju been doing well?
Yes.
- You told the rector, right?
- Yes, Chairman.
I bought you at least two hours.
Wooju, did you have lunch?
I'm hungry, too...
Shall we go have lunch together?
Here... Let's go.
You little...
Keep that up and I'll just drop you.
When will the results from Chicago be ready?
In about three days, I think.
Let's go back to the office.
Aren't you meeting with Minwoo?
Just let him be.
He doesn't have too much
time left to spend with his kid.
All right, Congressman.
Here...
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Here. Have this.
Why?
You don't like this?
I don't like fish.
Then, this?
How about this.
I like that.
And this?
It's incredible.
How could you have
the same exact tastes...
Ajeosshi, give me this.
That?
Wooju.
Try to call me "Daddy."
Just once.
Here...
Daddy.
Or else, I won't give you this.
You want it, don't you?
So go ahead.
Daddy...
Daddy.
That's right. Good boy.
When we meet, don't call me Ajeosshi.
Just use Daddy.
You can do that, right?
Then, I won't come see you again?!
So you'll call me Daddy?
Here... Promise.
Seal.
Want a drink?
No... Let me pour you one.
Your face's a mess.
So, tell me, why did you start working
under that loan shark, Noh Gapsoo?
I had some debts to settle so I
went asking for a job,
but I was kicked out because of Jeongyeon.
After she stole all the investors from him....
Dad.
If I don't pay back those forty million,
they'll kill me, Dad.
You pathetic twat...
So why disgrace yourself
becoming a gambling addict?
I want a better life, too.
I wanted to finally turn the
page before Mom died...
But now I really don't
know how I'm going to go on.
If you could only
give me those forty million,
I'll really wake up once and for all, Dad.
I mean it.
If I pay your debts,
will you follow your father?
What?
Don't you ever gamble again,
and just work under me.
But you're getting allowance
from Jeongyeon's mother...
Ohh Ohh, you little...
I will soon enter politics.
Po... Politics?!
Are you running for congress?
Learn how the world
goes 'round under my wings,
and make acquaintance with
some decent people, for a change.
It still beats wasting your life
away on the poker table, you fool.
Thank you, Dad.
I will work hard...
I'll do my very best.
Dad, let me pour you a drink.
I wonder...
how your mother could leave
you behind and just go like that...
Just giving them products that
do indeed work would be quite the start.
Of course, President!
Director Yang.
You've already been discharged?
After hearing the news, I
was just itching to come back.
Where is the experiment report?
Told you that nothing
can stop our Director Yang.
We have a meeting with
New City businessmen today.
Since you're here, check the paperwork
we'll have to present to City Hall.
I'll just follow you.
Will it be all right?
This should more than suffice.
Have you heard any
news of Hangang Construction?
They had a major
accident just a few days ago,
so I doubt they will have made any progress.
It is time, Chairman.
Let's head to City Hall.
I read you claiming
in an interview with the press...
that you found the
cause of those accidents, right?
So what was the problem?
I'm afraid I can't answer
that in a competitor's presence.
Gas was the problem.
Beaute Boilers'
products had no defects,
but the gas used in Europe
and Korea is different.
Yes... It can certainly be because of that.
And how will you solve
the over-heating problems...
which end up damaging the floor pipes?
By using an expansion tank,
we've already solved the issue.
And we also filed a request
for a patent as well.
I hear Manbo Construction's
expansion tank is an open circuit type.
Ours is closed circuit instead.
As you're well aware,
because of the influx of oxygen,
open circuit systems often
suffer from pipe corrosion issues.
Also, because of overflow, heat loss
in the pipe system is significant.
In consideration of such flaws, we
developed a closed circuit system instead.
Our patent will soon be ready as well.
Are you aware that closed circuit systems
cost thrice the usual open circuit ones?
I obviously am well aware of that.
But whereas an open circuit
system can last ten years,
closed circuit ones are semipermanent.
I see both sides have made great progress.
So how about we do this?
I think a collaboration would
benefit both sides in this case?
Chairman Jo.
How do you feel about that?
- We will discuss it with our board...
- We will have to decline.
I really see no reason
why we should join forces.
Yes... Fine, then.
Let's discuss this matter at a later time.
Here... Let's call it a day.
Thank you for your time.
- Thank you.
Let's have a word.
I'm prepared to establish a
partnership for this New City project.
What is the real motive?
Because it would not only help us cut costs,
but it would also help the both
of us in terms of research and development.
If it's all because of Miju,
I suggest you stop day-dreaming.
Think I haven't
figured you out by now?
You'd do anything
to gain what you want.
To be perfectly honest,
I would never even dream
of asking you to forgive me,
if it weren't for Miju.
- So?
- If it's for Miju's sake,
there is nothing I can't do.
If you want me to beg,
I can kneel down right now and do it.
Fine...
If you want that,
I will convince my father
to ask for forgiveness...
Cut the crap, Jo Minwoo!
If you felt even the slightest bit of
guilt for what you did to my family,
you would never,
ever approach Miju again.
I thought I told you back then?!
That if I saw you hang around
Miju again, I'd kill you.
You better....
You better keep that in mind.
Have you ever considered the fact...
that this grudge of yours
will only make Miju unhappy?
What?
You have time, so give it a thought.
I need no time.
Because I have no intention of
forgiving you and your father.
What brings you here at this hour?
Ohh... Director Yoo.
We were going to meet with
Congressman Oh this evening.
What are you doing?
Pay your respects.
How have you been, Director Yoo?
I've decided to take him under my wings.
Although we'll have to
see if he can earn his keep.
No way.
Fire him right away.
Gyeongok...
Hwang Jeongshik was working for Noh Gapsoo.
And President Noh is a
close confidant of Jo Pilyeon.
Do you even realize
how much he resents us?
Accepting that kid again is like
digging your own grave.
I know...
- I know that.
- You do... and still go ahead with it?
What else can I do?
No matter how wretched
he might be, he's still my son.
If even I end up abandoning him,
that foolish twat will
not be able to go on.
No matter what this will cost me,
how can I abandon
the son I gave life to?
His mother died without
being able to wake him up.
So I want to make a
decent man out of him.
Then, just promise this.
That you'll never let your guard down.
Because if anything happens to you, I...
I know.
I do.
I know what you mean, so don't worry.
So what he ordered us...
is to get blood on my hands, isn't it?
If you have a problem with that,
I can do it on your behalf.
Your role is to assist me.
Don't even think of abusing your authority.
Ailing companies?!
Are you telling me the government
will oust those ailing companies?
Of course they're only "ailing" on paper,
isn't he just getting rid of
everyone who refused to listen?
There's already a hit list
with several big names on it.
Is Jo Pilyeon getting involved?
I will make the final decision,
but as far as selecting the candidates goes,
I think I'll be forced to let Jo Pilyeon help me.
He's the man who collected secret
funds from corporations on his behalf,
so I'm sure he's got the president's
full confidence in that sense.
This is serious.
He's likely going to take this
opportunity to eliminate all his rivals...
Now that you mention it, he actually
volunteered to do the dirty work.
I categorically refused,
but Jo Pilyeon is never one
to be underestimated.
Things in the financial world are about
to get heated beyond any imagination.
I might only be holding half the blade,
but think of the benefits having
been entrusted this will bring us.
Are there already any confirmed names?
International Group.
They clearly fell on the president's bad side.
Guess they had it coming.
They'll probably vanish
without leaving a trace.
And Hangang Construction
will soon join that list.
Lee Gangmo has earned
Oh Byeongtak's confidence.
Can you really let something
you should have the monopoly on...
to someone like Lee Gangmo?
But you said you won't be the
only one with decisional power.
That is why you must take a step forward.
Start by making sure he doesn't
complete that boiler he's developing.
I will only be able to go at him
if he loses Oh Byeongtak's confidence.
That's right...
Why don't you just set his factory on fire?
Are you trying to limit him...
fearing he might try to get revenge?
Revenge?!
I'm well aware of who
killed Lee Gangmo's father.
Minwoo!
What the hell are you saying?
How many more people must
die to satisfy that greed of yours?
Have you already forgotten the days
when you wanted to kill him as well?
And you realize how much I despise
myself for even thinking that?
What?!
I will bear the consequences
of my sins on my own.
And stop committing sins as well.
Just witnessing all you do makes me sick.
- Stop there!
- Calm down, Sir!
Sir.
That fool must be crazy.
He's out of his mind.
I think that Wooju made him weak.
But he'll soon get a hold
of himself, Congressman.
Are things in the US proceeding well?
Yes, you don't need to worry.
Those results must be
a wake up call for him.
Enough to cry bitter tears of regret.
Let's just go.
What is that Lee Miju doing, these days?
She's shooting a promotional
video for the Olympics.
What?!
And whose decision was that?
I saw the dailies of the promotional video.
It was really nice.
I think it will be of great help to the city.
Thank you, Deputy.
By the way...
These days it's so
hard to see you on TV...
It's not like I watch TV
all that often, anyway.
Soojeong was banned from appearing on TV.
Seonhwa!
What is that supposed to mean?
It's nothing, Deputy.
Tell me.
Did you just say she was banned?
That matter will soon be settled.
Don't worry about it.
It's not like there were any problematic lyrics...
There looks to be no
reason why they'd ban you?!
Yes.
Deputy.
Congressman Jo Pilyeon is here.
How have you been, Deputy?
Aigoo, what brings you here, Congressman Jo?
I'll get going, Deputy.
Ohh... Sure.
- Mister Hong, escort them out.
- Yes.
It's all right.
I'll see you next time.
Here, have a seat.
So you want me to choose another
honorary ambassador instead of Cha Soojeong,
is that it?
With the Olympics around the corner,
what would be the point
of using someone like her?
I thought you were busy these days.
You still have time to involve
yourself in such matters?
Let me ask you one thing.
Who chose Cha Soojeong?
So I'll ask you something as well.
Soojeong being banned from TV...
Were you behind that?
I see that brat brought that up.
What on earth is going
on between you two, to...
That's exactly what I'd like to ask you.
I really can't figure out why
someone like you would waste time...
trying to interfere with a singer's career.
So? Does that mean you
refuse to make any changes?
City administration is under my jurisdiction.
So I don't really see any
reason why you should interfere.
Look, Deputy!
- For something so insignificant...
- Exactly because it's insignificant,
I'm afraid I can't help you.
I must ask you to leave now.
- I'll order later.
- Sure.
Chairman Choi has been showing
interest in my business venture.
Here's the contract.
So if you'd like to decide
the sum you'll invest...
You're just as beautiful as my father said.
Excuse me?
Have you heard my explanation?
I majored in business
administration at Harvard.
And I've been in management here for two years.
To be perfectly honest, all that
talk of investment sounds like French to me,
but I do like you.
Hand me that contract.
I invested great pride and
passion in this business of mine.
So I'd rather not change
my investors on a whim.
Look, Miss Hwang Jeongyeon.
- I majored in...
- You told me about Harvard already.
And that you've been
back in Korea for two years.
You don't have much in the way of manners.
I will give Chairman Choi a call.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
Mister Choi?
The exit is that way, actually.
Can you really treat customers that way?
Gangmo!
How did you know I was here?
Chairman Cheon and I
were going to meet here.
Then... I guess his daughter will come as well?!
Was it Suyeon?
But... Who was that?
The second son of Golden
Group's chairman.
The one Chairman Choi
talked about at the event...
He looked quite... charming?!
For a company called Golden Group,
the heir leaves a lot to be desired.
Really?
[*blockhead, idiot]
Then, should we
call them Golbin* Group?
Be that as it may,
losing that much money just
because of a single word...
I will make it back and more.
He's competing with his older
brother over control of the company.
He'll pay special attention
to what I tell his father.
Hwang Jeongyeon, you're really something?!
My mo...
Director Yoo told me.
That even money has a soul.
To not just look at money itself, but
try to capture the investors' imagination.
Jeongyeon.
There's still some time before my
meeting, shall we eat something?
Nah, I need to meet
another investor right now.
I knew they released you,
but knowing how tight
surveillance would be, I didn't call you.
I know that you're meeting
opposition party members as of late.
They might say this six-man
committee has been formed,
but if you can't secure support
on the ruling party's side,
all your efforts will be in vain.
You must keep pressing Min Honggi.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I've heard everything from Gangmo.
So you're Daesu's older son?
I really have no excuse.
But if you could only forgive me just a...
No...
You really don't need to forgive me.
However,
for fooling me and killing your father,
I must get rid of Jo Pilyeon myself.
That day when my father was killed,
I was there.
Wh...
What?!
So...
inside the truck...
Who's there?
I see.
So that boy...
That boy was you, Seongmo.
You saw that.
Be it the man who killed my father,
or the one who let his friend
fall into the trap that would kill him,
to my eyes you and Jo
Pilyeon are one and the same.
No...
On the contrary,
for allowing my friend to do
something that would kill him,
I'm even worse.
First, I'll destroy Jo Pilyeon.
After I'm done with him,
I'll decide whether I'll
get my revenge against you,
or just forgive you.
Right.
It must have been
really painful for you.
If avenging your father can help
you get rid of that resentment,
then I should just... Fine.
I will just pay the price for my sins.
Only then I will find peace in the afterlife.
What's this?
Is this all you could write?
They spent the entire day out.
Out?!
So Lee Seongmo and Yoo Chanseong
left you here and went out?
Yes.
If this is the kind of reports you'll write,
I could revoke your eligibility!
I will do better.
Stick to them at all times.
Who they meet, where and when.
Find out in detail and write it down.
Is that clear?
Yes, Sir.
Leave.
Can we really trust her?
The more gullible, the better.
Or else Lee Seongmo would suspect her.
What are you saying?
Ailing companies to be ousted?
I don't know the details,
but seems like Congressman Oh and
Jo Pilyeon were put in charge of that.
Dig deeper.
And find out if there's
already any company on that list.
All right.
But if Jo Pilyeon has
been put in charge of that,
Hangang Construction...
Quiet.
Hey, newcomer.
How did you know we would be here?
Pour me a drink.
Hey.... Now you even
try to act all bossy with your superior?
Chief Lee.
No...
Because of you, my
report was thrashed, Ajeosshi.
Next time you work outside,
don't even think of leaving me out of it.
Hey.... Ji Yeonsoo.
Why did you even join the ANSP?
The way I see it, a piano
academy would suit you better?!
- I can't play the piano.
- It's not like you're any better with the gun.
I don't like this, either!
My father forced me to do it.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- My father was in the army.
He said he would send one of
his daughters to the army at all cost...
So you came here
to avoid joining the army?
- Yes.
- Poor girl...
So just endure it for a while,
and find yourself someone to marry.
Men here are nothing special.
What?
You two aren't married either, right?
I can see it from a mile away.
You insolent little...
How about another drink, Ajeosshi...
Hey... Walk straight, will you?
Where do you live?
Let's go for another round...
What are you saying?!
Just tell me where you live.
The hell are you staring at, you losers?
What?
I apologize.
Why... Have a problem with that?
Want some?
I apologize.
Watch it with the drinking, will you?
Ji Yeonsoo! Stand straight!
You can find your way back home, right?
I can do that... for sure.
To the left. Execute.
Execute!
Find your house.
Execute.
Execute!
Ehh... Chanseong, you little...
Where the hell did he
run to, leaving me all alone?
Hey... Ji Yeonsoo!
Careful.
Chief!
What are you doing here?
Thank you.
Ajeosshi?!
What happened?
Where is your house?
That one.
Right under our nose...
I'm sorry...
So go in and sleep, you silly.
If you want, you could
come in for a cup of coffee.
Come here a second.
You better wake up starting tomorrow.
Is that clear?
Wooju, see you next time.
Yes.
What did I tell you to call me?
Daddy.
Answer me one more time.
Yes, Daddy.
Here are the results of the DNA test.
Chairman...
Wooju is not your son?!
I'll call Chicago and ask
them to verify one more time.
Don't.
Stop this.
But, considering the time he was born...
I said stop!
Congressman.
Seems like Minwoo has really
taken a liking to that boy...
If he's going to be shocked,
better do it so that he'll never forget it.
What do you plan to do with that boy?
No matter what, he's still your grandson.
I'll have to take him away from her.
What?
I can't let that lowly tramp raise
my precious flesh and blood.
I'll have to find the right
opportunity and take him from her.
- Thank you.
I apologize, we're done for today.
Come again, we'll sign it next time.
I'm sorry.
Don't make a scene here and just leave.
- Come in my car and let's talk.
- Seonhwa, let's go to the office.
Come to my car.
On our way here,
I had all sorts of thoughts.
Should we just die together like this,
or should I just let you go?
Should I resent you,
love you...
Abandon you, stalk you all day?
I thought all sort of
things, like a lunatic fool.
So? What do you plan to do?
If...
If I can't see you, I'll never be happy.
Whenever I see you, I feel unhappy.
Because of our families?
And what does that matter anyway?
I will ask you one last time.
Forget everything else and leave with me.
You really think it can work between us?
You really think I'd be able to ignore...
the fact that your father killed
mine for the rest of my days?
I told you I'd abandon my father and my family,
what else do you want from me?
Minwoo!
I'll accept you no matter
what the conditions are.
Even if you had another man's...
You're just like your father.
Selfish....
and cruel.
That's right.
I'm my father's son.
I've spent my life destroying
everything I couldn't possess.
So no matter what I do,
don't you ever resent me.
Because the one responsible for this all...
Lee Miju, it's you.
I want to raise that kid well.
But Minwoo now
thinks he's not his son...
We can just send him to the US.
The US?!
Ask around L.A.
Find a place with not too many Koreans,
a decent neighborhood, and
hire someone to raise him.
He will get the best
education available.
And then we can bring him
back in twenty years or so.
You know what I mean?
Yes, Congressman.
- But, when...
- Do it now.
All right.
The longer we wait,
the worse things will get.
The moment you find him a place in the US,
we must get our hands on that kid.
As a closed circuit system, we're
dealing with a semipermanent product.
Director.
Once our development is complete,
could we secure any export outlets?
We're going to export it?!
I think we might have a chance.
Ondol-based gas boilers.
I'm sure it can be a competitive
item on a worldwide scale.
If Beaute in France can help us out,
I think exporting to Europe might be possible.
Europe...
Here... To the development of our new boiler!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
How is Manbo Construction's situation?
In terms of technology, their boiler
couldn't possibly compete with ours.
Told you there's nothing to worry about!
When the prototype is ready,
it's game over.
Once the prototype is complete,
we'll start our advertising campaign.
Then, how are we going to proceed?
We'll advertise boilers and
apartments at the same time,
so I thought we could do a TV commercial.
But that's going to be expensive.
Is money the problem?
The New City concessions
depend on this sale.
Then, we'll have to find
ourselves a model for those CFs.
I'll do it.
President, my lifetime
dream is that of being on TV...
I'm really confident I can do well.
Gyeongja.
Please, don't get started, uh?
What's wrong with me?
If I stand up in Myeongdong,
everyone just starts staring at me.
Ahh... Who got Gyeongja drunk again?
Gyeongja, have a seat.
I've already decided who our model will be.
- Already? And who is it?
- Cha Soojeong.
That's nice.
Cha Soojeong is the best!
Cha Soojeong.
That's nice.
Cha Soojeong is the best!
Not to mention that she'll work for free.
For free?!
She might be your sister,
but how can you do that?
Cha Soojeong was Gangmo Oppa's sister?!
You didn't even know that?
Just drink.
After refusing our CF
offers on several occasions,
looks like Cha Soojeong signed
with Hangang Construction instead.
If Hangang Construction's boilers become a hit,
we will be badly defeated
in the upcoming Suseo sale.
Director Moon.
Yes, Chairman.
If my father was in my place as we speak,
how do you think he
would have reacted to this?
I can't say I'm really familiar
with Congressman Jo's style...
He would not hesitate and
go for the jugular right away.
What?
He couldn't care less
about rules or principles.
And of course, since he never
had such a thing as conscience,
he would never feel guilty to begin with.
He would just...
go at his foe's throat.
First, prepare the following.
Schematics of Beaute Boilers' factory,
and ex-convicts with at
least three previous felonies.
Co... Convicts?!
Yes.
Forgive all the other crimes...
It must be people sentenced for arson.
Arson?
Then, are you going to
set the boiler factory on...
I told you, didn't I?
That would be my father's way.
Start by making sure he doesn't
complete that boiler he's developing.
I will only be able to go at him
if he loses Oh Byeongtak's confidence.
That's right...
Why don't you just set his factory on fire?
Get ready.
Yes, Chairman.
The only one who's forcing me to do this...
is you, Lee Miju.
You're responsible for all this.
I mean... Aren't you drinking
a little too much tonight?
Why?
Are you afraid I'll get drunk?
Like you're not already drunk...
Don't you worry.
I can handle this much
without getting drunk.
I know how tough business is these days.
- Why don't you just leave it to Jeongyeon...
- So you want me...
to tell her everything that's been going on?
I'm not going to let her think
I'm in distress, at least not to her.
Ohh... Jeongyeon, it's you.
Come on in.
I had something to report,
did you have a few drinks?
No... It's all right.
Here's the permit application we will file
with the Financial Supervisory Service.
Are you already done
with all the preparatives?
The total amount we've been
able to raise is a little over 40 billion.
40 billion?!
Capital is important to get that permit,
[*non-executive director, part of the board
of directors but outside the executive]
but it also depends on who your NED* will be.
I know.
He not only needs to have
experience in the credit sector,
but also command great influence as well.
Who were you thinking of as NED?
The former Vice Minister of Finance
Im Jongtaek will be entrusted the job.
Minister Im?!
Have you already received his consent?
Yes.
Everything has been decided already.
Really?
The name will be Happy Bank,
and barring any last minute obstacles,
we should receive our permit by early next year.
Director Yoo.
Yes...
Baekpa suddenly came to mind...
Thank you, Director Yoo.
If you hadn't been backing me,
I would have never been capable
of achieving all this by myself.
Have a drink.
Good job, Jeongyeon.
We're almost there, Dad.
Nah. Let's walk until we get there.
It's right around
the corner. Go back.
My daughter has become a great woman.
You achieved all that on your own.
Dad... Director Yoo reacted that
way out of happiness, right?
Sure...
Of course she did.
She shed tears because of you.
Out of pride and happiness for you.
I actually worked even
harder for that very reason.
I wanted to see my mother smile for me.
Jeongyeon...
This is only the beginning.
I'm confident I can do well.
Right.
I have faith in you.
She will do great,
my daughter.
Chairman.
They're the ones I mentioned.
Have a seat.
They're the schematics of Beaute's factory.
Where is the most critical point?
That's right.
It's where they keep their fuel gas tank.
Upon completion of your task,
you will board a flight for the US right away.
Be it running a dry cleaner's or a supermarket,
you'll have a much better life there.
- Then, we'll go ahead as instructed.
- Yes.
Then, we wish you a safe return, President!
I haven't seen these fellas around before?!
Yes, they were just
hired as new security guards.
- I'll be counting on you, then.
- Yes.
In a few days the prototype will be ready,
so we'll get back to you in no time.
- Don't skip meals.
- Don't you worry, the food here is great!
- I'll get going.
- Take good care of him!
Come on in, Little Oppa.
Hungry, aren't you?
Yeah.
When did you get here, Hyung?
Been waiting you for ages...
I'm starving in here.
Wow...
What is this feast about?
Now that I think about it, I never
really cooked a decent meal for you two.
Doesn't something feel a little strange?
Be honest.
What is it that you want?
Just enjoy the food, will you?
Let me warm up the soup.
Congrats, Gangmo.
I hear the boiler development is going well.
You just wait, Hyung.
I'll be entrusted the entire New City project.
What do I owe all this to?
I see a different fire in your eyes.
Did anything happen?
How did it go with that list?
Congressman Oh and I
are compiling it as we speak.
How many companies will be ousted?
Well... About thirty, I'd say?
Why are you asking?
Save me a spot.
For Hangang Construction?
How's the stew, Oppa?
Any good?
It's really good.
I'm always eating out...
I finally get to eat a decent meal.
Miju. Another bowl, please.
All right, Oppa.
Since you're getting
up, turn on the TV.
You always order people around, don't you?
Breaking News.
A fire suddenly erupted at
the Beaute Boilers factory in Yongin.
According to eye-witness reports,
a blast was heard around 8 pm,
with fire spreading from
the gas tanks inside the factory.
Oppa...
Isn't that your factory?
Gangmo.
So that place is on fire as we speak?
Yes.
It's turning to ashes,
every single inch of it.
The police is confronting eye-witness
reports to find the possible causes,
with the possibility of an accidental
fire caused by negligence gaining ground.
No...
No.
- Gangmo...
- Little Oppa...
No...
No!!
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine Tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Is this what you mean by saving the economy?
Don't you exploit the situation in your favor!
Hangang Construction
will be ousted no matter what.
shares are hitting the bottom.
- We should take this opportunity...
- Wake up!
It's the last opportunity you'll get.
Who has that account?
There is no money in the world
that will convince me otherwise.
I'm sure Congressman Jo Pilyeon is here.
Tell him I'd like to see him.
That Lee Gangmo has a certain account.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com