Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
~ All characters and events portrayed
in this show are purely fictional ~
~ Episode 17 ~
Chairman Hong asked me for this...
You take care of it.
Seonbaenim.
My housemaid asked me
to find her family.
Father: Lee Daesu
Mother: Jeong Youngseon
Oldest Brother: Lee Seongmo
Second Brother: Lee Gangmo
Youngest Brother: Infant
Miju.
Miju!
Are you sleeping?
Lee Miju.
Oppa.
Where have you been?
Know how worried I was,
waiting for you?
Bought some sweet bread.
Gotta be good, uh?
How did you guess?
I was really hungry.
Here... Take it.
- Let's go in.
- Yeah.
Lee Gangmo!
What are you doing?
You are under arrest for the
murder of Chairman Hong Gipyo.
- Escort him down.
- Let go!
Follow us!
Oppa... Little Oppa!
- Stop it!
- Let me go!
What are you doing to my brother?
You just stay out of this.
Oppa... Gangmo Oppa!
Ajeosshi! Oppa...
Let my brother go!
- Miju!
- Oppa... Gangmo Oppa!
Let go! I didn't kill him!
I said let go!
- Miju!
- Take him.
Oppa...
Don't you worry.
I'll be out in no time.
Don't worry, Miju!
Oppa...
I said I didn't kill him!
It wasn't me. Let go!
Just go in!
It's my brother.
He's the brother I was looking for...
Gangmo...
And I shot him like a fool,
without even realizing who he was.
Seonbaenim!
- I tried to kill my own brother!
- Calm down.
Gangmo...
Gangmo.
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
What do you want now?
I have no accounts.
But... You said you
work for the KCIA, right?
I have a favor to ask you.
My brother was arrested by
the police under false charges.
If you could help me out...
Big Oppa?!
S...eongmo Oppa?!
- Miju...
- Oppa!
Miju...
Little Oppa was framed for murder.
He didn't kill the chairman, Oppa.
I know.
I know, Miju.
How can we help him?
What do we do now?
Don't worry.
It's all...
It's all my fault.
Don't worry, Miju.
Big Oppa...
Miju...
I remember this photo.
Was it Christmas?
We were really happy back then...
I thought that if we found you,
we would get to live happily
together like back in the day.
Don't worry, Miju.
I'll get Gangmo out of there.
I will...
help Gangmo get out of prison.
Big Oppa...
Are you going to keep playing innocent?
I've never been to that cottage!
And neither did I meet Chairman Hong!
Can't you see we have proof right here?
Then,
tell me why this was found in
the hands of the late Hong Gipyo.
Explain it to me, you fool!
Someone put it there
on purpose to frame me.
What?!
And who would that be?
That...
What is the matter?
Hwang Jeongshik.
You're under arrest for
the murder of Hong Gipyo.
Dad...
It wasn't me, Dad!
What's wrong with you?
You're calling my son a murderer?
What is all this about?
It's the copy of Chairman Hong's
account we found in his room.
Say what?!
Jeongshik, you lousy son of a...
You kill him, and try to
frame Gangmo for his murder?
Dad...
Go ahead and arrest him!
If you committed a crime,
you should pay for it.
Dad... He fell by himself!
I didn't kill him! I said no!
It's Lee Gangmo who will take the
blame and do time in the can, anyway.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
All I need is to wait
until the right time comes.
Until the right time comes...
Your engagement is tomorrow.
Drink this and go to sleep.
Gangmo.
Aigoo... Here you are.
Agasshi, it's getting late.
The chairman is
waiting for you outside!
Yes.
But, Agasshi.
What's wrong with your face?
You look like you didn't sleep at all.
Does Shideok have any news of Gangmo?
He left early in the morning,
saying he'll prove Gangmo was framed.
Framed?!
Did Shideok say Gangmo was framed?
Yes.
And did he mention any evidence?
Evidence proving he was framed.
I didn't hear any of that?!
What do we owe your sudden
interest in Gangmo's problems to?
Are you aware of anything,
by any chance?
What would I possibly know?
Ahh... It's hot.
*beef boiled in soy
Wow... There's even jangjorim* today.
- Bon appetit.
- You as well, Sir.
Is anything the matter?
You haven't touched your plate.
Did you two have an argument?
Argument?!
If anything's wrong,
I'll take you to the hospital.
Excuse me.
Ahh... Have you seen the news?
So the man who killed Chairman
Hong of Daeryuk Construction...
was that Lee Gangmo
from our company, right?
Yeah! I saw that, too.
I never saw him that way...
That's scary.
Lee Gangmo is innocent.
He's not the culprit.
The truth will be revealed soon.
Yes, I wanted to have a word
with you regarding Lee Gangmo.
Once Yeom Shideok arrives,
please tell him to give me a call.
Yes, I'll be counting on you.
Yes, thank you.
I want the upcoming apartment sale
to be jumpstarted by aggressive marketing.
Hwang Jeongyeon, you...
Hwang Jeongyeon.
Yes?
What did I just say?
What are you thinking?
Agasshi! Agasshi.
Agasshi...
Any news of Gangmo?
- Gangmo is at the police station.
- What?
We're having a meeting.
They arrested him?
Hwang Jeongyeon!
I apologize.
Stop using your heads just
as an ornament, will you?
Are you fools taking
my words lightly? Uh?
Do it right!
What is it?
Let's knock before we enter,
people are working here.
Gangmo was arrested yesterday.
Really?
If you commit a crime,
that's the most natural conclusion.
But why are you telling me that?
The day Chairman Hong was murdered,
you went to his cottage
with Park Sotae, didn't you?
Leave us alone.
Now!
What kind of bullshit
are you throwing around?
Don't try to deny it.
That day, you asked me
for Gangmo's car keys, and...
You little...
Get out.
Get the hell out!
Get out, Shideok.
Be honest.
Did you go there or not?
Why, if I said I did,
are you going to report me
to the police or something?
Don't see any reason why I shouldn't?!
Listen, Hwang Jeongyeon.
Might have different mothers,
but I'm still your brother.
How could you frame
your brother for Gangmo's crimes?
I'm not framing anyone.
- That day, you and Park Sotae...
- Report me to the police, then!
I have plenty of people
willing to prove my alibi.
If you have so many
people who can do that,
then let's hear who they are.
Hwang Jeongyeon.
I'm sure reporters will love this.
The daughter of Manbo
Construction's chairman,
framing her own brother for murder.
Unless you want to make
a fool out of our family,
let's start using this
thing over here to think.
Is that clear?
What the hell...
Gangmo.
What now?
What can I do now, Gangmo?
What? Lee Gangmo was arrested?
They brought him in last evening.
And the account?
Did he have it?
He's so strenuously
denying all his accusations,
it seems like the questioning
is not going well.
Anyhow, I'll have to
head to the station myself.
In the afternoon,
a lawyer will visit him.
Lawyer?!
Seeing how Chairman Hwang already
brought a lawyer into the picture,
all this must have something
to do with that account.
I called you earlier, I'm Lawyer Lee.
Welcome.
But, this gentleman?
He's the director of
the Intelligence Department.
Is that so?
Where is Lee Gangmo?
You know me, right?
This is Lee Sangtae,
he will represent you in court.
He will be of great help to you.
Lee Gangmo.
Korea is a state of law.
No matter the crime, everyone
has the right to be represen...
Let's get to the point.
I'm here to help you.
If you have faith in me and
answer my questions sincerely...
I'm tired as it is already,
so let's stop beating around the bush.
- So, what I...
- You have the account, right?
Chairman Hong's account.
You killed him because of that.
Go "represent" someone else.
I need no help from you.
Lee Gangmo!
If you cooperate, you can get a
reduced sentence of less than three years.
I have no such thing...
as that account.
Is that so?
Then, let's do this.
It's true you killed Hong Gipyo anyway,
so testify that you did it
under Jo Pilyeon's orders.
Just a quick confession in court,
and I'll take care of everything else.
If you keep this up, you'll get
up to seven years for murder, anyhow.
I trust you don't want to spend the
prime of your life rotting in the can?
Murder?!
How could Gangmo have done that?
Shouldn't we get him a lawyer?
Find the best lawyer money can buy.
The very best.
All right.
Dad, why burden yourself so much?
People will start
thinking he's your son.
You fool.
For my sake, Gangmo will risk
his life without blinking once!
He's a hundred, a thousand
times better than you!
Listen to you...
How can you say that...
Yes?
Director Jo is waiting outside.
Director Jo?!
How have you been, Chairman Hwang?
Come on in.
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
But, what brings you here?
I wonder why there are
no news of it being ready?
Ready?!
So you mean funding
for the election campaign.
I never fail to mention it,
but this election will be a battle
between the governing party and our money.
Min Honggi might have
gained their stamp of approval,
but electors will follow the
money trail and let it sway them.
I am doing my best
to gather those funds, but...
There is one way to cut our expenses...
Is there really such a way?
If we get our hands on the
copy of Chairman Hong's account,
we can kill off Min Honggi's candidacy
at the by-elections free of any expense.
But, how are we supposed
to find what doesn't exist?
Why do you think
Lee Gangmo committed murder?
Then, are you suggesting
Gangmo might have that account?
Let's drop the act, shall we?
I thought he acted on your behalf?!
Director.
Why would I covet that account?
Why would you...
I'm quite curious myself.
Even after our kids got engaged,
you still don't trust me?
You're my most precious ally
and now are even family.
How could I possibly suspect you?
I merely was surprised to
see you get him a lawyer so fast,
so I thought there was
something else going on.
A lawyer?!
Why, didn't you provide that yourself?
That is news to me.
Director.
Welcome, Director.
Who assigned that
lawyer to Lee Gangmo?
Director Min Honggi of the KCIA.
What? Min Honggi?!
Yes.
So what you're saying is,
you didn't kill Chairman Hong,
it was Park Sotae?!
How many times do I
have to repeat myself?
He's not the killer, I just said
he probably knows who it is.
You fool!
What are you, making fun of us?
You think we don't get you're
just trying to waste our time?
He's as stubborn as they get.
You two can leave.
Do you have that account?
I didn't kill Chairman Hong.
What did Min Honggi tell you?
I said I didn't kill him.
Just answer my questions.
Compared to Namsan's
underground room, this is heaven.
Speak.
What did Min Honggi tell you
when he brought that lawyer?
To testify in court that
Jo Pilyeon instigated me to do it.
That if I do so, he'll reduce my
sentence to less than three years.
Min Honggi, that son of a bitch...
What will you do for me, then?
What?!
If I have to rot in the can
under false accusations,
I'd rather give that a thought.
Be it Director Min or you,
aren't you both from the
same, rotten mold anyway?
You little...
What are you, trying to blackmail me?
What?! You'll testify that in court?!
Be my guest, then, you son of a bitch!
- Don't do this!
- What's with you?
What's wrong with you?
He's still only a suspect
who hasn't been indicted.
So what?
If you end up injuring him,
things could get messy.
So Director Min said
he'll watch your back?
Getting people executed out of
false accusations is routine for us!
You can kiss your freedom goodbye.
What are you doing?
Aren't you coming?
Seonbaenim.
I can't let this happen.
Calm down!
If I don't get him out of there,
it'll drive me crazy.
We must first find the killer.
- Until then...
- He's my brother!
And he's being exploited.
Those rotten scumbags are making him
a scapegoat for their own benefit!
- Seonbaenim!
- Let go!
If we look for it,
we'll find a way to help him.
Big Oppa...
How are you feeling?
How about Gangmo Oppa,
heard any news about him?
You haven't had anything
to eat all day, I bet?
Here... Have some.
You always liked chicken.
I have no appetite.
You should eat and regain
your strength, you silly.
Here... Eat.
Let's eat, Miju.
He won't be hurting, I hope?
I wish he could have this.
Will they feed him properly?
Oppa... Can't I at least
bring him some food?
Food?
Yeah...
Just some rice soup,
to keep his mood up.
It's always a pleasure to witness
beards like yours, Hyungnim.
Is that so?
Can't we get our hands on a mirror?
Ahh... Really, haven't seen this
masterpiece in so long, it's killing me!
Lee Gangmo.
You have visitors.
Come out.
Miju!
Oppa...
You don't look well.
This place is better than it looks.
I'll soon be out,
so don't you worry.
All right, Oppa.
It's time.
Oppa... I brought you some food.
You must finish it all, got it?
They're feeding me well here.
You take good care of yourself.
Anyway, you must eat it.
Are we clear, Oppa?
All right.
Let's go.
Miju.
Oppa...
Don't cry.
Don't you cry.
That's what worries me the most,
you crying because of me.
I won't cry.
I'm not going to.
Same goes for you, Oppa.
Oppa. Finish it all.
You must eat it all.
Oppa...
Little Oppa...
What's with you?
I... I'm sorry.
Wipe it.
Excuse me?
Can't you see what you did?
Ahh... Really...
You made it worse!
I apologize.
I'll pay for dry cleaning.
This is all I have at the moment,
but if you leave me your number,
- I'll...
- Forget it.
Just my lucky day, really...
I'm sorry.
Did you tell Gangmo?
Yeah.
To finish all of it.
You kept quiet about me, right?
He would have been
happy to hear I met you...
Let's wait it out a little longer.
We must be careful
until Gangmo is released.
But he didn't look too well.
I was called by Director Jo.
Was just wondering if there was
any progress in your investigation.
Are you certain
Lee Gangmo is the culprit?
That is all we can deduce
from the available evidence.
So is there no possibility whatsoever?
Of Lee Gangmo being innocent, that is.
This is top secret information,
but we found bloodstains
on the murder weapon.
Was it Lee Gangmo's blood?
No.
And neither was it Chairman Hong's.
Then?
Are we dealing with a third person?
That's possible, but it
could just be an accomplice.
If this is revealed, it will
put us in a difficult position,
so we're restricting this
to private inquiries.
And if the man matching those
bloodstains is not found,
what will happen?
We'll have to indict
Lee Gangmo, naturally.
Allow me to meet him just a moment.
I said visiting hours are over already.
I'll just see his face
and leave right away.
Ahh... You really refuse to listen.
What is the matter?
This lady keeps insisting
to meet Lee Gangmo...
Then, at least convey him a letter.
That should be all right, I hope?
And they went for us! 3 vs 13.
Of course we were the three.
And what would you think
in such a risky situation?
You'd just charge and
put your life on the line!
Gangmo.
I believe you.
I'll prove your innocence at all cost.
Whoever framed you for this will pay,
even if it ends up being Jeongshik.
I'll find that Park Sotae.
Don't be discouraged, Gangmo.
I'm here for you.
Got it, Gangmo?
~ Jeongyeon ~
Jeongyeon...
Oppa! You're so cool!
Give me a fucking break.
Cool, my ass... Hey, you bitches!
Do you like money that much?
Does it make you go crazy?
Of course we like it, Oppa!
Oppa...
What line of work are you in,
to make so much money?
Me?! What else, a thief...
No, wait. A conman.
A conman?
The kind who would
sell out a friend, why?
Must have been worth
quite the money, then?
I wish I had someone
to sell off like you...
What did you just say?
I asked you a question.
Out.
Oppa, what's wrong?
Oppa, my ass...
Get the hell out!
Lee Gangmo.
Don't resent me too much.
This is what I've always been.
The kind of man who would
do anything for the right price.
The kind of man who would get
on all fours for a little money.
You're a fool for ever
thinking of me as a friend.
Would you have taken
responsibility for me? Uh?!
This is what Park Sotae
has always been about.
A son of a bitch, nothing more.
That's what I've always been.
That is...
That is what I am!
I've been looking for you all day long.
Ever considered the possibility
that Lee Gangmo might be lying to you?
Everyone but you thinks he's guilty.
Aren't you listening?
Will you leave me alone?
All I'm thinking of right now
is how to get Gangmo out of prison.
All that populates your
thoughts is Lee Gangmo?
So, what,
you're not thinking
about me in the slightest?
Should I?
Fine.
Fine with me, just fine.
But don't cry for
another man in my presence.
I can tolerate everything else,
but I'm afraid that crosses the line.
Go in, you must be tired.
Ohh... Minwoo.
Did you drink?
Yes... A little.
I'll go to my room.
Listen.
Is Jeongyeon making things hard for you?
Nothing of that sort.
Really?! Don't lie to me.
Think I wouldn't realize you're
having it hard because of her?
I said it's not that.
- I'll meet Jeongyeon tomorrow, and...
- I said don't!
Are you starting as well?
Hey... Minwoo.
Just let me deal with this. Please.
Hey.
~ Lost Birds of Passage ~
(by Choi Heejun)
There must be a reason,
An explanation for what happened,
For those migratory birds
who lost their way.
Expelled?
Are you telling me the government will
put pressure on the construction sector?
As you're well aware, the real estate
sector is scraping the bottom,
not to mention the
succession of unsold apartments.
So what's the standard here?
What will their decision
be based on, just a whim?
The company's finances and
their credit rating, I suppose?
Can't we learn the list of
these businesses getting the boot?
It's top secret, obviously.
But what are you concerned about?
If you successfully complete
the subway construction,
isn't it just a matter of time
before you reach the top of your sector?
Our country's economy
is facing a crisis,
could I start dancing in
jubilation all by myself?
Anyhow, we hope you'll
keep our committee in mind.
If you'll excuse me...
Commissioner.
Are any of the committee
members part of that list?
Well...
There will be a rise in
companies filing for bankruptcy.
Shouldn't we find a solution ourselves?
Of course.
Baekpa and Congressman Oh Byeongtak
are in the VIP room.
Is it the kind of meeting
I can interrupt?
If I were you, I wouldn't
lose this opportunity.
I don't know how long it's been
since we've met this way, Hyungnim.
Just speak plainly with me.
That's too much reverence for
a mere private lender like myself.
What are you saying?
If it weren't for you,
how could today's
Oh Byeongtak even exist?
Here, let's drink.
Come on in.
What brings you here, Chairman Hwang?
I apologize for the sudden intrusion.
May I sit?
It'd certainly be all right with me,
but this gentleman here is
not one to favor the mundane.
I've heard you were here,
so I couldn't just leave.
I tend to sleep early,
so I'll have to get going.
Buses are still running, right?
I might be an ignorant fool,
but I'm well aware that nobody
can succeed in this business...
without you two gentlemen's help.
Chairman Hwang.
What's wrong with you?
I'm just looking for your support.
Once the subway
construction is complete,
I'll turn all that land in Gangnam
into a new world of opportunity.
All I'm asking
is for some support, Sir.
Good shot!
Still can go at it, I see.
Seems like the police
are following another lead.
Really?
I hear they found different
bloodstains on the murder scene.
So did they find out
who that blood belongs to?
Not yet,
but since they're going to investigate
the scene again, they'll soon find out.
You went to meet
Chairman Hong that day, right?
Did Jeongyeon tell you that?
That I went there.
Why are you getting all agitated?
Ruin the mood, will you?
Ahh... That feels good.
Why are you staring at me that way?
Did my badmouthing Jeongyeon upset you?
Let's save golf for tomorrow.
Today's just not my day.
I'll get going.
For my sake, Gangmo will risk
his life without blinking once!
He's a hundred, a thousand
times better than you!
Is there really such a way?
If we get our hands on the copy
of Chairman Hong's account,
we can kill off Min Honggi's candidacy
at the by-elections free of any expense.
Ahh... Could it get
more tangled than this?!
With this, Dad would finally start
acknowledging me more than Gangmo.
Wait...
Did I leave anything behind
at Chairman Hong's cottage?
Ahh... I'll be damned.
What now?
It'll take about an hour to get there.
Looks like you didn't
close an eye last night,
so sleep on the way.
No need.
I wouldn't catch sleep.
Never imagined Lee Gangmo
could mean so much to you.
Enough to rob you of
your sleep and appetite.
First you force me to
go there against my will,
and now what, trying to rile me up?
Pull aside right now.
Now that's my Jeongyeon.
What?!
All fierce and grumpy,
that's your charm.
Looking so dejected,
it just doesn't feel like you.
And I don't like that.
It's you?!
Was it you?
- Minwoo... It's not that...
- Minwoo!
Jo Minwoo!
Run.
I said run!
How about that man?
I lost him.
Have you seen his face?
Have you seen that man's face or not?
No... I couldn't.
Was it Jeongshik, by any chance?
Think I wouldn't even recognize him?
You've seen now, haven't you?
Someone else was behind that murder.
It wasn't Gangmo.
It could just be an accomplice.
Of Gangmo's.
Minwoo...
The reason I went to
Chairman Hong's cottage...
The blood they found on that stoker...
Should I head to the police right now
and find out who it belongs to?
M...Minwoo...
Confess the truth just to me.
It was you.
You killed him, right?
It was an accident.
Chairman Hong attacked me first,
and I just pushed him a little...
What did you do with the account?
Where did you put
Chairman Hong's account?
I set it on fire.
I was too scared.
Minwoo.
What can I do now?
Should I just escape abroad?
Tell them that, on the day
Chairman Hong was killed,
you were with me.
Uh?!
You never met him.
You did leave to meet him,
but met me on the way,
and we went out for drinks together.
But... How about the bloodstains?
Gangmo must be aware I met Chairman Hong.
Leave all that to me.
If your alibi is strong enough,
then they won't
even start investigating.
Thanks, Minwoo.
You're a true friend.
One day, I'll make it up to you.
Thanks, Minwoo...
Thanks...
Now that you mention it,
Lee Gangmo kept mentioning
Hwang Jeongshik this, Park Sotae that,
so we were about to
call you in for questioning.
Nasty prick...
Gangmo and I have never
really seen eye to eye.
Anyhow, when your alibi is confirmed
by someone as trustworthy as Chief Jo,
I see no need to
investigate any further.
By the way, is Lee Gangmo
still refusing any confession?
We'll have to wrap that up soon.
We can write that
deposition for him, anyway.
So you're not going
to give up, are you?
What were you writing?
Uh?
Did you find Park Sotae?
Park Sotae is nowhere to be found!
Stop trying to waste our time,
and just confess that you
killed him while you still can.
Is that clear?
And mine?
Haven't had lunch yet?
Ahh... How can you...
I'm starving in here.
I'll be right back,
so hurry up and eat.
Oppa.
I brought you some food.
You must finish it all.
Are we clear?
Any emergency can get
you out of detention.
Just get out of there, for starters.
Just the sole thought
would make me lose sleep.
So I haven't slept eight hours
straight since I've been here.
Any questions so far?
No questions.
Yeah... There are times when
it's better to have none, indeed.
Hey... Kiddo.
From what I hear, you're,
like, some killer and stuff?
You!
The hell are you staring at?
Do you even know
who he is, you little...
Forget it, as if I was that famous.
Listen. By any chance,
ever heard of White Beard
from Wangshim-Ri?
Seeing how your beard
doesn't even scare him,
must be still wet behind the ears.
Do you expect him to know everyone?
Will you come here and introduce
yourself or what? You s...
Looks like quite the
promising kiddo, actually.
Aigoo... Ohh my!
You look nice.
I see fire in those eyes.
Sit down.
Kiddo.
So who did you kill on your way here?
Boys.
If you're going to get time in the can,
do it like him, show some balls.
Forget all those petty charges, go for
the kill or it's useless, are we clear?
So what's your name?
Your name.
Didn't your old folks give you one?
The hell does he have, some handicap?
What did you just do to me?
You little prick, how dare you!
The hell are you waiting for?
Teach him a lesson, you scamps!
How dare you...
Hey! What's wrong with you, again?
You motherless little scamp...
- Hold him!
- Hold him.
Do you have a death wish?
Let's shut that trap for good.
You dare continue to pluck
White Beard's claim to fame?
Hey.
Do you have some kind of
lifelong grudge against facial hair?
Forget everything else,
but I can't tolerate people
messing with my beard.
Right...
You must be sorry?!
You were indicted for murder,
so I tried to be lenient, you know?
Where did this prick come out of?
He's scary!
What the hell happened?
- Seems like they beat him up.
- They did what?
Those damned thugs...
We'll even have to change
our gang's name now.
Calling ourselves
the White Beard Gang...
would be going a little
overboard, don't you think?
Hyungnim!
~ For Authorized Personnel Only ~
How is his condition?
Other than a cracked rib,
no major injuries.
We'll keep him under observation for the
night, so you can come for him tomorrow.
- Let me ask you something.
- Yes.
The name of the patient here...
Who the hell are you?
Let me go!
Who are you?
There's no time. Get moving!
Excuse me.
What happened?
Go and get him...
Go get Lee Gangmo!
Thank you.
But who are you, to help me...
Stop the car.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: MisterX
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
~ On The Next Episode Of ~
On the day Chairman Hong was killed,
Jeongshik went to his cottage.
That account must be in his hands.
There is a ship heading for Hong Kong.
I'll find you a spot there,
so get prepared.
Go search around the pier. Lee Gangmo
will surely try to smuggle himself out.
Even those you're waiting for
must be anxious.
What are you, trying to rile me up?
This is what you
were looking for, right?
Why do you have this?
This is where Gangmo is, right?
He's hiding here, right?
- Go.
- No way!
- You really...
- I missed you, Gangmo.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com