Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 55
Come on in, President Noh.
- Have a seat.
- Yes.
Is everything ready?
The moment results of the
selection come out later today,
we will set things in motion right away.
I'm sure you're confident
that you'll succeed?!
- Director Moon.
- Yes.
Anyhow, I thank you all for
completing our boiler on time.
But, what now?
We had no time to
do any performance tests.
So I guess you won't even be
able to produce any test results?
We didn't even have time
to write performance reports.
How about Manbo Construction?
I've asked at City Hall,
and looks like they annexed
performance reports as well.
Ahh... Jo Minwoo, that son of a cunt.
If only he hadn't set the factory on fire...
Here... If you're all
done eating, let's get up.
How about that?
Would that be enough to reassure you?
So the prototype Lee
Gangmo is about to present...
is nothing but an incomplete product
which didn't go through any performance tests.
Not to mention the fact that the factory
it was produced in was destroyed in a fire.
Overcoming this handicap in
consumer confidence won't be easy.
So I guess there's no
need to wait for the results.
I'll head to the stock exchange right away.
We should go to
City Hall as well, Chairman.
- Manbo Boilers -
Gently... Gently!
Gently.
Push it forward.
That should do it.
Will this do?
What?
Right.
Here it is.
Aigoo, Congressman Jo,
what brings you here?
My son told me he was developing
a brand new Korean-styled boiler,
so I came to have a look.
But tell me, what are you doing here?
The New City concession
selection will grant priority...
based on the results of
this boiler development selection.
Of course I should be here.
But I'd like you not to forget that
Hangang Construction was already...
added to the list of ailing
companies to be forced out.
But don't you forget, either.
That today's results could completely
turn that list upside down.
That old fart...
keeps trying to test my patience.
You should have accepted
my offer to share our technology...
in a co-production while you still could.
That tenacity and self-righteousness of yours...
will only bring you closer to failure,
as you'll witness today.
You talk as if the winner
has already been decided.
What could you possibly use to defeat us?
Your technology?
Capital?
Or else, your company image?
There is not a single
thing you can use to beat us.
Just a moment.
If I was Lee Gangmo,
I would have tried to stop you...
from pouring water
into a bottomless pit, Miss Hwang.
So I was wondering.
Will you keep your undying
loyalty for him if he fails once again?
Don't delude yourself, Jo Minwoo.
Because I didn't make
this investment to help Gangmo,
but merely to make a profit.
I'm sure you did.
It must be because you don't have a
clue that you so blindly bought their shares.
I know you were the
one who set that factory on fire.
Isn't that all I need to know?
- Hangang Construction 7010 won -
If things go well, Hangang Construction
shares might even go up today.
They're announcing the boiler
concession results today, right?
Then, shouldn't
we send someone there?
There's no need. If President Noh
Gapsoo starts buying, we can just follow him.
I guess that'll do it.
When it comes to
information, he's second to none.
Aigoo...
Are you going to sell all your
Hangang Construction shares as well?
I don't know.
We'll see whether I'll sell or buy more.
What everyone knows already
is not called "information," it's just news.
If you want, I could give you precious
intel well ahead of the curve?!
There's no need.
I was taught by Baekpa to make
the stock market move.
Make the stock market move...
Sounds just like him, all right.
The boiler we will select...
will be proclaimed as the official boiler
used in every New City apartment.
Also, I must also announce
that results of this selection...
will significantly impact the
New City concession as well.
Then, for starters,
we will listen to Manbo Boilers' briefing.
Chairman Jo Minwoo.
The Manbo Boiler we just developed...
not only solved many of the existing
flaws plaguing today's boilers,
but it also manages to
retain most of the advantages...
of conventional ondol-based heating systems.
Particularly when it comes to the gas leak
accidents which so often affect Beaute boilers,
we developed the world's first electronically
controlled gas exhaust mechanism.
An electronically controlled mechanism would
be an epochal improvement in terms of safety?
Have you conducted
sufficient performance tests?
- Performance Test Report -
Here is a report of around 120 tests
performed throughout the last three months.
As you can see, the success rate
is approximately 98.7 percent.
What happened to the remaining 1.3 percent?
They're negligible errors
occurred during preliminary tests.
Of course we improved
upon those minor faults as well.
[*approx. 45,000 square meters]
A 15,000 pyeong* boiler factory
is about to be completed in Yongin.
Once Manbo Boilers is enabled to
produce in such large quantities,
we will achieve the impressive feat
of exporting our products to Europe and America.
Now that's interesting.
Everyone in this room is looking at you.
I'll treat you to an even more
interesting spectacle in a moment.
It's me.
How did it go?
All right.
- Hangang Construction 1405 won -
- Hangang Construction 1380 won -
In jargon, this is referred
to as "selling climax."
When investors panic and sell all
their shares, leaving no one to buy them.
Selling climax.
You really don't know much
about the stock exchange, do you?
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Lee Gangmo of Hangang Construction.
First, as a fellow competitor,
I only have words of praise for
Manbo Construction's impressive achievements.
Instead of the previously
announced forced exhaust type,
one of our new technologies is exactly
this automatic flame adjustment system.
That is, the possibility for the customer
to choose their desired temperature at all times.
Considering that our country is forced
to satisfy all its energy needs via imports,
I believe this new technology
will help people significantly cut costs.
Could you show us any test reports?
We still haven't completed
our performance tests,
but we still haven't
encountered a single failure.
And of all new technologies a factory
destroyed in a fire could come up with,
a flame adjustment mechanism...
Will customers truly show
confidence in such a product?
You'll forgive us, but even this
jury has no confidence in that.
Not to mention the fact that
you have no test reports, either.
Deputy, I think we can
wrap up this conference.
If that is what you think,
I will bring this briefing to an end.
But may I show you one
last thing before we leave?
Yes...
Go ahead.
Let's suppose we're
facing the possibility of a fire.
It could be a malfunction of the boiler itself,
or maybe someone else
deliberately engaging in arson.
The boiler we developed,
as you noted, was produced in
a factory which was destroyed in a fire.
And that is the very reason why
we developed this fire alarm system you see.
The flame adjustment system which
lets customers choose their desired temperature,
along with this fire alarm that warns
them of any possible accidents,
are two of the revolutionary new
technologies of Hangang Construction's boiler.
Thanks for setting my factory on fire.
Listen well.
That is what will lead
you to your downfall.
Jina.
Buy all the Hangang
Construction shares you can.
- Hangang Construction 995 -
Yes... Taeyang Securities.
What?! You want to buy
Hangang Construction shares?
You want to buy
- Hangang Construction 1050 -
Seems like you're behind this?
Need to make the market
move, don't you think?
Moving the stock market was
only possible for someone like Baekpa.
It's not something you can do.
I'll keep those words in mind.
We will announce the results.
The company entrusted
with boiler production for...
both the Suseo and New City apartments...
The jury chose the
winner via unanimous vote.
Unanimous!
And they selected the Hangang-Beaute Boiler.
Congrats, Gangmo.
Thanks, Jeongyeon.
But didn't President
Lee say their tests failed?
But how could they...
Jo Minwoo.
Stop trying to make
criminals out of honest people.
The restaurant owner.
This is not too bad, either.
Because if your foe
crumbles after the first strike,
it's not much fun.
You were so confident about this,
what the hell did just happen?
And what have you been doing
while that announcement was delayed?
What?!
If Hangang Construction
had been part of that list,
then we wouldn't have
had to go through all this.
So stop making stupid mistakes
like this and focus on politics.
Are you trying to lecture me?
You just wait.
If those M&As go according to plan,
it'll be only a matter of time
before Manbo Construction...
becomes a giant in the financial world.
That little fool is showing
hostility right in my face now?!
Try to understand him, Congressman.
These days he's quite irritable.
- Hangang Construction 1390 -
Trading is closed for today.
Wait there!
How do you explain this, President Noh?
Is it true that Hangang
Boilers won the concession?
Did you spread false
information to con us all?
You people...
Have I ever told you to buy or sell anything?
- You told us to trust you!
- Be honest.
This is all a trick, isn't it?
Did you find out which
companies President Noh was investing in?
Yes, Director.
How is our matter in the US proceeding?
Everything is ready.
I also found a nurse for him.
No need to waste any more time.
I'll have to go get Wooju
and bring him there right away.
Are you going to do it yourself?
It's where my grandson will be
living, of course I'll have to see it.
Devise a plan on how to get that boy.
All right, Congressman.
We did it!
We did!
Folks, that'll be all for today.
Thank you everyone.
Thank you.
Stop shooting.
I'd like to have a word.
Go ahead first.
All right.
You'll treat us tonight, right?
Of course.
But forget the samgyeopsal today,
how about beef and...
All right.
Let's go.
Is anything wrong?
You told me Cha
Soojeong is your sister, right?
Yes.
Why?
I've heard this strange story from
a younger colleague at Celeb Daily.
He says that Cha Soojeong
was hiding a son.
A son?
There is no way.
If that was the
case, why would I not...
What's even stranger...
is that an assistant of
Jo Pilyeon named Go met him,
and started asking all sorts
of questions about that kid.
Jo Pilyeon?
I thought something might
be up, so I came to tell you.
Just because Wooju keeps
bringing home all those toys...
That?
You know that our playground is
undergoing a renovation, right?
Employees of that company took
a liking to Wooju, and bought them.
Employees?
What is the name of that company?
Ahh... How are you?
It's you.
I don't see the kids today,
did they go somewhere?
They're out on an excursion.
But, you like the facilities?
Yes, I do.
Where did the kids go, again?
To a nearby park.
I'm really enjoying
your songs, they're so nice.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Hi.
Yes?
Just a moment.
Soojeong.
Get the phone.
Excuse me just a moment.
Yes?
Miju, you're in trouble!
What's the matter?
Where is Wooju now?
How did it go?
Hangang Construction won.
Gangmo finally did it.
He beat Jo Minwoo.
Anyhow, your brother is really something.
But... What about this toy?
Ohh... I was going to
meet Wooju later today.
I miss that little rascal
so much, it's driving me crazy.
Go now, or else Ji Yeonsoo
will stick to you all day long.
- I'll be right back.
- Yes.
Yes, I understand.
Go to the park near Jamshil.
What are you going to do?
If it's really Jo Minwoo's son...
Are you confident you can accept him?
Chick.
Sparrow.
Duck.
Puppy.
- What is this?
- The bridge.
Wooju.
How have you been?
Come here.
Wooju?
Come here, Wooju.
I'm your uncle.
Uncle?!
Uncle?
What the hell are you talking about?
Lee Miju is my sister.
W.... What?!
The sister I lost because of you!
Fascinating.
Things are getting
tangled beyond belief,
but all this is quite fascinating.
Wooju...
Come to me.
Come to Uncle, Wooju.
Come on.
Wooju!
Wooju!!
Kang Wooju!
Wooju!
Oppa...
You two knew about Wooju?
I never imagined that Gangmo knew.
I said come here!
Here... Come.
That is my grandson.
Give him to me.
You just try to lay a finger on him.
Wooju, come on.
Come to Grandpa.
I see...
Your blood doesn't lie.
Lowly blood flows in your veins,
so you can't even recognize your grandfather.
If Jo Minwoo knew of this, he
wouldn't just sit back and watch?!
My guess was right.
You were planning to hide Wooju
so that Minwoo wouldn't find out.
I suggest you give up while I
still give you the option, Congressman Jo.
Uncle...
Uncle.
That's right, Wooju.
I'm your uncle.
I want to go to Mommy.
All right.
Let's go meet Mommy.
I'm scared.
Scared?
Ahh! It tingles!
It tingles?
Ahh... The beard?
Mommy!
Gangmo Oppa.
Back then, after I ran away,
I tried to get an
abortion more than once.
But every time I convinced myself to do it,
the baby would start
kicking inside my womb.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Seongmo Oppa.
Sorry, Gangmo Oppa.
Don't cry, Miju.
Wooju is your son.
He has nothing to do with Jo Pilyeon.
And...
he's my one and only nephew.
Oppa...
Your uncles will come for you
soon, so listen to Grandma, uh?
All right.
Wooju.
Don't worry, Miju.
My sister loves Wooju, too.
We'll write you news of him every day.
Mom...
Aigoo...
You poor little thing...
Here... Here.
It's time to board the flight.
Sotae, is everything ready?
Don't you worry.
We'll take them to the UK and come back.
Of all people, why did
you have to send me with him?
You can't even speak English,
wanted to go all alone?
Why, you do?
Try anything funny over
there, and you're both dead.
Don't you worry, Brother-in-law.
- You can trust me.
- Aigoo...
It's because it's you that I'm worried.
Can't you even save a few nice
words for me when I leave?
You two, watch it!
It's a list of the companies
Noh Gapsoo invested in.
He invested a huge sum of money.
Seems like he put everything on the line.
So it has something to do
with the list of ailing companies.
That's right.
They'll make huge profits out
of M&As with companies from that list.
Looks like Manbo Construction
was eying a few major M&As as well...
We could take this opportunity to inflict...
a major blow on Manbo
Construction and Noh Gapsoo.
One good strike, and it
won't stop at a major blow.
Particularly when it comes to
Noh Gapsoo, this could be fatal to him.
So all we need to do is saving the
ailing companies involved with them?
It's like belling the cat.
You can give this data to Congressman Oh,
but you must be careful not
to offend him or arouse suspicion.
I'm sure.
Because he'll certainly suspect
we'll have something to gain as well.
Who could be fit for this job?
I do have someone in mind...
Ohh! And what is all this?
Just thought I'd bring you lunch.
What?
Wow... I'm really touched.
So, what, you were thinking
of me while preparing this?
Try it, I don't know if you'll like it.
All right.
I was really hungry,
so you'll have to excuse me.
How is it?
Ohh... Good enough that my eyes
are about to pop out from the shock.
Here... Join me.
Go ahead, I've already had lunch.
I'm really thankful for
what you did last time, Deputy.
If this is about that,
let's talk when I'm done eating.
I think it might make
me get an indigestion.
I detest Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
The fact I could hate
someone with so much passion...
surprises me more than I could ever imagine.
Did anything else happen?
That man tried to
take my son away from me.
And because of that, I had
to separate from my beloved child.
Let me hear the details.
Once the list of ailing
companies is announced,
Jo Pilyeon will gain
immense profits in the process.
I'm not going to ask you for help.
Just keep that data.
If you don't need it,
you can just throw it away.
Soojeong,
you've really changed.
If I only could, I'd
like to change even more.
Here... For starters,
let's finish my lunch.
So what you're saying is
that Jo Pilyeon showed this list...
to a private lender going
by the name Noh Gapsoo?
Yes.
And he's going to
gain great benefits from it.
So Manbo Construction is putting
that list to use and planning acquisitions.
Your guess was right.
Weren't you suspecting both Manbo
Construction and the private lending cartel?
But how come you have this data?
Ahh... Yes.
- That...
- To get revenge against Jo Pilyeon,
I could get my hands
on even more than that.
Revenge?!
Did you just say revenge?
Yes.
Because that man...
killed our father.
Soojeong...
You never told me that?!
Jo Pilyeon is a murderer.
And he used that money
to get where he is today.
Go ahead and open it.
So you want me to take this money,
and engage in trafficking of official posts?
Is that not enough?
What do you take me for...
Take it and leave!
I'm not here just for the money!
That money is not for you.
Just funds I'm devoting to our country.
If you wish to maintain power,
you need immense funds.
That's right... I remember.
Back then,
he brought the kind of money that a
mere army lieutenant couldn't even dream of.
So that's what happened.
Is it from back in your childhood?
Yes.
And I've heard that the statute
of limitations has already expired.
I surely can't say my hands are clean.
But letting a murderer enter congress...
is something my conscience would never allow!
I'm sure you're not here to meet me.
Is there anyone else
you came here to meet?
Just came to have a look at that
power you always love to talk about.
And?
Did you meet the savior that can help you?
Coming here seems to have taught
me how to fight with you, at least.
Fight with me?!
So an ignorant, lowly
little tramp like you would fight me?!
Laugh all you want,
and just remember my words.
If you commit a sin,
you'll be punished for it.
That's the truth of life an ignorant,
lowly tramp like me has learned.
Turns out you sent Wooju
somewhere out of the country.
There are no two ways
about it, I'll have to raise Wooju.
I can't let you corrupt that child's
mind with foolish intents of revenge.
Then, give it a try.
Because we will no longer
just sit back and watch.
That tramp...
Who the hell did she just meet?
- Ailing Company - Viable Company -
- Hangang Construction -
- Viable Company -
Seems like plenty of heads
will roll, after that list is announced.
We did our best.
Whatever the result might end
up being, we'll have no regrets.
Right, Director?
If that's what you believe,
I'll just lower my expectations.
By the way, Director Yoo.
Isn't it time we get Jeongyeon married?
Stop right there.
Let me eat in peace, Dad.
Ohh Ohh... You little...
Every time I mention
marriage, look at how she reacts.
Aigoo!
Isn't this Chairman Hwang?
Chairman Cheon, what brings you here?
I had to discuss business with President Lee.
How are you, Jeongyeon?
Fine.
I'll see you again, then.
Yes.
Enjoy the evening.
I'd like to use your new
boilers in our apartments.
Thank you.
We'll be sure to give you a discount.
So let's leave business at that.
Actually, I wanted to
have a word with you.
As you well know,
I have two daughters.
The older one married a doctor,
and I'm left with her.
Let me tell him.
I kept pestering my father
that I wanted to marry you.
He wants a son-in-law who
can later take over the company.
I told him I liked you,
and he gave me his consent
without a single hesitation.
Can you take care of my
daughter and the company for me?
I'll be right back.
Jeongyeon...
Gangmo.
Can you give us an answer here?
Both as an entrepreneur and a man,
I believe you won't refuse our offer.
I'll be honest, then.
As a businessman, getting the chance
to take over Gwangmyeong Construction...
is a very alluring offer.
And as a man, marrying with
a woman as beautiful as Suyeon...
would be a true blessing.
Then, are you giving us your consent?
But, you'll have to forgive me.
Because, for a very long time,
I've been in love with someone.
Excuse me just a moment.
You idiot.
It would be so great for Gangmo...
Guess I had one drink too many.
The more I see her,
the more Suyeon grows on me.
She's so affable,
pretty...
Tonight my father kept pestering
me about getting married.
I guess he was setting up
some meetings with matchmakers.
Good for you.
I'll spend the rest of my life alone instead.
Uh?
I won't get married.
I'll live alone for the rest of my life.
Until I'm old enough to die.
That's nasty.
Getting married by yourself, and all.
Jeongyeon.
Will you do me just one favor?
Just like me,
can't you just live alone
and not get married?
You know...
Then,
I think I'd feel a little less bored.
Can you do that for me?
Ohh.... Give me the paper.
- Ministry of Finance
Announces 21 Ailing Companies -
[Stock Exchange in Turmoil]
Wh... What is this?
Come on in, Congressman Jo.
Why is it just 21 companies?
Where did Hangang Construction
and the remaining ten companies go?
I consulted with specialists,
and we compiled a new list.
What's wrong with giving a few
promising companies another chance?
We worked on this together from the start!
You weren't supposed to
decide this all on your own!
I received the president's
consent before we announced the list.
If you want to bring that up,
head to the Blue House and ask him.
Congressman Oh, you...
See how long you last here
after showing me such contempt.
Watch what you say, Jo Pilyeon.
Already forgot when you walked
into my office with those shabby military boots,
groveling at my feet and
begging me to make you a big shot?
Say what?
Let this be a warning.
Watch it.
I still haven't mentioned all the
skeletons in your closet to the top brass.
Skeletons?!
Out of the thirty-one companies on that list,
I omitted exactly the ten you and
those loan sharks made a move on.
I'm sure you understand what that means?!
Insolent prick...
It's Noh Gapsoo's list of assets,
along with his management
plans for the organization.
Send these via fax to each member.
All right.
Are you ready, Jeongyeon?
Yes, Director.
Look, President Noh.
Why should I be
held responsible for that?
If you really want to bring
that up, go talk with my father!
You son of a bitch...
I'd like to speak with Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
When does that
goddamned meeting end?
I'm Noh Gapsoo!
President.
A meeting was gathered.
A what?
- The cartel...
- I am the cartel, you idiot!
Who gave the order?
So... Who organized this meeting?
Why aren't you answering me?
I asked who called for this meeting!
I did.
And how can someone who's been
expelled from this organization sit there?
The report you've been given
lists Noh Gapsoo's remaining assets.
I'll let President Noh answer firsthand.
How much capital do you have left?
I never imagined your cash flow
situation was in this state.
You disappoint me, President Noh.
The logic behind our organization is power.
And power means money to us.
President Noh was foolish enough to
squander all that money on the stock exchange.
For incompetence,
for allowing politicians to deceive
him and threaten our organization's foundations,
and for running this organization
with only personal gains in mind,
I present a motion to expel
President Noh from this organization.
Expel?!
And with what authority would you do that?
Anyone opposing this motion,
please raise your hand.
- Yoo Gyeongok, you...
- Watch what you say.
Because starting today, I inherit
leadership from you.
Starting now, I will be in
charge of this organization.
Should anyone oppose it, you
may follow President Noh out of here.
Right as the report suggested,
our organization is going to fund
the opening of a credit institution.
And Director Hwang is
going to be in charge of it.
I'm Hwang Jeongyeon.
Opening a credit institution has
been a long-cherished dream of ours.
And it is time you and I open
a new future for this organization.
So in the end, Noh Gapsoo let Yoo
Gyeongok gain control of the cartel.
This is all because of Oh Byeongtak.
Not content with damaging me,
now he even blackmails people.
How do you plan to deal with him?
We need to get rid of him.
But what you're dealing
with is a huge political player.
Or else, I'll be the one to be ruined.
This fight depends on
who wields his sword first.
- Demonstrations Spread Across the Nation -
- Jo Pilyeon -
Jo Minwoo --- Noh Gapsoo
What do I owe all this to, Congressman?
Chairman Hwang.
I hear rumors that you're in close
contact with opposition party members?
Well... There is no ulterior motive.
It's just a personal friendship, that is all.
Did you by any chance
give that account to them?
What are you implying
with that question?
I won't beat around the bush.
Give me that account.
Last time I tried to give you something,
you didn't even take a look at it.
Why would you suddenly
ask for the secret fund account?
It's only a matter of time before
the world is turned upside down.
People like me can
sense that instinctively.
People are shedding blood on the street,
claiming they'll open a new world.
But with politicians like Jo Pilyeon still on top,
how are we ever going to
repay those precious sacrifices?
Congressman.
I've been waiting
a moment like this for years.
When can I give you that account?
The opposition and demonstrators
are soon going to ask for direct elections,
and organize massive rallies.
That's our chance.
So that's when you plan to
reveal the secret fund account.
Then, will you resign?
Once Jo Pilyeon is out of the picture,
I have no more reason to work there.
You really want to run an orchard?
That would be the plan, I guess.
But I don't really know
how much that would cost me.
And would you happen to have
a job for me, if I came there?
Why, want to quit as well?
Honestly, I've had
it with all this myself.
So hand your resignation
and come right away.
You can always raise pigs next to me.
- I really will!
- Have a drink.
You two are really something!
So what, are you going to
quit and leave me there alone?
It's Chairman Hwang?!
You don't have your beeper on you?
Call him.
Where are you going?
Why?
Are you going to follow
me to the man's room?
The man's room...
Ahh... He's not here at the moment.
Tell me a time and place
where we can meet with Oh Byeongtak.
All right.
I'll tell him.
Ahh... Right.
Congressman Oh said
he had something for us.
I think it's some kind of
secret report on Jo Pilyeon.
All right.
I'll go to Congressman
Oh's office at that time.
Don't forget the account.
So are you finally going to use that account?
Jo Pilyeon better be counting his days.
Aren't you leaving?
I'm so behind on reports...
So wrap them up first.
Let's go.
How nasty... You're
leaving all by yourselves?
You really...
Of all people who could escort
Oh Byeongtak, Yoo Chanseong?!
We'll kill two birds with a stone.
That's right... No need to
get our hands dirty twice.
Anyhow, you're really brilliant.
You used a newcomer to spy on them?
That's what experience is all about.
Yes?
You're still at work.
You'll have to bring
me the account tomorrow.
All of a sudden, why...
Congressman Oh finally
decided to make a move.
Seonbaenim!
You just got here...
Where are you going now?
No need to know.
Take this.
What is it?
Beats me.
Just eat it.
I'm bored, so hurry back here.
I'm busy today, so I can't follow you.
I'll let you work.
Not bad?!
Saw that?
I gave it to Chief Yoo as instructed.
Well done.
But what kind of test is this?
I might forget it,
so you give this to them.
All right, Sir.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Final QC: Anarchist
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Yoo Chanseong was
bearing a grudge against me.
So is that the reason why you killed him?
Jo Pilyeon sent a spy to our office.
He made sure he was
killed by a colleague of his!
If you're involved in his death,
the president won't forgive you.
The congressman treated you like a son.
Why...
And I thought you were clever.
Guess I was wrong.
Doing this to me was the
worst mistake you could make.
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com