Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 45
Hyung.
I must be late by now?
You came in this state?
I told him to just watch her on TV
at the hospital, but he's so stubborn...
Let's go in, Hyung.
Jo Minwoo is here.
Yes, and with that we conclude
Hong Jiyoung's performance.
Good luck on your debut.
Cha Soojeong, you're next.
Hurry up!
Here... Shall we find out, then?
Dancing, singing, and a pure image
to boot, she's got them all.
Ladies and gentlemen, please
welcome newcomer Cha Soojeong.
"Under the Spotlight."
Give her an applause.
Stop there.
If she dances with those clothes on,
the pin won't help much?!
What if she ends up
half-naked on live TV?
Cha Soojeong! Cha Soojeong!
Soojeong!! That was great!
It was awesome.
You better not scare me
over stuff like that again.
Yes, Director.
Refuse any interviews
and leave right away.
For the time being,
no further exposure.
All right, Director.
- You looked so cool out there!
- Thanks...
Soojeong.
You were the best tonight!
The best!
He's going to meet Miju, isn't he?
Let's just stay out of this.
Miju can take care of this by herself.
Let's trust her, uh?
I don't think we'll get to meet her here.
Let's go.
You always have my support.
Congratulations on your debut.
Who could this be?
He's not even leaving a name.
Seonhwa.
Did two men come looking for me,
by any chance?
Two men?
Not really?!
Why are you asking?
Haven't you read the sign outsid...
Miju!
It's Mi...Minwoo!
Miju.
I have nothing to say to you.
Please, leave.
Can you leave us alone a moment?
Yes...
- Don't leave, Seonhwa.
- A moment will do.
I'll be waiting outside, so have a talk.
Lee Miju.
Didn't you miss me?
- All this time...
- I've long forgotten you.
Look at me. Say it to my face.
And it's time you forget me as well.
- Miju...
- Don't touch me.
Let go!
I thought something terrible
had happened to you.
If anything happened to you,
I would have never
forgiven myself or my father.
Miju...
I've just become a singer.
And today was my debut performance.
You acting like this is only going
to make things awkward for me,
do you know that?
I have no intention of
causing you any trouble.
On the contrary,
I'll give you everything you want.
I can do that for you now.
Miju, the director is on her way here!
The director is very strict
about my personal life.
I don't want her to
learn about you and me.
Come to Hangang Hotel's
restaurant at seven.
I have no reason to meet you again.
Don't talk to me like that.
It's been four years...
For the last four years!
There hasn't been a single day
I haven't looked for you.
And now that we finally meet,
is that all you...
If it's because of my father,
you don't need to worry.
He doesn't dictate my life anymore.
It's not because of your father.
I don't have any feelings left for you.
Miju!
Are we clear now?
I don't love you anymore!
But I still do.
My feelings for you
haven't changed at all.
It's the Hangang Hotel.
I won't leave until you come.
I'm sorry, Minwoo...
It's not even your fault...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
What were you doing
around Soojeong's waiting room?
So Cha Soojeong was
under contract with you?
I asked you a question.
I was impressed by her performance.
See you again.
What's going on between
Jo Minwoo and Soojeong?
What could possibly be going on?
They just met for the first time.
Director.
Miss Jeongyeon went to meet
Congressman Jo Pilyeon.
What?!
I'm sure you're not thinking
I will give them back to you?!
What did you really come here for?
Was it to let bygones be bygones?
You will be forced to give that
pledge and the IOU list back.
This is a list of all the bribe money...
I paid to you during my tenure
as chairman of Manbo Construction.
I see it's a copy.
So?
I would like to exchange the list
and the pledge with the original.
Or else you'll ruin the
both of us by leaking this?!
But you know what?
I knew you'd be writing something
like this from the very beginning.
Think I wouldn't have
prepared a counterplan?
All this time, I have been donating
a certain amount of money...
to various coalitions under our names.
It is likely the amount will
match the figures you listed here.
This brings Chairman Hong Gipyo to mind.
It was because of an account just like this
that your son killed him, right?
I'm sure the statute of
limitations hasn't expired yet?!
You motherless son of a bitch...
Calm down, Dad.
You sure have two
remarkable parents, Jeongyeon.
Your father puts his life on the line for your
sake and threatens to reveal this account,
and your mother gave up
all that money for you.
Look!
Jo Pilyeon!
Why?
She still doesn't know
who her real mother is?
Let's just go, Jeongyeon.
What's that supposed to mean?
My mother gave up
all that money for me?
Your birth mother
is Director Yoo Gyeongok.
So that's why Bucheol abducted you.
Why did you hide that from me?
You know how long I've been looking for her.
- So why...
- She struggled her whole life.
Afraid her dark and shameful past
would become a burden to you,
she always thought she
had no right to be your mother.
She remained by your side,
hoping things would go well for you.
And after witnessing you succeed,
she would then ask for forgiveness.
Jeongyeon.
Your mother cried even more.
So much that you could see the
scars in her heart from a mile away.
Will you be able to forgive her?
Can you accept her as your mother?
No...
I will keep waiting.
She wants me to succeed.
So it is only if I succeed on my own...
that she will be able to get
that burden off her shoulders.
Jeongyeon.
Pretend as if nothing happened as well.
Let her do as she wishes.
That's what I want to do as well.
I will succeed right under her watch.
Director.
Noh Gapsoo is gathering
members for a meeting.
Here...
Let's begin.
The reason we gathered here today,
as you well know...
Who organized this meeting?
I did.
The only one who was
proclaimed as Baekpa's heir is me.
- How dare you do this without my con...
- The reason we gathered here today...
is to discuss a motion to expel
Director Yoo from the organization.
There are only two days left until
the principal will have to be paid back.
So I guess you forgot a certain pledge
you signed, renouncing that principal?!
Congressman Jo Pilyeon will soon join us.
Our organization will never
have to hang from her lips again.
And you think I will take this lying down?
Starting today,
Director Yoo is no longer
part of this organization.
The principal under Director Yoo's control
will be paid back by the four of us,
so should anyone wish
to join her, please rise.
You are free to follow her out of here.
Baekpa tried his best to
defeat me before his time came,
but looks like I won instead.
I recall telling him, back then.
That once he was dead,
I'd get rid of every
single achievement of his.
It's all right.
I'm fine.
It's my fault.
Let me take responsibility for this.
Any problems within the organization
are for me to worry about.
And your role is making Baekpa's
dream come true.
By Baekpa's dream...
*"2nd financial circle" is Korean business lingo
for every financial institution other than banks
you mean creating
another credit institution*?
A lot of preparation will be
needed to be granted a permit.
So forget all the rest and
focus all your efforts on that.
Yes, I will.
I will succeed and create our
own credit institution at all cost.
I will keep the pledge and the IOU list.
I have no ulterior motives,
so you can rest assured.
I'm merely seeking mutual dependence.
All I want is a symbiosis between
politics and the financial world.
Then, we'll be counting on you.
Instead, there is something
you must do for me.
Go ahead and tell us.
The political situation
is quite tense these days.
Although I'm sure you're too concerned
with your business to worry about that.
It's a list of opposition party members.
I hear you're pros at
hooking up with people,
so get acquainted with them.
Let's see you in action.
Did I make myself clear?
Miju should be here by now?!
You shouldn't take it off already.
I haven't met her in years,
so I don't want her to worry
on our first meeting.
Will you be all right?
Of course.
She's my one and only sister,
I need to endure it.
Yes.
Tell me, Chanseong.
All right, fine.
Good job.
What is it?
Jo Pilyeon completely gained control
of the private lending cartel.
It's not a good sign.
We're about to go full force against him...
What's that supposed to mean?
You're going full force against him?
Never mind.
Here's Miju.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you.
Aren't you coming in?
Ohh... Go ahead first.
Don't make me wait.
Big Oppa...
Little Oppa.
It's been four years,
but you two haven't changed a bit?
Don't hug him so hard.
It's all right, Hyung.
You looked great on that stage today.
You were there?
'Course...
We saw our Miju's concert
from beginning to end?
I thought you hadn't come,
and was so disappointed.
- Hyung... Let's just go, shall we?
- Ohh... Sure, let's go.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah... Heard Gangmo had
a gift for you or something?
A gift?
Here... Let's get going!
Oppa, I'm scared.
Can't I open my eyes?
Nope, no way.
You must not open your eyes
until I tell you.
All right.
What could it possibly be,
to have me keep my eyes closed?
It's nothing special.
Don't expect too much.
Yeah.
You two are killing me!
Here... careful.
Where are we?
- Can I open them now?
- Nah! Not yet.
- Just a sec.
- Wait a moment.
Not yet.
Get ready.
One... Two... Three!
You can open them now.
Oh my...
Congrats on your debut.
This house...
Miju, it's yours.
- Congrats on your debut,
Seongmo and Gangmo Oppa -
Gangmo built this apartment.
Little Oppa...
And all the furniture was picked by him.
Toothbrush, soap, sofa, TV... All.
He bought them all.
Miju.
So now don't ever leave us again,
and live here.
All right?
I don't deserve any of this...
You're our one and only sister.
You're the apple
of our eye to us, you know?
Seongmo Oppa... Gangmo Oppa...
Chairman, we're about to close.
- Cheers!
Aww... I'm so full.
It's the tenth toast, already.
Really?
Have we already done that many?
Looks like Gangmo is really happy
you debuted as a singer.
Now all we need to do is finding Junmo.
You still haven't heard a thing?
He might have been adopted again,
away from the US.
Again?
Why?
They say that if you don't
meet the right foster parents,
it can happen at times.
Our poor Junmo must
be having it really hard.
Ehh... You people!
On such a nice day,
what's wrong with you?
Miju, don't you worry.
Whenever it might be,
we will find him. All right?
Don't worry, we'll find him.
Wait a moment...
Let's change the mood a little.
What's that?
Hyung! What are you, dancing?
Don't tell me, Lee Seongmo is dancing!
All right. You just wait.
Miju, take a look at how he dances.
So you're telling me you won't
join your brother and dance?
Young lady... May I?
I'll let you dance instead.
Lee Miju! Lee Miju!
Did you practice it or something?
Here!
I will never let you go.
I'll make you...
fall in love with me again.
Yes.
Chairman, it's me. Director Moon.
Did you acquire the rest
of Beaute's core technology?
Yes.
But our contact would like
to be transferred to our company.
Should he suddenly hand in his
resignation for no apparent reason,
he might be accused
of industrial espionage.
Even if he does transfer,
make sure it's all handled with prudence.
Yes.
All right, Chairman.
- Beaute Gas Boilers -
If you still haven't found
any mechanical defects,
how about adding a mechanism to automatically
force gas out of the exhaust pipe?
That's not possible.
It's not?
This boiler shows no defects,
I'm sure of that.
Add a damper and you'll only be
admitting that there is a flaw.
He's right, Gangmo.
Not to mention that it would
damage the company's image.
There's nothing worse for a company's
image than customers complaining.
We need to avoid product
returns whatever it takes.
That's going to cost us, and it's not
like we can raise prices to compensate.
Until we find the reason,
we'll have to bear the costs ourselves.
You're peculiar, all right.
- Are you going to lose money just to...
- You know, our president...
is famous for his
rather charitable nature.
- To put it bluntly, he's a blockhead.
- Ehh! How dare you...
President, why don't you
just fire his ass?
Why didn't the factory manager
come with you?
I think he might be
thinking of leaving the company.
Leaving?
Are you telling me he
will hand in his resignation?
Even I get the urge to quit because
we can't even find a little defect,
imagine how the
factory manager would feel.
I'll get going.
Yes, we'll be counting on you.
Now I've seen them all...
As if that mechanical defect was his fault,
now he even hands in his resignation?
He's really a honest man.
He sure earned my respect.
The factory manager, along with
the technical director from earlier on,
are the best this field has to offer.
We can't let him leave, Gangmo.
Here, have a drink.
Let's have a drink and forget
all our troubles for a moment.
Why are you doing this?
We've heard everything from Director Kim,
about you handing in your resignation.
What?
Ehh... Don't act like that,
and let's keep working together.
He's right. Manager.
Gyeongja, can you do that to anyone?
What's wrong with that? I respect him.
If I raised your pay twofold,
would you stay?
Two... Twofold?!
I apologize.
- I will quit.
- It's twofold, twice the pay!
I will add an apartment to that.
Aren't you going overboard?
Give that to me, uh?
If you give that to me,
I'll work until all my bones break, uh?
I already made up my mind to leave.
Wow... He's like a saint.
What are you, Buddha's
half-brother or something?
I've heard your son was hospitalized,
don't you need money?
Feel free to speak.
Where have you decided to transfer to?
Tr...Transfer? I merely
wanted a little time off...
I will say it for you, then.
Isn't it Manbo Construction?
How much of our boiler technology
have you leaked to them?
What are you trying to insinuate?
I know how hard things are for you.
If you are honest with me,
I will forgive you.
If you have any evidence,
report me to the police!
I will hand in my resignation.
What the hell?! So he was a spy?
With his family struggling so much,
the only reason why he'd decline such offer...
He's a spy, all right.
What? So I respected him for nothing.
That sorry-ass son of a cunt,
should we just report him?
We have no evidence!
It's likely he already leaked
all our core technology to them.
Chairman.
The factory manager said he
just handed in his resignation.
How could he quit already?
He claims that Lee Gangmo
already found out about it.
Looks like we'll have to take him in.
People's eyes are on us, so not now.
But his situation
looked to be quite delicate?!
He's the one who foolishly
handed in his resignation.
Tell him to wait.
All right, Chairman.
Right.
About the model for our apartments.
Change it to Cha Soojeong.
What?
Yes. I will.
Director Yoo Gyeongok and I
are not exactly on good terms.
So win over her road manager.
I know what you're trying to say.
So you want our Soojeong
as model for your apartments?
Yes.
For a debuting singer like her,
it's a great honor!
But... This contract.
Could we set things in motion without
telling Cha Soojeong and Yoo Gyeongok?
Excuse me?
This is for you, on the side.
- New Singer Cha Soojeong..
A Quiet Storm on the Horizon -
Yes... She's not available that day,
but she can always shoot it on Tuesday.
You want her to sing as well?
Yes.
So Tuesday,
recording at three.
So this is what being popular means.
I can finally feel it!
Soojeong!
We're about to sign a contract
for an apartment CF!
An apartment CF?
Which company is it?
Co...Company?!
Ohh... It's called Suyoung Construction.
Suyoung Construction?
I never really heard it before?
Know how many construction firms
there are in this country?
How could you know them all?
When are we signing?
They'd like to sign today.
Right... Your schedule
for the afternoon is full, right?
Yes...
Ahh... This is trouble.
We might even lose this?!
You can just go on her behalf.
Still, I'd at least
like to read the contract.
It's just a one-year contract.
And the director has given us her consent.
I'll just go and sign for you.
Go ahead, then.
- Aww... Congrats, Soojeong!
- Thanks.
How did it go?
We signed a contract with Cha Soojeong.
Have you found out
whether she was dating anyone?
She's not dating anyone
at the moment, either.
Also, here's today's schedule
and her home address.
I'd like to get her schedule
from her manager every day,
would that be possible?
He is easily convinced,
with a little money on the side.
I'm sure it can be done.
That's right.
All that land was sold already.
The house as well.
She told me to find a three-room
house for just thirty million,
but you call that easy?
Our basement is empty,
so she could move there,
and just pay a monthly rent...
Aigoo, you brat.
What are you talking about?
Drink it.
It's citron tea.
Where are you...
Aigoo...
They said he's become
addicted to gambling...
He doesn't even know
what's happening to his mother.
How can he find a house for that money?
Tell me about it.
That's why they should
have saved some while they had it.
Demonstrations supporting direct
presidential elections have been staged...
all over the country, with the launching
of molotovs, fires and other acts of violence...
continuing until the early morning.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did you let things get to
this point without saying a thing?
If I told you,
would it have made any difference?
Mom.
We can't live with just thirty million won.
Think about it.
Even if we get a place with that money,
how are we going to make a living?
Worst comes to worst, we'd at least
have to open a little mart...
You really think you can live that way?
So?! What am I supposed to do?
So why did you waste
your time with stocks?
Just so that someone here
could finally bring home some money.
Since all you do is loaf all day.
What are you going to do with
all the money we lost, anyway?
Even if I have to
live on ramen every day,
as long as you wake up
I'll be just fine, Jeongshik!
It's because you're so clueless that you
let Jeongyeon's mother steal Dad from you!
You...
What did you just say?
Jeongyeon's mother?!
Yoo Gyeongok, that woman...
is Jeongyeon's birth mother.
Dad has been deceiving us all along.
So how can I not feel sorry for you?
So you want to live on ramen every day?
And how are you going to
cope with the embarrassment?
After foolishly losing all our money,
letting her take away your husband
and ending up on a street!
How are you going to endure all that?
What?
That woman...
is Jeongyeon's mother?!
Then,
from the very beginning,
I was nothing but a castoff?
I...
This Oh Namsuk...
was nothing but a mistress?
Those lights,
the ones past the Han River.
I likely built close to half
the entire apartments in Gangnam.
You miss those days?
More than missing them,
I should say I'm sad to have seen them go.
Tear gas sweltered those
streets once again today.
But it's a concerto of
lights and glasses at night.
Isn't this country fascinating?
We fight each other all day,
then we go out for drinks
and make up at night.
Jo Pilyeon is using the underground
market's resources to convince...
congressmen from both sides to rally
against the constitutional amendment.
The situation is critical.
So give me that secret fund account.
I'll meet Congressman Oh tomorrow,
and go for broke to convince him.
I'll bring it to you tomorrow.
By the way, weren't
you and Min Honggi close?
Maybe trying to convince him
instead could speed up things.
I don't trust Congressman Min.
I've seen enough over the years
to convince me not to.
Then again...
Be it Jo Pilyeon or Min Honggi,
in the end all they care about
is filling their pockets.
Anyhow, you must
convince Congressman Oh.
It was rewritten using
Jo Pilyeon's calligraphy.
When you meet Congressman Oh,
copy this and bring it to him.
Seonbaenim.
This is serious.
Looks like Congressman Oh Byeongtak,
along with Jo Pilyeon,
receives secret instructions
from the Blue House.
What time is it?
He already left to meet him.
No way...
He must not show that account to him.
Chairman!
Seongmo.
What brings you here?
I was looking for some data
at the congress library.
Really?
I'm a little busy.
I'll leave you to your business.
Yes.
What's that supposed to mean?
So there is a secret fund account
inside this briefcase?
I will just show it to you.
Wait!
You know what?
I've been secretly
ordered by the Blue House...
to seek out all proponents and sympathizers
of the constitutional amendment.
What?!
If I ever open that briefcase,
I'm afraid I won't be able to
let you walk out of here alive.
You said you want to change the world?
I'm sure what you want
is for that amendment to pass.
Fine...
I'm sure we will soon find out
who will end victorious.
And should that be you,
don't you ever forget that I
was the one who saved your life.
Congressman Oh...
I have no intention of running
against the tide of history,
and neither do I want to
turn my back on this regime.
Am I making myself clear?
This is what the politics you wanted
to join so much is all about!
Did you show him the account?
- Here... Let's save the details for...
- Chairman Hwang.
What are you doing here?
I came to meet Congressman Jo.
Chairman Hwang. Let's have a word.
Actually, I am trying to
convince ruling party members...
to vote in favor of
the constitutional amendment.
Is that so?
But none of them have any courage.
We'd need a strong incentive
to encourage them...
For instance, that secret weapon
you mentioned some time ago.
If my guess is right,
it probably is an account for
the secret presidential fund?!
Most congressmen have
at least heard the rumors.
The issue is whether
such a thing does indeed exist.
With that account, would you be able to
gather all those approving the amendment?
I certainly could.
Can you show me that account?
Let's do this.
First gather all those congressmen.
Then I will come looking
for you with the account.
That's Congressman Kwon Haeryong.
He's in his third term,
and comes from Masan.
Thanks to his academic
and local affiliations,
many first-termers
in the congress follow him.
And I'm sure you know
Congressman Kang Changhwan quite well?
They are men of great pride.
Acting all tough and uncompromising
is embedded in their way of life.
If you'd been keeping a low
profile to learn who was who,
I suggest you change your approach.
Bear this in mind.
You now hold the knife by the handle.
My apologies.
Looks like I lost my way
while coming here.
Yes.
So... Let's start by seeing that account.
Before that, I have a request as well.
- Agreement -
I approve the constitutional amendment
to allow direct presidential elections
You will have to personally
sign those agreements.
Look, Chairman Hwang!
Don't you know that something
like this could get us killed?
And the account you're
about to see is so dangerous,
even a hundred of my lives wouldn't
be enough to cope with the repercussions.
Shouldn't you prove
I can trust you as well?
Faith is what we need here.
And I have faith in our people.
For dinner?
Yeah... They want you tonight
at Hangang Hotel's restaurant.
If it's an advertiser,
shouldn't you dress up tonight?
Why are they suddenly
asking me out for dinner?
Advertisers often like
to see their models firsthand.
But, Manager... I couldn't
really check the contract.
Haven't you checked your account?
I'm sure they already wired some money?
Check it. You should be
fifty million richer by now.
Fifty million won?!
She's a newcomer,
and they pay her that much?
It's because it's a two-year contract.
What are you talking about?
You said it was only a one-year contract.
Soojeong...
There's nothing like money
in this business.
Got to strike the iron while it's hot.
Hangang Hotel?
Yeah.
I need to tell you something.
I'll see you there.
All right.
Put those on.
I can do it by myself.
Just go home now, Jeongyeon.
Just for today...
Just today.
Then I won't do this again.
I always liked your back so much.
It's still as warm as I remembered it.
Thank you for everything you did today.
I owe you one again?!
Careful on your way back.
And you, recover quickly.
You're here?
What were you studying?
I promised Director Yoo
we'd establish a credit institution.
There's plenty to study.
But, what did you want to talk about?
I knew that Director Yoo
was your mother.
I got a call from Chairman Hwang.
He said you're having it hard.
I wonder if what I need
is to be consoled,
or just to be congratulated.
Just tell Director Yoo first.
I'll wait until she tells me.
Just the fact I finally found
my mother makes me happy.
Jeongyeon.
Forget this place, and just
buy me soju at a stall outside.
What?
Just because you made a little money,
you start showing off with me?
I already ordered.
Jo Minwoo.
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
The Intelligence Department
got a hold of this.
You must keep them quiet.
Looks like they found out
about our meeting.
And who forced me to go all
through this just to meet you?
Then, there's only one way.
Forcing you to hate me.
You really think I invested in you?
You still have a lot to learn!
- It's all we have.
- Just this once...
If I make enough to open a store,
I'll never gamble again.
Give me that account.
I will do it.
Then, nothing will happen to you.
Who did it?
Who is accusing me of betrayal?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com