Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 50
Thank you for coming.
- Congratulations.
- Yes, please go in.
Thank you for coming,
President Lee Gangmo.
I have high expectations
about tonight's party.
I'm sure you'll welcome me
even without an invite, Jeongyeon?
It's been a long time.
Isn't it a wonderful night?
I hear there were no
demonstrations in Seoul today?
There have to be days like this.
Since you organized it, I'm
expecting even more from this party.
I'm sure it won't disappoint you.
Esteemed Federation of
Korean Industries members,
and representatives of
the ruling and opposition parties.
I think this gathering is particularly
meaningful, more so than ever before.
We are only one year away from a
worldwide festival like the Seoul Olympics,
and it is to ensure this event's
success that we all gathered here tonight.
Other than being a competition pitting
sportsmen of every country against each other,
the Olimpic Games are also a golden opportunity
for business and culture...
from all over the world to meet.
There are too many unfamiliar
faces among the journalists.
Not to mention the event
personnel and bodyguards.
Seeing as Jo Pilyeon joined us,
maybe he smelled something already?
What is the matter?
What could possibly be going on, to
see ANSP agents all over the place?
We have reason to believe that opposition
party members might be plotting something.
You're talking about people
formally invited by the hosts.
We can finally get the entire
congress under the same roof,
must you really spoil the mood this way?
Listen well, Congressman.
There might be a secret bipartisan
agreement on the constitutional amendment.
What?!
A secret agreement?
And what ruling party
member would agree to that?
I guess this will be a good opportunity
to find out who the traitors are.
If what you say is right,
we can't let this slide.
They must all be captured.
The second part of
the event will soon start.
Keep a close eye on all congress members.
Check every single one they
meet, even if apparently accidental.
Don't worry.
We not only have agents
on the field, but CCTV cameras as well.
But shouldn't you
release Lee Seongmo by now?
It's way too early to jump to conclusions.
Why, don't you know that this
operation already leaked to the outside?
It can't be Lee Seongmo.
If any secret bipartisan
gathering happens tonight,
it could also mean it was
planned from the very start.
And Lee Seongmo
might be part of this complot.
We must catch them by the end of the night.
Is that clear, Chief Oh?
Do it right, will you? What if
this falls down during the event?
Stay put!
Let me see.
That should do it.
So how do I look? Don't I look
at least ten years younger?
Wake up, will you?
If anything goes wrong, you could
croak twenty years before your time.
Like I wouldn't know that?
Look what I have to do for a living...
If only Jo Pilyeon couldn't
recognize me, I would have done it.
Hurry up and come out.
The second part is starting.
Ahh... What the hell...
Your pants... Eww...
You pissed all over them.
You must remember these faces.
They're the people
you will give your red roses to.
Miju, come out.
It's your turn.
Here... Let's change the mood.
Our first act of part two is a new
shining star causing a stir in the pop scene.
Here is Cha Soojeong.
Miss Cha, please.
You smell like the
scent of sweet flowers,
Waking me up from this deep sleep.
Like a thorn blooming
into a fresh new petal,
You might resemble a rose.
Your face glitters like a rose,
So when I call your name.
When I call your name,
I will say Rose.
You will see the singer we invited
give red roses to certain ruling party members.
They are those who would approve
a constitutional amendment.
- Lee Juil, along with Shim Hyungrae, Korea's
1980s "King of Comedy" -
Guys, just sit and have a drink.
We're fine.
Why, afraid I'll knock
you down and run away?
Please, don't let them catch you, Gangmo.
I beg you...
It was truly an impressive performance.
Thanks to you, I can
finally see some sparks in the air.
Thank you, Congressman Oh.
So I was thinking.
I'd like to recommend Miss Cha as
honorary ambassador for the city of Seoul.
You really mean that, Deputy?
You won't disappoint us, right?
It would be a great honor.
Soojeong, you better thank
the deputy mayor with a big bow.
So let's make a toast.
The financial world is keeping a close
eye on Hangang Construction these days.
I appreciate it.
I hope I can count on
your continued support.
Right...
I hear you have a keen interest
in the credit sector, Director Hwang?
Yes, we plan to start our
own credit institution very soon.
Retaining your clientele
must be the key here.
You will get preferential treatment
if you decide to join it.
I see Miss Hwang takes after her father.
I know that only simpletons
would brag about their kids,
but my Jeongyeon
leaves nothing to be desired.
But, did you get married?
Why, are you interested
in some matchmaking?
My second son is still single.
I see there was another reason
why you came here, Chairman Kim.
I suggest you keep Min Honggi
and his surroundings in check.
All right.
Did you tell the opposition party members
that you'd show them the account?
Otherwise, they'll never trust us.
And how are you going to
do that in this atmosphere?
Let's wait.
Is there anything else I
can bring you, gentlemen?
To verify the account, call the
waiter and order some beverages.
Can I have the menu?
Yes.
Here you go, Sir.
Here as well.
One more glass of this, please.
Yes.
Will you take a look as well?
Yes, let's do that.
Bring me the same.
Have you enjoyed your dinner?
The steak here is delicious.
They have been shown the account.
All right.
What's going on?
Nothing is happening.
The party is not over yet.
Min Honggi is approaching Congressman Jang.
I wonder what convinced you to leave
your precious street demonstrations for a day?!
Are we in the mood for
sarcasm, by any chance?!
Don't you think that instigating
people to demonstrate on the streets...
is beneath a politician worth his name?
What's more democratic, demonstrating
on the street for the sake of one's country,
or ignoring this sad state of things because
it's beneath you, like some politicians I know?
Democratic?!
Is throwing rocks and Molotovs at
the authorities democratic behavior?
Have you people ever stopped a moment
to consider what the people really wish for?
How else are they going to resist
the oppression of authorities...
who let rifles and batons
speak on their behalf?
Look, Congressman Jang...
Watch what you say!
Right as we speak, our people
are shedding blood on the streets...
to finally turn the tides of
this wretched reality of ours!
And all you worry about is winning
favors with those in power...
You should be ashamed of yourselves.
Hey! Shut that insolent mouth of yours!
What's wrong with
you people? Give it a rest!
So what, we're basking in a
cesspool and you're completely clean?
You're the only reason
why people are reacting this way!
Stop it, Congressman Min!
There are journalists here.
Enough with this, and follow me!
Ehh.... How embarrassing!
Here... Folks.
Here... Here.
We all gathered here today to show unity.
Even if you argue, don't do it here.
There are journalists all over
the place, so let's reconcile.
Go ahead.
Ohh Ohh... Come on.
Shake hands.
Here! Let's leave them alone.
What is going on?
Did you reconcile?
Here... Everyone, you saw that, right?
They reconciled, so no need
to write anything about this.
Have you seen the account?
Yes, we verified it.
I'll take care of securing enough ruling
party members to enact the amendment...
by the next plenary session.
Let's give it our all and
fight for our people together.
Let's do it.
That's our signal that
they've made it, Gangmo.
What did I say?
I told you not to act so impulsively.
Have you forgotten
whom we're dealing with?
Congressman.
Are you leaving?
Did the secret agreement go well?
Excuse me?
My guess was right.
Pushing you behind closed
doors was the right thing to do.
Thank you, Sir.
It wouldn't have been
possible without your help.
Ahh... I wasn't looking
for acknowledgments.
It's just that you remind
me of when I first entered politics.
Ohh... Here's my car.
I'll have to get going.
Don't you forget that spirit.
Don't let politics spoil it like with me.
The event just concluded.
What embarrassment did you get us into?
First we capture Lee Seongmo
without a shred of evidence,
then we get stared at by everyone
for ruining the mood here.
What goddamned embarrassment is this?
You more than deserve it.
Since that is all you could do.
What?
You still refuse to admit
any mistake on your part?
My judgment was flawless.
You were just too incompetent
to get a hold of all this ruse.
Hey... Jo Pilyeon!
Careful what you say, Chief Oh.
Don't delude yourself into
thinking you can talk to me like that.
I'll take Lee Seongmo.
Just release him.
Fine.
Do as you damn please!
It's Seongmo Oppa.
Big Oppa...
will be all right now, I hope?
They're releasing him because
he's no longer being suspected.
Right, Little Oppa?
Let's go wait at the apartment.
Not there, Oppa.
Minwoo knows where I live.
If he learns Seongmo is my brother,
it could put him in danger.
Did you catch the culprit?
Nah.
We couldn't.
Have you seen that account personally?
I haven't.
Who saw it?
All I needed was the confirmation
that you weren't the culprit.
That's good enough for me.
But not for me.
I must find who did this to me.
Seongmo.
Enduring injustice is part of life.
If you let that affect you
every time, you will find no peace.
Except for the fact that you would
never let any such injustice slide,
if you were on the receiving end of it.
You still resent me?
If I say I do,
will you accept that?
Seongmo.
The congressman invited
you here to console you.
I'll have to get going.
I guess time might console me a lot better.
Try to understand him.
I'm sure all this really shocked him.
I still have doubts about this all.
I'm sure there's more than one culprit.
Are you suggesting
there was an accomplice?
The account was obviously
written by one man alone.
But there must be someone
backing him from behind the scenes.
So you're still suspecting Seongmo...
In my mind, nothing has changed.
Because there are only two people
who could have written that account.
Me and...
Lee Seongmo.
Chief.
Chanseong.
It was hard, wasn't it?
Thanks for everything you did.
Your siblings are waiting for you.
Miju.
Gangmo.
Big Oppa...
Oppa, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oppa is all right.
Look at your face...
It must have been so hard...
I said it's all right.
Come on, it's getting awkward...
Hyung.
Gangmo.
Thanks, Gangmo.
Chanseong told me.
You did great.
I owe you my life.
Next time, discuss it with me before
you do something like this.
Don't try to do it all alone.
I've suddenly become
the pest of the family...
I'm sorry,
Big Oppa, Little Oppa.
I finally realized how hard it's
been for the both of you.
I will never make you worry again.
See?
Thanks to you, even Miju has matured.
All right.
Fine... I won't make you worry again.
Oppa!
You're out there, right?
We're not going anywhere, stop worrying.
Take your time, Miju.
It's all right.
She still can't go to the
lady's room alone, can she?!
Gangmo.
Give that account back to me.
It's dangerous.
If things go wrong,
you might even lose your life.
I don't believe that Jo
Pilyeon no longer suspects you.
I will keep it.
- Gangmo.
- Just this once, do as I say.
When you need it, I'll give it to you.
By the way,
because of me you couldn't
focus on your boiler project, what now?
If you let Jo Minwoo beat you,
it'll also influence the New City concessions.
It's all right, Hyung.
The sale hasn't even started.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I'll help you, Oppa.
And how would you help him?
You're talking to a
very expensive model here.
I'll be the model for Hangang
Construction's apartments.
That sounds cool?
"The apartment Cha Soojeong lives in."
He'd hit the jackpot?!
Fine, Miju.
We'll pay you generously.
And how would that help you?
You've given me an
apartment, so I'll do it for free.
Hey... Still, how can I
ask my own sister to...
No discussions.
I want to help you.
No way, Lee Miju.
Hey... Don't start arguing.
Let's just do this.
You'll do it for free,
and if you hit the jackpot, you'll
move her to a much nicer apartment.
- Happy now?
- Sounds good, Big Oppa.
So should the water reach boiling point,
it would increase volume?
Ahh... You ignoramus.
Don't even know that?
What....
Ignoramus?
I always worked at the construction
site, how would I know?
Listen well, Brother-in-law.
The issue here...
is that if the water reaches
boiling point, it'll increase its volume...
and leak into the
layers linking all the pipes.
Aigoo... And I thought all you did
all day was looking awry...
We've become a boiler expert, already!
So... How would you solve that?
Who...
Me?!
So what I was saying is...
The water would start leaking, right?
- Just like this.
- Yeah, leak.
Ahh... I can't take it anymore.
Take off that damn wig!
Ahh... Really.
I'm the one throwing a blanket over
the scalp, and you're the one complaining?
Allow me to explain.
All we need to do is create a space
which would house this increased volume,
and we're testing out what
the appropriate size should be.
I think water is boiling?
What's this... We failed again?
Why the hell did you take it off?
I can't even look at that scalp.
What are you, fueling the fire?
I can't bear to watch it, so just cover it!
Let me pour you a drink.
Nah, forget it.
Why let that disappoint you?
It's not like we don't
know how to solve this.
I'm not in the mood,
and if we want to match
the start of the sale,
we don't have the time, either.
Ahh... Why are you acting like this?
I know you've been spending
sleepless nights working there.
So have a drink and a good night of sleep.
Why, if we sleep, is anyone
going to solve our problems?
Right.
We need to solve this whatever it takes.
You don't always have to
use technology to solve such problems.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why, what are you going to do,
call a mudang and have a ritual instead?
When technology doesn't work,
you need people to solve your problems.
Is he drunk?!
Aren't technicians people, too?
I've had it with all this,
just serve me a drink.
Here you go.
Let's make a toast and cheer up.
President, it's really been a long time.
This is on the house.
Thank you.
Ohh... On the house!
Told you Auntie's the best!
That's why I always come here.
- So, what, is she your real aunt?
- Aren't we all the same anyhow... Here!
You don't always have to
use technology to solve such problems.
What's that supposed to mean?
Why, what are you going to do,
call a mudang and have a ritual instead?
When technology doesn't work,
you need people to solve your problems.
Is he drunk?
Aren't technicians people, too?
Don't come here again.
Pretend we don't know each other,
and don't ever show up before me again.
So you're saying that you don't
care even if this will kill me.
I'm sorry.
Chairman?
Seems like President Lee is
developing a similar technology.
What we can rely on is the fact that
we're still one step ahead of him.
How far has development proceeded?
Other than the toxic gas exhaust
mechanism, everything is complete.
Start by securing a patent for it.
That will help us tremendously.
All right.
Lee Gangmo's side will try everything in
their power to steal our technology.
So maintain tight security.
Yes, Chairman.
But, about that factory manager from Beaute.
How about we give him a
position at the research lab?
Considering his reputation in the
boiler sector, he could certainly help us.
I'll leave that to you.
Yes, Chairman.
What?
They've already paid the rest of the bills?!
Yes...
While you were away this
morning, they settled it all.
You said his name was Moon
Seongjoong of Manbo Construction?
It's probably him.
Yes?
Ahh... Yes! Director Moon.
What? The research lab?
Until the factory is complete,
you'll focus on boiler
development at the research lab.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Director Moon.
You can rest this weekend,
and start working on Monday.
All right.
Director Moon.
I'll never forget the help you gave
us, paying all those hospital bills.
Hospital... bills?!
Weren't you the one who paid those bills?
I guess you got confused.
I never did such thing.
What else do you want?
I guess he's being discharged?
Ajeosshi!
Minsu!
So you're fully recovered?
Yes, I'm fine now.
Great.
You've come.
It's a relief Minsu recovered so well.
It's all thanks to you, Director Moon.
Thank you so much.
I really can't figure him out.
Why even help someone who knows no shame?
Go to the Samcheong camp
and you'll get your answer.
What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
Oh, it does mean something.
Something powerful enough to
force you to look at the mirror.
Didn't that make
a decent man out of me?
I stole Beaute's core technology.
I know.
And I sold it to Manbo Construction.
I'm sure you did.
I will soon start working at their research lab.
Good for you.
Why did you help someone like me?
I have no excuses.
I'm nothing but a shameless traitor.
After losing traces of
each other in our childhood,
I just met my family again.
If I were in your shoes,
and anyone in my family was hurting
and in need, I would have done the same.
All I asked you was to develop my boilers.
I never stopped a moment...
to think about
how you were living,
or what was worrying you.
That hurts me even more than
seeing our core technology get stolen.
It's a relief that you'll soon start working
at Manbo Construction's research lab.
Take good care of Minsu.
I'll take this opportunity
to look at our employees...
as if they were my own family.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, President.
Soojeong.
Let's have an interview.
I'm sorry.
- The people know nothing about you...
- I'm sorry,
no interviews for the time being.
Wait a moment.
Have you heard the rumors?
What rumors?
About Cha Soojeong
being the mother of a child.
What?!
Speak the truth!
I apologize.
I always planned to at least tell you.
You told me your private
life was completely clean!
If people learn of this, it's all over.
Everything you've achieved
so far will be in vain, got it?
Quit your singing career and leave.
Director...
Think people will accept an
unmarried mother as a singer?
Think you'll be able to continue
acting like a star while hiding that?
I have no confidence in someone like you.
Before those rumors end up
on a tabloid, quit on your own.
Are we clear?
I...
did nothing wrong.
What?
Not telling you was certainly wrong,
but I don't believe that giving birth
to a child without a father is a sin.
Are you kidding me?
Because if I committed any sin,
that would make my son a sinner, too.
What did that poor
child ever do wrong?
If being born that way is a sin,
then how can that boy go on living?
Hey!
What did this poor
child ever do wrong?
Do bar girls have to go
through so much scrutiny?
Is it a sin to give birth to a child?
Aigoo.... Really...
Fine... The hell with this.
The hell with you and this place!
Think I won't find any other place?
I'm sorry, baby.
I scared you, didn't I?
Don't cry, baby.
I won't do it again, Jeongyeon.
Mommy won't scream again.
Don't... Stop crying, Jeongyeon.
I'm sorry...
Thank you for everything
you did for me, Director.
And sorry.
Whatever damages I caused you,
I will do everything to pay them back.
Don't go.
Manager Park.
Come in.
Yes!
Find that reporter,
and keep him quiet at all cost.
What?
All right.
As you said, giving birth is no sin.
But it can only damage your career.
Director...
Limit your meetings with him.
And should any strange rumors
start spreading, don't let them get to you.
You better be careful as well.
- Yes, Director.
- All right.
And don't you ever
cry because of this again.
I don't like it.
Soojeong...
The director is here.
Director.
Have a seat.
So you said you're
meeting investors today?
Yes.
I have a dinner tonight with five chairmen
from the Korean Federation of Industries.
Really?
Which companies?
Joyang Chemicals, Golden Group, Taeyang Group
Oseong Electric and Cheonha Heavy Industries.
How much do you plan to raise?
For starters, I think over five billion.
If we add all other companies
affiliated with the Olympic Support Committee,
I think reaching the
ten billion might be possible.
Baekpa always used to
say that money has a soul.
What?
And that whomever is able to capture
that soul can successfully conclude any deal.
He meant that you should never look
at the money, but at whom is investing it.
Thank you, Director.
I will bear it in mind.
No need to thank me.
Since I only said so
hoping you will succeed.
Yes, Director.
How did it go?
Did they leave?
They all went to the golf course.
The golf course?!
We had an appointment for today.
Their secretaries all said
that the meeting would take place there.
They never informed me of that?
Who changed those plans?
Where is this golf course?
Come on in, Director Hwang.
We've heard from Director
Hwang Jeongshik already.
If it was really urgent, you could
have just canceled the meeting.
Didn't I come on my
sister's behalf, Chairman?
I've had a good time, thanks to you.
I apologize.
- Have you had lunch...
- We were just about to get up.
We've already discussed
business with Director Hwang here.
We'll let you talk with your brother.
- Here, let's get up.
- Right.
- See you next time.
- Yes.
- See you again.
- See you soon.
See you again, Chairman.
Sit down a moment.
What are you trying to do?
I'm working under President Noh Gapsoo.
- I know.
- Really?
That's surprising.
To hear you show any interest for me.
Are you trying to steal
clients under my nose?
No.
I'm afraid that won't be enough.
I'm actually trying to bring
you and your mother down.
What?
Do you even know why my mother died?
It was because of your family.
You and your mother...
Your father.
Stop it right now.
Say what?
You really think you can
secure any investment from them?
- Hwang Jeongshik!
- I'm Hwang Taeseop's son to them,
not to mention your brother.
They'll soon invest in me.
Thank you for keeping me on my toes.
It was a welcome wake up call.
- What?
- Let's do it.
I'll give my best,
so give it your all as well.
It looks much more dignified than wasting
your life away on the poker table.
Fine...
You'll keep looking down on
me to the very end, won't you?
Let's see if you'll have such kind words
when I force bitter tears out of you.
Want me to help you?
You're Kang Wooju, right?
Don't you remember me?
Want some chocolate?
My teeth will rot.
Mommy said I shouldn't eat that.
It'll rot your teeth, right...
Did you eat lunch?
Must be hungry.
You like jjajangmyeon, right?
Want me to buy you jjajangmyeon?
You don't want to?
Mommy said I shouldn't follow strangers.
She did?!
Our Wooju is really clever?!
Mommy's name is Lee Miju, right?
Yes.
See? I even know her name.
So do Mommy and this
ajeosshi know each other or not?
Let's go eat jjajangmyeon.
Is it that good?
Wooju.
Is there anything you'd like to have?
I'll buy it for you.
- Really?
- Sure...
This ajeosshi here can buy you anything.
Let's hear it.
What do you want?
A father.
I wish I had a father, too.
But Mommy said my father is in heaven.
I wish you could be my father.
Here...
Wooju.
You and I meeting today...
Let's keep it a secret, shall we?
Yes.
Promise.
Seal.
What?!
Canceled?!
Are you telling me Cha Soojeong
will be left out of this live broadcast?
I mean... We even finished
rehearsals, what is all this about?
Hello?
What happened?
First they started canceling
all those radio appearances,
and now even TV?
I'm late.
Let's go, or PD Kim will scold me.
Soojeong.
Your gig was c.... canceled.
What?
It was canceled?
All the broadcast gigs are off the schedule?!
Were they all canceled?
They didn't tell us the reason,
but there must have been
some outside pressure involved.
Outside pressure?!
So someone is trying to
prevent me from appearing on TV?
I'll be damned...
Revenge?!
And you little tramp
would get revenge against me?
Coming here was a grave mistake.
Since you'll soon find out
how scary and cruel life can get.
We better let the director know, Soojeong.
Wait a little longer.
I need to verify something first.
Verify?
I'll be right back.
Congressman.
Cha Soojeong is waiting outside.
Cha Soojeong?
We have no reason to meet.
Send her packing.
All right.
Ten minutes... No.
Five minutes is all I need.
My broadcast appearances
have suddenly been canceled.
Were you behind that?
I thought I gave you a word of warning?
Give me back my gigs.
You were the one who ignored my warnings.
I won't meet Minwoo again.
We have no reason to.
I see you don't get the point.
I don't like the fact that you're a singer.
And I certainly don't want to
see you prance around on TV...
and make Minwoo increasingly miserable.
Singing might not look all that special to you,
but it's the dream of a lifetime to me.
Aren't those five minutes up?
Let's go.
Just because you don't approve of it,
can you really ruin someone's life this way?
Is that what this mighty
authority of yours is all about?
I'm stopping at this just for Minwoo's sake.
Keep trying to rile me up,
and I'll make you experience what
our mighty authority really feels like.
If you really want to sing,
go do it on some stage
away from people's attention.
I'll allow that much.
You just wait.
As I won't let this slide, either.
You lowly little tramp...
Think a little make-up is all you
need to act all haughty around me?
Reporter Kim.
Are you really sure?
I did receive a report that Kang Wooju's
mother looks exactly like Cha Soojeong.
Her son frequents
that kindergarten, is that it?
Yes.
So let's find out.
You're Wooju.
Who are you?
Is your mother's name Cha Soojeong?
No.
It's not Cha Soojeong?
It's not.
Then...
What's your mother's name?
It's Lee Miju.
Is it really Lee Miju?
Yes.
I guess it was a false report, after all.
Allow me to apologize.
Soojeong.
How have you been, Deputy?
What brings you here?
She probably has a
meeting for the promo shoot.
Is that so?
- Then, why don't you show her the way?
- Yes.
No. That won't be necessary.
All right, then.
I'm a little busy today.
See you next time.
Yes, Deputy.
Deputy?!
I examined the boiler
projects you sent me.
It seems that boilers will decide
who wins the Suseo sale, after all.
Well, if you allow me to
get straight to the point,
when it comes to the Korean-style
ondol-based boiler you presented,
Manbo Construction seems to have the edge.
After you acquired Beaute
Boilers, I had high expectations,
so I'm honestly a little surprised.
Our development process
still hasn't been completed.
We will satisfy your
expectations before the sale begins.
And will that be so easy to achieve?
Because you can't develop a technology
out of the blue with hard work alone.
Jo Minwoo.
I might not like the way you did it,
but I do acknowledge that you
found a solution to those flaws.
Your boiler research lab seems
to have quite the potential?!
Don't act all accommodating with me.
It makes me sick.
Maybe I have a good reason to do so.
And if this Suseo apartment construction
ends up becoming your last,
will you say the same thing?
- Try to make it happen, if you can.
- Hey, Lee Gangmo.
Manbo Construction, Daeryuk Construction...
Already forgot who made them collapse?
If I only wanted, I could destroy
Hangang Construction in a heartbeat.
You know that?
Chairman!
I'll stop by the research lab on my way home.
Chairman.
Go ahead.
Is anything the matter?
I just learned this...
Cha Soojeong.... No.
Lee Miju has been hiding a son.
Here's the child's census register.
- Kang Wooju -
Grandma...
He's registered as son
of a certain Kang Jeongja,
but she's too old to have a child.
The mother is clearly Lee Miju,
but as for the father...
Turn the car around.
What?
Bring me to this child right now.
By now, the kindergarten might already...
I said turn around!
See you, Wooju.
Chairman...
It's that boy.
Brought to you by WITHS2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Subtitles by Anarchist
Fine tuning by wichitawx
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Are you suggesting we change our
marketing strategy based on groundless rumors?
You've found yourself
quite the remarkable sponsor.
Hangang Construction
will be added to the list.
I know who killed Lee Gangmo's father.
Chairman Hwang is meeting
those opposition party members.
Find out everything about that account.
If I don't pay back those
forty million, they'll kill me, Dad.
Don't you ever gamble
again, and just work under me.
- It's Lee Miju's son.
- Are you telling me Minwoo is the father?
Here are the results of the DNA test.
Wooju is not your son?!
Better go all the way, since we're there.
What do you plan to do with that child?
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com