Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Episode 44
Coffee for three.
Gangmo!
You dare bite me?
Listen.
Are those people regulars?
They come pretty often these days.
What kind of people are they?
Gangsters.
You can't imagine how annoying they are.
Wait here just a moment.
Ahh... I'm sorry.
Hey... Did you leave your eyes at home?
I apologize.
I should have been more careful.
- I ought to...
- Hey.
Stop.
Pay for the dry cleaner's,
and get the fuck out.
Don't ever do anything you'll
have to feel sorry about again.
Where are all the others?
I came here alone on their behalf.
Have a seat.
Care for a drink?
No, thanks.
But forget that...
There is only one week left before
the principal will have to be paid back.
I'm sure you know already,
but if you retrieve all that money,
our organization will collapse.
Is that what you wish for?
It was Baekpa's last wish.
And no matter what,
I will fulfill his wishes.
Baekpa is no longer with us!
The living must go on.
What are you trying to imply?
Many people are voicing their
grievances within the organization.
I'm just saying this for your own sake.
I suggest you just put all this to rest.
If you don't wire that money
by the end of the month,
I will begin legal litigation.
Convey it to the others as well.
Bucheol...
He's rougher than I thought?!
So it was you.
The one behind Jeongyeon's abduction.
You have nothing to gain
by reporting it to the police.
Right.
Bucheol also wanted to tell you this.
That he couldn't care less whether
Hwang Jeongyeon is your daughter or not.
If you don't answer them in two days,
Hwang Jeongyeon won't
get out of there alive.
I'd prefer to see this matter
conclude peacefully.
A little compromise on your part,
and I think we could settle it all?!
If you'll excuse me.
Look at how pretty she is.
So, what, you're telling me
they're Bucheol's sidekicks?
Anyhow, I told you Gangmo
has a quick eye for this.
First, we need to find out
where they're hiding,
so let's start by trailing them.
Okay.
Hey... Here they are.
They're going.
We'll lose them, speed up!
Stay put, will you?
There are little to no cars,
so they'll find out right away.
Hey...
Those fools behind seem to be following us?
Find a quiet place and leave the road.
What's this...
Why are they going that way?
Did they find out?
Follow them.
Look.
Why do you keep following us?
Aigoo... Look at this one.
It's the prick from earlier on?
I just thought I gave you a
little too much money, that's all.
Say what?
This prick must be retarded.
Where is Cha Bucheol?
Lee Gangmo?
I asked where Cha Bucheol is!
You fuc...
Shideok... Hit him!
Hyungnim!
It's Lee Gangmo! Leave that place!
What's the matter, Hyungnim?
Take the boys and leave immediately.
What?
Lee Gangmo is here!
Are you telling me Lee Gangmo
followed us all the way here?
Then, why don't we wait here
and just beat him to a...
Think he'd be crazy enough
to come alone?
- Hey... Go start the car.
- Yes, Hyungnim.
Let's go.
Hey.
Hwang Jeongyeon!
Open the door!
Hey!
You really have a death wish?
Hwang Jeongyeon!
Hey... Speak while I still play nice.
Where is your hideout?
We have no idea.
Just kill us.
You son of a...
Go ahead.
Kill us!
Throw them in the car.
Let's go.
Get up.
Get moving.
You're dead. Got it?
The hell is this?
What are you doing?
What the hell are you trying to do?
Guys.
Stay away from the car.
G...G...Gangmo...
What's wrong with you?
Come with me.
- Gangmo!
- Sit.
If you don't tell me
by the count of three,
you're all dead.
- One...
- You crazy son of a bitch!
Two!
Don't kill us!
Three!
Spare us!
Don't kill us!
I try to treat you decently,
and you look down on me?
I ought to...
It's the police, right?
I'd like to report an abduction.
What? Yes. That'll be...
Samgo Reservoir!
Samgo Reservoir.
The villa by the reservoir.
Speed up.
- I'm already pushing it to the limit.
- It's not a prank call!
Here!
I think we lost them.
It's me, Lee Gangmo.
No need to beat around the bush.
If you want this bitch to live,
bring the pledge and
the IOU list to me alone.
Let me hear Jeongyeon.
Gangmo.
Jeongyeon.
Are you okay?
Is everything all right?
Yeah... I'm all right.
Listen well.
I'll come to get you,
so don't be afraid and calm down.
- Got it?
- Don't come, Gangmo.
You must not come alone.
Are we clear, Gangmo? You can't...
You filed the report?
Seems like you didn't live up
to your end of the bargain?
What about Yoo Gyeongok's
pledge and IOU list?
Give me just another few days.
What?
President...
The thing I hate most is people
who don't keep their promises.
You know that.
I apologize, President.
For the last time, you have three days.
If you fail again,
you'll get to meet Baekpa six feet under.
There... Right there.
Turn around.
What?
Where are we going, Hyungnim?
Back to Seoul.
Se...Seoul?!
Lee Gangmo got in the way,
so time for a little counterstrike.
Take a good look.
At how I beat your Lee Gangmo to a pulp.
What have you two been doing all this time?
Lee Gangmo is breathing down
Cha Bucheol's neck.
Everything we planned
might be ruined, you get that?
It's my fault.
- I was so busy with other things that I...
- I know how busy you are!
But how many times did I
tell you how important this is?
We're back to square one.
After what happened,
Cha Bucheol will try to get his revenge.
What are you trying to say?
He'll try to use Hwang Jeongyeon
as bait for the pledge and IOU list,
so that Lee Gangmo will
be forced to bring that.
Then, it would be much
quicker to find Lee Gangmo.
I'm sure of it.
I will tolerate no mistakes
this time, is that clear?
All right.
What is keeping Seongmo so busy?
- As you know, the situation is very ser...
- Tell me something I don't know!
I'm asking you what he's doing these days.
Ahh... Yes. That...
I don't really know.
Yes.
Yes, Sir!
Certainly, Sir.
I will be there right away.
I never imagined there could be support
for direct elections within the ruling party.
I guess they've heard
the voice of the people.
And what are you trying to imply?
It's for the president's sake.
Isn't letting him hear what the
people are saying part of our duties?
Anyhow, with this secret mandate,
we must eradicate these
traitors at the very root.
I'll handle all third-termers and below,
so you take care of all the veterans.
It's a list of ruling party
members who are sympathizing...
with the prospect of
a constitutional amendment.
If I think of what I had to
go through to compile that list...
To make that amendment happen,
these numbers won't do.
This all depends on Congressman Oh.
But once he sees that secret account,
he'll surely join forces with us.
I wouldn't jump to conclusions yet.
Until you find out his true intentions,
you can't show him our cards.
Right.
I only have one life, so better be careful.
We'll be late for tonight's meeting.
I'll have to get going, then.
May I ask you one thing?
Why did you join forces with Hwang Taeseop?
I didn't join forces with anyone,
I'm just using him.
If things go according to plan,
our country's political circles
will be turned upside down.
And of course Jo Pilyeon will be
the first to suffer the consequences.
But it could also fail.
Then, I guess we'll be in
for a huge crimson tide.
And Hwang Taeseop will bear the brunt of it.
So if we succeed, Jo Pilyeon. And if
we fail, it'll be Hwang Taeseop's turn.
But we can't fail.
Because if that happens,
then we'd only have helped Jo Pilyeon
build an inexpugnable fortress around him.
Before that happens,
he must be destroyed.
Most of the people who
claimed to know Lee Miju...
just made false reports
with the cash reward in mind.
And considering that we got
reports from all over the country,
verifying every single one
would be a little bit of a challenge.
Stop it.
Some suggest she does resemble
a certain singer named Cha Soojeong.
I said stop!
I apologize, Chairman.
You may leave.
Your mother will be discharged this evening,
so she asked if you could take her home.
She practically spends all
her time practicing these days.
If she keeps this up, her live debut
will be a huge success, Director.
I am quite busy these days.
I won't be able to
visit often until her debut.
So keep an eye on her training schedule.
All right, Director.
I knew your father ran this hospital
and your uncle was an army general,
but you're telling me
your other uncle is a diplomat?
Yes...
You're here?
Yes.
Are you going to be discharged now?
What's with all the rush?
Why don't you two have dinner together?
You're not going to
stand me up again, are you?
What are you doing?
How much is it?
30,000 won.
Let's go.
Wooju was here just a moment ago.
Where did he go again?
Aww... I can't take my eyes off him
for a single second.
Wait here just a moment.
Wait a moment.
I'll go get changed and will be right back.
Give it back.
It's mine, give it here.
That toy is mine.
And?
He won't give it back.
So?
All right.
So I can just get it back for you, right?
Let's go.
Kiddo.
That's not yours, is it?
It's his.
Give it here.
Here.
Happy now?
Thank you.
But you never seem to cry?!
Mommy said men shouldn't cry.
You can cry, since you're still a kid.
I'm not a kid.
Then?
What are you?
Mommy...
Mommy, why are you crying?
I'm not crying, Wooju.
I've made you wait, didn't I?
Let's go.
I will pay back the courtesy today,
considering all you did for my mother.
But I'd like you to stop trying
to use my mother for this.
It's quite offensive, actually.
Why? Surprised?
Thanks.
I was starting to miss
that ugly mug of yours.
Give me a break... Still acting cocky?
I'll keep it short and sweet.
You have until tomorrow at midnight
to bring me both pledge and IOU list.
Where should I go?
Don't take it so lightly.
Hwang Jeongyeon is going to die.
My boys will show you the way tomorrow.
Should the police be tagging along,
or if you try anything funny,
neither you nor Yoo Gyeongok
will ever see Hwang Jeongyeon again.
Are we clear?
Looks like we'll have to give them
that pledge and the IOU list first.
That's out of the question.
There is no other way if
we want to save Jeongyeon.
So, what,
will you just take that
to them all by yourself?
We're forced to follow
their conditions for now.
Don't you get what they're scheming?
Both Jeongyeon and you are in danger.
And you'll even lose
the pledge and IOU list.
It won't go as they wish.
What are you trying to say?
Do you have any plan in mind?
Leave this to me to the end.
At this point, I am the
only one who can solve this.
Let's put our faith in him.
If it's Gangmo, I believe he can do it.
I'd like to meet my brother tomorrow.
1 pm, at the usual Japanese restaurant.
Yes, I will tell him.
Anything else you'd like to convey?
There are people following me.
Yes. He just met Yoo Gyeongok.
He's probably just going back home.
Don't take your eyes off him for a moment.
- Got it?
- Yes, all right.
But can we really leave Lee Gangmo's
surveillance to Chanseong?
That's his specialty,
so you don't need to worry.
Chanseong.
I'm back, Chief.
Lee Gangmo?
He just went back home.
Other agents are checking on him,
so there's no need to worry.
I need some shut-eye,
so wake me up a little later.
This is the IOU list,
and here are the rest of the documents.
Are you really going to sign
a pledge renouncing the principal?
Now everything depends on you.
Will you have company, Sir?
Yes.
I've heard from Chanseong.
So you must meet Cha Bucheol alone?
They will tag along
from the very beginning.
So it won't be easy to trail you.
The slightest suspicion,
and Jeongyeon will be in danger.
Did you prepare all the documents?
I have them.
You were after
Cha Bucheol as well, right?
Told you, didn't I?
That I was dealing
with this troublesome fella.
It doesn't matter anyway, does it?
You'll be following me, after all.
Open the chopstick holder.
It's a tracking device.
It does have limited range,
but we'll be able to follow you
without arousing suspicion.
The key is that nothing
must happen until I get there.
I'll try to hang in there,
whatever the case.
Who did you come to meet?
I thought you might
have something to tell me.
The IOU list and the
pledge are ready, I hope?
Of course.
Come to the riverbank
in Mapo tonight at nine.
By yourself.
Hey... Gangmo.
Just report them to the police
and get it over with!
If you go there by yourself,
they'll kill you!
Unless you were completely crazy,
why would you go there?
Or if you don't want the police
to get involved, go there with us.
We need to live and die together!
That's right, let's go together.
I still have a lot left in the tank.
Look at these biceps.
I can handle them!
Aren't you going home?
Should we be worrying about that now?
Did you just get angry at me?
I'll have to go.
- Gangmo...
- Hey, Gangmo.
How could you get angry at me?
Let me go, will you?
My God...
- Hey...
- Gangmo.
Gangmo.
Wake up, please.
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
A plan?
Did he, what, report this
to someone without telling us?
I'll see you again soon.
- Gangmo.
- Gangmo!
Gangmo!
Gangmo is not the type to
just barge in without a plan.
I'm sure he thought of something.
I really don't know what to do anymore.
Hey, Gangmo!
Ahh... That damned stubbornness.
Gyeongja, what's the matter?
Sotae... How could you do this to me?
Gyeongja, is anything wrong?
Gyeongja!
What's wrong with her?
All right.
Careful, Gangmo.
Looks like Lee Gangmo
might soon make his move.
Get ready.
All right.
Where is he now?
I managed to plant
a tracking device on his car.
Let's get ready.
Don't you have one for me?
You know that civilians
can't carry firearms.
We have a baton.
Do you want this?
- You weren't followed, right?
- Of course not, Hyungnim.
Nobody followed us.
Just in case, stay behind
and watch our backs.
All right, Hyungnim.
The documents?
We're leaving right now, Hyungnim.
Yes.
It was just Lee Gangmo.
You verified the pledge?
Of course, Hyungnim.
Yes.
All right, Hyungnim.
Let's go.
When is Lee Gangmo coming?
That's the car.
Seems like that's all, shall we start?
Wait.
You said it had a
five-kilometer range, right?
We can't allow them to spot us,
so let's keep our distance
and start a little later.
I've given it a thought,
and it does surprise me a little.
That Lee Gangmo.
Unless he's really got a screw or
two loose, how could he come here alone?
So it's one of the two.
Either he's completely
gone crazy for you,
or maybe he thinks
I'm just a half-witted thug.
Once you get what you want, let us go.
Don't hurt Gangmo.
Do you even realize what I had
to go through because of that prick?
And you think I'd just let
someone like him get away with it?
You rat bastard.
I've heard that so much over the years,
it almost sounds like a compliment.
So take a good look.
See what happens to your Lee Gangmo.
You'll see a warehouse around the corner.
We're almost there.
- What's wrong with it?
- We're out of range.
Go faster.
Gangmo!
Let's see the documents first.
First set Jeongyeon free.
You're not thinking you'll
get out of here alive, are you?
Don't! Stop, Gangmo!
Gangmo!
Stop there!
Set her free right now.
If you don't, you'll need
an ashtray for these.
If you want to see this
bitch dead, go ahead and try!
Gangmo...
She's important to you, isn't she?
Isn't that the reason you
risked your life and came here?
Take your hands off her.
Give me those documents
while you still can.
- Do it!
- Don't, Gangmo!
Don't do it.
With those in your hands,
you can get out of here alive.
You can never give them
those documents, Gangmo.
You can't...
Give me those damned documents!
Stop!
Gangmo...
You fool.
Why did you come here?
Gangmo...
No!
No... Gangmo!
Gangmo!
Stop.
Gangmo...
I was an amateur boxer back in school.
I saw at the health club
that you box a little?!
How about it?
If you beat me, I could let you go.
Gangmo...
What the hell is going on?
What if we lose him?
They might have stopped around here.
Slow down a little.
I guess because you only saw me
groveling at people's feet,
you thought I was
just a pushover, right?
Didn't you?
So that's why you
came here afraid of nothing.
Since you must have thought
I was nothing but a retard!
Get up.
Get up!
I told you that
if you beat me I'll spare her.
Uh?
Don't get up, Gangmo!
Don't get up, you idiot!
Die... Die!
Die!
Gangmo!
Freeze!
Gangmo...
Gangmo.
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Freeze!
Hey!
Gangmo.
Gangmo...
Wake up.
Gangmo!
Gangmo...
Are you all right?
You idiot.
Am I the problem now?
If you are okay, then that's it.
Hey... Cha Bucheol!!
Come here.
You piece of shit!
It's Go Jaechun!
It's not Cha Bucheol, it's Go Jaechun.
Are you telling me Go Jaechun
took the documents?
I think so.
Gangmo.
Are you all right, Gangmo?
He's my brother.
Gangmo.
Thanks for coming, Hyung.
How about the documents?
Go Jaechun took them.
First, let's go to the hospital.
Can you drive?
Don't worry about Gangmo.
I'll take him there.
Good job, Jaechun.
You were brilliant!
It wouldn't have happened
unless Seongmo held them back.
You never betray my expectations.
I'm proud of you both.
How about Lee Gangmo?
Yes, he's been hospitalized.
I wish we could have just gotten
ourselves rid of him once and for all.
I wasn't implying I wanted you
to get your hands dirty.
If that Cha Bucheol had taken care of him,
we would have killed two birds with a stone.
Let's go out for drinks.
I'll treat you all the way.
I need to go somewhere urgently.
Really?
Then, we'll have to
save it for another time.
Right.
With this in my hands,
it's only a matter of time before the
private lending cartel is under my control.
Now that those documents
are in his hands, what's next?
I need to go to the broadcasting station.
Right... Miju's live debut was today.
Gangmo?
He is still likely at the hospital,
would he be able to make it?
Everyone get ready.
Soojeong, I'll go deal with your costumes,
so say hi and get your makeup done.
Yes.
I'm new singer Cha Soojeong.
I'll be counting on you, Seonbaenim.
So you're Cha Soojeong?
Yes...
Hong Jiyoung Seonbaenim, right?
Seonbaenim?
Who ever said I'd consider you a peer?
What?
I hear you're selling
your albums on the street?
How dare they let some corny
tramp embarrass our profession?
What connections did you have,
to get on this show?
By any chance, did you sell
something else other than those albums?
Look, Hong Jiyoung.
What?
"Hong Jiyoung"?
You said you don't consider me a peer.
So you can forget that
"Seonbaenim" from me as well.
Look at this little tramp...
Consider this a warning.
I can fight quite well.
So if you keep acting
like that, I could just...
I apologize for all that.
I'll be counting on you, Seonbaenim.
- Costume Room -
- Cha Soojeong -
Let's see how you deal with
an embarrassment on live TV.
What do we do now?
Don't you have any other costume?
This is all we have...
I'll be damned, really!
What's the matter?
Someone ruined my stage costume.
What happened to that costume,
all of a sudden?
Everyone, get ready.
We're starting soon.
What are you going to do?
I can't go down without a fight.
Find me a pin, at least.
A... A pin?
Would that be enough?
There's no other way. Find it.
Yes, all right.
Don't dance this time.
Then, you'll be able to
manage one way or another.
Still... It's a dance song...
What if you end up half-naked
on a live broadcast?
Chairman, I found Lee Miju.
Here.
The information we received was right.
Cha Soojeong was really Lee Miju.
Miju...
There's a live performance
on SBC at four,
and she's debuting there.
Soojeong, it's your turn. Quick.
Don't run.
It'll mess up your image.
Walk out there slowly,
and with your head held up high.
You were born to be a star.
If you have no faith
in yourself, believe in me.
Yes.
Go out there and make
all viewers fall for you.
Seongmo Oppa... Gangmo Oppa...
Miju...
Lee Miju, you!
Brought to you by WITH S2
Written In The Heavens Subbing Squad
This is a FREE fansub. NOT for SALE!
Get it for FREE @ withs2.com
Main Translator and Timer: Anarchist
Timing QC: wichitawx
Editor/QC: thunderbolt
Coordinators: mily2, ay_link
Just for today.
Then I'll never do this again.
As for the model for our apartments,
let's go with Cha Soojeong.
Soojeong! You're about
to star in an apartment CF!
Which company?
Which one?
I'll be honest with you.
I'm trying to build a new business model.
That sorry-ass son of a cunt.
He seems hell-bent on ruining us.
It's pretty obvious our
core technology was leaked.
We're going to fight it with quality.
He handed in his resignation.
Looks like Lee Gangmo
found out about him.
What do you think you're doing?
Where is Lee Seongmo?
Where is he, you prick?!
Watch dramas legally at
dramafever.com | crunchyroll.com