Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 7]
I believe that the police will prove my innocence.
Do you think you could stand up to the investigation?
If I can't then the whole Sales Department cannot stand up to it as well!
Do you want to drag everyone in the Sales Department into this?
Let me tell you. It's impossible. For this situation,
we only have one solution. That is, you quit by yourself!
I won't quit over making a false report on the invoice!
Ziting, where is Sister Yuan?
She went to a meeting.
When will she come back?
I don't know.
Hello, the subscriber you have dialed is not available right now. Sorry...
Where is GM Pan?
GM Pan is abroad.
All right. I will contact you again.
Hello, the subscriber you have dialed has turned off the phone. Sorry...
His phone is turned off.
I'm guessing he is on the plane at this moment.
- Sister, what exactly is going on?
- Sister Siyu!
There is definitely someone making trouble for Sister Siyu!
You guys go back first.
Sister Siyu.
- Did something happen?
- Yes.
- Is what they said true?
- What did they say?
It has been spreading around that you have embezzled hundreds of thousands RMB in recent years.
Nonsense! I didn't embezzle anything!
They said the company has already reported it to the police.
The police station will send someone to arrest you soon.
What exactly is going on?
- Someone is framing me.
- Who?
Sister Siyu, I trust that you would never do something like this.
But... do you think you can get out of this?
I don't know.
Then, what should you do?
Let me answer the phone.
What's up? Do you need something or do you miss me?
What does you not talking mean?
What? Are you letting me admire your beauty quietly?
Wait for me. I'm heading over to you right now.
What's happened?
Take me to abreact first.
Why isn't she answering?
Chen Yiming also isn't answering the phone.
What exactly is going on at your company?
I don't know. When I left,
I heard Director Fang ask HR to fire her.
Fine, fire her! Or she can resign first!
Whether it be firing or resigning, she will be blacklisted.
It'll be very difficult for her to find a job in the future.
Then wouldn't workaholic Li Siyu be devastated?
That's why I'm worried.
Siyu, go in from the other side.
Why do you kill good people as well?
[Zhang Zhizhi]
I can't tell who is good who is bad.
Let's go.
Here is your water.
Thank you.
Now, would you like to tell me?
I don't want to work there anymore.
What happened?
Can you support me?
Of course, I am willing to. I've always thought about doing that as well.
I knew you were going to say that.
I will do that as well.
Now, do you want to tell me the reason?
It's okay. You have me.
Hello?
Hello, hello. Yes, yes, yes. I'm Chen Yiming.
Right now?
All right. No problem.
Right. I'll head over right now.
Okay. Okay. No problem.
Thank you.
Thank you, Director Mao. See you.
Siyu, my friend introduced me to a job.
But the boss wants me to see him now.
Are you leaving?
I need to support you,
so doesn't that mean I have to find a job?
Can you understand me?
Is Li Siyu with you?
Come here quickly to stay with her.
[Shanghai Sjijia Urban Fun Park]
Siyu, Xiaoling says she will come to stay with you very soon.
I don't have much time, I really need to rush over there.
Li Siyu hasn't given in yet?
Whether she gives in or not, before Pan Zhiyong comes back,
we must fire her.
Isn't this too cruel of us?
Don't worry.
Based on her capacity, she can find a job immediately after she leaves.
Moreover, she will definitely get one with better conditions.
I mentored her for 7 years,
yet we have ended up like this.
I still don't have the heart to do this.
You mentored her for 7 years,
so you must know her very well.
Will she give you the position of Sales Director willingly?
- She won't.
- Based on her capabilities and ambitions,
will she be soft-hearted with you in the end?
This ending,
starting from the moment Pan Zhiyong picked her as your opponent,
is destined.
You don't need to feel guilty.
After Sister Yuan took over the Sales Department,
she disliked the application for overtime pay, thinking it was troublesome,
so she had me just add it directly to the PR fees.
She would just sign an approval.
So this issue...
is Sister Yuan framing you behind the scenes?
Except for her, nobody knows that I reported ¥500 more for reimbursement that day.
Furthermore, she could have cleared it up when the Supervising Department was investigating.
But she said that she didn't know.
Also, I still can't get in contact with her now.
Bitch!
What if you go to ask other colleagues in the Sales Department?
What if other colleagues are willing to prove
that you have this unofficial rule in the department?
I think you can explain this, right?
Most of them are Sister Yuan's team members.
Will they help me?
So the key to solving this...
is Sister Yuan. We have to find her.
I think based on the relationship between you and Sister Yuan,
she wouldn't be so ruthless. Right?
From Lin Ling's situation, I've discovered
that she has changed.
I think there is not much to discuss about this situation.
First, do not quit unless they clear this up and give you your innocence back.
Second, if it is this Yuan Huizhong framing you, then fuck her up!
How?
Make a big deal out of it!
Our Liu Yang got promoted!
I think it is either director or section chief.
Anyways, he got promoted.
He is busy every day.
Of course, I stay at Liu Yang's house!
His house is quite big.
I have my own room.
All right. I'm boiling water. I'm busy right now.
We'll talk another time. I'm hanging up.
Yuwei, have some water.
Liu Yang,
let me ask you something.
Go ahead, Mom.
Did your wife drink the medicines that I sent to you guys?
She should have drank them.
She didn't drink them at all. The medicines are hidden in the kitchen cabinet.
I saw them!
Mom, if she doesn't want to drink them, lets not force her.
Also, we haven't made any plans for a second child.
Then, when do you plan to?
There's no rush.
Why not? Yuwei has already gotten this big.
Also, the country is encouraging everyone to have a second child.
You have to support this policy, right?
We have to follow the policy!
Mom, the country has stopped the only-child policy.
But every family's situation is different.
The situation of our family
is you should seize the time to have a second child. Do you understand?
Look!  My body is still well. If my legs aren't working well in a few years,
who will help you if you have a baby?
Mom, I'm busy. Lets talk about this later.
This is a big thing. Pay attention to it!
Okay! I will discuss it with Zhizhi later.
What is there to discuss? Why do you need to discuss it with her?
You decide this!
Grandma, I want to eat cookies!
Eat cookies? Your mom already said you can't eat things freely.
Have you listened to what I said?
Yes, I did.
Wait for me. I will get cookies for you.
This one.
Slowly.
Take a good rest when you get back.
Don't think about anything.
Watch the steps! Slowly!
Get your spirits up. You have a lot to do tomorrow.
I asked Chen Yiming to come and pick you up.
Thank you.
If you need anything, just tell us. We are here for you.
I have watched all the palace dramas. I know all the evil tricks!
Let's go.
Slowly!
Bag.
Be careful.
We're leaving now.
Drink some warm honey water.
Sorry.
I wasn't able to stay with you all day today.
Are there any new developments in the situation?
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
How was your job interview?
You should know that I was wronged.
We have been using this method to get our overtime pay in the past six months.
Sister Siyu, I want to help you.
But at this moment, if I admit it,
I will lose my PR fees as well.
- Won't I be walking myself into a trap?
- But if you don't help me now,
in the future, if the Supervising Department finds out, then they will definitely report you.
I... let me think about it.
[Li Siyu, please go to the Finance Department.]
You came.
Take these falsely reported invoices back and then give me new invoices
for overtime pay according to the amount on these invoices.
What do you mean?
Also, from now on, overtime pay is overtime pay.
PR expenses are PR expenses. Don't mix them up, all right?
What exactly happened?
GM Pan came back early.
Come in!
GM Pan, I want to explain the situation to you.
From beginning to end, I have never falsely reported PR fees.
This matter is over now.
I have to explain it even if it's over.
- I don't want to hear it.
- Why?
Because I know you.
You would never do such a thing for ¥500.
You were wronged.
GM Pan.
Li Siyu,
this... I helped you get over this obstacle.
But I can't guarantee that
I will be able to help you next time.
Do you know what you must do so that trouble doesn't find you?
You must be in a high enough position so that trouble can't reach you.
GM Pan, I understand.
Don't worry. I will be a good team leader.
In three months, I will be the Sales Director.
Great.
- Xiaojia.
- Yes, Sis?
- Do we still have the wine from last time?
- Yes.
- Pour it out.
- Got it.
- Sis.
- Pour it.
Since everyone trusts me and is willing to follow me,
I will not let you guys down.
We must work hard to do our best together.
It doesn't matter who will be the director after three months, the important thing is that
we must not let the company, our friends, and ourselves down.
- Cheers!
Sister Siyu, all of us will listen to you.
We will let our characters speak for us and let our strength prove what we are capable of.
- We must do better than them.
- Ch—
- Let's drink.
Sister Ziru.
That's a bit too long. You haven't changed jobs in ten years.
-  Your experience is lacking.
- I dare not recommend you to my clients.
- Our company products are targeted for post-90s.
- They won't want you.
I suggest you get a few more years of experience before applying for the position.
Your age is too old for us.
Where are you?
- Near your company.
- Then I'll go find you.
I have good news to tell you.
Send me your location.
Okay.
When have you become interested in this social circle?
Ever since my dad had a passion,
he forced me to work in this field.
It's too boring; it's not interesting at all.
- I'm leaving.
- Wait a moment.
My dad arranged a connoisseur to discuss some things with me.
- Let's go together.
- That's fine.
- Let me answer this call.
- Okay.
This brushstroke has me obsessed.
- Then you must like Mondrian’s earlier works better.
- Who?
A master of "De Stijl."
(T/N: Dutch art movement)
Don't tell me you've never heard of him?
Of course, I have heard about him. It's just...
The person you are talking about, she has several of his work hanging in her house.
You collect Mondrian's paintings? Which ones do you have?
The most famous one.
- Could it be the "Red, Blue and Yellow"?
- Exactly!
That's the one.
Miss Gu, my biggest dream
is to see Mondrian's work with my own eyes.
Please let me go to your home.
T-This... we can talk about it another time.
A friend is looking for me. I will go over there for a moment.
Miss Gu.
Miss Gu!
Mondrian. Neoplasticism.
Neoplasticism.
Pure abstraction.
Mondrian. Neoplasticism. Pure abstraction.
GM Pan came back early.
He helped me take care of the invoice situation.
Finance Department told me to submit an overtime payment application to make up for it.
The matter is settled.
- That simply?
- It was originally something out of nothing,
it's back to the original point now.
That's good.
Sister Yuan and I have completely torn apart.
This is the end to seven years of her being my mentor and friend.
What a pity.
Did I do something wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
It's...
too complicated.
Must we experience all this just to become a sales director?
In the battlefield... m-must we disregard feelings?
If I knew the answer,
I wouldn't have lost my job.
Oh, right. Have you gotten a job yet?
Can we not talk about this?
Doctrine. Pure abstraction.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
Amazing.
You understand it?
Deconstruction.
My friend recommended me to buy it. Do you think this can appreciate?
Deconstruction stuff appreciates every year.
But Mbappe and Suarez...
are believers of deconstruction.
Of course, Cristiano  Ronaldo and Pogba
(T/N: famous European soccer players)
would not agree with this viewpoint.
Miss Gu, what do you think?
Sorry. Are those you have mentioned all artists?
Yes.
Why do they all sound so familiar?
Excuse me.
I think you can
- consider buying this painting.
- Really?
Amazing.
Oh, Sister Ziru called me today.
She invited us to attend a new energy lecture this weekend.
Let's go together.
Forget it.
Sister Ziru specially asked you to go.
I don't want to go.
Let's go, let's go.
You are free anyways.
Instead of staying at home all day, go walk around outside.
Maybe you will come across an opportunity.
How do you know that I'm idle all day?
I went to a lot of places today.
I mean, Sister Ziru has many friends.
Maybe she can introduce you to a job.
It's my own business, I can solve it myself. I don't need outsiders to help me.
Your official competition with Sister Yuan is about to start.
Are you confident?
When discussing personal capabilities, I don't lose to her.
Discussing about teams,
although she has almost all the elites of the Sales Department,
but my team is younger
and more hard-working. I can also go poach people from the outside.
The only thing I lack in comparison to her
is that I don't have as many customers as she does.
After I get back home, I can comb through some of my former clients
to see if you can use them.
No need.
What I need is mature sales
for a fierce fight.
Aren't you going to be busier than before then?
I don't have a choice.
It's only three months,
I can hold out.
I believe that you can hold out
but can your body take it? Can you bear all that stress?
I think it's no problem.
You travel weekly, work overtime every day, and drink during every meal with clients.
Can your stomach take all that?
Do you want to talk about business trips, overtime, drinking, or my stomach?
What I want to say is, you don't need to work that hard.
- But...
- But what?
But I don't have a job now.
I don't need you to support me. I can rely on myself.
I—
What I am saying is not what are you thinking.
I know you want what's good for me.
I also know you are in a bad mood.
Let's not quarrel, okay?
You can't be out for too long, right?
Hurry back to work then.
How about you?
Me? I will sit for a bit and then I'll leave.
Then, I'm leaving.
I'm bored looking at the exhibition.
Where do you want to go tonight?
I'll talk to you later.
What are you doing?
Hey, Miss.
The chair is very long.
Or I can sit in the car.
Why are you here?
I have been here all along.
Who is looking for you?
- I'm looking for my girlfriend.
- She's your girlfriend?
I'm sorry. My girlfriend and I have something to do, I'll talk to you later.
What's your problem? You keep haunting me. What do you want?
- I'm helping you.
- Are we close?
Do I need your help?
Let me tell you.
That man's name is Xiao Kehe's my middle school classmate. I know him very well.
I know his personality very well. He is the upgraded version of Lan Ke.
Don't believe it? Look at his WeChat Moment.
(T/N: WeChat moment is equivalent to Facebook feed)
Look.
Look. To old classmates,
he is pretty true to himself. To women,
he is a true piece of trash.
So dangerous.
So you can't judge a man just by the money he has.
Don't leave. I saved you.
You should treat me to meal or I can treat you to a meal.
- You are Lei...
- Thunder rolling in the sky—
(Thunder is "lei")
Thunder rolling in the sky, listen.
Scram as far away as you can!
Why are you so ungrateful? Won't your conscience hurt?
Gu Xiaoling! Listen well! From now on, I won't get involved in your business!
Otherwise, let there be thunder and let lightning strike me!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫