Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 1]
Excuse me. Let me pass.
- Hurry.
- All right, let's start.
[Marry Me]
♪ Always believed you would appear ♪
♪ in my life ♪
♪ Always sure that you're the love ♪
♪ I'm waiting for ♪
♪ Even if time is pressuring us,
or the pouring rain is drenching us  ♪
♪ Fate or destiny  ♪
♪ For you, I'm willing to do this a million times ♪
♪ Don't know if we could meet again in our next lives ♪
♪ In this lifetime, I just want to watch the scenery with you ♪
♪ Give the best of myself ♪
♪ To my dearest you ♪
♪ One day, we'll grow old ♪
♪ At least I'll have our happy memories ♪
♪ Our serious love is clearer than crystals ♪
♪ Loving you so much, ♪
♪ there's no room for anything else ♪
Kneel... and then give the flowers.
Yes, I will.
What are you doing? Where's the ring? When will I give it to Siyu?
In a bit, I'll put the ring in the drone. The drone will bring it to you.
- Then drone will bring it to me?
- Yes, yes take a look.
Everyone! Rest for a bit where you are now.
I have already looked at all the material about Zhang Yanzhou.
He values credibility and loyalty
but likes money as well, so I think we still have a chance.
You must get the ¥5,000,000 order back.
I'll try my best.
[Yiming]
Sister Yuan, who do you think leaked the price to Qiji?
I'm looking into it, too. I am not sure right now.
Find out who it was.
I'll definitely beat him up until he regrets living.
Don't worry. I'm more ruthless than you.
Just close the deal with Qiji and I'll treat you to a spa day when you get back.
Sister, they won't let us in because we don't have an appointment.
Sister, Feiyu's people just went in.
Sorry, you cannot enter without an appointment.
Hello, I'm from Beijing Feiyu Batteries. I have a meeting with Director Zhang of Qiji Group at 2:00 p.m.
- What should we do?
- We still have 15 minutes.
Give me all the materials.
[Yiming]
Hello, the number you called is currently busy.
Hello, I'm from Beijing Feiyu Batteries. I have a meeting with Director Zhang at 2:00 p.m.
I believe two of my colleagues have already arrived.
- Yes, that's right. Please come in.
- Thank you.
-  Can you help us just this one time? Please.
-  Sorry, I really can't.
- Learn Piano!
- Okay.
The subscriber you dialed cannot be connected right now.
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed cannot be connected.
[Yiming]
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Director Zhang.
- You are...?
- I'm from Feiyu.
Didn't we ask you to wait in the reception room?
Director Zhang went to the bathroom. He will be back soon.
- Thank you.
- Please wait a moment.
I think this is pretty good.
Brother Yiming, where is Sister Siyu?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
She went to the office around noon saying she had work and hasn't been answering my phone calls since then.
Such an important day, why didn't you have her take the day off?
I wanted to give her a surprise, right?
So I didn't give her any hints.
[Gu Xiaoling: I'm on the subway.]
Haowen.
- What's up?
- Siyu's younger sister is at the subway station. Go help me pick her up.
Send her WeChat to me. I'm the best at picking up pretty women.
What else?
Don't mess around.
Well that depends on whether she's pretty or not.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Hey, did you go to the wrong place?
No, I didn't. I'm looking for you. Hello, Director Zhang.
You are?
I'm Li Siyu, the sales manager of Lubao Batteries.
Qiji and Lubao have already ended their contract.
If you have any questions, you can contact the Legal Department.
Please give me 15 minutes, Director Zhang.
Thank you.
I can. Go make an appointment with my secretary.
If I was able to get an appointment, then I wouldn't be here blocking you.
Get out of my way.
Director Zhang, with Qiji electric vehicle's rate of sales and profit margin,
you can probably earn around ¥2,000 a minute.
But if you give me 15 minutes, I promise I'll help you make ¥50,000,00 more.
Listen here.
I won't do any more business with Lubao.
Maybe you'll change your mind in 15 minutes.
I'm calling security.
Once security gets the call, they'll have to come up from the first floor,
break this door open, and drag me out. It'll take at least 10 minutes.
That's fine, too.
Director Zhang, let's get straight to the point.
I never discuss business in the bathroom.
Then let's go to your office and talk.
Baby, what are you up to?
Remember to eat on time.
Baby, do you miss me?
Don't be angry. You'll get wrinkles.
Let me tell you. I discovered a really good restaurant.
Goddess...
Of course, I love you the most.
I'm in a meeting right now. I'll go look for you later.
Be good. I'm hanging up now. Bye-bye.
Yiming, I have no words to describe your sister-in-law's looks.
She doesn't look like Li Siyu at all.
Their parents remarried, they have a different mother and father.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I thought Li Siyu's little sister
would be a 7 out of 10 in terms of looks.
Whatever, whatever.
I rented a sports car for nothing.
Don't even think about hitting on her.
Otherwise, I wouldn't know how to explain it to Li Siyu.
Don't worry, I wouldn't want it even if it were free.
Oh! Warning.
I'll talk to you later. Your bro might experience something
with a goddess.
You...
- Hello?
- Hello—
Xiaoling?
You have 15 minutes. The countdown starts now.
Director Zhang, Yunhai's contract price was higher than yours by 1%.
The final execution price is 5% lower than ours.
This is our sales team's tradition.
For first-time customers, we give them all the sales commission as a thank you.
- We also did that when we signed the contract with Qili back then.
- I don't care.
Giving my competitor a lower price means being on bad terms with me.
This shipment of batteries has only 200,000 in total.
When it comes to both parties' cost and pricing,
there's basically no impact.
But this has hurt my trust in you guys!
This is our negligence. Before we signed with Yunhai, we should've
- notified you first.
- Enough, enough. Stop talking.
It's already too late to apologize.
Director Zhang, if we move up the delivery time,
can that make up for it?
I don't accept it.
Director Zhang, what if I listed you as a priority client for this product?
Sit back. My car is powerful. It can accelerate to 100 kph in 3.2 seconds.
It's been a long time since I drove this car. I always keep it at the club.
Actually, it's not like I can't keep it at home since it's a villa in the city.
You should know... The garage is small though, it can only fit three cars.
So I just switch off between those three cars.
[If you keep ignoring me, aren't you afraid that I'll run away with someone else?]
Turn on the air conditioning.
I really don't use this car very often.
[Brand New Product - Lubao 3rd Generation]
Lubao 3.0?
Lubao 3.0 not only can be produced ahead of schedule
but also outperforms all other batteries on the market.
Did you guys finally succeed in your research?
If you are the first to install Lubao 3.0
then the output value of Qiji's whole product line could increase by at least ¥50,000,000 next year.
- Price?
- We will definitely offer you the lowest price.
What about Yunhai Group?
Lubao 3.0's product line is newly developed.
The first three months' production capacity is only ¥10,000,000.
If Director Zhang places a ¥10,000,000 order,
then we won't be able to supply Lubao 3.0 to any other companies.
You not only want to get back that ¥5,000,000 order
- but also want me to place a ¥10,000,000 order?
- Yes.
Time's up. You can leave now.
Director Zhang...
Thank you, Director Zhang.
Sister Siyu, how did it go?
I didn't get the deal.
- Are you okay?
- Sister, hurry and sit.
I'm fine, just let me relax for 30 seconds.
- Xiao Tian, book me a ticket for the earliest flight to Guangzhou.
- Got it.
Xiao Jia, contact Yunhai Group's Purchasing Department.
Tell them that I need to see them as soon as possible.
Manager Li.
Director Zhang wants you to stay behind to discuss a few things.
Li Siyu's wedding ring.
This is way too small.
Xiaoling.
Rest for a bit. I'll go take a look.
- What's going on?
- I don't know!
What happened?
- What's the problem?
- I'm not sure.
Hubby, go take a look.
Hello, can you help me hold this for a bit?
Come on.
How long will it take you to fix it?
I'm also not too sure about that. Let me take a look.
How come you don't know anything? Can you fix it or not?
He's proposing today. It's his whole life's happiness on the line!
This is also my first time encountering this problem.
Quickly take a look!
Have you tested the endurance system?
No.
Check the endurance first, and if there are no issues with that then check the operating system of the platform.
If the platform is fine then there must be an error in the interactive system.
There's indeed an error in the interactive system.
Can you fix it in 30 minutes?
- I'll need at least 3 hours.
- Three hours?!
The sky will be dark!
Do you know why I'm against Yunhai?
Because Yunhai's two largest shareholders used to work for you.
When they left, they used unethical methods
to steal your core technologies at that time.
I have a batch of defective batteries.
Not many, just 100,000.
I hope that Lubao Group can help me transfer it to them.
If you get it done, then I'll personally give you ¥1,000,000 as a reward.
Director Zhang...
I'll give you one minute to think about it.
Director Zhang.
I've always admired you.
But it's not because Qiji Group's performances repeatedly hit new high records,
nor is it because of your place on the list of wealthy people.
It's because you've said before
that you want to create conscientious electric cars.
And I've always used that as motivation.
I want to be a conscientious salesperson
Well said.
A conscientious salesperson.
Have Director Liu meet with Feiyu's people.
Also, tell the heads of each department to come to my office.
Also, ask Manager Liu from the contract department to come.
No problem.
I'll continue with the ¥5,000,000 order from before.
In addition, I'll place another ¥10,000,000 order.
Brother Yiming, she's in Wuxi right now.
Wuxi?
Our company had a client suddenly cancel an order.
The company sent her to fix it.
Then will she be back in time?
According to what I know,
they will arrive at Hongqiao airport at 4:44 p.m.
Manager Li, why don't you eat before heading back?
Thanks, but my boyfriend is waiting for me.
Okay, then I won't keep you any longer.
But there's one thing I'm very curious about.
If I had rejected you just now, then what would you have done next?
Before your secretary came out,
I was booking a ticket to Guangzhou.
- To go to Yunhai Group?
- Yes.
- To sell the batteries that I canceled on to them?
But according to what I know, their purchasing plan for this year is already done.
I had to try, right?
After all, Lubao's quality is well-known.
In addition, we have your 10% cancellation fee.
If I offer that to them,
I feel that they would be interested.
Manager Li, have you considered changing your environment?
What you mean is...?
Come to Qiji.
Both the position and salary will definitely make you satisfied.
Do you want to switch to sell electric cars?
Yes. You're a very talented, outstanding salesperson.
Thank you for the praise, Director Zhang.
But... you're too greedy!
You just bought ¥15,000,000 of our batteries.
Do you want to poach the sales manager as well?
How about it? Think about it.
How about this? Once you've bought ¥200,000,000,
we can then talk about my indenture contract.
Okay, it's a deal!
It's a deal!
Oh no, something big happened.
I'm sorry, I was discussing some things with a client just now.
- Are you done?
- I'm done. Did you need something?
Yes, something very important.
But it's all been delayed.
Where are you? I'll go find you.
We'll talk later.
- Does your stomach hurt again? Do you want to take some medicine?
- Yes.
Sister, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Sister Siyu, I really admire you!
You really turned the tables!
Honestly, in our sales department,
whether it's talent, character, or work ethic,
if you were placed second,
then no one would dare to place first.
Where did you just place Sister Yuan?
Don't say nonsense.
I didn't think.
But Sister Yuan has been in charge of the sales department for more than half a year,
yet hasn't been officially appointed.
What's the situation?
You guys, stop thinking so much.
Sister Yuan becoming director will happen sooner or later.
That's right.
- Sister Siyu, we'll leave first.
- Sister Siyu, see you tomorrow.
Sorry, I wasn't purposefully ignoring your calls.
My phone was muted.
You know that there can't be an interruption in the mood when discussing business with a client.
As soon as I was finished, I gave you a call back.
Wow, all of my favorites.
Yiming,
how are you this caring?
- You are using a Ubuntu 15.04?
- That's right.
Delete the upgraded system and reinstall it. It'll only take forty minutes.
- Will that work?
- Try it.
Fine. If there's any other problem, don't blame me.
All right, you seem to know a thing or two.
It's just basic UAV knowledge.
What "AV"?
UAV.
"UAV."
Everything is ready, just waiting on the female lead.
OK.
Since you treat me so well, how do I repay you?
- Tell me, I'll agree to anything.
- Hey, hey.
I'm driving. Sit properly.
Let's go. Let's go home right now.
We can't. I've already prepared everything.
What did you prepare?
To go see a movie.
"To go see a movie"? A movie with a 5:00 p.m. showtime?
This movie has a limited showtime.
It'd be a shame if you miss it.
Okay!
Are you in a better mood now?
No. You played with my feelings.
Your phone was not muted.
It was busy the first time I called, and then you didn't pick up any of my other calls.
I was on the phone with Sister Yuan.
Even if you were on the phone with Sister Yuan, shouldn't you at least pause for a moment to tell me?
I was almost done talking to her.
You didn't call me back after you finished talking to her.
Didn't I tell you? I only had 15 minutes to talk with my client.
Oh, it was that intense? I thought you were clearing mines or something.
Believe whatever you want.
It's not that I don't believe you.
It just made me feel uncomfortable.
One moment the call went through,
the next moment you ended it.
When I called again, you ended it. There was even a busy signal once.
What are you trying to say?
I'm not trying to say anything.
It was just weird to me, and I was worried.
Was it weird or were you worried?
Worried.
I've told you many times,
I'm not a little kid. If I really ran into a bad guy, I'd know how to handle it.
What's there to be worried about?
Let's not be angry anymore. I was wrong, okay?
I should have given you a reply on WeChat.
Don't worry about me anymore.
I'll remember to reply to your WeChat messages from now on.
Let me tell you, I wasn't just worried.
I thought it was strange, too. What was going on?
I had prepared everything already. Then, without a word, you went on a business trip.
You even went to Wuxi! Not only did you not pick up my calls, but you even hung up on me.
Yiming, are you done yet?
What do you mean by "are you done yet"?
You always work overtime endlessly to accompany customers.
Your body can't stand it, either.
Aren't you just saying that you want me to quit?
Don't excite me. It's possible. My income right now is enough to take care of you.
I can take care of myself. Why do I have to depend on you?
Then you can at least get a less strenuous job, can't you?
- That's enough.
- Did I say anything wrong?
There's no wrong or right here. It isn't that you're worried about me, it's that you don't believe in me.
Are you just putting words in my mouth right now? From beginning to end, have I said anything about not believing in you?
Stop the car. Stop the car! I'm telling you to stop the car.
Siyu. Siyu! Siyu!
What's wrong with you?
- Why are you throwing a tantrum?
- I'm tired.
I want to go home and rest.
The— We haven't watched the movie yet.
I'm not in the mood today.
Sister Siyu, Xiaoling got into a fight with someone.
-  Stop fighting. Stop fighting.
- Xiaoling!
Stop fighting!
- Xiaoling! Xiaoling!
- You dare lie to me!
- Are you crazy!?
What are you doing?!
Xiaoling was bored waiting
so she asked the operator to teach her how to use the drone. The result is
that she saw this.
I can't tell if there if he lost control or if it was deliberate,
but the drone smashed Lan Ke's car.
Then Lan Ke's car hit the elder sister's car.
Xiaoling, Lisa, and Lan Ke started fighting.
Let me answer this call.
Hello?
This was supposed to be Brother Yiming's surprise proposal for you.
It was so romantic.
Zhizhi.
If you have other things to do, you can leave first.
It's fine. I'll wait here so that there's someone to take care of them.
Liu Yang, you guys head out first. I'll go find you later.
Okay.
Okay, I understand. Thanks.
Siyu.
Lawyer Liu called me back. It's best if we settle this in private.
But Lan Ke hit Xiaoling and pushed Zhizhi.
Didn’t Xiaoling throw the first punch?
How is it? Have you all thought about it? Will you accept mediation?
We're willing.
I got beaten up like this for no reason. I don't accept!
- If you didn't get involved, would I have hit you?
- Xiaoling!
We are at the police station and she's still so ferocious.
- I will sue you!
- Calm down!
Don't pull me!
That's enough.
Why are you getting all worked up?
- Xiaoling is Siyu's sister and you are my brother. We are a family. How can I not be worked up?
- Can you not cause more trouble?
- I want to go home! I want to go home!
- What's wrong baby?
- How about this? You take Liu Yang home.
- Then, what about Gu Xiaoling?
How could we let the child be at this sort of place?
- All right.
- Come on.
Why are you pulling on me?!
Do you feel like you have made a big enough scene out of the situation?
Don't they just want to sue? Do it then!
Do you want to have a record?  What about your job? How would you find a boyfriend in the future? How would your future in-laws look at you?
- Listen to me. Compensation is the best plan.
- I won't.
Are you going to listen to me or not?
Compensate how?
Are you going to listen to me?
Lan Ke, I used to wonder why Xiaoling liked you so much.
I finally know today.
I've seen your photo on Xiaoling's phone.
I thought you were pretty handsome.
But after seeing you in person today, I realized, hey,
you are better looking in person.
Come, sit and take your time to talk.
Lan Ke, since you and Xiaoling used to date,
let's forget about today.
Lan Ke, think about it.
If your father hears about today, what would he think?
He is a well-known entrepreneur. He probably especially hates your scandals, right?
Lan Ke was beaten in public to look like this,
where is our "face"?
(T/N: face is equivalent to dignity/respect/reputation)
Lisa, since today's events took place, Xiaoling and Lan Ke's relationship is completely over.
Who do you think will be Lan ke's next girlfriend?
What are you trying to say?
It was wrong for Xiaoling to hit you.
But it's a fact that you got in between their relationship.
Lan Ke and I are just friends.
The drone took the photo.
Lisa, as I remember, you are a live broadcaster. Right?
If someone uploads today's photo online, I wonder what your fans will say.
- Don't threaten me!
- I am not threatening you.
I'm being considerate of you.
If today's event gets blown up, then you, an internet celebrity, will be yelled at online.
That... would be a huge problem.
Lan Ke, I will listen to you.
I will do whatever you say to do.
All right, I won't pursue the assault,
but you guys are responsible for repairing our cars.
Sure.
Are you still at the police station?
Wait for me. I will go pick you up soon.
Want to relax?  I'll keep you company tonight.
Lisa! Thank you for getting rid of the garbage.
Let's go, Xiaoling. I will take you back.
Let's go.
If you knew this would be the result, then why did you do what you did?
- I don't need you to bother me.
- I just helped you take care of such a big mess.
Did I ask you to butt into my business?
- Let's go. Let me take you back.
- I don't want you to take me back.
Driver, be careful.
Zhizhi, let's go. We will take you back.
It's okay, I will take a taxi myself.
It's really nothing. We'll take you home on the way.
There's really no need.
Yiming, how's it go? Where is Xiaoling?
She went home.
How could you let her go home alone? She needs someone to keep her company right now.
Don't worry. She is strong.
By the way, Brother Haowen, are they home?
They are. Don't worry.
Is there an event? How come they are at home right now?
Yuwei was tired and fussing about going home so Liu Yang told me to take them home.
Damn it! That's not good.
- I have hurry and head back.
- What's wrong?
Today, we have a parent group meeting.
They said it's to discuss something very important.
It wasn't easy to finally get Yuwei in kindergarten.
We can't let others look down upon her.
Understood.
- I'm leaving. Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
Thank you for today.
You're not angry at me anymore?
I've always been weak. I can only be angry for two hours.
It's my fault. I didn't do well today.
I didn't control my emotions well.
I'm also at fault. I did not expect
that you would prepare
a limited-edition movie.
That's right, I—
I wanted to give you a surprise.
Turns out, not only was it spoiled
but I also turned a romantic movie into an action movie.
Siyu...
Yiming...
You don't want to continue showing the movie
at a midnight showtime, right?
I— Siyu, actually, I—
Do you really think we are ready for that?
You forgot to take this.
Thank you.
Can I call you "sister"?
Sister, I am really sorry.
Your car was hit, and we took up so much of your time.
- You can solve problems quite well.
- No,
I was just reasoning with them. Sister, how about we add each other's WeChat?
There's no need, right? I have your number. I'll call you if necessary.
That works. Once the 4S store determine the damage costs,
(T/N: 4S store means authorize car dealership that does sales, spare parts, service, and surveys)
- I'll pay what I need to pay.
- All right.
- Goodbye.
Actually, you are not ready, right?
What I mean is that...
It's the middle of the night...
and we're at the entrance of the police station. We just took care of the fighting situation.
Isn't it a bit inappropriate?
Besides, I hope that when I remember it in the future that it would be especially beautiful.
There wouldn't be so much mess like this.
All right. Then...
I will... pick another time.
But don't worry.
I will definitely give you the most beautiful moment.
Yiming, thank you.
-  Is she asleep?
- Yes.
Why didn't you go to the parents' group meeting?
Yuwei was so tired. If we went then she would have been fussing too much.
You should have still gone. It wasn't easy to get into kindergarten.
How could we just not go?
I have to submit an important report tomorrow.
If something goes wrong, a mere parents' meeting wouldn't make up for it.
Okay, okay. Report, report.
Is Gu Xiaoling's matter resolved?
With Sister Siyu and Yiming,
there's nothing that can't be solved.
Did Chen Yiming propose at the end?
- I don't know. I left first.
- Oh.
Back then, there were no roses
nor a diamond ring,
yet I stupidly got married to you.
You don't like those things anyway.
What kind of woman doesn't like those things?
Now all those are not important.
The most important now is our Yuwei.
Yuwei's education. Yuwei's kindergarten.
We cannot be absent from the parents' group meeting from now on.
Why are you at it again?
All right, all right.
[This is Shanghai.]
[Work hard for your dream]
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears.  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫