Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 39]
I'm tired. I want to rest.
Xiaoling.
Xiaoling!
What are you doing?
If you don't tell me today, then you cannot leave.
I don't want to talk to someone who is drunk!
Xiaoling, there are some things that I can't say unless I'm drunk.
Gu Xiaoling! I love you, Gu Xiaoling.
Can you get together with me?
Let me go!
But I do not love you!
I know.
I know that you don't love me.
You don't love me.
In your heart, there was never a place for me.
There wasn't in the past, and there isn't one now.
In the future, there won't be either.
Haowen,
I've always regarded you as one of my most important friends.
If I had any problems,
I wouldn't tell my boyfriend, but I would tell them all to you.
In my heart, you're not someone who doesn't matter,
but you've always known what type of man I've wanted to get married to.
This He Mu is the person I am determined to marry.
Come in.
- Manager Fang.
- What's going on?
The work proposal for next year.
You finished it so quickly?
[Work Proposal]
I took a look at the department's work proposals from the past few years and made a few adjustments.
The goal for next year is to increase the revenue made from the scenic area by 5%.
That's pretty good. You've worked hard.
And this is... what?
After looking at travel agencies, online and offline promotional channels,
I made another completely new work proposal.
You made two?
If we re-consolidate our marketing,
I'm sure that the revenue next year will increase by at least 80%.
You want everyone in our department to open channels?
That is my suggestion.
Everyone is in charge of one sector?
Also, have nighttime events?
That's my suggestion.
Xiao Ding, inform everyone that we will be having a meeting this afternoon.
We will be discussing Li Siyu's work proposal for next year.
Yes, everyone.
- Then I'll go make a few more copies.
- No, no, no.
Let's just make copies of this one.
This one is the old one.
We're going to discuss this one.
Why?
According to the company's plan for future developments,
we must consider market equilibrium as we are growing.
We must consider the five-year plan and the ten-year plan,
We also need to think about the benefits
of the employees and the company.
We also need to consider how to invoke employees' enthusiasm and motivation.
So, in consideration of the consistency of our work,
we should just discuss this one.
Siyu, you are very passionate,
but you're not mature enough.
Then, why did you have me make a useless proposal?
To get you to mature more quickly.
Hurry and go make copies.
You...
Li Siyu!
I will...
Siyu, why did you come back so early?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Siyu, let's go. Come fishing with me.
I don't want to go.
You must go.
Just go.
Dad, wait for me.
Okay.
Be careful.
You felt wronged at work, right?
No.
That workplace of ours... I know how it is.
Then, how come you stayed there all your life?
It was suitable for me.
With your personality, you don't fit there.
You definitely can't stand it there.
I offended Manager Feng.
Child,
you are not like me at all. You're just like your mother.
When I was young, I was pretty afraid of my mom.
I was also afraid.
I didn't want to be like her at all.
But at your core,
you are more like her than I am.
You are ambitious and don't accept defeat.
You are bellicose and serious.
Honestly, I came back this time
because I didn't want to be that version of myself.
That's not up to you.
The personality a person is born with
cannot be changed.
When you were young,
you placed third place for a test in the math olympiad once.
Your mother hit you and punished you by not letting you eat.
My heart ached for you,
so I secretly took you out for noodles.
I told you that from then on, you won't need to study for the math olympiad anymore.
Hey! You rejected me right then!
On one hand, you were saying that your mother is cruel,
but on the other, you were swearing to me
that "next time, I will definitely get first place!"
This situation...
A child like you,
may be beaten until blood drips from your head
and is definitely in pain;
however, if you are not allowed to go onto the battlefield,
to go fight and work hard, you'll feel even more pain.
Your point is that
I should still try my best to strive for what I want?
I didn't say you should do anything.
I'm just telling you what kind of environment your personality is suited for.
Go back. Go back to Shanghai.
I can strive for what I want here as well.
A few days ago, I just treated Old Zhai to dinner.
In the next few days, it looks like I'm going to have to treat Old Fang to dinner.
You... With your bellicose, serious personality,
if you stay for a few more days,
the good character and the likability that I've spent my life building
will all be ruined by you.
Dad!
In such a tiny place,
I meet acquaintances everywhere I go.
If you offend someone and your auntie and I go out,
we will be too ashamed to greet them if we see them on the street.
In Shanghai, it's different. Shanghai is huge.
If you offend someone,
and you can't stay in Xuhui District, then you can go to Jingan District.
If you can't stay in Jingan District, then go to Huangpu District.
Pudong District! You won't have to see them for the rest of your life!
But I want to spend more time with you.
If you could change your personality
and stop hitting or killing,
like me,
talking happily with anyone while keeping me company,
then, of course, I'd be happy.
But you cannot change.
You're sulking and unhappy every day.
I feel bad for you.
Let m-m-me make it clear.
I'm not trying to drive you away.
I just hope that you can find
a place to live that is more suitable for your personality.
That way, you will be happy!
Thank you, Dad. I understand.
I have goosebumps now.
Why are you being polite with me?
Dad,
I want to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
Did you ever love my mom?
Your mom was so outstanding,
who wouldn't love her?
Then how come after my mom died,
you got re-married in a matter of months?
After your mom died,
you were only 12 years old.
It's the time when you needed to be taken care of the most.
The age where you needed the most guidance.
At the time, I really didn't know how I was supposed to teach you.
It just so happen that someone introduced your auntie to me.
I remember the first time we met,
she asked me
what kind of flavors you liked.
Later, she made you lots of food for me to bring to you.
At the time, I was certain
that this woman would surely treat you well.
So, it was for me?
That's not completely it. It was also for me, too.
Your auntie happens to be the exact opposite of your mom.
She had absolutely no expectations for me.
Siyu.
I love your mom.
But to tell you the truth,
your auntie is more suitable for me.
Dad,
you actually understand everything.
I'm not stupid.
I'm just satisfied with what I have.
Honestly,
I've never forgotten about your mother,
but life must go on.
We're back!
How was the harvest?
Tonight, we're eating fish! Eating fish! Eating fish!
That's great!
- We didn't catch a single fish.
- This child.
You annoying old man.
Siyu, your Uncle Zhou called. He said if you were not happy at the marketing department,
then he can switch you to a different department.
There's no need, Auntie. I'm planning to go back to Shanghai.
Go back to Shanghai?
Don't look at me, it wasn't my idea. It was her own decision.
Here, here. Give this to me.
Is it because of Xiao Tang?
No. I just want to go back.
What's wrong with home?
Home is perfect in every way.
However, I can really put my skill to good use in Shanghai.
You said that you wouldn't leave.
I did.
At the time, I also thought I wouldn't leave;
but now, I finally know who I am,
what I want, and what places suit me better.
Just let her go. You won't be able to make her stay.
I understand, but...
Auntie,
thank you for taking care of me and my dad all these years.
What kind of words are those?
After I go back and work for a few more years,
and save enough money to buy a big house,
I'll bring you and my dad to Shanghai with me.
Then, you'll be able to see me and Xiaoling every day.
Okay.
Mom.
Mom!
Daughter.
Yes.
Dad.
Tomorrow, I will go back.
Okay.
Child,
if your mother was here, she'd definitely say
that you should go strive for what you want.
But I must say, you shouldn't care too much about success and failure,
winning and losing, and results.
Also, don't care too much about how much money you make or how big your house is.
Happiness is the most important thing.
Enjoy the process of striving for what you want.
Experience the joys of it.
That's the most, most important part.
I understand.
Come on.
Zhizhi, wait a second.
Niu Niu!
Niu Niu's mom, please help me look after her for a moment!
This is for you.
What is this?
When you open it, you'll know.
- Okay.
- I'm leaving now.
Be safe!
- Hello?
- Hi.
You never officially replied to the proposal I made to you,
and I'm afraid that you would think that I wasn't being serious,
so I bought this gift for you.
Are you proposing to me?
Yes.
Zhizhi,
please marry me.
Be my wife. Be Sushan's mother.
Let me think about it.
Okay. I will wait.
Okay.
You're back?
Yuwei!
It’s daddy and mommy!
Zhizhi, sorry.
[This is the first picture of us together. That year, you were 21 and I was 25.]
I remember the first time I met you, I felt you were especially pure and warm.
At that time, I thought that if I can spend the rest of my life with you,
I will definitely be very much at ease and happy.
My dream came true, we became wife and husband.
[Half a year later, we got married.]
I was too poor to hold a wedding ceremony then.
I couldn't even afford wedding photos with you.
But you didn't complain at all.
On the contrary, you told me that you were very happy and satisfied.
One year after that, you gave me the cutest daughter in the world.
[After Yuwei was born, our world of two became three.]
You gave me more new experiences. You made my life more complete.
Is that me?
However, I didn't cherish what I had.
I only saw my own busyness, ignoring your exhaustion.
I only felt my own stress but couldn't see your sacrifice.
Finally,
I made a huge mistake one day.
I didn't realize until the day I lost everything,
of what kind of happiness I had before.
Zhizhi,
I don't dare to ask for your forgiveness.
I only hope
that I can have a chance
to make up for what for my negligence towards you and the hurt I've caused you before.
I also don't dare to have wild hopes of us returning to the way we were before,
but I do hope that I can put double the effort into
giving you a future full of sunshine.
♫  Your voice is light and soft  ♫
♫  Forms the love I want  ♫
♫  Your eyes are innocent and clear  ♫
♫  like the ripples in the middle of a lake  ♫
♫  The world suddenly became quiet  ♫
Daddy!
♫  As if someone pressed pause  ♫
♫  How much luck did I exchange in order to meet you  ♫
♫  In this lifetime, I just want to tightly hold your hand  ♫
♫  As we slowly walk and slowly feel  ♫
Zhizhi,
although we met
a very long time ago,
it is only today
when I got to really know you and myself.
Zhizhi,
please marry me one more time.
Mommy, hurry and say yes! Hurry and say yes!
Liu Yang, stand up first. It's not good for Yuwei to see this.
Daddy and mommy, what's not good about this?
I just started working in my new position, so I'm very busy. I really don't have time to think about this.
You mean...
that you want me to...
give you a bit more time?
Then...
I'll leave this here for now.
Zhizhi,
no matter how long you need to think about this, it's okay.
I will wait for you.
No matter what decision you make,
I will accept it.
You guys rest early then.
Yuwei, I'm leaving now.
Bye, Daddy.
Listen to your mom.
Mommy, why didn't you say yes to daddy?
I don't know either.
Two men proposed to you on the same day.
Zhizhi, your charm is explosive!
I've never experienced this before.
At the beginning,
I couldn't even breath. Dong, dong, dong. My heart was flustering so much.
Who are you going to choose?
What do you think?
Pick the person who gave the bigger diamond.
However, Liu Yang is Yuwei's dad so that is an added point.
But...
I don't want to choose either one.
Why?
I feel like my situation right now is pretty good.
Although work is tiring, I'm at peace.
I also don't want to change.
Then you need to return both these diamonds.
What a pity.
What is there to pity? In the future, when I earn enough money, I can buy one for myself.
It's all the same, a marriage proposal.
Why doesn't He Mu gift me a diamond?
What did he give you then?
A miraculous device that helps you sleep.
What?
This thing. Super good at making me fall asleep.
Every time I turn to page 5, I'm unconscious.
Xiaoling, do you really think he is the one?
He has what I want and I have what he wants.
We are a match made in Heaven.
[Shanghai Long Distance Northern Bus Station]
Aren't you picking me up? Where are you? Where's your car?
I suddenly had work to take care of.
You are so unreliable!
I called a DiDi for you.
(TN: DiDi is China's version of Uber/Lyft)
License plate number.
Hu W N 1400
I see it.
Older Sister, what a coincidence!
What a coincidence! Let me help you.
Gu Xiaoling.
You are addicted to betraying me, aren't you?
He gifted me a set of Lancome. I couldn't reject him.
Gu Xiaoling!
There is a surprise!
You're a poor boy yet you bought a set of Lancome? Are you out of your mind?
Hey! That's the exact feeling! You haven't hit me for a long time.
I've been itching for it. Hit me some more.
You can't blame me. Why didn't you reply to my messages?
If you have that kind of money, why couldn't you buy some better clothes?
Why couldn't you buy a nice meal? Why couldn't you rent a bigger house?
Older Sister, why do you talk about money all the time? Aren't you a bit tacky?
If you have the time to spend on me, will it kill you to better yourself?
Will it kill you to go look for a better job?
But if there is no love, I'll die, Older Sister!
Find a girl your age! Wasting time and money on me, even if your heart doesn't ache, my heart aches for you.
I like challenging myself with someone like you.
Where are you taking me to?
We're almost there. We're almost there.
President Guan.
Why haven't you returned the car yet?
Where do I return it to?
The car rental company.
Older Sister, although you were born after 1985,
why do you nag like a person born after 1955?
Fuck off.
Guan Xiaotang, where on earth are you taking me to?
We're almost there. Be patient. It's just upstairs.
Let's go, let's go.
We're here.
Hello, President Guan.
Let me introduce you.
This is our company's Director Li.
Director Li.
This way.
What's going on?
[Siyu E-Commerce Company]
Come here.
This way. Let's take a look over here first.
This is the tea room.
It took a very long time for me to choose the wallpaper. Lately, I've been spending all my time on the renovation.
The renovation for this company just finished a few days ago. I haven't hired a lot people yet.
I even haven't decided on the main business yet. I've been waiting for you to decide.
What are you up to?
Everyone, stop working for a moment. Let me  make an introduction. This is our company's Director Li.
Hi, Director Li.
This way.
Let's go. This way.
How is it? This is our office.
You can choose either table. Do you like it?
What exactly are you up to?
Did you forget? I said that I would make a website for you.
Guan Xiaotang, where did you get this much money?
Did you borrow money from loan sharks?
I didn't. This was just the allowance my dad gave me.
Your dad collects junk, how much money could he possibly have?
The annual report he got last month says a few hundred million RMB.
RMB?
American dollars... he doesn't have the skills for that.
When you were eating dinner with my relatives, everything you said was true?
I've never lied to you before.
Didn't you pick up junk with your grandpa when you were little?
Yes. My mom
re-married so my dad left me at my grandpa's place when I was 2 years old.
I collected junk with my grandpa.
Didn't you say that your dad passed away from a car accident?
My dad did business for many years out there and didn't come home, so to me, it's like he passed.
When his business got bigger and he brought me to his side, I was already a teenager.
The transformer without the leg...
Yes. It was made by the pieces of junk I collected.
The car downstairs?
The present my dad gave to me for my eighteenth birthday.
Why did you come to work by bus then?
I like it.
Why did you live in your friend's place and freeload off them?
Older Sister! Older Sister, are you mad?
Older Sister.
I don't like people lying to me.
I never lied to you.
You make me feel very stupid.
You especially cute when you do stupid things.
If you don't like this company, then tell me what you like. I can gift it to you.
If I want something, then I will earn it myself.
I just want to give you a present to make you happy.
Do you know when I am the happiest? I'm happiest when I work hard for what I want.
I'm happiest when I insist and fight on despite repeated setbacks.
- I'm happiest when I win after going through all the difficulties. Do you understand?
- I understand!
- I like the feeling of surpassing others and overcoming myself. Do you understand?
- I understand! I understand—
No, you don't!
A rich second generation heir like you who opens a company as if you are just buying a toy will never understand!
Older Sister, why are you going through menopause again?
Guan Xiaotang, this is not what I want.
Okay. I'm wrong in this. I love you. That's not wrong, is it?
We're not suitable for each other!
I think we are quite suitable for each other!
I'm so many years older than you!
If you were the same age as me, then I would feel that you are superficial and stupid!
But I feel like you are superficial and stupid right now!
I will grow up.
Perhaps.
But I don't have the confidence and patience to wait for you to grow up.
If I become mature as soon as possible, will you love me?
People mature after they get hurt again and again.
Xiaotang, I'm afraid you don't have a chance.
Don't you feel that I'm being hurt right now?
If this is called hurt, then you-you really are too young.
Li Siyu, don't look down on me!
Li Siyu, I will definitely let you see me become super ripe!
(T/N: ripe = mature)
Wait! That day won't come too late!
It won't be long!
Why are you here?
I came to consult with Lubao's PR department.
They told me that you were also here so I came to see you.
How was it?
It was okay. But it was as you said.
Right now, Lubao's PR strategy is from ten years ago.
It's a bit out of touch with today's society.
Yiming, I will support you in whatever you do. What I want is the outcome.
But this isn't an easy job.
Otherwise, I won't have asked you for help so many times.
I definitely won't let you down.
Thank you.
I should thank you.
Why are you so polite?
Okay. I need to go back to the company. I'm leaving now.
What's wrong?
Nothing, I just want to take another look at you.
Enough. Stop being naughty.
I will leave now.
- Brother Yiming.
- Zhizhi.
What brings you here?
I came here for work.
How are you guys doing?
We're doing well. Well...
Nevermind.
Okay. That's good then. I'm leaving then.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Okay. Okay. See you. Bye.
Zhzihi, you lost some weight. But you look more energetic!
Really? Your complexion also looks better than before!
Look at me! Look at me! Look at me!
How is it? Do I look younger than before?
You are always the most young and beautiful one.
It's a pity that I have nothing else besides my beauty.
Here.
I don't drink sweet things.
Fussy.
Sister Siyu, I made plans with someone. I have to leave in a bit.
Okay.
Zhizhi, did you make plans with that Mr. Su?
Zhizhi, you have a boyfriend?
He doesn't really count as one.
He even proposed. How is he not?
I didn't agree to anything.
How is he?
He is a nice guy.
Then... do you love him?
What is love?
You stumped me.
When I first started dating Chen Yiming,
my heart rate would speed up and my palm would sweat.
My heart rate would speed up and my palm would sweat only when I go see clients.
With that Su Lixing, we are like an old couple.
We're not disgusted with each other when we meet up. But we don't miss each other when we're separated.
That's already very good. He Mu and I
don't miss each other when we are separated. We feel tired when we are together.
Then, are you still going to marry him?
Of course.
Although he is bored and inflexible, all of his other conditions are very good.
You guys told me to not be so picky; thus, I decided to listen to you two this time.
Xiaoling, you've changed.
I've just thought it through. Although I can't change him,
I can change myself. As long as I don't pursue perfection, he is the perfect one.
Those words make sense.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Ye... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫