Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 17]
My super-rich roommate called his dad immediately once he went back.
"Dad, my classmates all take the subway to school,
I'm the only one who drives a Ferrari." As soon as his dad heard that, he got anxious.
His dad said,
"Hey, son.
That's not good. We can't let the Europeans look down on us.
How much money is the subway? I'll send you ¥100 million right now. Is that enough?"
Really?
Of course, that's fake.
But Xiaoling, to be honest, the lifestyle of these foreign new money people,
make me, a Chinese rich guy, feel really shocked.
Really?
My goal right now is to work hard and earn money.
I eventually want to buy my son...
a subway.
Xiaoling,
when you smile, you look like the girl painted by Duffy Sheridan.
A little arty.
A little free and easy. But also a little cunning.
Really?
I want to give you a present.
What's is it?
When I was in the park this morning,
this leave dropped on me without any cause.
I was thinking at that time,
it is very much like you,
entering my heart without a reason.
So I decided that I must gift it to you.
Thank you.
I will treasure it very well.
[Lubao: New Energy]
Hello, sir. Are you here to look at cars?
Yes, I want to have a look at the cars.
Please come in and I can introduce them to you.
Are you guys even humans?
I was dumped! Originally, I thought I got Gu Xiaoling,
but she is ignoring me now.
Reply! Do you have any sympathy?
It's nothing.
Hello, sir. This is the latest Chinese new energy car.
It uses a Lubao battery. The battery life is very long.
It can go 410 kilometers. It's also very quick to charge the battery.
It only takes 1 hour to be fully charged.
This here is the production of chargers.
We put the counter electrode
into the battery pack,
then we put it into the water tank to conduct charge-discharge.
Compared with the old technique,
the container formation technique
greatly improves environmental protection.
President Wang.
Yes, Yiming.
What's this?
The valuation of Lubao company is on the higher side
mainly because the future outlook of Lubao 3.0 in the market is very good.
Right now, Lubao 3.0 hasn't entered the market on a large scale.
But I have already done research on the trial customers of Lubao 3.0.
This data can probably help you reevaluate
the future market prospect of Lubao 3.0.
Why did you think of doing this research?
Because I believe that you would need this in your next negotiations.
I also took a look at the evaluation of Lubao
by the Planning Department. I think it's not very accurate.
So I reevaluated it based on my experience.
This is my evaluation report.
[Market Value Investigation]
Yiming,
I remember I told you,
you don't need to take part in this project.
But...
I want to let everyone know
that I'm the Planning Director of Tianye Group now.
I have the responsibility and duty to prove my ability
and professional integrity.
Afterward, I examined
Lubao Group's series A funding.
Towards Pan Zhiyong's personality and mentality,
I have made a rough analysis.
Please take a look.
I think it can help you negotiate with him more smoothly.
Yiming,
you are not only well qualified for this position but you have also gone beyond my expectations.
Thank you, President Wang.
I will go back to work now.
Come on.
Thank you for everyone's hard work. A toast to everyone!
Mr. Liu, once the work for the bid is done,
your appointment as Deputy Director will be officially announced. Right?
Definitely! Yes!
What are we waiting for now? Let's celebrate with Mr. Liu together!
Come on!
Congratulations!
That matter is not settled yet.
Drink up first!
Right! Drink it.
I will drink,
but don't spread those words around.
- Got it!
- Bottoms up!
Excellent!
It's so late already, why hasn't Liu Yang come back?
Mom, he is an adult and he knows his own mind. He will be fine.
How about you call him?
If anyone were to make a call, it should be him calling home.
Mom, I need to work tomorrow. I'm going to bed first.
The work for the bid is not done yet.
We need to continue working hard.
Let's strive for the final success!
Mr. Liu, success! Drink for another around!
Sure!
Come on!
Brother Yang, don't drink so much.
We all call him Mr. Liu.
You call him Brother Yang. That is a different kind of relationship.
Let me tell you!
Wei Yayun is my younger sister.
You guys are not allowed to bully her.
No, we don't dare!
Yayun,
let's drink.
You two must! Get closer.
Drink!
Drink up. Drink up.
Cheers!
Thank you!
Brother Yang, I should thank you.
Wait. You two wait.
Let's have a “cross-armed drink”.
Crossed-arm drink! Crossed-arm drink!
Crossed-arm drink! Crossed-arm drink! Crossed-arm drink!
- Crossed-arm drink!
- Did I just say that you can't bully her?
Crossed-arm drink! Crossed-arm drink!
Come on!
Bottoms up!
Crossed-arm drink! Crossed-arm drink!
Hello, the subscriber you dialed is temporarily unavailable.
Yayun, are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
We'll leave Mr. Liu to you.
Sure, don't worry! Bye!
Brother Yang,
are you all right?
Sister Yun, I'm sorry.
What are you saying, Brother Young?
Slowly. Slowly.
Brother Yang, let's sit for a bit.
Be careful.
Sister Yun,
do you know?
Today, I just wanted to be with you alone.
The bidding job
has been conducting smoothly.
You have made undeniable contributions.
Brother Yang,  you regard me as an outsider if you say this to me.
Brother Yang, you—
Why are you looking at me like that?
Sister Yun,
you're so beautiful.
Are you guys waiting for car 6745?
Yes.
Let's go.
Careful.
He's finally called.
Hello?
Is it Auntie?
I'm Mr. Liu Yang's colleague.
He's drunk. I'm bringing him home by cab.
Okay. Thank you. Thanks.
It's nothing.
Could you please tell me the address?
Jingcheng Road, no.85, the south building.
Thank you so much.
It's no trouble.
We're almost there.
Why are you drunk like this?
- Mom!
- Aunt!
Oh my god.
We've just finished our preliminary work. Mr. Liu Yang is very happy so he drank a little more than normal.
You should prepare some honey water for him when you guys get back and don't let him get cold.
All right. Thank you.
Mom! Let me introduce her to you.
This is my colleague Xiao Yun.
Xiao Yun is really nice.
Hey!
Careful.
Be careful, Brother Yang. I will help you clean the jacket.
No need. It's okay.
Look. Your shirt is also got dirty.
Do you want to clean it upstairs?
No need. I can clean it when I get home.
This is Mr. Liu Yang's bag and phone.
I'll take my leave, Auntie.
Okay.
I won't take you home then.
It's nothing.
Next time when we get the chance,
we'll celebrate alone.
I got it.
Brother Yang, have a good rest.
- I'm leaving now.
- Bye!
Sorry for not seeing you out. Thank you.
Hurry up.
Sorry for not sending you off.
Why did you drink so much?
I'm happy!
Why are you so happy?
Let's see how you are going to explain it to your wife.
Come help me.
Slowly, slowly.
I want to drink water.
Quickly get some water for him.
Zhang Zhizhi!
I'm going to be promoted to Deputy Director very soon.
You will be the wife of a director!
Yang, are you really getting promoted to Deputy Director?
This is great!
Give him water to drink.
Do you know...
during these years,
how much I've put up with
and how much I've suffered?
But...
you just need to bite your teeth and you'll persist.
That's how I got my accomplishments.
You, don't be so sensitive.
Don't be troubled anymore.
Just live your life well.
Yuwei!
What are you doing?
I need to tell Yuwei this good news.
The kid is asleep.
I can just wake her up.
Who does that as a father?
What's wrong with a dad like me?
What I do, I do wrong as a dad?
Let me tell you!
I'm the most capable dad in the world!
I'm the most capable husband in the world!
I'm the most capable son in the world!
What on earth are you trying to do?
I want to ask Yuwei if I'm the best dad in the world.
I want to ask her if I...
Just go be your director.
Mom!
What's wrong? Baby, go to sleep.
I want dad.
Dad is not back yet.
Wash up.
What kind of wife is she? Why did you marry this wife?
She doesn't know how to take care of her husband. She doesn't care about her husband either.
Look at this. Come on. Let's sit up, son.
Liu Yang...
Brother Yang, the moment you kissed me, my heart
was already forever with you.
[Delete]
Are you done? Let's go.
Here.
Dad and Grandma, bye!
Okay, okay. Bye!
Be careful on the way.
I'm heading to work now.
Sit down.
What's up?
Who was the girl who sent you home last night?
My colleague.
Colleague?
From what I see, you care a lot about her.
It's just a normal colleague.
Let me tell you.
Even though I'm not very satisfied with Zhizhi,
she is your wife after all.
Also, there's Yuwei. You need to have integrity.
You can't do any wrong to her. Do you hear me?
I got it. I got it.
I'm going to work.
I don't know what I did yesterday. Did I offend you?
Brother Yang, you didn't offend me.
On the contrary, I feel very happy.
I finally know that we share the same feelings.
No. No. No. You may have—
Maybe I made you misunderstand something.
As long as you allow me to love you, I don't care about anything else.
That is impossible.
I have a family.
I can do anything for you.
Everyone is watching us at work.
-We—
- I understand.
I understand.
Don't worry.
You can call me Brother Yang. I can call you Sister Yun.
That's it.
That is where the boundary is.
Are you trying to lose weight? You are getting so much to eat.
This Wolong nut is low fat and also tasty. I eat it for breakfast.
Liu Yang and I are going to play basketball together. Will you come over? Is there anything you want me to tell him?
I'm with Zhizhi. There's no need.
Say, he is an art curator
and has his own art investment company so he must be rich. Right?
We have known each other for over a month now,
yet he either gives me a leaf or a stone as presents. He even went further the other day. He gave me a button.
Button?
He took it from his old shirt. He said the button knows his heartbeat so he gave that to me.
- It's quite romantic.
- But I'm not interested in romance.
I like the practical and trending thing. It's even better if it preserves its value. Even if it's tacky, it's fine.
What kind of method is there for me to hint at him?
Just tell him directly.
That won't do. My persona right now is a chic and refined female artist.
Hey, you got so many drinks. Can you finish them?
These are like fresh juice. I can take my time to drink them. Artists like me need this.
I obviously like money yet I have to pretend not to like it. Don't you think it's hard for me?
I think you should properly expose your true nature of worshiping gold.
I'm afraid I will scare him away.
If he has money, he won't be scared away. If he is scared away, then he definitely doesn't have money.
That makes sense.
Hello. Do you have a membership card?
Zhizhi, membership card.
(What's wrong?)
Zhizhi.
Zhizhi, has Liu Yang been bullying you lately?
What's wrong?
I pick up Yuwei every day.
Whenever I see them, I feel disgusted.
I feel so upset.
I really want to curse at someone. Zhizhi, you are hopelessly stupid.
Gu Xiaoling, shut up!
But, Zhizhi,
we have to transfer schools. Definitely transfer. Must transfer.
Liu Yang opposes it strongly.
He thinks that I'm sensitive, I'm making trouble for no reason, and I'm wasting money.
It's nothing to do with the money. It's also not about being sensitive. It's your dignity.
That's what I think, too, Sister Siyu. But I can't explain it clearly.
How come you can't explain clearly? You are just hopelessly stupid. You don't have—
Look at that kindergarten! Full of snobbish people. What good will your daughter learn from it?
Zhizhi, I'm going to say something you may not want to hear.
I think it was wrong for you to transfer Yuwei to this high-end kindergarten in the beginning.
At that time, I was thinking
that as a parent I should give my kid a better environment.
I have to send my kid to a higher class.
Then, have you thought about if the higher class will accept you or not?
Transfer Yuwei back.
Even if you will lose about half the tuition money, the school here
will be cheaper, right? You can work it out.
More importantly, nobody will look down on you. Nobody will bully you.
You also don't need to please anyone.
I will go through the process of transferring schools tomorrow.
In my opinion, Liu Yang is wrong in this matter.
Hey. Don't stir up trouble.
How am I stirring up trouble? His wife was bullied by others, yet he can just let it go?
It's good enough that you don't get bullied. You're always trying to get into the rich people circle every day. Which one of those people are not snobbish?
I just don't understand.
I've already successfully persuaded Gu Xiaoling to move into a house one alley from me.
From a psychological perspective, I should be her male best friend. Right?
Say, why is she still dating some curator?
Generally speaking, once you entered the friend zone, for the rest of your life,
- you won't have a chance.
- Why?
Give me the ball!
Boyfriend, from my perspective, is to layup.
A male best friend is different. It's a three-pointer. Even though it's further from the backboard,
once you make the shot,
3 points!
I advise you to give up.
Why should I?
She is so good-looking.
Haowen, don't be obsessed with looks.
Look more at the inner beauty of the girl.
Her shallow inner beauty
matches my flatulent personality very well.
Why did you sigh?
Xiaoling is right. What hurts me the most is
that I have given so much to this family and Yuwei. It's fine that he doesn't understand.
But when I am the most hurt, not only did he not care nor support me,
but he also thinks it's not an issue at all.
- You brought this on yourself.
- Xiaoling!
Look at you. You are reluctant to spend money on clothes. You use the cheapest skincare products.
You're even reluctant to take a taxi when you go out.
You don't even prioritize yourself. How could you expect a man to treat you like treasure?
Are you done stirring up trouble? It's not easy for Liu Yang as well!
He has to be cautious at work.
He has to make some accomplishments while not offending people.
He earns a fixed salary. How many problems does he need to fix?
What Xiaoling says makes sense as well.
Women can't give all of themselves to men.
You also must pay some attention to yourself.
From now on, don't care about anything.
Don't care about Liu Yang or Yuwei.
Just make yourself beautiful. I can guarantee that Liu Yang will circle around you.
Yuwei is just a kid. How can I not care for her?
Also, after having a family, I don't even know where so many problems have come from.
Don't listen to her. Just being pretty is useless.
The best solution is to have your own career. Then you won't be overlooked by your husband.
I understand everything you've said. It's just...
I want to dress up. I also want my own career.
But after having a family and a kid, you can only imagine those things.
As long as you are willing, nothing is impossible.
You can apply to go to the Sales Department tomorrow. I will train you personally.
Let me think about it.
You can't figure out why she thinks this way.
It's very simple. I can just explain it clearly to her.
I'm get exhausted at work every day.
After I get home, she troubles me with everything.
If she isn't arguing with my mom, then she is giving me the silent treatment.
I'd prefer working overtime rather than going back home now.
I read a book recently. The core thinking is
never try to reason with your wife. You have to influence her with emotion.
How?
For example, be more considerate. Think of her.
Whatever she needs, do it for her.
- Gu Xiaoling needs money. Can I afford it?
- That's why
you and Gu Xiaoling are not well suited.
Liu Yang,
don't listen to him. It's very crucial for you now. You are about to get promoted.
Your backyard can't have a fire. There can't be any problems, or else everything will be a mess.
Yiming and Siyu are so nice. You have similar goals and work hard together.
You guys also have a lot of topics to talk about together.
Actually Siyu and I also have many problems.
What problems?
We think differently about many things.
Can't we rest for a moment?
It seems that I was right to not get married in a rush.
You are not the same. Yiming is so in love with you.
Let's talk about you and Liu Yang. Let's talk about my parents.
They also got married because of love.
But my mom only passed away for a few months and my dad got remarried.
Weren't your dad and my mom happy together?
Yes. I'm happy for him.
But because he is very happy now,
I feel sad for my mom.
You are hurting me a lot saying those words.
Sensitive.
It's you who is obviously sensitive.
If Aunt were alive, Aunt and Uncle would be living together very well.
But she is not here anymore. You can't stop Uncle from starting a new life forever.
But it's just too quick!
It was so fast that it makes me suspect
that everything between him and my mom was fake.
So, you think Chen Yiming's love for you is also fake?
No, Yiming's love for me is definitely real.
- But that doesn't eliminate that in the future—
- You...
are just dramatic. Who can be certain about the future?
Chen Yiming becoming a playboy and Liu Yang cheating are all possible.
You can't deny the current relationship because of an uncertain future.
You have finally said something useful.
I have more.
You say Liu Yang is not easy.
In order to marry you, Chen Yiming went through great pains. Was it easy for him?
I didn't say I wouldn't get married.
- You don't fear marriage anymore?
- I do!
But...
as long as I get married, I can defeat the fear of marriage.
- Hello?
- Yiming.
Tomorrow, let's go to the realtor's and
sign the contract for the house.
Didn't you want to look at more?
- I changed my mind. I want this one.
- Good.
Come on.
- Nice!
- Thermos thermal mug. Keep your stomach and your heart warm.
Thermos thermal mug! Warm your stomach and your heart!
Bro, buy one for someone you want to give warmth to.
Bro, the days are about to get cold. Consider buying one.
It's very cost-effective to use as a gift or to have for personal use.
Thermos thermal mug! Warm your stomach and your heart!
Thermos thermal mug! Warm your stomach and your heart! Brother.
- How much is it?
- This is a German brand.
They're usually ¥300 to ¥400, but there's a promotion today, so they are only ¥268.
Yes, that's how you write it.
- Write it ten times, okay?
- Okay.
Mom, didn't I throw this in the trash can?
I fished it back out.
It's expired. We can't eat it anymore.
It's fine. It's only been expired for a few days. It not a big deal.
We still can't eat it.
If you guys don't eat it, then I will.
It's not like you're rich, throwing everything away.
Let me see what you wrote.
- Yang, you're back?
- Yes.
You came back quite early today. Give it to me.
Come eat.
The food we saved for you is still warm.
Sit, sit.
Dad, my pen isn't working!
If it's not working, you can get a pen from my bag!
Mom! Look what this is!
It's a thermal mug.
Such a pretty thermal mug, who... who did you buy it for?
It's for Zhizhi.
There's not much food left. Let me make you some sweet and sour pork.
Okay.
Vegetables went up in price again. Yesterday, potatoes were just ¥2.99,
and today they've raised it to ¥3.59.
Didn't Mom say her leg is hurting? I want to buy her a therapy knee pad.
I inquired about the brands.
There's a promotion going on in the next two days.
How come you're not using the new thermal mug to drink?
I can't bear to.
It was more than  ¥200. What do you mean you can't bear to?
¥200 is too expensive. Where did you buy it?
- A store next to the subway station.
- Where's the invoice?
- I threw it out.
- That store
sells things at much higher prices than online.
Since I bought it for you, just use it.
Oh, right. Today,
I did the paperwork to transfer schools for Yuwei.
This time, it was my fault for losing us so much money.
I'm glad I corrected myself, so we wouldn't lose even more
and I know I was wrong. This kind of thing won't happen again.
You were right. We are not in the same social circle as those other people.
Yet, I forcefully joined them resulting in me
being upset.
Everything else is unimportant.
As long as you've thought it through, then it's fine.
There's something else.
Sister Siyu wants me to go to the Sales Department.
Forget about it.
Why?
Think about it. After a while, I will be the deputy director.
I'll be busier than I am now.
If you really transfer to the Sales Department, you'll be leaving early and coming back late.
What would happen to Yuwei? Who would take care of her?
If we gave her to Mom, would you feel at ease?
Besides, I know about Siyu's situation.
Even Chen Yiming often says that he can't tolerate it.
We probably couldn't either.
That's true.
I think that the Administration Department suits you well. Even though the salary is not very high,
it is an easy job and there are regular hours.
You don't have to worry about earning money. I'm here.
But women need to have their own careers as well.
I'm your career.
Yuwei is your career.
Don't think about too much.
Let's just steadily live our days.
Mr. Wu! Mr. Wu.
I checked all of the companies that were qualified,
- and guess what I found?
- Tell me.
My middle school classmate's husband works at the R&D Department at Lubao.
This is a picture that I found in his Wechat Moments.
Is there something a problem?
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Isn't this the same person?
- Isn't that Liu Yang's wife?
- That's right.
Her name is Zhang Zhizhi. She's in the Administration Department at Lubao.
I found out that she and the person who submitted the bid for Lubao, Director Li,
are cousins.
That's wonderful!
Mr. Wu, how about tomorrow morning,
we report this to the director?
This time, Liu Yang is doomed.
Don't be anxious. Let me think about it.
What if Liu Yang already told the director about their relationship?
Even if he didn't,
Liu Yang was only responsible for the preliminary work.
The people who make the official decision are experts.
Liu Yang can still get himself out of trouble.
Then we'll find a way to make him unable to do so!
Xiao Zhao, you have finally gotten smart.
I was forced to after working in reception.
We must be smarter than the first two times.
We can choose not to, but if we do it,
we must make sure we don't fail again.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫