Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 40]
Xiaoling, you've changed.
I figured something out.
Although I can't change him, I can change myself.
As long as I don't pursuit perfection, he is the perfect one.
That makes sense.
CEO Wang.
- I poured water for you.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Chinese medicine.
- Tomorrow, I will send the contract over to you.
Okay.
She is like the previous you more and more.
Everyone is changing.
Only you're the one going in circles.
Why do you say this?
Nowadays, when dating, who cares about the age gap?
Look at others. Too many people.
You are talking about Guan Xiaotang?
Yes!
Look at him. He's generous, sweet, and easy-going.
He is also good looking.
He is even considerate. He bought nuts for you to supplement extra nutrition for you.
You rejected him! You are even using it.
First, that is called "not using things."
Second, I rejected him is not because of his age.
Then why?
He is not the one.
Who do you want?
You still want Chen Yiming?
Xiaoling.
It's okay. She mentioned him just now.
It's okay. I recovered already.
That's good.
It's really in the past?
The business goes up and down.
So do relationships.
Life goes up and down.
Everything happens for a reason.
The point is what to do next.
What do you plan to do?
Keep on.
Keep on being myself.
I need to leave first.
Sister Siyu, I will treat you a meal next time.
Take it. Eat it on the way.
You are too busy to even drink water.
I don't have enough time.
Before you were like this.
You were like the previous Zhizhi more and more.
Seize the moment?
Parenting book?
You even read parenting books?
To get prepared.
Why?
No why.
I don't agree.
I'm asking for your opinion.
I'm informing you.
But you should have a reason, right?
It's normal for a company to reduce its staff.
Even if the company needs to reduce staff, she is not the one you should reduce!
She pointed out to fire her.
Who is she?
President Wang?
Why? Why does she do this to Zhizhi?
I don't know.
Since this woman came to Lubao, shit happens one after another.
Huizhong...
You are afraid of her. I'm not. She can fire me as well.
Huizhong!
You put on the number? It'll be easy to put them in the other place.
This one. Remember to handle gently.
I get it, Brother.
- Brother Yang.
- You came back!
I have been back for a few days.
Hey...
No need. Are you moving?
Yes. Because we have had no breakthrough in the laboratory,
the school wanted Professor Gao to change his research direction.
Professor Gao didn't agree so he quit.
Then your experiment?
Professor Gao sold the house to continue. But now all the money has been used up.
The school hopes that we can empty the lab.
So we have to move out.
How about you?
Me? I will move with Professor Gao for sure.
Brother Yang, sorry.
It was all my fault. If it was not me,
you wouldn't have lost your job.
No need to apologize.
I'm doing well now.
But Zhizhi and you have come to this point.
It's nothing to do with you.
It was all my own fault.
Brother Yang,
I came here today to apologize to you first.
Second, I want to restart work for my old industry.
So I came to consult you about
the latest trend in the battery industry.
If talking about this topic,
you should ask Professor Gao. He has a more comprehensive idea than me.
But you know him. Sometimes he thinks differently than others.
I want to listen to different ideas.
Siyu?
President Wang.
You didn't change. You are the same as before.
I think you are also like before.
Is Professor Gao here?
I want to see him.
Go inside, please.
Wait a minute. Excuse me.
Can't go.
I can't get through.
You said two days! It has been three days now!
It's been so long! You haven't finished!
Excuse me. We have been moving, soit's a bit messy.
Take a seat, please.
Professor Gao.
What's up? Say it quickly.
If you don't talk, then leave quickly.
I'm annoyed now.
I came here to meet you. Do you remember?
I remember. You want to buy 60% of my shares with ¥20,000,000.
Your memory is really good.
How much do you plan to offer this time?
Ten million.
Less than last time.
Professor Gao, time changes.
Two years ago, many people looked to further increase their knowledge in membrane-less batteries.
But now,
even your university stopped the project.
It means that not many people are thinking positively about this project.
It's not promising.
It's my biggest sincerity to offer ¥10,000,000.
Since it's not promising, why did you come here?
I admire you!
Don't!
If you really admired me,
you should offer 500 million.
Professor Gao, if the money is mine,
there is no problem for me to offer 500 million.
But it's the shareholders' money.
I can't spend it freely.
Professor Gao, I know.
You have spent all your money on this project.
Now you are moving the lab.
Is it because you can't afford the rent?
Is it your business?
Are you hardhearted enough to waste
all your previous efforts?
Professor Gao, as long as you sign,
¥10,000,000 will be sent to you right away. You can continue researching.
Liu Yang, walk the guest out.
Professor Gao, I'm offering timely help.
President Wang, you were never a person offering timely help.
You are good at looting a burning house.
Siyu, do you have some misunderstanding with me?
Misunderstanding?
Others probably. It's difficult for me to
misunderstand you.
I understand.
You don't feel happy about Yiming and I.
Chen Yiming has nothing to do with me.
You and Chen Yiming has nothing to do with me, either.
Oh...
You have problem with me because of Lubao?
Siyu, it's like this.
People have different identities.
Take me as an example. I am your friend.
But I'm also Lubao's chairman of the board and general manager. I have to be responsible for all the shareholders—
Stop.
If you were me, you would do exactly the same.
I wouldn't.
Why are you still here?
Siyu,
let me teach you one lesson.
Offering timely help and looting a burning house
are the same thing with different perspectives.
I will teach you today what is "offering timely help."
Professor Gao,
I'm donating all my property to your lab.
Without any extra conditions.
Are you feeling wronged and acting rashly with me?
Yes! I want to grab your limelight!
You should change your impulsive problem.
I can't change it for my whole life.
Siyu, I tell you out of my utmost kindness.
If you want to compare with me, you are not even close.
Your money is even not enough for their pocket money.
You want to invest? You want to steal my limelight?
You keep it to save your life. You will pay for your impulsiveness.
I'm not afraid.
Are you done?
Professor Gao, it seems today is not a good time.
Let's talk another day without miscellaneous freeloaders.
Sorry for not walking you out.
Who are you?
I'm Li Siyu.
I'm Liu Yang's friend.
Hi.
I listened to your lecture before.
Yes?
You really want to donate the money to my lab?
I've said this and I took out the card.
Can I still take it back?
Oh my.
Thank you.
It's great. I really appreciate it.
That's great!
How much is it?
More than ¥50,000.
Thank you.
It's not even enough for the electricity bill.
How much do you need?
¥5,000,000.
Professor Gao, why didn't you say yes to Wang Ziru?
She wants to spend ¥10,000,000 to buy 60% of my shares.
She was insulting my research and IQ.
The ¥5,000,000 you said means?
I've found the breakthrough.
As long as I have ¥5,000,000, within 1 year,
my battery will work.
Professor Gao, take this money to pay the electricity bill.
I will collect the rest of the ¥5,000,000.
What do you mean? Tell me what you want?
Professor Gao, do you know why your lab is driven into a corner?
You don't lack scientists. But you lack people like me
who knows the battery and business well.
From today on, I don't want your salary. I'm joining your team officially.
I'll collect the money for you and guarantee your experiment especially.
But the whole industry doesn't look to our further increase.
Wang Ziru came to buy you for the second time.
This woman won't do anything if it's not profitable.
She offers such a low price. It means that she knows it's very risky.
Didn't Professor Gao say he had found a breakthrough?
During the last 10 years, I found a breakthrough 127 times.
But I found that...
these breakthroughs are dead ends.
This time will probably be like this.
So what?
Maybe the ¥5,000,000 you collect will be down the drain.
I have experienced this. I don't fear this at all!
I will call you back later.
Zhizhi,
the HR has informed you?
Sister Yuan, am I really bad?
Zhizhi, you are very capable.
Also, you never dragged the sales department down.
I have been working in this industry for over ten years. I've trained so many people.
Your comprehension and capability are at the top 3.
Then why?
No one has been sacked. Only me.
It is said this was a direct order from the board.
The board?
President Wang.
Yiming,
- am I late?
- No, you are just on time.
Tell everyone, President Wang is here. Get ready.
President Wang, you need to accept two prizes today. One is the Top 10 Battery Company of the Year.
The other one is the Annual Trustworthy Product of the Client.
After you accept the prizes, there is a press conference. I invited around 30 reporters from different media agencies.
So many?
If you want me to increase Lubao's valuation, we must do this.
Give the marker to President Wang.
Take a photo.
Show me the photo.
Okay. It's good.
If I knew this, I would have asked President Fang to come.
President Fang is attending another forum. That's also very important.
Tell them the guest is ready.
The guest is ready.
Yiming,
I need to tell you something.
What's wrong?
I visited Gao Zhengdao.
Gao Zhengdao?
That battery expert who rebels against orthodoxy?
Yes. Guess who I met?
Liu Yang? He is professor Gao's student.
Oh, that's how they know each other?
Yes. You want to work with Professor Gao?
Yes. I wanted to buy his lab with a high price.
But I was rejected harshly.
Why?
Because of Li Siyu.
She came back?
Siyu has a deep prejudice with me.
Because of me?
How about this? I can ask Liu Yang to try to talk to Professor Gao.
Okay. Thank you.
No need.
It's the Party B's job to share the Party A's trouble.
The guest, prepare to enter.
Okay. Ready.
Yiming,
all of sudden, I'm a bit nervous.
Let me share my experience with you.
When you get nervous, think about some happy things, you can overcome it.
Really?
Let me think about it. What happiness do I have recently?
I love you.
Happy?
Very happy.
Let's go.
Open the door.
Let's welcome the award-winning guest, Miss Wang Ziru.
Say...
- It‘s because—
- Mom!
It's because I'm Sister Siyu's cousin so they fired me.
-This reason—
- It's nothing.
I worked in a company before. Because the staff's Chinese zodiac sign doesn't fit the boss's,
they fired him directly.
But I just got the hang of my job.
I need to start over again.
It maybe a good thing.
Good thing?
The company informed me they will send me to work in Europe for five years.
Five years?
When do you leave?
As quickly as next month.
Then it's just in a few days.
Yes.
Zhizhi,
I want to take you, Sushan and Yuwei to go together.
- Me and Yuwei?
- Yes. It's okay to take the family with me.
Also, the company will subsidize the family expenses every month.
The four of us will live happily in Europe.
- Well...
- I know.
To you, it may be difficult.
When I received the news,
I also didn't know what to do. I know you like your job.
I'm also not sure if you will give up your job for me.
But now it's a coincidence that it happened.
Maybe... it's destiny?
Destiny?
The heavens want us to be together.
It's okay. Don't think too much.
The ugly little duck walks out of the bushes and raises his wings
and quickly found out that its wings were full of power.
He flew to the central lake and looked at his reflection.
He was surprised to find that he was no longer that ugly duckling.
Instead, he became a beautiful swan.
The ugly duckling became a swan?
Okay, that's enough for today.
Tomorrow, we continue.
Go to sleep now.
Yuwei,
I want to ask you
would you be willing to study abroad?
Together with Sushan?
I am willing!
I know now.
Go to sleep.
Here.
You want me
to invest in Gao Zhengdao's membrane-less battery study?
Not unless my brain turned to liquid.
It's just ¥5,000,000. It's just a small sacrifice for you.
You still owe me ¥3,000,000 that you never returned!
So that's why I'm trying to make investments everywhere!
Li Siyu, if this was your own project, I could've taken it into consideration.
But Gao Zhengdao? No way am I investing.
Why not?
First of all,
I am a representative of membrane batteries.
I have always blatantly opposed membrane-less batteries.
Second,
Gao Zhengdao? Him?
He and I are absolutely incompatible.
Guan Zhong and Bao Shuya had their own masters.
(T/N: Guan Zhong and Bao Shuya are politicians in ancient China.)
But they worked together and made a huge achievement in the end.
The thing he's researching
can't even be reach success in his own lab. How could it be successful in the big market?
Right now, he's on the brink of a breakthrough.
Every time he thinks he's seen one, it's just failure waiting for him.
GM Pan, just take a look.
I'm not going. His stupid lab?
I went ten years ago. Dirty, messy, crappy, and underdeveloped.
I said a few things with good intent, but then he scolded me fiercely.
Maybe now, he changed his views?
Gao Zhengdao?
He can't change.
GM Pan, you should see for yourself first. You can help me gatekeep.
I'm not going!
But it's not like you have anything to do anyway. Go out more.
Maybe it will help you with your revenge plan!
Professor Gao,
it's been ten years. I think you haven't really improved.
Even if I didn't improve at all, I've still always been ahead of you.
You designed round batteries?
Who am I?
These years, you've actually improved, no?
You've finally spoken a truth.
How about this?
I can invest ¥3,000,000 first. On round battery technology,
Let's try the solid—
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're talking about membrane batteries?
Of course.
This is the only way to solve Lubao 3's
bottleneck of energy density that we can't break through for a long time.
Do you think the research I've spent so long doing
was all in order to solve the inferior problems of your inferior products?
As long as we can change the quality of human life,
there's no such thing as superiority and inferiority. Understand?
You don't understand anything.
You two great masters.
You were talking civilly just a few minutes ago. How come you've started bickering?
Leave. You're not on my level.
Go, please.
Let me remind you...
that membrane-less batteries have no future.
You can research for 10 or 20 more years, but that doesn't change that fact.
Gao Zhengdao, all around you is darkness.
You cannot see beyond your nose.
If you have things to say, be proper. Let's not try to infuriate each other.
Gao Zhengdao,
as long as you are willing to change directions, I will invest immediately.
Liu Yang!
Let the dogs out!
You're so stubborn and foul-tempered.
Better than your stench of money!
GM Pan, GM Pan, don't go.
- Let him go!
- You guys should keep discussing.
I'm not going to collaborate with such people!
I'd rather work for a person like Wang Ziru
than work with a self-centered person like you!
GM Pan, we still have a proposal. We can keep talking about it.
Get out! Get out! Don't let me see him!
What kind of trash was that?
- Professor Gao.
- What's wrong?
¥3,000,000 went down the drain.
I'm not afraid!
After the battery is successfully invented,
the people who want to invest in us will be lined up all the way to the Oriental Pearl Tower!
But the situation right now is that we have no money!
The membrane-less battery will die on the vine!
Professor Gao, at this point, we're begging people right now.
We... can't you control your temper—
This is just my temper!
Next time... I'm not going to nose into the investment business.
Y-You can decide for yourself.
All right.
What? ¥5,000,000?
¥4,000,000 is fine, too.
¥3,000,000 could work too.
Of course, ¥6,000,000 would be best.
Sister Siyu, I trust you. The things you believe will definitely be successful,
but...
I really have no money. The most I could possbily take out is ¥50,000.
Don't you understand that none of us have money?
I'm not saying you guys should take that money out.
I'm saying the people around you can.
Thank you guys.
Zhizhi! What is this?
Zhizhi, you accepted him?
Zhizhi,
if you were still a saleswoman at Lubao,
would you have accepted his proposal and go to Europe with him?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Sister Siyu, don't say that.
It's true that I was kicked out because of our relationship,
but that also means that my value in the company wasn't high enough.
If I could've become irreplaceable,
then the company wouldn't have fired me so easily.
No, Zhizhi, as a saleswoman, you're already so talented.
Then I'll have to thank you even more.
If it weren't for you, I never would've known that I could be a saleswoman at all!
I also wouldn't have known that I had this much potential.
But right now, you're giving all of this up?
Why can't you think of the things Zhizhi gained?
She got a steady, kind husband,
a peaceful life, and a stable family.
These are things you cannot buy!
I just don't want history to repeat itself.
What do you mean?
Sister Siyu is trying to say that before Liu Yang did all of that stuff,
I also had a peaceful and steady family life, too.
People are different from each other!
Liu Yang and that Su- Su whatever are not the same person.
You and her are different as well! She was born to be combative.
Don't you forget
Zhizhi said that before meeting clients, her heart would beat rapidly.
What does this mean? This means that clients are her lovers.
Business is her love!
Zhizhi even put on the ring. She picked it herself!
What are you doing?
- She picked it herself!
- You two, that's enough. Stop fussing.
Stop! Stop fussing!
- Stop fussing.
Stop fussing. I'm telling you to stop.
¥5,000,000?
Originally, I hadn't wanted to bring this up to you,
but she is my only sister.
Did you bring the project startup proposal?
T-T-T-he what now?
Just briefly explain the strengths of this project.
This project has so much potential.
You also know that new energy—
No matter how much potential the project has,
but not all the companies in this industry are good.
My older sister worked as a saleswoman in Lubao for ten years.
She has the sales resources and channels.
You mixed the concepts again.
Being a good salesperson and R&D are two very different things.
Besides,
no matter how good a salesperson is, that doesn't mean that they'd be a good CEO.
How about I invite her to come and talk to you?
I do not see the necessity. According to your analysis just now,
your sister prefers high risk. Right?
She is the type of person who cares too much about one thing, am I wrong?
Aren't all of you business creators like this?
Wrong.
The most important thing in business-making is the desire to survive,
meaning that the company has to keep existing.
Then... Then if you aren't investing,
can you start by taking into consideration that she will be your family member,
and help her by letting her borrow some money?
Right now, we are not legally married,
so I cannot use our family relationship to help her.
Then, what if it was me who wanted money to borrow?
In the prenuptial agreement I gave you,
the first page,
part two, clause seven states that before marriage,
I do not have any obligation to give you any money.
Page five,
part three has a clause that says that after marriage,
according to the time length of our marriage and the cost to take care of you,
you will receive a cash payment that is proportional to it,
and this payment
is the money that you are allowed to use.
So your point is that you won't let me borrow money from you.
So we need to sign the prenuptial agreement before marriage.
Then we can know the duties and rights of each other.
This will be easier and more clear
to prevent unnecessary disputes currently or in the future.
I get it.
Can we order?
Sushan!
Daddy, I want to eat ice cream.
I'll get you some.
Wow.
You want mango-flavored?
The thing I talked to you over WeChat about, have you considered it yet?
What thing?
My cousin's thing.
Your cousin's project?
If it was you who needed help...
Be careful. I would not hesitate to help you,
But if you want me to let your cousin borrow my money...
I think... it's not proper.
Why not?
This project is too risky. If something bad happened,
first, it would affect your relationship with your cousin,
and second,
our relationship will go through trouble as well.
But my cousin is determined to do this project and I want to help her.
Then tell her to quit while she can.
Look, with her experience, she can go to a big company
and become a high executive. Isn't that good for everyone?
Why suffer so much?
But she just got out of a big company and doesn't want to go back.
At the very least, even if she succeeds in setting up a company,
as a woman, do you think she's happy?
It's not certain.
I'm talking about the highest probability.
Think about it, out of all the women with successful careers,
part of them do not have good marriage lives.
So, she should find a stable place to work
and a suitable man to marry. That's should be the way.
Then you think that in the end, all women should deal with the household?
Well, we cannot generalize it that way.
Then tell me about it.
If, in the house,
there is not enough money, it's unrealistic to talk about "household."
What if the family makes a high income?
If the family makes a high income...
then I think that if one person could stay at home all the time, wouldn't that be nice?
Each one performs his/her own functions.
Here, Sushan.
- Come out, okay?
- Okay.
The ice cream is ready.
The ice cream is ready!
Come, let's come up.
Our ice cream is here.
Thank you, Older Sister.
- Thank you, Older Sister.
- No problem.
- Say bye to older sister.
- Bye, Older Sister.
- Bye-bye.
- Let's go.
Daddy, you eat.
I'll take a bite.
Thank you, precious.
Look at the bubbles.
Did you see?
Here. One, two, three.
Yuwei.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Recently, have there been any men coming to find your mom?
No.
No?
Do you like coming out to play with me?
Yes.
Then, do you like coming out to play with mom and dad together?
I like that, too!
Then you need to learn to make requests, okay?
In the future, when you come out with mom, invite me too!
Okay. Then next time when we hang out with Sushan
and Sushan's dad, you can also join us.
Who is Sushan's dad?
He's Sushan's dad, of course.
Then... what about Sushan's mom?
I've never seen her, but one time, Sushan told me that
her dad asked if she was willing
to let my mom be her mom.
Sushan said she was!
Then, Sushan and her dad are always hanging out with you?
Sushan is my best friend.
We play together every week,
and we are going to go to Europe to go to elementary school together!
Who said that you were going to do that?
Sushan said so. Sushan's dad said
that he will bring me and mom to Europe.
Did they say when?
I don't know either, but it's soon.
Dad, take another bite.
Did you finish reading the prenuptial agreement?
Not yet.
It shouldn't take this long.
Normal people can read 200-400 characters in a minute.
People who read quickly can even go up to 600 characters.
Even if you were the slowest reader,
if you read for 30 minutes a day, you would've finished in ten days.
So?
Do you have dyslexia?
No.
I'm just a slow reader, and I have been since I was little.
Besides, I need to think while reading.
Fine.
I'll give you thirty more days.
Thirty days later, we step into the next procedure.
Fine.
I hope we can start the wedding procedure this year.
If we waste too much time on the prenuptial agreement...
He Mu, do you love me?
Why are you laughing?
I really don't understand
why females need to hear direct answers
right from the other person's mouth for confirmation.
I don't understand.
This might be the difference in thought processes between males and females.
It might be because of the difference in these thoughts
so human beings keep being curious about marriage.
I feel unwell, I'm going home to rest.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[ Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫ Some sweet and some hopeless ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫ It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫ Learned to let go ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫ Don't back down from the crowd ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ Dear Myself ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫ Hugging you, hugging me ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫ The sky has finally cleared ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫ The sky has finally cleared ♫