Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 4]
Come in.
Sister, the first team's members have already been fully established.
There's Huang Bibo, Kuaizi, A Fu, Zhou Zhiyu, Yang Tian, and Zhang Jiaqi.
I got it.
I heard that after we left today,
Sister Yuan brought each of them in, one by one, for a discussion.
She made them each sign a form saying that they'll follow her.
Really?
So besides you, the top ten salesmen
are all on her team.
Sister, were you tricked?
Come in.
Sister Yuan.
You all head out.
- Close the door.
- Sure.
- You want to talk to me?
- You purposefully pushed me out
and then approached them one by one to tell them not to pick me, but you.
These are terrible accusations, what type of person do you think I am?
Then you did not say it?
Do you think I have to do this?
Did your trip go well?
I got the contract signed for you.
Siyu,
- didn't you say you wouldn't fight me?
- I did.
Then, why do you care who picked me and who picked you?
How about this? This commission will be considered yours.
Is it all right?
Liu Yang, time for dinner!
Let's eat dinner. Stop playing.
I'm late, you both eat dinner first.
After you finish eating, you can just leave it here. I'll wash it later.
- Where are you going at this time?
- Didn't I tell you yesterday?
I'm going to find Miao Miao's mom and have a meeting with all of them.
- If you leave, what happens to Yuwei?
- Aren't you here?
- I still have work to do!
- But what I'm doing is also work.
Mama, bye!
Bye, sweetie.
That's good enough for now. Thank you.
Didn't you say your boyfriend was going to come, too? He didn't come with you?
He's probably on the way now.
Xiaoling was planning on coming too,
but she had work today and couldn't get out of it.
She told me to tell you that
she was very sorry about how big of an impact those events caused you.
- I'm very sorry, too.
- It's no problem.
It's not a big deal.
Director Wang, I'm so sorry.
I was a little swamped with work.
- It's okay.
- I apologize.
I rushed to get off work as soon as I could, but I was still a little late.
Sister Ziru, thank you,
The proposal you had to solve the problem was very touching.
I said it already. It isn't a big deal.
It was clearly our fault. If we made you pay for it, I don't think it would be suitable.
I think it's better if I paid the money.
Exactly, Director Wang. We have felt your kindness.
We hope you will accept this money.
I can't possibly accept this.
- Sister Ziru.
- Even if I did take it, I couldn't have a use for it.
The paperwork has already been taken care of.
I couldn't change it if I wanted.
Just take it.
This way, we would feel a little more peace of mind.
You shouldn't make me feel wrong just to give yourself a little peace of mind, should you?
Sister Ziru, then
we owe you way too much.
It's okay.
Maybe in the future, when I need your help,
you can pay me back then.
I guess so. Thank you, Director Wang.
If you need anything, please don't hesitate to ask us.
Sister Ziru, thank you so much.
Siyu, are you getting busy?
I'm very busy. I have to run even when going to the bathroom.
It's good to be busy. Being busy means that your work is very important.
I think it's because it isn't very important, and that's why the pressure is even higher.
Yiming, what are you doing?
I'm in production planning.
That is very interesting.
Yes, it's all right.
What company?
Just a small company.
It's not that small. A finance company. Quite highly ranked in the industry.
I remember last year, the market value was around 800 million.
- That sounds about right.
- It's all due to his planning activities last year.
Their stock index went up two billion.
That's definitely not true. It's not like it was my work alone.
You're such a promising young man.
He's the company's youngest planning director.
- Okay, can you not talk about it?
- It's true though, isn't it?
Excuse me. I have a phone call.
- GM Pan.
- I'm asking you. What happened today with the group splitting?
It's just... That's what everyone picked.
What do you think?
- I...
- Thank you.
I didn't really think about it.
Li Siyu, do you not care about Lubao Batteries?
You were scolded by GM Pan again?
It's complicated.
What is it?
Please, this way.
There aren't a lot of people here today.
Yes, today is good.
Let me show you, I ordered a pink diamond!
It's not that busy here today.
Come, this way.
Today's weather is not great.
The landscape is so pretty.
Right, I made the reservation with that in mind. It's very close to the window.
- Wow, you're so good.
- Yeah, a special reservation.
- Let's take a look.
- What should we order?
Are we drinking alcohol?
My driver didn't drive me today. I drove myself.
- I drove as well.
- Then we'll pass on the alcohol. Next time then.
- Want to order one without alcohol?
- It's okay.
No, drinking fruit juice is healthier.
So who's writing the proposal this time?
Do you have any recommendations?
Get the freshly squeezed one.
- I can.
- You?
Really? Okay, you can do it then.
Sure.
Their family always recommends this.
Okay, then I'll order that.
[Husband]
Okay.
When I was the CEO in a foreign company,
I don't like when people in a meeting
were on their phones.
Yuwei's mom, what are you drinking?
I'll have soda water.
If I try my best for the position, I'd be letting down Sister Yuan.
If I don't try, then I'd be letting down GM Pan.
And at the same time, I'd be letting myself down.
I don't know what I should do.
How did things become like this?
It only happened after I came back from Ningbo.
Don't rush to make a decision then.
Time waits for no one.
I normally decide by flipping a coin. Do you have a coin?
- I didn't bring any coins.
- I have one here.
Let's do it like this.
If the picture faces up,
then you try hard to get the position of sales director.
If the number is face up, then give up.
Okay.
It seems it's God's will.
No, Siyu.
Actually, the game doesn't tell you what you should do;
instead, it lets you know what you really want deep down.
You were disappointed to see the number face up.
It means you never wanted to give up.
Yes.
If I were you, I would respect my inner will.
Yuwei's mom, can you finish your plan completely tomorrow?
Yes.
How about we discuss tomorrow evening?
Still at this place at this time, okay?
All right. Let's finish here today.
Waitress, bill please.
Hello, ¥1,935.
- Send the bill to the group we can split it with you later.
- Okay.
I sent it.
I paid.
- It's quite cold.
- Yeah.
Your jacket looks very nice when the wind blows it.
Does it? I like it as well.
You didn't drive, Yuwei's mom?
I didn't drive today.
I'm too full. I'll take a taxi after walking a little bit.
Okay. I will leave first.
Take care. Bye-bye.
Bye.
I'm leaving.
See you tomorrow.
Liu Yang, you called just now?
What?
See you, Director Wang.
I think Sister Ziru understands me.
You will try hard to get the position as she said?
I... Let me think it over.
Sir Chen Yiming, congratulations that you have passed the resume screening of the company's planning director selection. We have planned the time for your interview.
Who was it?
Nothing. Spam.
Spam? You smile so happily!
Did I? I am worried!
What are you worried about?
I'm worried about you.
I knew nothing about you and Sister Yuan's situation. Nobody told me.
I told you. It came all of a sudden.
When I called you in the afternoon, you were angry with me for nothing.
Was I?
Was I angry for nothing?
Should you tell me if you go to Ningbo?
Otherwise, when friends ask me where you are, how can I answer them?
I told them that I didn't know. Then, what is the relationship between you and me?
All right. You are so busy with so many things.
You need to worry about this and that, I just want to save you some trouble.
Everything else can be saved.
Loving you cannot be saved.
If you need to go on a long journey again, you must tell me!
How long is long?
The places with housing prices less than ¥30,000 per square meter.
Then I have to check the housing price after I arrive at a place. So inconvenient.
This is what I mean.
Then you should let me think about it.
- How is she?
- The anti-allergic treatment has worked.
Observe for a while, after one hour,
if she doesn't have any other symptoms flare up, you can go home.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- But your daughter had a quite serious allergic reaction.
There is such a thing as an EpiPen. You can buy one.
If there is an emergency, it can save her life.
All right. I will prescribe it for you.
All right. Thank you.
How did this happen?
She said she wanted to drink milk. I asked her to get it by herself.
How would I know that she'd eat some chocolate?
The chocolate is for you when you stay up late!
It has peanuts inside so I hid it inside the fridge.
How could I know this?
Why didn't you watch her more carefully?
How could you let her open the fridge by herself?
Why didn't you watch her?
I was busy with something.
That counts as something? Waste of time!
- Did you tell Mom?
- What?
- Hello?
- Yang!
- Mom!
- I sent another package of medicine to you.
Have you received it?
Yes.
Have you finished the one I sent last time?
- Almost done.
- Then continue taking this one.
- I know it.
- This is for warming the uterus
That Li Sanwa's wife,
it worked really well with her! She had 2 boys in a row!
Mom, Zhizhi is right next to me, I'll give the phone to her.
- Hey, Mom.
-  How's it going?
Have you felt any movement recently?
What movement?
Maybe you two aren't preparing it correctly.
- How about I come over and make it for you?
- No, no, it's okay. We're fine.
All right, all right.
Then I'll just wait for your good news then.
My mom wants to come and visit, doesn't she?
Never let her come; otherwise, there will be a lot of trouble for us.
Why does your mom always want us to have a second baby?
The neighbors all have one now.
Also, they are all boys so she is jealous.
- What do you think?
- A second kid?
That will kill me.
Raising Yuwei already makes it inancially difficult!
When your mom brings it up again next time, tell her the truth!
It's impossible for my mom to listen to me.
Do you like the flowers that I gave you?
Yes.
May I know which friend sent this to me?
- Your coffee, sir.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I heard you broke up with Lan Ke?
Who told you this?
Someone saw him hang out with a new girlfriend.
I was the one who broke up with him.
- Why?
- He was too clingy. I couldn't bear it.
- Really?
- Ask him if you don't believe me!
Who's that mystery man who's been sending you flowers every day?
I don't know, either. It's annoying.
Is it?
New policy. Carry out from the first day of next month.
What policy?
The company is really crazy.
Gosh!
They're even beginning to sell to groups.
¥159 for 120 minutes of play and 2 cups of coffee for free.
Yeah. So now, can anyone just come in?
The membership fee that you bought before for ¥500,000. Now they can play for half a day at ¥159.
This is too low.
This time even we are also dropping the price.
I'm going to study for a Master of Business Administration.
What can you learn with your qualifications?
At least you can raise your own worth.
Hello, waiter.
Coming!
Be careful.
- Be careful.
- Let's go.
Being a team leader, you have so many things now.
Printers and paper shredders are all tools you can use.
By the way, Sister Siyu, Yuwei's class is going to hold a party.
The theme is "I love Mom."
I am responsible for planning, and I made one.
But I'm not satisfied. Can you help me with it?
You should find Yiming for this. This is what he does.
You give me the information and I will pass it to him.
Okay, I'll send it to you right away.
Sorry.
Lin Ling!  From your sales department, right?
I know.
I guess, she just finished the resignation procedure.
She's also pretty miserable.
Her dad was found with lung cancer and needs money.
- How do you know that?
- She consulted with me two days ago about medical insurance.
Now, it’s not easy to find a job in this big environment.
Lin Ling,
you want to be in my team. Right?
- Yes, but...
- Go report to Liu Xiaojia.
Just say it was me.
You are now in the second sales team.
Sister Siyu.
Sister Siyu, you will offend Sister Yuan if you do this.
It's none of her business.
Right.
Elevator going down.
- Hello.
I made an appointment for an interview today.
- What is your name?
- Chen Yiming.
Chen Yiming. Please wait here.
Okay, thank you.
- Hello.
- What? She took Lin Ling in?
- Yes.
She was going through the resignation procedures. But she paused it again.
Sister Yuan, the person you fired, she called her back again.
Well, what does that mean?
The company is about to fire someone,
you still want to keep her?
I just want to help her.
- So you are doing some good deeds?
- Yes.
If you want to do good, then give her money yourself.
Let the company give her a basic salary.
You want to help her at the company's expense?
President Pan, I already told the HR Department,
Lin Ling does not occupy the quota of the sales department.
I will pay her the basic salary.
Three months.
She didn't have a single transaction. What does this mean?
This means that she is not suitable for this position.
Not suitable for this company. Do you know?
I have read her work log.
She has worked hard for these three months.
She just lacks a little method and luck.
I think if you give her another three months, she will be able to resuscitate.
- Impossible.
- Why?
I am now preparing for equity financing.
Sales revenue in the next three months will determine the company's valuation.
So I don't have time for you to train new people.
I want data. Continuous rising data.
The data that can bring capital confidence.
Then one month.
Let her stay if she signs an order;
otherwise, I will personally fire her.
I know that you are very compassionate.
But the company is about benefits,
it has no place for compassion.
I know, but...
- I just can't bear—
- Li Siyu!
Li Siyu,
sometimes blind kindness
to others, to yourself,
to the company, and to the overall situation
can be extremely irresponsible.
I understand, GM Pan.
Chen Yiming!
Hello, Sister Siyu.
Sister Siyu, the party related materials are all ready.
- When do you need it by?
- Tonight.
Mothers have to discuss it.
Then we have to prepare separately according to the plan.
Then, I'll contact Yiming immediately.
You were born after 1980?
Correct.
Don't underestimate my ability just because of my age.
- Actually I have 8 years' experience.
- No, no, no.
Our company products are for post-90s.
You are a bit old for us.
So you think thirties are too old?
If your mentality was still young,
then we could also consider it.
- Your media resources are quite extensive.
- Yes.
I was one of the first in our circle to recognize
- the power of We Media [self-produced media].
- We Media is now outdated.
Now, all that's in the past. Now everyone in the world is of blended media.
You're right.
The number you have dialed is temporarily...
Still, no one's answering?
What can we do?
I promised Miao Miao's mom that I'd give her the plan today.
Miao Miao's mom has a strict sense of time, very principled.
If I can't do this, she'll surely be mad.
Don't get too anxious. I'll go see him.
Did you come up with Caijin's plan for Qingyun?
Yes. I designed it.
Last year, our company analyzed the case of the Qingyun plan.
Really?
But if I could re-do that event today,
I myself think I...
that plan wasn't too complete.
True. The plan's foundation is indeed quite good.
But, unfortunately, the planning wasn't too good.
If that had been given to our planning team,
Caijin Company's value would have increased by at least 500 million.
Thank you.
Zhang Shengyun!
I called, but you didn't answer or reply to my text.
I need to talk to you about something urgent. I'm headed to your company right now.
I need to talk to you about something urgent. I need to talk....
I'm headed to your company right now. I'm headed...
- Hello, Yiming.
- Siyu, where are you now?
I've parked at the entrance to your company.
Don't go up. I... I'm not at the company right now.
- Where are you?
- I'm... I'm out speaking with a client.
- Okay. Then I'll come to you.
- Okay.
- Waiter.
- Wait just a minute. I'll be right there.
Siyu, over here.
Why are you alone?  Your client?
The client left after he ate. He just left.
Waiter.
Clear this up.
What's up?
Hurry and help Zhizhi with this plan.
- She must have it done before she gets off work.
- What's the rush?
Zhizhi's in a panic, so I brought it to you.
This won't work. I... I... I have two meetings this afternoon and I have an appointment with a client.
No matter how important those are, you have to finish this first.
This concerns Yuwei's position in her kindergarten,
concerns Yuwei's circle of friends, Yuwei's future.
You're being too serious about this. It's not that bad.
That's what Zhizhi told me.
Okay, then. I'll... I'll do this first.
Do you want something to drink?
I don't want anything.
What's wrong? Are you feeling down?
Today, I was a little too impulsive.
I let an intern that the company was preparing to fire stay at the company.
Why?
Her father has lung cancer.
Back then, my mom died from lung cancer.
I understand.
But everyone, including GM Pan,
all think I was wrong to do it.
Because a company only concerns itself with profits, not compassion. Was I wrong?
But in every case, it's a human. So we can talk about compassion.
But a company only concerns itself with profits.
Siyu,
do you know what it is about you that attracts me most?
My beauty is unmatched.
It's your kindness.
I think that your kindness surpasses all other profits.
Thank you, Yiming.
I know what I should do.
If that girl really can't stay at Lubao,
could your company find work for her?
It's possible that... I can't help with this.
Aren't you always complaining that you don't have enough people in your department?
It may be that you...you don't quite understand our circumstances. This year, our company
is doing mass layoffs.
Didn't your company have great momentum last year?
That was last year.
Now... it's different this year.
I got it.
Siyu,
if I were to...
- get laid off too...
- How could that be?
No matter how bad the markets are, we would never be laid off.
Why are you so odd?
Who? Me?
What would be odd about me? I think you're the one acting odd.
How long will this class take?
Hello, Ma'am. Do you have interest in this field?
"For your field of art appreciation
and art institution management..." What are the required qualifications?
Do you have a foundation in drawing?
- I do.
- Did you bring one of your pieces?
Just look at my face.
I prepared it myself.
- How is your foreign language ability?
- I'm okay with French and Italian.
- Louis Vuitton, Chanel, Hermes, Prada...
- Okay, enough.
Xiaoling.
- Hello.
- Where are you going? I'll take you.
No, thanks.
This is the bustling downtown area. It's not easy to get a cab.
It's so windy. Get in.
After you left last time,
I actually looked for opportunities to get an appointment with you.
I even asked Yiming so many times.
That buddy really isn't reliable.
He doesn't concern himself with me at all.
I can't believe that in this vast sea of people,
the two of us would meet each other on the street.
Tell me. Is that destiny?
It makes a person cherish it.
- Let's play a game.
- Okay.
In this game, the first who can't contain stop himself from talking,
starting right now, is the loser.
- The loser treats the other one to dinner.
- Begin.
Xiaoling, I think that this time
you're even more pretty than before.
Yo, yo, yo. I lost. I lost.
Punish me.
Tomorrow, the day after that or the day after that, you choose the place.
Is that guy called Lei-something,
a good friend of Chen Yiming?
- Actually, I haven't had the chance...
- Yes.
- ...to formally introduce myself.
- Then, I'll let him live.
I'm Lei Haowen. The "Lei" from "thunder,"
the "Hao" from "integrity,"
the "Wen" from amazingly "cultured."
(T/N: explanation of the characters that make up his name)
It could be from that last time, you got a mistaken impression of me.
What? That sports car from last time really belonged to you?
That sports car really isn't mine.
It belongs to our family's housekeeper.
Then, what about this car?
Don't look down on this car.
Even though it costs only about two or three hundred thousand,
I bought it with each penny I earned by myself
from my work-study jobs while I was in college.
So, when I can, I often drive this one.
It brings to mind the days of my youth.
Even though I'm a "second-generation rich" guy,
I don't have the bad habits of that type of person. None of them.
- I can see that.
- Really?
Do you know what the worst habit of the "second-generation rich" guy is?
It's their wealth.
But fortunately you aren't wealthy.
If you use wealth to judge a person...
isn't that behavior a little shallow?
Do you think I'm shallow?
No, no, no. That's not what I meant.
You're actually right. I am indeed shallow.
People all have their shortcomings.
I don't think that's a shortcoming.
If a young woman
is too vain and seeks material things,
it's very possible that they will miss out on some valuable things.
For example?
For example, you could lose a man who is
truly charming, powerful, and has great potential.
I think... based on my base vanity,
I'm not worth a guy whose charming, powerful, and full of potential.
No. You are worth it.
- What's wrong.
- Stop the car. I'm here.
Don't you want to go to the subway entrance?
I can't take this anymore. I feel nauseous.
Are you carsick?
I'm sick of you.
How can you say that?
Gu Xiaoling, what do you mean by that?
If we meet on the street again, I'm begging you not to even greet me.
Don't think that just because you're pretty, you can say things to hurt others.
It was you that came after me, that's a legitimate defense.
Whoever goes after you deserves to be single forever.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears.  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫