Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 31]
- Please wait a moment. President He will be here shortly.
- Thank you.
Ms. Gu.
Mr. He, hello.
Hello.
Please sit.
Here is your coffee.
Thank you.
President He, I will leave now.
Mr. He, we meet again.
Indeed.
I only have 15 minutes.
This is our art museum's member's manual.
Ms. Gu, you could have shipped the member's manual to me,
or you could have sent an electronic copy.
You could even have given it to me the next time I visit the art museum.
Why did you come here personally?
Because you are our most important member.
I speculate you came all this way for me, right?
In order to make it so you didn't come here for nothing,
as well as to save time and increase efficiency,
I will get straight to the point.
My name is He Mu. I'm a male, 35 years old.
I graduated from Stanford as a computer science major.
I came back to the country two years ago and created this company.
Currently, the annual profit is around ¥50,000,000.
This is my diploma and this is my business license.
My body is very healthy. I am passionate about fitness, do not smoke, and drink occasionally.
I don't have any hereditary diseases.
This is my genetics report, and this contains my physical examinations from the past two years.
I have never gotten married but have had three relationships before.
I broke up peacefully with each woman. After the breakups, I have no more business or relationship connections to them.
I do not have any siblings and my parents were in the education industry.
They have both since retired and are living the rest of their days in our hometown.
They are both in good health. This is my household registration.
These are my honorary credentials.
It's your turn.
W-What?
I still have eight minutes.
I... don't really understand.
You can start by explaining your living habits.
My living habits are really good, I'm very healthy.
I also like to exercise,
and my parents are both in our hometown.
I...
Ms. Gu, your thought process is a little messy.
- How about this? I ask questions. You answer them.
- Sure.
- Do you smoke?
- I do not.
- Do you drink?
- A little bit.
Are you willing to raise two or more children?
Y-Yes.
Can you briefly introduce your family dynamic?
When I was eight years old, my father died,
so then my s- my mother married my stepfather and took me along.
My stepfather is a great person. He's an engineer.
My mom is a normal office worker.
Also, I have an older sister who has different biological parents,
and she's starting her own business right now.
- Your father died due to...?
- A car accident.
You don't have any hereditary diseases?
Definitely not.
- Height?
- 170 cm.
- Plastic surgery?
- Yes.
- Weight?
- 48 kilos.
Is that net weight?
That is for when I only have undergarments on.
Ms. Gu, you completely meet all the criteria I have for my future wife.
I have to go to a meeting very soon.
Next Thursday, from 4:44 p.m. to 6:21 p.m., I have time.
I hope that we can go out on a date.
- Isn't this...
- Ms. Gu.
My secretary, Ms. Chang, will give you my contact information.
See you next week.
Yuwei's mom, how about you take Yuwei to the hospital for an examination?
Teacher, this kind of thing has never happened with Yuwei before.
Perhaps it was not triggered in the past, so it didn't happen then.
Yuwei doesn't have any problems.
She has already peed her pants three times this week.
This is not normal.
It might be because she just got put in a new environment and isn't used to it.
She's already been in this kindergarten for half a month, how could she still not have adjusted?
This daughter of yours is too much of a princess.
Teacher, could it be because she ate something she shouldn't have?
How is this possible? All of the children eat the same thing.
If there was a problem with the food or drinks, then all of the other children would also experience the same thing.
How come it only happened to your Liu Yuwei?
Mommy,
I want to go home.
Fine. It's almost time to go anyways.
Today, you can go home early with your mom.
Thank you, Teacher. We've troubled you.
Yuwei, you never peed your pants in the past.
What has been going on recently?
Did you do it on purpose?
- No.
- Then why?
Mommy, I want to go back to my old kindergarten.
Is this kindergarten not good?
This kindergarten is bad.
Why?
Yuwei, don't be afraid. Tell me. I will protect you.
The teacher scolds me and is mean to me. I'm scared.
I don't know what happened, my pee came out.
Why did she scold you?
She said that I eat too slow
and my actions are slow,
and she wouldn't let me eat. She made me stand in a corner as punishment.
What?
Let's go.
Liu Yuwei's mom, do you have some kind of misunderstanding about me?
Liu Yuwei already told me everything. There are no misunderstandings.
Can you really trust everything that comes out of a child's mouth? They exaggerate.
- So you didn't scold her?
- Why would I scold her?
She created trouble and as a teacher, I just said a few words, is that not all right?
What about when you punished her by not letting her eat and forcing her to stand in a corner?
That's because your Liu Yuwei wet her pants and it smelled.
The other children were still eating, so I made her stand in the corner. Is that wrong?
What kind of teacher are you?
Principal, please say something.
I pretty much understand the situation now.
How about this? Teacher Fang, leave us for now.
Let me talk to Liu Yuwei's mother. Go ahead.
Principal, I demand that you assign a new teacher for Yuwei.
That's impossible.
- Why?
- The truth is that Teacher Fang
is just a little bit impatient. She's pretty good in every other way.
She doesn't have a kind heart!
We have criteria here to fulfill in order for someone to be a teacher.
Principal, this is my daughter, my entire family's baby.
I paid money for her to come here so that she can have the best care,
not to have her teacher look down on her!
Liu Yuwei's mom, how much money did you spend? You want the best care?
Still, the teacher shouldn't scare her to the point where she wets her pants!
The teacher just spoke a little too loudly.
Your baby has not developed fully in that area.
She's already four or five years old and still wets her pants. Whose fault is that?
What kind of attitude is this, Principal?
I think that as a parent,
the first thing is that you should not be so sensitive.
Every child here is just from an ordinary family.
Getting some set-back education is a good thing.
The second thing is don't try to get more than what you paid for.
Everyone should know the principle of "you get what you paid for."
I'm going to report this to higher authorities! I'm going to expose you guys!
Do as you wish.
It would be good to let people know about our kindergarten
only costs a little over ¥1,000 per month
and the children get food, drinks, and to play unharmed.
There are also teacher-led activities to help them learn characters and numbers.
Where could you possibly find a kindergarten like this?
Mommy, do I have to come to this kindergarten tomorrow?
Mommy, can I not come?
I'll stay at home with Daddy.
I promise that I won't eat junk,
won't make a fuss, and won't pee my pants.
Mommy, why are you crying?
I promise you
that in the future, I will never let you be bullied again. Okay?
According to President Li's proposal to reach 500 cities by the end of next years
and the goal of 8,000 service areas,
I estimate that our marketing cost each month
will be at least
¥1,580,000.
I can give you at most this number.
[158]
Then there is no way I can do it.
Is it possible to exchange resources with other websites?
Then we must have at least one million or more users.
before others will talk about exchanging resources with us.
- When can we reach one million?
- I can do it as long as the marketing is in place.
As long as there is money, I also have no problem accomplishing things.
As long as you can earn the money back, I also have no problems.
I will kick whoever kicks the ball again!
(T/N: kicking/passing the ball/problem to each other)
If we don't consider marketing,
before the end of this year, can you get one million users?
If we don't consider marketing then we must consider services.
Right now, our franchisee of service areas hasn't reached a certain number. Even if they reach that number,
we could still lose them.
Within two months, get another two hundred franchisees.
President Li, just kill me.
Even if I get one a day, in two months, I can only get sixty more.
- I—
- All right. I will handle the one hundred and forty left.
- President Li—
- Sister Tian, help me book the earliest train ticket to Hefei today.
- Okay.
- Xiao Lu.
You told me last time that there was someone who wanted to be a regional agent in Hefei. Give me the material about them.
That's all for today. Meeting is over.
My goodness. President Li wants to risk her life.
- Sister Fan, can't you just give some more money?
- Where do I get the money?
Doesn't our company still have money?
Have you thought about it clearly?
Yes, I have.
I'm a great person in a lot of ways,
but I'm petty and love to hold grudges.
Director Yuan,
I'm sorry.
In the past, there are things that I didn't do well.
I apologize to you for it.
You're pretty good with words, pretty smart.
I'm not smart, but I will not be lazy.
Fine. I accept.
However, as my subordinate, your pressure will be immense.
I will also be able to learn a lot.
I still don't understand. Didn't Li Siyu just start a new company?
If you want to make money, why not reach out to her?
She just started the business,
so it is quite a difficult time for her.
- Older Sister.
- How come you're here?
Look. A-Accompanying you on your business trip.
Who asked you to accompany me on this business trip?
You put so much work aside just to come here, are you out of your mind?
No, Sister. Don't be so irritable.
Sorry, please excuse me. Sorry.
I-I'll help you.
Sit, sit, sit, sit, sit.
Sister, first, I did all of the work you assigned me.
Second, I made this webpage for Hefei that you can directly click into.
If you take this to the discussion, I'm sure it will be successful.
- When did you make this?
- Just now.
If they have any uncertainties about my design skills, I can clear it up right there and then.
If there are any problems, I can also fix it right there.
After I finish working in Hefei, I will go to Nantong.
Ask Xiao Lu for the materials.
Before the train arrives in Hefei, I want a webpage for Nantong as well.
Got it.
- Hello, how many people?
- I have a reservation.
Hello.
You are late by 5 minutes and 32 seconds.
I'm sorry, there was traffic.
At this time, there is definitely traffic downtown,
so you should have left at least 15 minutes earlier.
- I know now.
- Waitress.
Are the two of you ready to order?
I would like a steak set meal and a soda water.
Thank you.
Same, thank you.
What kind of drink do you want, Miss?
Iced latte. No sugar. Skimmed milk.
You're drinking it iced?
What's wrong?
If a woman tends to have cold drinks, it will cause the uterus to get cold and make it difficult to make children,
(T/N: very common belief in China)
so I hope that in the future, you will not have any iced drinks.
This is in consideration of your well-being.
Please change the drink to a hot lemon tea, thank you.
Okay.
This time period you picked is quite interesting.
4:44 to 6:21.
Is there any specific meaning to it?
My meeting ended at 4:30. It takes me three minutes to go down to the parking garage to get the car.
It takes nine minutes to get from the company to here and two minutes to park,
so I made plans with you to meet at 4:44.
At 6:45, I have an online meeting.
Even though it's the evening rush hour, there won't be a standstill.
It will only take three traffic lights' time.
From here to get back to the company, I need twenty minutes.
It takes three minutes to park and go upstairs,
so at 6:21,
our date will end.
- What are you doing?
- Weighing it.
My personal trainer gave me a diet plan.
I have a strict limit on my calorie intake.
Look at them.
Don't mind the stares of others.
I don't really mind,
but I never would have thought that you would be so strict with yourself.
One's degree of self-management is an important standard use to distinguishing the elite from the grass-root class.
This kind of management is not only for work.
It also includes one's body and mannerism
as well as how the family operates and children's education.
That makes sense.
Later, I'll create one for you as well.
- Create what?
- A self-management plan.
Next Thursday, from 12:14 to 3:44,
we can have lunch together and then watch a movie.
We're meeting next week, too?
We must have at least one date per week.
That will allow us to get to know each other better and develop our relationship.
Next week...
Next week, I am n-not sure whether or not I'll be free.
If you don't have time, you can contact Ms. Chang.
She will help you set up our next date.
- Okay then.
- See you next week.
N-Next week...
let's meet?
- She's asleep?
- Yes.
Right now, I'm asking my college seniors to help me find a job.
Didn't the doctors tell you to rest?
Why are you being so impatient?
Just stay here and take care of Yuwei.
I want to quickly find a job
to lessen the stress you're under.
I can deal with my own stress.
Xiaoling?
Wait, wait, wait!
Lei Haowen, open the door! Nobody will look at you!
- Quick!
- Coming, coming!
Why aren't you wearing shoes?
Come put on the slippers.
- Do you have band-aids? I cut my feet.
- Yes!
Where is the cut?
Let me see.
Your foot just healed. Why did you wear heels?
The heels are so tall, too.
It isn't easy for me to date, you know?
Who were you on a date with?
I went on a date with a nerd.
After that?
I don't know if I should have an "afterwards" with him.
It's done.
Do you have any food here?
In the kitchen. Help yourself.
I'm too lazy to move. Just pity me and go to help me get it. Go.
Fine.
Why don't you tell me in advance every time you come?
What if I'm keeping a lover here?
- If you bump into each other, how embarrassing would that be?
- You?
Impossible!
Don't look down on me.
If I really have someone one day,
it will be too late for you to cry.
- Who?
- My girlfriend.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to let your girlfriend in.
Are you stupid? I'm a lonely man, you are a lonely woman, and you are so hot,
when she sees this, won't she be angry at me?
What should I do in your opinion?
Go hide in the room for now.
- No, I-I should—
- Go hide in the room first. I will get her to leave in a bit.
Come out after she leaves. Remember, don't come out.
- I should—
- Don't come out! Listen.
Come out only when I say to.
Hello, Sir, your—
takeout.
How many times have I told you already? I don't eat dinner!
I'm trying to lose weight, don't you know?
Don't you know?
Don't cry. What is there to cry about?
Don't contact me anymore. Call me if you need me.
Leave, leave, leave!
Xiaoling!
Come on out!
Your girlfriend left so quickly?
She brought me some delicious food but I said I won't eat it.
Then I asked her to leave.
Is your girlfriend's surname "Mei Tuan"?
(T/N: Mei Tuan is a Chinese food delivery App)?
Yes. I have another girlfriend.
Her surname is "e."
Her name is “leme."
(T/N:Eleme is another Chinese food delivery App)
Those two get into jealous fights over me.
They have some fierce fights.
You need to treat both of them well then.
That is mine.
I'm just taking a few bites, what's the big deal?
You just went on a date!
How could you steal food from someone who hasn't eaten?
I—
Let me tell you. My saliva is on that.
So what?
Aren't you afraid that I have some kind of disease?
What disease could you possibly have?
You will die if it gets serious.
Then I will die for your saliva. It will be a worthy death.
Then my deep affection for you won't be wasted.
When people talk to me about meaningful things,
I feel bored.
Yet when you say nonsense to me, I feel happy.
What kind of person am I?
It's because you are the same kind of person as me.
We two are both Chinese counterfeit goods!
I'm going to beat you up!
Hit me. Come hit me.
Come down from there.
Come, come hit me in the bedroom.
Come out here!
Lei Haowen, open the door!
Give the shoe back to me!
Didn't Qijue Group sign a contract with us for an order? How come we lost the order?
Director Yuan, it was really not my fault.
- Who is to blame then?
- You don't know
just how weird the manager who was in charge of this project was.
Every time I go to see him,
- I will shiver.
- I'm asking you about the contract!
That Manager Su is asking for a lot so I don't dare to comply with his demands.
- Thus, he backed out of it.
- How much is he asking for?
It's definitely beyond our limit!
Then how will we calculate your sales performance for this month?
I...
I will accept any punishment.
- Also, Zhang Zhizhi is joining our department.
- What?
- What would she do here?
- Sales.
- Can she do it?
- Is it possible that she has ulterior motives?
I asked HR, and they said that her family is struggling so she wants to earn some money here.
- That's quite naive of her.
- Karma.
Back then, when she scolded Director Yuan, she was so arrogant.
Director Yuan, use this opportunity to teach her a proper lesson.
Let her understand what it means to regret.
I have an idea.
Hey, let's rearrange this place so that it's cozier. This way, the clients will be happy when they see it.
Kuai Zi, put this green plant
over there on the side.
Put it inside.
Director Yuan, I'm here for work.
Director Yuan, where do I put these files and chairs?
Well...
- Empty out that room and use it as a storage place for all of these things.
- Okay.
Quickly, move, move, move. Xiao Wu. Bibo.
Director Yuan, I'm checking in.
Xiao Liu, push this shelf back.
Yes, here.
Put it against the window.
Here, put some more. Put some plants here
Yes, put them here, here.
Let me see. Put that here. Here.
Yes, yes, yes.
-  Yes, put them right here.
- Zhang Zhizhi.
Why are you standing like an idiot? Find a place to sit.
Are you waiting for others to take care of you?
- This seat is not occupied. Sit here.
- Thank you.
Why did you pick this department? Aren't you asking for hardships?
(Literal translation: Aren't you looking to eat bitterness?)
As long as there's something to eat, who cares if it's bitter or sweet?
Director Yuan is definitely not going to let you have it easy.
Without her, my life won't be easy either.
Zhang Zhizhi!
Come here for a moment.
- Go visit this client?
- By myself?
What? Do you want me to hire you a secretary, a chauffeur, a nanny, and a hairstylist?
That's not what I meant. I'm just afraid that I'll mess up.
Since it's my first day in sales.
It's because it's your first day,
that's why I assigned you a top-tier client.
As long as he signs for the order,
your assignment for this month is done.
- Go on.
- Thanks, Director Yuan.
Lin Ling, put this in that room. Hurry, go.
Kuai Zi, come here and help me carry it.
Take it away. Take it away.
[Su Lixing]
Come in.
Are you Director Mei?
- Yes.
- Hello, Director Mei.
I am Li Siyu from Laidianle. This is Guan Xiaotang.
Why are you here looking for me?
We are here to talk about being a regional agent.
Collaborations, right?
Who is it?
Take a seat first. Don't just stand there.
You guys are from Laidianle?
Yes.
Do you know how to play this?
I've played it before.
Let's play a game.
Sure.
I rarely meet girls who knows how to play King of Fighters nowadays.
Do you play anything else normally?
- Just this. This is good.
- Just this?
Then you must be quite great at it.
Round One
Ready, go!
Hit! Hit!
[2 Hits]
Legs. Legs. Use your legs.
Leg!
You seem out of practice.
I haven't played in a long time.
Round Two. Ready, Go!
Director Mei,
if you can guarantee that you can get 200 points,
I can give the Hefei region agency to you.
I heard that some of your franchise businesses
are not as great as what you promoted.
That is because our customers
numbers haven't increased yet.
But our trend is quite good.
Trend?
I don't think your trend looks optimistic.
Hit him! Beat him up!
You're too strong!
- Player one wins!
- That was boring.
I'm not playing anymore.
All right, today we have...
In front of a pro like you, Director Mei,
I truly lost with admiration to you.
With your skill, do you really lose with admiration?
Director Mei, this is our newest statistical data.
You will know after you have a look. We are very promising.
I am the type of person who distrusts statistical data most.
How about you play instead?
Come on then.
In this game, I have never lost.
In the pugilistic society, they called me
the "young and attractive little password."
"Young and attractive"? All right.
All right let me see what you, Little Thanos, got.
Come in.
Hello, Director Su.
You are...?
I'm Zhang Zhizhi, a salesperson from Lubao. Can I bother you for 15 minutes?
No.
I want to introduce our latest product to you.
I don't want to hear it.
- But—
- Where is the previous salesperson?
My colleague was occupied with other work today so—
- so my boss sent me today—
-So they sent a you, who can't even speak clearly. Right?
Your Lubao Group is really
becoming more and more rude.
- Today, I-I'm—
- What?
Please tell your boss that Qijue Science and Technology won't use any of Lubao's products!
From now on, you and your colleagues, have some  self-respect
and don't come back to harass me again. Don't.
Director Su, this is the introduction of our latest product.
If you have time, please have a look.
If you need to, please call me.
I've only used 10% of my skills.
I can't believe you sneak attacked me.
Don't be too happy. Again.
Who are you looking for?
How did you get in here?
That was intense!
Player Two wins!
You just had good luck.
Let's switch to another game. I don't believe it.
Pick whatever you like.
- Do you know League of Legend?
- Yup.
Come on. Let's play a solo round.
Don't stop me.
- Do you have an account in Dianyi?
- You're also in Dianyi?
Not high-ranked, just level 5 diamond.
Send me your ID! I'll add you.
This one.
You are "Great God of Love"?
That is me.
No way!
- I'm your diehard fan!
- Really?
I've watched all of your competition videos!
I hope that we will have a pleasant collaboration.
Pleasant! It will definitely be pleasant. Pleasant, pleasant!
I met the real Great God of Love.
Continue working hard, okay?
- How about I add you as a friend?
- Okay, okay! Okay!
Look!
Guan Xiaotang. I love you.
Guan Xiaotang! I love you!
You don't regret bringing me along this time, right?
Let me ask you. I told you to let Director Mei win. Why didn't you listen?
- Why should I let him win?
- You want to do business with him.
You have to make him happy.
However, when I do things,
I make myself happy first.
Do you never care about the feelings of others?
I barely care about my own feelings, why would I care about others'?
I'm not going to bring you along to visit clients from now on.
Why not? But...
If I wasn't here this time, you never would've been able to get Director Mei on board.
That was some odd coincidence.
I was using my capabilities to speak for me!
You don't understand how to socialize at all.
I'm just too lazy to be fake.
Besides, do you think those clients are stupid?
That they can't see through your tricks?
Instead of letting them see through you, you might as well take the initiative and pull out the big guns.
Beat them until they become obedient to you.
Then business will come to you with ease.
Where did you learn all these principals from?
It's in my genes.
However, some clients really do get convinced by your methods.
Most clients.
Older Sister, that's why the next time you go on a trip, bring me along.
The two of us can fight side-by-side.
No one will be able to beat us!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After pain is when we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from a crowd of people  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫