Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 41]
He Mu, do you love me?
I feel a bit unwell today so I'm going home to rest now.
We welcome you to come next time!
[Lei Haowen]
[Share your location.]
Lixing, where is the soy sauce?
In the cupboard. Look for it yourself.
Lixing,
are there bigger bowls?
See for yourself.
Stop working, we're having dinner soon.
Time to eat!
It's ready?
Come on, Sushan, let's eat.
You are hungry, right?
Okay. Let's go and eat.
Here.
Sit tight, okay?
Wait a minute. Haven't I told you that
you need to wipe your hands clean before dinner? Otherwise, there will be germs. Did you forget?
Here. Let me wipe them for you, okay?
The other one.
All right, they are clean now. Eat.
Here, I just made some dishes with whatever I could find. Try the noodles.
How is it?
These are the best tasting noodles I've ever had!
- Really?
- Right?
Best tasting? Then eat more, okay?
You should try it, too.
This is the life I want the most.
I work hard out there while you stay home to take care of the house chores and children.
Every day, when I come home, I can see Sushan's adorable smile,
and there will be a hot bowl of noodles to eat.
Tomorrow's the weekend, yes?
You don't have any plans, right?
If you don't,
then help me take Sushan to training class in the morning.
I have some things to take care of at work.
I'll probably be at the company all day.
Okay.
The cleaning lady will also come in the afternoon. You should come and take a look.
Also, kids are usually not used to the food and water in a foreign country.
If you walk past a pharmacy, you should buy some children's medication. I'm afraid she might catch a cold or get sick.
Here.
Eat some vegetables, okay?
I thought you'd never talk to me again.
I don't want to talk to you,
but I can't resist the temptation of large intestines.
I also wanted to cut off ties with you
but then I thought about it and I can't just lose like this.
Then, what do you want to do?
Aren't you still not married yet? Even if you are married,
isn't there the possibility of divorce?
Even if you don't get a divorce,
if you want to have an extramarital affair, then wouldn't I still have hope?
Lei Haowen,
if you still want to be friends with me, then give up on those ideas right now.
Otherwise, I'll leave right now and never see you again.
Hey, hey, hey.
There's no "if," okay? Don't get angry.
Sit, sit, sit.
They're all staring.
Sit down.
You need to give me some time, all right?
You have to let my heart slowly die.
We can only be friends.
Friends. Let's drink.
Here. Your favorite, large intestines.
Lei Haowen,
if I asked to borrow ¥5,000,000 from you, would you?
That's with the assumption that you have that much money.
I'd lend it to you.
I might not be able to return it.
I'll still lend it to you.
Aren't you going to ask what I'm going to do with it?
Nope.
Aren't you afraid that I'll use it to do bad things?
Don't I know you well?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
With your brain, besides buying purses and clothes, what else would you possibly save for?
Hey, don't, don't! There you go again!
Why are you so agitated?
It's fine. Just a couple, a couple arguing.
Stop talking!
Pick up the phone. Pick up the phone.
Did you guys get into an argument?
None of your business.
Right, right. None of my business.
If you could really give me ¥5,000,000, then that would be great.
Why do you want that much money?
It's not me. It's Li Siyu, that prodigal woman.
Why does she want that much money?
Lately, she's been working on a project and needs investments. She's been so anxious, she's about to go crazy soon.
Why are they all blowing into our faces?
Look who's here.
Mommy!
Did you have a good time with your daddy today?
Yes!
I have something to say to you.
I happen to have something to say to you as well.
Be careful.
Okay.
Sister Siyu wants to start a business again.
And it's in collaboration with your lab. Is this reliable?
What do you mean by reliable?
Will the experiment be successful?
There's... a 0.01% chance.
That low?
Then Sister Siyu is really risking too much.
I understand her.
The risk is worth it if you can do the thing you like.
This is something that you want to do as well?
Yes.
After graduating from graduate school, I wanted to continue working in research
but my rational side told me that I should get a better job.
That way I didn't have to worry about anything in this lifetime.
That's why I entered my old workplace.
You spent ten years there.
To be honest, in those ten years,
I had many thoughts of changing my career,
but I was afraid to start over. I just thought about it. That's it.
Then, did your wish come true now?
Of course.
Right now, even though I have a very low salary, every day is very fulfilling.
Although the experiment keeps failing,
but to a researcher, failing is very normal.
Then what if... in the end, you still fail?
What does "the end" mean?
Success is the only ending.
As long as we haven't succeeded, it is not the end.
You were never like this before. You've always wanted stability.
That's because when I was young, my living conditions weren't well. I couldn't afford to make mistakes.
So every step I took, I had to be sure.
However, after experiencing everything that's happened in the past two years,
I found that
life is full of unforeseen circumstances.
No matter how careful and cautious you are,
in the end, you may still fall into a pit.
So, instead of being overly cautious and indecisive, I would rather choose something I like
and put my heart and soul into it.
You've changed.
You have also changed.
In the past, we would never discuss things like this.
You never asked either.
I would have never thought that we could talk like this after getting divorced.
It looks like being divorced is better.
I've thought about it.
It's better if I return this to you.
Are you certain?
Of what?
Yuwei told me already.
Then after you go to Europe with him, will you continue to work?
His company's benefits are very good. Once we're there, I won't have to work.
Don't worry. He treats Yuwei and I very well
Zhizhi, I'm actually pretty happy.
I don't have money nor many capabilities.
If you were with me, you'd have to keep working. That would be too hard for you.
But Sushan's dad is completely different.
With him,
you can live without worries.
That's pretty good.
Liu Yang,
I have never looked down on the fact that you were poor.
I know.
Zhizhi, you are an amazing wife.
The best wife on this Earth.
It is I who is not worthy of you.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Honestly,
I like working.
If you like it, then go do it.
Don't let yourself regret anything.
You should keep this. I owed it to you.
I'm back.
What are you doing?
What is going on?
I looked into it already.
It's better to sell these bags on Huafer.
(T/N: a Chinese website used to sell specifically high-quality items)
You get much more money than secondhand shops.
Xiaoling, all of these are your beloved items.
I'm most annoyed when I see you like this. Can't you just be cool about it?
Fine. After I make money, I'll buy them all back for you.
- You need to get more than just them for me!
- I'll buy you twice as many things!
Deal!
Answer the phone.
Hello?
Xiaoling, let's have dinner together.
Let's go to your favorite French restaurant.
Today is not a date night though.
Oh... One of my clients suddenly had something come up, so I have free time now.
So we can meet up.
I have a guest at my house.
I can't go.
Can you see if you can make time?
We didn't meet last week either.
I cannot make time. She's leaving Shanghai tomorrow.
Okay. I hope you two have fun then.
Did you two get into an argument?
It would be great if we actually argued.
Then what happened?
I asked to borrow money from him. Not only did he say no, but he also went off on a long lecture.
Xiaoling, in regards to lending money, people do it out of kindness but are not obligated to do it.
I think that He Mu's actions were not unreasonable.
But you're my older sister, and it was me who asked.
So what?
First of all, the two of you are not yet married. Second of all, even if you were married,
he still has no obligation to help me.
He's so boring. Why would I marry him?
It's because he is rich. However, now that I need money,
not only does he do nothing, but he—
Why would I get married to him?
Xiaoling, break up with He Mu.
Not because he won't lend me money but because of what you just said.
What did I just say?
You were going to marry him for money.
What's wrong with that?
There's nothing wrong with that.
However, a happy marriage comes from love, not from money.
You still believe in love?
I've always believed in it.
You and Chen Yiming loved each other so much, but you two still broke up, didn't you?
Chen Yiming and I broke up because we didn't love each other enough.
The two of you were engaged yet you two didn't love each other enough?
Perhaps our love was just enough to get engaged.
Now that I think about it, when two people are truly together,
they need to sacrifice bits of themselves,
and, more importantly, they must be brave enough to face life's pressures.
But I wasn't ready for any of that.
When did you figure all of these things out?
After Laidianle failed.
On that day, I looked at myself in the mirror.
I was anxious, impetuous, and paranoid.
I wanted instant success and was defiant.
Even I loathed that woman.
What right do I have to ask someone else to love me?
Then, what about now?
Now... Don't you think I'm very cute?
Then...
If another person appears in your life, how would you love him?
I definitely would still put my heart and soul into loving him.
You have already "hit a wall causing your head to bleed",  yet you still don't know to change. (T/N: already been brutally hurt once before by someone who does not reciprocate)
Since my head already bled, then it's even more important that I don't change.
What if I hit the wall a few more times and it falls? Then I win!
I hope you will be happy.
Xiaoling, I also wish that you will be happy.
Don't marry someone because of money.
If you only have love, then you will starve to death.
If you only have love then you will starve to death!
Let go.
I can't communicate with you.
Hurry and think about what else we can sell.
Hey, take a look at my purse, how much do you think it's worth?
Maybe a bit over ¥1,000?
Then let's sell it.
How did I forget about Guan Xiaotang?
Look at the female superhero I made.
That's awesome.
Let's have her sit here, all right?
Zhizhi,
I'm sorry. I wasn't able to keep you.
Director Yuan, you already did your best.
To tell you the truth, Lubao is not the same as before.
Even I don't know how long I'll be able to stay there.
Hey, how old is Yuwei this year?
She's five.
When I got divorced, Meng Meng was also five years old.
Director Yuan, can I ask you a personal question?
Go ahead.
Raising Meng Meng alone, was it very hard?
Of course.
Did you ever think about reconciling with Meng Meng's dad
or find someone else to marry?
Do you think that two people spending their days together would definitely be easier than spending your days alone?
For normal people like us, nothing is easy.
Since life is difficult anyways,
then let's pick the thing that gives us the best reward.
What gives the best rewards?
A stronger self, of course.
A stronger self?
Yes.
All these years, raising Meng Meng alone, I had faced many hardships.
I had neither support nor a way out.
I had to face everything and carry all the burden myself.
Over time,
I had gotten myself several ailments.
My reputation also became bad,
but I gained skills as well as courage.
Things that belong to me, no one can take these assets away from me.
Yes.
Before getting a divorce, I never would've thought I could be a saleswoman.
After divorcing, I have become one of the backbones of the sales department.
Speaking of that,
Director Yuan, a toast to you. Thank you for taking me in.
No need to thank me.
I was so harsh to you in the past. As long as you don't hold a grudge towards me, it's fine.
Then I need to thank you even more. Good thing you pressured me then; otherwise, the person I am today would not exist.
If you must thank someone, thank yourself.
The you today didn't come about because of me, but because of yourself.
Thank you, and thank you, to my dear self.
Remember, we can lose anything but ourselves.
I will remember.
Cheers.
You two, are you full?
- Yes.
Do you want to eat some more?
- No need.
- Thank you.
You don't want more?
Xiaotang! Do you still want this computer? If not, I'm taking it away.
Take it. If you like the computer desk chair, you can have that as well.
Thank you!
Xiaotang, I will take the water machine!
Xiaotang, I'm taking these two lights!
Take it. Take it.
If you want something, just take it.
Your company collapsed faster than Laidianle.
Wow! My goodness! Older sister! I want to kiss and hug—
Hug and hold you up high.
Don't move.
I won't, I won't.
Older Sister, why are you here? Did you miss me?
Oh! You've been enlightened.
You want to suddenly start dating.
What's happening here?
It just flopped.
Oh, right, Older Sister!  If you want anything, you can take it.
However,...I think the best thing for you to take is me.
Out of everything here, you are worth the least.
Why are you so bad at recognizing product value?
I came here for business.
You-You go ahead.
How much money do you still have?
I... don't have cash. Let me see.
I still have ¥73 in my Alipay account. Oh, I also have a card.
This card has a limit of ¥500,000,
but I think there's only ¥3 left.
This... I think this one still has ¥30.
This has been frozen.
This is useless, too.
Oh right, on Wechat, I-I-I still have 30 something yuan.
Wh-Why so little?
I've always been poor, it's not like you don't know.
What about your car?
I mortgaged it to my friend.
It was worth over ¥1,000,000!
Look around. Starting a company "burns money." It's not like you haven't done it before.
If I had known earlier...
- W-W-What's wrong, Older Sister? Are you in need of money?
- Yes.
How much do you need?
¥5,000,000.
That's nothing.
You're already like this yet you are saying "that's nothing"?
Even though I don't have money, Old Guan does.
- Your dad?
- Yeah.
Oh, right! We can get him to invest in this project!
I've got this.
Hey, Guan Xiaotang.
Let me be clear. This is just business, nothing else is involved.
Oh! You're afraid that I would use money to blackmail you into h—
Shut up!
It's fine. That won't happen. Impossible!
At most, I'd just use the money to blackmail you into being my girlfriend, I would never use it to m—
- Shut up!
- But we're—
If you keep talking, I'll hit you.
Hit me, hit me, hit me!
Hit me! Hit me! I don't believe it. What are you doing?!
- Broom!
- Broom?
The broom is over there!
Broom. I— hey, do I need to take my pants off before you hit me?
Wait, wait. First, hit my butt. I need to call my dad.
Don't always be hitting my face.
- It's fine. You can hit me.
- Hello, the number you have dialed cannot be connected to right now. Sorry.
I'll call Sister Meiying then.
Hit me. It's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
If you don't hit me, then I—
Hello, Sister Meiying.
Um, where's my dad?
Oh. Okay, I got it.
Are you hitting me or not? I've been lying here for so long! Are you going to or not?
If you aren't, then let's go.
Where to?
To ask Old Guan for money! Let's go! Look how happy you are.
Let go!
As long as your father is willing to give me 30 minutes, I'm confident I can persuade him into investing.
It's not that bothersome. Just tell him that it will surely generate money. Then he'll definitely invest.
I really can't guarantee that.
That's fine, too.
Isn't it just ¥5,000,000? If he doesn't lose it on you, then it'll just be lost on someone else.
Does your dad often lose his money?
In this past year, that seems to happen a lot.
It's upstairs.
- Hey, Sister Meiying.
- How come you're here?
I have an urgent matter to talk to my dad about.
Oh, he's treating people to a meal inside.
Let me bring this wine in first.
Hey. How much has he drunk already?
There are four people. They've already had four bottles. This is the fifth.
Oh... Then hurry and bring it to them.
- Sit.
- Okay.
I understand his alcohol tolerance. If we let him have one more bottle, your investment will be a done deal.
Here.
The wine is here. The wine is here
Great.
- More wine?
- Having wine with you makes me happy.
Old Guan, your stomach is in bad shape.
If you keep drinking, your stomach will bleed again.
Being able to drink with you,
even if my stomach bleeds...
Your dad also has a stomach ailment and can't drink wine?
He has a stomach ailment?
I-I didn't know.
Older Brother, I shall drink first as a sign of respect.
Director Wang, you must drink some more today.
Not bad, right?
Um, in regards to the loan from the bank,
- I would like to bother you to help me with that.
- Old Guan.
It's not that I don't want to help you,
but this matter really won't be approved by the company.
You and the company should make some arrangements.
That's right, Old Brother. We must trouble you for this.
All right?
How about you repay the ¥30,000,000 from before first?
Then I can approve the ¥5,000,000 for you immediately.
If you loan me this ¥5,000,000, and let me make a capital turnover,
I'll surely be able to return not just the the ¥30,000,000,
but also the ¥50,000,000 from before!
I really cannot approve it.
Old Brother.
Let me tell you the truth.
Right now, my company just needs one more breath of life.
If you let me take this one breath,
then I am willing to do anything.
I really can't. I really can't loan you this ¥5,000,000.
T-Then... just ¥3,000,000 then!
¥2,000,000!
As long as you can loan me this sum of money,
then my company will survive!
Older Brother, I'm begging you.
During these past few decades,
who have I ever begged? Tell me.
I'll get on my knees right here, right now.
- Old Guan, Old Guan, Old Guan.
- Old Guan.
Get up. Quickly get up.
Fine, fine. I'll promise you.
He promised.
- Get up, Old Guan, okay?
- Thank you, Older Brother. Thank you.
Thank you, Brother.
You really just saved my whole family's life.
Xiaotang.
I... I always thought that he had it easy.
The truth is, no one has an easy life.
My dad...
For a few million yuan, he got on his knees in front of someone.
Yet I still burned through his money like that.
I'm really— I'm really—
Even if you beat yourself to death, it would be useless.
Guan Xiaotang, look at me.
Look at me.
Guan Xiaotang, your father is going through his most difficult time right now.
If you want to help him,
go in there poised and with dignity,
to toast to all of the uncles in there.
You show that you're very sensible,
capable, and self-confident.
You want the uncles to see
that there is a successor in the family, that the company has a hope and a future.
That the money they loan out will be returned.
That way they will easily lend money to your dad.
Bu-But your situation...
No need to care about me. I have other ways to get what I need.
This.
This should be worth some money.
It should be able to help your dad.
Older Sister,
so-sorry.
Xiaotang,
if you can help your father get through this hard time,
then you would have truly matured.
By then,
would you consider me?
Your family is in chaos right now,
so don't be immersed into love.
Right now, your father needs you.
Hurry and go in.
Wipe your tears dry.
Dad. Uncles.
Come, come, come.
My son. Come here.
- How much have you drank?
- Say hi to Uncle Li.
Where's Li Siyu?
She's already inside.
Li Siyu.
President Zhang.
The group's Sales Director position has been kept open for you this whole time.
None of the terms have changed.
Thank you for your kindness, President Zhang.
How's it going? When do you plan on reporting for work?
Come over here and sit.
President Zhang,
I came today for a different reason.
What reason? Tell me.
I want to borrow money from you.
How much?
¥5,000,000.
For what?
Research on membrane-less batteries.
That is... Gao Zhengdao has been researching that.
You know of him?
I've heard.
But this project...
doesn't seems to be progressing smoothly.
The prospect is not optimistic as well.
All of the investments have been withdrawn. Is that true?
That's why I came to find you.
This... You have to know
that no one is optimistic about this project.
If everyone did, then I'd have no chance.
President Zhang. ¥5,000,000.
I will borrow it for a year. After one year, I will repay you ¥5.8 million.
Then what will you use as collateral?
All of my assets,
including my car, were all invested into the Laidianle project.
I have nothing right now.
I don't really have anything to use as collateral.
If you don't have anything as collateral,
then I really cannot accept such a thing.
What if I used myself as collateral?
What you mean is...?
Haven't you always wished that I join Qiji?
Once a year has passed and I cannot repay this money,
then I will join Qiji Group and work for you for ten years, free of charge.
This condition you offer,...
I really can't reject it.
However,
I can only lend you ¥3,000,000.
In a year, repay me ¥4,000,000.
You also need to use your ten years of a labor contract as collateral.
Can you accept that?
Zhang Yanzhou, you old sly fox.
You just realized?
I accept.
Deal.
Come in.
Director Su, a delivery for you.
Help me put it on the desk.
Okay.
What is this?
[I'm sorry.]
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫ Listen to me about the latest news ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫ Learned to let go ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫ We are so small yet so determined ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫ Listen to the voice inside ♫
♫ The sky has finally cleared ♫