Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 25]
The information that I got was that GM Pan rejected the idea
and insisted on waiting until you came back. Director Fang didn't really say anything,
but a lot of mid-tier employees want to sign a letter
to invite Yuan Huizhong back.
Then, what did they decide in the end?
The Board of Directors plans to decide via voting.
Right, the Board of Directors now has a new member.
She is also a new shareholder of the company.
Sister Ziru?
How about you go talk to GM Pan?
Go talk to him and have him reinstate you early.
This way, Director Fang and Yuan Huizhong will give up.
We'll be voting next week.
Do we have a chance?
There are nine people on the Board of Directors.
Old Feng, Old Qin, and I will vote you for sure.
Pan Zhiyong,
the Finance Department, and the R&D Department will definitely vote for Li Siyu.
What about the other three votes?
Ma Chao, Shi Xin, and the new shareholder.
Who's the n-new shareholder?
She does financing. We met once, during the signing of the contract.
but we've never had a real interaction before.
If she doesn't understand the situation,
then she'll definitely listen to Pan Zhiyong and vote Li Siyu.
I talked to Ma Chao and Shi Xin privately,
but their attitude towards this
is not obvious.
Since Pan Zhiyong was the one who suggested to make the decision through voting,
he must be quite certain about the outcome.
Sister Ziru, Yiming won't let me drink wine,
so I'll use tea in place of it. Congratulations!
Speaking of it, I must thank you for all this.
If you didn't connect us all together, this never would have happened.
You've heard of my situation already, haven't you?
I've heard.
After we signed the contract, GM Pan explained the whole situation to me.
Siyu, you had to take the blame for the company.
I have to do what's best for the company. GM Pan also treats me well.
Taking the blame for the company is my duty.
As Lubao's shareholder, I thank you.
Thank you for being understanding, Sister Ziru.
Sister Ziru, I heard some news
about how the company's Board of Directors
is preparing to discuss who the new sales director should be.
Yes. The meeting is next week.
What do you think about this?
Right now, I'm Lubao's shareholder. Of course,
I will do whatever is most beneficial for Lubao.
I'm the most suitable for the position then.
Whether it's personal performance, team performance,
or the new records we made when I was the Sales Director,
all of these things can prove my capability.
But Director Fang recommended Yuan Huizhong,
and many of the executives support that.
Half a year ago, Sister Yuan and I
already had a competition to show who is better.
I've heard you talk about it before.
There's something else that I'm not sure whether GM Pan has told you or not.
At the time, when he suspended me, it was only temporary.
His plan was that when the situation had calmed down,
he would reinstate me.
He did tell me that.
From the start of my suspension till now,
it's been a long time.
People have also stopped bringing it up online.
Also, Lubao's sales
can't be left unattended,
so I think this is the best time for me to be reinstated.
Sister Ziru, if the Board of Directors talks about it,
whether it's in regards to work or personal relations, whether it is for sentiments or logical reasons,
I hope you will support me.
Siyu, the Lubao worker
I've known longest and talked to most is you.
From you, I saw Lubao's qualities.
I also saw Lubao's future.
That's why I made the decision to invest in it.
Do you understand what I mean?
Sister Ziru, thank you.
Dad.
What happened to me?
You fainted on the street.
Some kind people brought you to the hospital.
The doctors have diagnosed it
as Diabetic Nephropathy Stage Three.
What kind of illness is that?
Can it be cured?
The doctors say that it's in the early stages right now.
Your kidney damage is still reversible.
However, the treatment period may be long.
If you recover well, you will be able to live and work normally.
Recover...
Don't think about anything, just treat your illness first.
Zhizhi, I didn't think
that you would come and visit me.
After all,
you are Yuwei's father.
How has the Sales Department been doing lately?
Not great. There are so many rumors, and everyone feels disheartened.
However, the three of us have been the same as always.
Sis, we know that you will return sooner or later,
so the few of us have not slacked off.
I guess you are all smart.
Sister Siyu, when are you coming back?
After the Board of Directors has their meeting, we'll know.
- When the Board of Directors meeting?
- In the next few days.
Sister Siyu, we'll only feel at ease after you return.
We can't wait.
When I come back, I plan to rearrange the Sales Department.
You guys should be prepared.
- Got it!
Here, take a look.
If you have any concerns or suggestions, reach out to me at any time.
GM Wang, you wanted to see me?
- Yiming, come sit.
- Okay.
There's something I wanted your opinion on.
Tell me.
Siyu came looking for me a few days ago.
She hopes that at Lubao's Board of Directors meeting,
I will support her reinstatement.
She still hasn't given up on that thought?
I understand it.
In order to become the sales director, she worked very hard.
Of course, she doesn't want to give up so easily.
But she...
she's a little obsessed with it right now.
Yiming, from a business perspective,
Siyu's contributions to Lubao can be clearly seen by anyone.
She is also very qualified to be the sales director.
From a personal perspective, she and I have a friendship.
I am obligated to support her.
I wanted to hear your opinion about this.
I heard GM Pan say that after Lubao's incident,
you were the one who wrote all of the public relations responses.
Yes.
At the time, I advised Siyu to take the blame and resign,
but because GM Pan
values Siyu so much
he changed the resignation into a suspension.
Then from a crisis public relations perspective,
do you think Siyu is suitable to be reinstated?
She is very unsuitable.
I remember you'd said that Siyu's health wasn't very good either.
You also wish that she will resign or choose a less stressful job.
Yes, that's what I care about more.
Last week, I also tried to persuade her into doing that.
Then Yiming, should I vote against her?
GM Wang, as your subordinate,
and as Tianye Group's employee, I will definitely advise you to vote against her,
but as Siyu's f-fiancé,
I feel quite conflicted.
On the one hand, I want her to be happy,
to do what she wants, and to make her dreams come true;
but on the other hand, if she continues to be the sales director,
then her health, our relationship,
or even our future family might be affected negatively.
You have made this a hard decision for me.
GM Wang, don't you often talk about roles?
I think you should go back to playing your role
and not care too much about what I just said.
Decide how you think you should decide.
I don't have any prejudice against Li Siyu.
When it comes to capabilities, she is impeccable
but she just created a huge problem.
If we let her be reinstated,
what will the other employees think?
What will the clients think?
How would the public evaluate it?
But don't forget
Yuan Huizhong did something even worse before.
The truth about that has already come out.
The police just recently solved the case.
The con artists actually had no relations to Yuan Huizhong.
Still, the economic losses that she caused us cannot be fixed.
Yuan Huizhong did not ruin the company's reputation though.
I also think Yuan Huizhong's capability, compared to Li Siyu's,
is almost exactly the same.
Also, we wouldn't risk ruining public relations with her.
She is more suitable to be the sales director.
Li Siyu's capability is still better than Yuan Huizhong's.
These two candidates are very outstanding.
Honestly, I don't even know who I'm supposed to vote for.
However, as the Board of Directors, we do not only represent ourselves,
but we also represent all of Lubao's shareholders and employees.
So, please do not think from your own perspective when trying to solve this problem.
Do your best to stand a little taller and consider things from a broader perspective.
Since Director Fang mentioned all of the shareholders
and all of the employees, I need to remind everyone
that a few days ago, the office
received a letter from company executives a few days ago.
They all agree
to ask Yuan Huizhong to return to the company.
- How many people signed it?
- Eighteen people.
However, they are the backbones of this company.
GM Wang, in total, Lubao has 652 employees.
The letter is here. Everyone can take a look.
There's no need to look.
I still have a meeting after this, and GM Wang is also busy.
How about we follow the old rules
and vote on the decision?
All right. There are two boxes in front of everyone.
The red one represents Li Siyu, and the green one represents Yuan Huizhong.
Put your pencil into the box of the person
who you think would be more suitable for sales director.
[Yuan - Li ]
[Yuan 0 : Li 1]
[Yuan 0 : Li 2]
[Yuan 0 : Li 3]
[Yuan 1 : Li 3]
[Yuan 2 : Li 3]
[Yuan 3 : Li 3]
[Yuan 3 : Li 4]
[Yuan 4 : Li 4]
GM Wang still hasn't voted.
GM Wang, please cast your vote quickly.
[Yuan 5 : Li 4]
Li Siyu, four votes.
Yuan Huizhong, five votes.
According to the voting results,
the sales director will be Yuan Huizhong.
I still have business to attend to.
GM Wang.
Director Fang, there has been no one to manage the sales department for a while now.
I think we should announce the decision quickly.
Okay.
Siyu,
the results of the Board of Directors voting has come out.
It is... Yuan Huizhong.
Siyu, this was the decision of the Board of Directors.
Hello? Hello? Siyu?
Siyu?
Is there a possibility that this result can change?
How did it come to this result?
It is will be like this for now.
Then I... can't go back to Lubao?
How could this have happened?
I did all of these things for Lubao!
GM Pan, you promised me!
I did promise you, but things changed.
Aren't you the person in charge at Lubao?
Li Siyu, please calm down. Okay?
The Board of Directors is not just me. There are nine of us.
- But—
- First calm down. Calm down.
There's something I must tell you.
Today, at the Board of Directors meeting,
between you and Yuan Huizhong,
Wang Ziru made the most important vote.
What do you mean?
She voted for Yuan Huizhong.
Impossible!
Before the meeting, I calculated it.
Even if Wang Ziru didn't help you, she would help me
because when we signed the contract, she promised me
that at the Board of Directors meeting, she would side with me unconditionally.
That was the reason why I decided that the decision should be made through voting.
I didn't think this would be the result.
Why would she do this?
That's right, why?
You should ask her personally.
Thanks, Senior Brother.
Don't need to thank me.
I did this for everyone and for Lubao.
Once I take care of things here, I will report to Lubao immediately.
After you get back to the company, when you meet the shareholder, Wang Ziru,
you need to be cautious.
The woman from Tianye Group?
You were able to come back because she made the most important vote.
Didn't you say that she and Li Siyu had a good relationship,
and Li Siyu was the one who introduced her to Old Pan?
That's why I think she's very strange.
Could it be that she has some other motives?
I don't know.
GM Wang, Li Siyu is downstairs. She wants to see you.
Where is Chen Yiming right now?
Okay, okay.
Ms. Li, GM Wang will see you. This way, please.
Ms. Li is here? This way, please.
GM Wang, Ms. Li is here.
Siyu is here? Come.
Sit over here.
Come.
This is your first time coming to my office, right?
- I want to know why.
- What?
What are you referring to?
You promised that you would support me.
Why did you fail to keep your words?
Did I say that?
You won't even admit it?
Think about it.
What exactly did I say?
Siyu, the person I've known the longest
and the person I have interacted most with from Lubao, is you.
From you, I saw Lubao's qualities
and I also saw Lubao's future.
That's why I chose to invest in it.
I guess I misunderstood.
Siyu, I approve of you, but
this doesn't mean that you are the best for the sales director position.
In your eyes,
Yuan Huizhong is more suitable than I am?
The truth is, you are both suitable.
But after thinking about some other reasons,
I decided to vote for her.
What reasons?
You really shouldn't ask me that.
Then who should I ask?
Our first installment is almost ¥4 million–
- Chen Yiming! Why did you do that?
- Director Chen, I couldn't stop her.
Don't worry. You can go back to work.
What gives you the right to take away my right to work?
Siyu, we are in the office, please calm down. Let's talk outside.
I originally had my own office. Because of you, I have nothing!
What are you saying?
Stop acting! You always do what you want to do and never care about my feelings!
I'm working right now. Let's talk when we get home.
Don't touch me!
You think that because you wrecked my chances at being the sales director
that I will obediently go home with you and get married to you,
to be your housewife.
Let me tell you. Impossible!
- Siyu.
- We're breaking up!
I apologize, some personal problems. It's nothing. Let's continue.
- Where did we get to?
- The first installment is ¥4 million.
- Yes, right. The first installment is ¥4 million.
Yiming.
GM Wang.
Earlier, Siyu came looking for me.
Right, she just left from here.
In the vote for Lubao's sales director... I gave it to Yuan Huizhong.
She came to question me just now and I accidentally mentioned you.
I figured.
- I'm really sorry.
- Don't. President Wang, you don't need to apologize to me.
It's not your problem, it's a problem between Siyu and I.
It didn't impact your relationship, right?
- She just told me she wanted to break up.
- What?
How about I go and talk to her?
No need.
You don't need to talk to her.
She should know that you're doing this for her own good.
She can't understand that right now.
How did this happen?
I was originally thinking that once her health was better
I could find her a less stressful job here at the company.
President Wang, please don't.
You've already done enough for us both. Really.
How about I give you a three-day break? Go keep her company and explain things to her.
There's no need. I don't want to explain anymore.
You guys...
aren't really going to break up, right?
I don't know.
All right.
Yiming,
if you need any help or want to vent,
I am here.
Okay. Thank you, Sister Ziru.
Stop drinking!
Aren't you not allowed to drink? Give it to me.
I'm going through a heartbreak, can't I drink my sorrows away?
Yiming did this for your own good.
In this world, the most selfish words are
"I'm doing it for your own good."
What?
Do you know...
what words goes before that?
It is, "I am right
and you are wrong so you must listen to me.
You must follow my plans and be the type of girl I like."
Yiming isn't that bossy, right?
That's what he did.
No matter how much I liked this job,
but because he doesn't like it, he made them fire me.
He's not selfish. He really is doing it for your own good.
"For your own good."
Just because other people think it's good, it doesn't mean it's good.
It's only good if I think it is good.
You guys think that I should stay at home and be pretty.
No. I just want to go out there and fight for what I want.
You guys think I can't be the sales director,
yet that is exactly what I want to be.
Then, what do you want to do?
Not only will I become the sales director,
I will also be the general manager, the chairwoman.
I want them all to regret their decision today.
All right.
How are you?
I'm a lot better.
Zhizhi cooked these for you, right?
Yes.
Does she come to take care of you every day?
Oh, you. You used to blabber about how Zhizhi is like this or Zhizhi is like that ,
but look how good of a wife she is. Right?
Can we not talk about it?
All right, we won't talk about it.
Right now, take care of your health.
Once you get out of the hospital, find a job.
After that, you should commit yourself to a life with Zhizhi.
Eat it.
I also think the same way.
I just don't know what Zhizhi thinks.
She must think like this, too.
Would she be stupid? She makes food for you and take care of you every day.
Let's not talk about me.
What's wrong with Yiming? Why does he look so depressed?
Siyu wants to break up with him.
What? Want to break up?
Siyu and Yiming are talking about breaking up.
How is that possible?
Yiming, wake up! Wake up!
Tell me. What happened? Why did you break up?
Say something.
Perhaps we are not suitable to get married to each other.
You can't say those words so casually.
But is that the case?
Before, with just one glance, we understood each other.
Now, I don't approve of what she wants
and she doesn't understand the things I do.
Then you should work hard to get back to what it was like before.
You make it sound easy. How have I not been working hard? Haven't I been working hard this whole time?
Right now, she—
- She said that she wants to break up with me.
- Even if she says that,
you still can't let go of her that easily. I am your warning from past experience.
But this time,
I'm really tired this time.
No matter how tired you are, you have to communicate with Siyu.
I remember something you said before.
"If you're a man,
you have to take action."
He's right. You're a man. You have to take initiative. Go find Siyu and talk.
Something happened! If you don't come back, we won't be able to be the best man and bridesmaid!
I'll change my flight right now! I'll be back tomorrow!
How do I look?
Though I haven't fully recovered, the woman standing in front of you right now is the Gu Xiaoling from ten years ago.
Let's go.
How is Zhizhi?
Say something.
I left for only half a month, yet so much has happened.
It seems that I am the one who "home-guards" out of the three of us.
(T/N: slang for staying at home all the time instead of going out to have fun and cause trouble)
That's right. Not only do you "home-guard," but you also protect against disasters.
How do you plan on welcoming me back?
I reserved a restaurant.
Just us two?
Zhizhi has to go to the hospital to see Liu Yang. She won't make it.
Come in.
Director Fang, please sign this.
Thank you, Director Fang.
[Stranger]
Director Fang, I have booked a private room at Hanhai Hall.
I want to ask about Lubao's future developments.
Awaiting your favorable reply, Wang Ziru.
I'm going to go to the restroom.
I'm here. I'm already inside.
Yes.
Where are you?
On the left? The le—
I'm hanging up.
Haowen asked me to come here.
How is it?
This place has pretty good food.
There are lots of good things to eat here. We can get more.
The environment is also good.
You're really good at finding places to eat.
Of course. Could you ever go wrong with what the God of Food recommends?
Here. Let's have a drink.
What are you staring at? Have you never seen a pretty woman before?
I have, but I've never seen one as beautiful as you.
The thing is, you're already quite old, yet you can be so beautiful.
Lei Haowen, do you want to cut all your ties with me?
What do you mean by cutting our ties?
- Lei Haowen!
- Hey, don't, don't, don't.
I was wrong. I won't say that again. Never again.
Here, I'll compensate you. Here, instestines, your favorite food.
You've probably missed it, haven't you? Try it.
It's still very good.
What do you think the two of them are doing right now?
According to my understanding of Chen Yiming,
he is probably apologizing and reflecting on his wrongdoings.
According to my understanding of Li Siyu, she definitely will become soft-hearted.
And then, Yiming will say a few more sweet words,
and then Li Siyu won't be able to control her tears.
The two of them will hug.
They will promise to never separate from each other again.
They will reunite.
You and I make a great pair of partners in providing great services to mankind.
Here, cheers to the best man and bridesmaid getting their jobs back!
I really never expected
that losing the position of sales director would hurt you this much.
I should've comforted you immediately.
But at that time, I didn't think to use your perspective to think about the problem.
It was my fault. I'm sorry.
I was also too impulsive that day.
No matter what the reason was,
I shouldn't have caused such a big scene at your workplace.
Siyu,
I think I need to explain this situation again.
At that time, Sister Ziru did ask me, s-she asked me about my opinion,
and I did say something about not wanting you reinstated,
but I really did say that for myself.
I really was just worried about you.
When I was at the hospital,
looking at your examination report,
did you know what my mood was?
You've been with me for over five years. You've done so much for me,
yet I didn't take care of you well enough.
If in the future, I can't even help take care of your body,
then what would be the purpose of having me as a husband?
Siyu,
let's not break up.
Okay?
Let me take care of you.
I know.
You want to have your own career.
It's no problem. I will support you.
But... our first priority
is to better your health.
I understand my own health problems.
What do you understand? Huh?
Tell me what you understand.
The doctor is the one who makes the decisions.
When the doctor says that your body has fully recovered,
then I will let you go out there to work hard for your career.
When will that be?
A year? Two years?
This isn't an issue of time.
As long as your body gets better, you can go out
there whenever you want.
Also, we can use this time
to take care of our wedding.
But my career
might be continuously delayed this way.
But you... even if you want
to work right now, but you can't go back to Lubao anymore.
I don't need to go back to Lubao.
There are lots of things I can do.
Then, what would you like to do?
I want to start my own business.
Start a business?
Starting a business is a good thing,
but can't you start a business at any time?
But real opportunities are fleeting.
Why are you so anxious?
In the future...
Won't there be more suitable times?
Because—
Because I'm already over 30 years old.
Because I just lost
everything I had at Lubao,
so how could I not be anxious?
Siyu...
Why don't you understand?
Ever since we've been together,
you aren't alone anymore.
You still have me.
Everything that is mine is yours.
Trust me.
Trust me. I will have the capability
to take care of everything for you.
Let's get married first,
then take care of your health, and then we will take
care of everything else one by one.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫