Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 2]
Sister Yuan.
Hi, Siyu.
- You worked hard yesterday.
- It's not a big deal.
There's no problem with this season, right?
- Not yet.
- Really still not.
Not everyone is like you.
I'll think it over again and see where else I can go for more orders.
- Never mind. You haven't taken a break for two weeks. If we come up short, so be it.
- No way.
Now's the crucial time that will determine if you can be promoted to Director. We can't let up now.
What's wrong?
Recently, my stomach keeps acting up from time to time.
Come to my office for a bit.
I'll go set down my bag.
- Morning, Sister Siyu.
- Good morning, Sister Siyu.
- Good morning.
Take this.
I haven't even finished the ones you gave me before.
- Keep it in reserve. You should take care of your stomach. Pay attention to how you eat.
- Thank you.
Get an invoice. I'm going to give you an extra ¥500, take it as a bonus for your overtime.
I should claim my overtime, too.
You want the ¥500 for normal work?
Okay. I'll speak with Director Fang. He has to sign for it.
Go on.
[Financial Department]
You're welcome. Take care.
Sister Siyu.
In the end, did Brother Yiming propose to you yesterday?
He wanted to propose.
But I stopped him.
Why?
I don't really know either.
Do you have some other plans?
What other plans could I have?
If I get married to anyone in this life, it will be to Chen Yiming.
Then, why are you hesitating? You've been dating for 4 or 5 years.
Four years and five months.
Then, you should get married.
Liu Yang and I only knew each other for 6 months before we got married.
Zhizhi, from the time before you and Liu Yang got married,
are there things about your life as a single woman that it's hard to live without?
No.
Back then, I was really anxious to be with him.
But I...
When I'm with him, I really happy too.
But when I think about getting married,
think about how I'd be a wife, then a mother...
I feel a bit panicky.
Could you be overthinking it?
Maybe.
So here you are, Siyu.
- You're looking for me.
- Director Pan wants to see you in his office.
Come here. Everyone. Come over here.
- What's up?
- I just heard that they laid off some people in the department next door.
- Layoffs again?
Tell me. Will our department be next?
- I'm wondering about that.
- Yes.
If this keeps up, we...
You're speculating, right?
Boss, the Administration Department laid off three more people today.
Don't worry. Those layoffs won't come to our department.
Boss, the Tactics Department laid off two as well.
That's true.
In those departments, there are three people to do the work of one. If there are layoffs, who else would they lay off?
In our Planning Department, each one of you does the work of three people. What are you afraid of?
You should get back to work on those plans for the Mid-Autumn Festival.
We need the price for social media, then there are replies from the advertising companies.
- Hurry. Get those to me.
- Hurry. Let's get to work on them.
- Let me tell you.
- What do you think will happen?
- We can't go on like this.
- Why?
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- What's up?
- After we left yesterday, did you propose to her?
No.
The high moon on a beautiful night. So romantic.
- Just the right atmosphere for a proposal.
- That's true, isn't it?
- Then, why didn't you act?
- I'm not sure.
If you're not sure, or is she unsure?
Maybe both of us.
Women... really need to feel secure.
She doesn't feel secure?
That's true. You're young, smart, and talented.
Everything about you is great.
If I were a woman, I'd be willing to marry you.
That's about enough.
You didn't come to see me just to ask me about the proposal, did you?
- Of course not.
- Go on, then.
Help me get a date with Gu Xiaoling.
What are you doing? You already have Gu Xiaoling's WeChat, don't you?
I've been blocked.
[Message: Blocked]
- That was quick.
- Help me out.
- I can't help you.
- Why?
If someone's blocked you, it means they aren't interested in you.
But I'm extremely interested in her.
The type of person Gu Xiaoling wants for a boyfriend
would scare you.
Maybe she'll come to value true love with me.
Wake up, okay?
If I can't make it work with her, what about her back up?
- You're not qualified.
- Then just in case.
How can you be so cheap?
That's just the way I am.
Right now, everyone in the company is worried about being laid off.
How do you have the heart to think about all this?
What do I have to be afraid of? I'm a second-generation rich guy.
When did you become a second-generation rich guy?
Doesn't my father's name include the word for "rich"?
- What's up.
- Please come to the Human Resources Department.
Director Wang wants me to go to the Human Resources Department.
- Help me arrange a date.
- Go away.
- Arrange it.
I need to talk you about something.
Xing Dian stopped production yesterday.
What's the reason for that?
Not enough orders, financial difficulties.
Lubao's sales
have been steadily declining. If that continues,
we'll be the next to stop production.
Where do you think
the problem lies in our Sales Department at the moment?
It could be...
that we haven't been able to raise everyone's spirit of initiative.
How can we raise everyone's initiative?
Director Pan,
I need to think carefully about this before answering you.
I've already thought it through. I'm preparing to split the Sales Department into two parts.
You and Yuan Huizhong will lead each team.
In three months, whichever team's track record is best...
Remember this. Whichever team's track record is best, their team leader will become Director of the Sales Department.
- Me?
- You.
- Become a team leader?
- Not just a team leader.
I hope that you will work very hard
to become the future director of our Sales Department.
Your asking me to compete one-on-one with Sister Yuan...
- Is that appropriate?
- How is it not appropriate?
I've been at Lubao for 7 years. Sister Yuan has been here for over 10 years.
Lubao Company has never been a company that operates on seniority.
- But...
- I know
that the two of you have a good relationship, but you must remember
that if there is no competition in an enterprise;
and instead, we care that you feel good, I feel good, everyone feels good...
sooner or later, we'll be finished.
Does Sister Yuan know about this plan?
She will accept it.
Li Siyu.
In the beginning, why did you come to work at Lubao?
Was it just for a job? Or did you hope to
find a platform to show what you can do?
Now I've set this platform up for you.
For the rest, you'll have to depend on yourself.
Director Pan,
let me think this over.
- Siyu.
- Director Fang.
- Is Director Pan in?
- He is.
Our department only has eight people altogether and you still want to do layoffs?
This is the decision of the Board of Directors.
Every department in the company will be cut in half.
This method of treating everyone the same is very unscientific.
But it's effective.
Yes. Those departments that are overstaffed should have layoffs.
But every person in our department is already overworked.
If we don't make cuts in personnel,
the company might not be able to continue existing.
Let's do this. Before you get off work today, give me a list.
- I can't do it.
- Director Chen!
I recruited those people.
They've been with me for so many years.
They suffered a lot and also made lots of effort. But they didn't earn much money.
I already feel sorry for them.
Now you want me to lay them off?
I can't do it.
- You can't act impetuously.
- But as long as you are human, you can't avoid emotion.
But the company only values benefits.
All right.
If the company has to do this, I'll quit.
I can give you my resignation letter this afternoon.
Then you can give it to me now.
Ziting, where is Sister Yuan?
They asked her to join a meeting.
That much?
Are they robbers?
Where am I going to find that much money?
You can't claim the money from the insurance.
I already asked on my way here.
They said Lan Ke's car didn't have insurance.
Bastard!
You must not tell Yiming about this.
Why?
This is my own matter. It has nothing to do with him.
Didn't he already propose?
Based on what?
The roadshow you planned last month,
you get full of praise even from my department.
And last year...
The company faced a problem,
they forgot who the front fighters were to sort it all out.
How can Caijin Company gain today's fame?
- Isn't it all because of you?
- All right.
I just feel wronged for you.
You are the company's no.1 hero.
If they need to lay people off, it shouldn't be you first.
Right now, the company lacks money.
They probably have to lay off the one with high expenses.
He planned to cut my whole department.
I just walked into their trap by doing this now.
You are too simple. You were calculated by them.
Yes.
I was caught. What can I do?
It isn't that bad. Aren't I more relaxed now?
You're really leaving?
Headhunting companies have contacted me many times over the years.
They wanted to give me an offer with any condition. But I wanted to stay with the company.
I rejected them all.
Now it's good.
Now I am free. Finally free.
Don't tell Li Siyu yet.
- Why?
- There's no point in telling her.
I'll tell her myself when I get another job.
I felt so guilty the entire night for ruining Chen Yiming's proposal.
Turns out you didn't want to get married to him?
I did rescue you from a siege. You blamed me!
It's okay that you don't thank me. Will your conscious allow you to do this?
This is another thing.
I didn't plan your Lan Ke to perform.
You owe me anyway.
You are already married now if I didn't help.
Don't mention that.
I'm scared just hearing it.
What's wrong with a married woman?
Zhizhi, we're not talking about you.
Sister Siyu, I think...
the next time Brother Yiming proposes,
- don't hesitate any more and agree to it.
- I agree.
Although Chen Yiming is just so-so, he is more than enough to me.
I think marriage shouldn't be delayed.
A lot of people who dated for over ten years
didn't get married.
Let's not talk about this anymore.
We should talk about compensation.
What's your next step then?
I'm exhausted with the roadshows.
I will take advantage of this time to rest.
I will also keep an eye on suitable opportunities.
Did you not eat lunch either?
Here. I happen to have one left.
I'm going.
- Where are you going?
- Enjoying my beautiful life.
- You don't want your things?
- Put them in your house for now!
How are we going to pay that much money?
We have to even if we can't afford it.
We have a signed mediation agreement.
All of my money is here. It's ¥17,000-18,000 all together.
Isn't that purse pretty valuable?
That's why I have no money!
Sister Siyu, I have ¥20,000 savings with Liu Yang.
But I bought finance products with that money.
I don't know if I can withdraw it now or not.
- Where are you going?
- Buy a lottery ticket.
- To bump into luck!
- You are Liu Yang? You are a top student of the university?
- Yes.
Your memory is really good.
I don't have other strengths. I just love money.
Xiao Liu, I hope you can successfully complete this bidding job.
- Of course. Definitely!
- Stay assured, Director Lu.
I won't let the superior leaders down.
- Work had!
- For sure.
Go back. See you, Director Lu.
- Thank you.
- You are too polite.
Safe journey, Director Lu.
Supervisor Wang, it's too windy outside. Quickly get inside.
Liu Yang, not bad.
About the bonus,
I will ask the Finance Department to pay you.
You should hurry up. How many people you need,
how many other departments you need to collaborate with
in a report and I will check immediately.
- All right, Supervisor. I will walk you out.
- No need. Go back to work.
Yes, Supervisor.
Liu Yang, don't forget.
We will go to pick Yuwei up together today.
Wait! Wait!
Liu Yang, brother, I didn't notice that
you knew how to take advantage of the alumni?
- Director is also from Jiaotong University?
- Don't pretend anymore.
I really didn't know!
You are awesome! ¥50,000 bonus plus the team leader of the bidding team.
You made it with one step!
I just suggested a plan.
But you proposed what Director Lu likes.
Brother, the next step, preparing bidding documents.
if you don't mind me, I can help you.
No, no, no, Old Wu. What are you talking about? How can I bother you?
- What? You dislike me?
- Of course not.
Then that's a deal. I can learn from you.
Old Wu!
- Hello, Sir. May I know how many guests you have?
- Yiming!
- I have a friend there.
- This way, please.
Okay. Thank you.
The traffic was a bit bad. What's going on with the car?
Has the loss assessment come out?
Not yet. They said we have to wait a few more days.
- Why is it taking so long?
- There have been a lot of car accidents lately.
I'm going to answer a call.
What do you want to eat?
- Like to order two coffees. These two.
- Okay.
- Okay, please wait.
- Thank you.
[Bank- Xiaoni]
- Hello?
- Hello.
Xiaoni, I'm Chen Yiming.
Isn't Sister Siyu not there?
Siyu isn't here right now. She went to use the bathroom.
Mr. Chen, it's like this. I asked for her just now.
What's the amount of the loan she would like to apply for?
- Mr. Chen? Hello?
- How about I tell her to call you back later?
Okay. That's it then.
This is your coffee.
Hello? Laozhou, I'm Xiaoling.
Hey, beauty, you finally remembered to call me!
I had some trouble recently.
Can you lend me some money?
You called the wrong number.
The the most correct thing I did was dumping you!
Jack, I'm Xiaoling.
Xiaoling, who are you?
What's your relationship with my husband?
- Xiao Ping?
-Xiao Ping?
Xiaoping has already run away.
Something on my face?
How much is the compensation?
I told you. I don't know yet.
Li Siyu!
This is my business.
- You can't do this every time. As soon as you encounter a problem—
- I've been independent since I was young.
Yes, you are independent.
I really appreciate it. And it's also what I love about you.
But many things in the future, including me,
if you are too independent, it will create a sense of distance.
I know.
Siyu... you're not alone.
You still have me.
I know.
Okay, let's talk.
How much is the compensation?
A lot of money.
- How come?
- Both are good cars.
They have insurance, right?
Lan Ke's car was not insured.
Excuse me. We are recruiting students.
Hello, you can take a look.
You said you can come by yourself. Why did you call me?
This is the teacher's request. The dad must participate in the shuttle every week.
Education is not just mom’s business, it's dad's business too.
I still have a lot to do.
I don't let you come every day, only once every week.
We should let the teacher know
that our family still attaches great importance to education.
Hello, excuse me. Our dance school is recruiting students.
It's very cheap, ¥300 per class.
Liu Yang... Look, this ballet class...
¥300 per class.
Do you think Yuwei needs this?
Okay.
That's right. Miao Miao is three years old and has started to learn ballet.
Our Yuwei is four years old now.
¥300 is a bit expensive.
It is expensive.
What's expensive? Even Miao Miao's
class is ¥500.
I don't agree with what you said.
Even if its expensive, we need it.
Even if she is not a dancer, it's good to practice her temperament.
Look at that girl. It's very good for her character.
- It's very important.
- Okay.
Why are you so generous today?
I got the bonus.
- Really!?
- Yes.
I forgot to ask you.
How was the report today?
You guess!
The supervisor is satisfied.
Not only satisfied but also announced on the spot
that I would lead the bidding.
Really!?
That means you became the team leader?
- Husband, I knew you were great!
- Look at you.
Just a team leader. I'm not a director yet and you're so happy.
The next step is the director, isn't it?
That's too far.
Let’s talk about bonuses first.
I got the  annual energy saving innovation first prize for my plan
and was rated by the company.
Bonus. ¥50,000.
¥50,000?
That's great.
I was thinking of
sending ¥30,000 to my mom and then set aside ¥20,000 for Yuwei.
Something big happened yesterday to Siyu and Xiaoling,
they are in need of money now.
Give your mother ¥10,000 and the rest to Sister Siyu.
This is not suitable, right?
What's wrong with this?
They are closer than my own sister.
Nothing.
4S shop often demands an exorbitant price.
At this price, we can discuss it with them again.
Yes, we can discuss this with them.
But it won't change a lot.
This matter originally doesn't have anything to do with Zhizhi.
As for Xiaoling, the money she earned over the years,
she spent it all on various specialty stores.
So, I have to pay the money.
I will pay the money.
I saved a little money before to pay for the down payment of a house.
I can take out half to pay for the compensation.
I can still afford it.
I know you can afford it.
But you will have no savings
after you pay for it?
I can earn more money.
I don't want to be excluded, Siyu.
I still think this is not good.
You have to let me pay at least half.
It's not a small number.
Yes, that's not a small amount.
Actually, it's not a small number.
But compared with a lifetime for us,
it's not much of anything, right?
Yiming.
Thank you.
But I have another condition.
Go on.
In the future, whenever you meet with any difficulty,
you have to tell me about it immediately and you can't hide it from me.
And even more important, you can't bear it all alone.
I'll do my best.
It's me who will do my best.
Then, I really do have a problem right now.
I'm telling you right immediately.
Tell me.
Miao Miao's mother.
I'm sorry about yesterday. Something happened to my sister.
And Yuwei had a problem and went straight home.
- Miao Miao, you're done with school?
- I'm so sorry.
- School's over.
- Hey, Miao Miao.
- Were you good in school today?
- Miao Miao is so cute today. Look at that barrette.
Yuwei's parents!
Hey, Yuwei.
- Good-bye.
Today, Yuwei had some problems with the other kids and isn't very happy.
She was in a bit of a mood.
But she's okay now. When you get home, you should console her a little.
- Okay.
-  Goodbye, Teacher.
- Thanks for your trouble. See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
Why are you in such a hurry? Wait for me.
Right up til now, she hasn't said a word to me.
That's a dangerous sign.
You can't treat that lightly.
I... How have I offended Director Pan?
It doesn't have anything to do with you.
They're after me.
Ever since I came to Lubao, it was Sister Yuan who taught me
step-by-step how to talk to clients.
For me, Sister Yuan is the model worker in our office.
A competition between a tutor and disciple
really is a little difficult to navigate.
But...
if the Director of Sales will get stock in the company,
plus an increase in salary and year-end bonus...
that's enough compensation for a full year.
Plus, Director Pan will give you the title.
If you hastily refuse him,
that... that's not too appropriate either.
So, exactly what should I do?
Have you discussed it with Sister Yuan?
I haven't had time yet.
Call her and speak with her about it.
It's Siyu.
See what she says.
Sister Yuan, I have something important to discuss with you.
- Where are you.
-  I'm at the hospital.
I have a fever. I'm getting an infusion of fluids.
Then, are you finished yet?
- Almost.
- Which hospital are you at. I'll come pick you up.
- I'm at Blue Cross Hospital.
- Okay.
See you soon.
Whatever happens, talk it over. Be clear, so there's no misunderstanding.
- I'm going.
- Okay.
- Zhizhi.
- Sister Siyu.
I have  ¥40,000.
Liu Yang just picked up his bonus today. You can take it.
Zhizhi, you don't need to worry about this.
Yiming and I have reached an agreement.
The two of us will split the cost.
- I have something to take care off, so I'll hang up.
- Okay.
Then, go about your business. Bye-bye.
You weren't even willing to give it to her.
It turns out that Sister Siyu doesn't need it.
Since Li Siyu doesn't need the money,
let's give my mom ¥30,000 and ¥20,000 for Yuwei.
Give your mom ¥10,000 and leave ¥40,000 for Yuwei.
You want to give my mom less than the norm, right?
You can say that? We give your mom money every month.
We're never short a penny with that.
Then, let's give mom ¥20,000 and give ¥30,000 to Yuwei.
Doesn't the roof on her home need to be repaired?
There's also my father's tomb which needs to be renovated.
What's wrong? Are you unhappy?
Did you have a bad time with your friends today and now you're sad?
Miao Miao and the others wouldn't play with me.
Why won't they play with you?
I don't know.
If they won't play with you, you can play with other kids.
They're not the only kids at the kindergarten, are they?
You don't understand. Miao Miao and her friends are the best kids.
I feel at ease when she can play with them.
I don't think Miao Miao's mom is so great.
Miao Miao's mom just doesn't like to say much.
[You've been removed from the group chat.]
Why did the elite group kick me out of the group?
She's not even answering my call.
Yuwei, quickly.
Baby, change shoes.
I want to watch TV!
One episode, okay?
This is for Yuwei.
- I want to drink something with flavor.
- With flavor? Here.
What are you rushing around for after you get back home?
You eat first when I finish cooking.
You put it here when you finish.
I will do washing up after I come back. Just take care of Yuwei for me.
What are you going to do?
To meet Miao Miao's mom.
She is the head of the parents.
I have to ask her why she removed me from the group.
Is it necessary?
Of course!
I told you at the beginning that you paid money to find a rival.
You will see.
[Emergency]
Sister Yuan.
Siyu, thank you for picking Mengmeng up.
Why are you being polite to me?
- What did you eat for dinner?
- Instant noodles.
Didn't I give you the money to order takeout?
It's not good to order food in the school all the time.
- Have you finished your homework?
- Not yet.
Why didn't you finish it? Did you play digital games in school?
I told you that I did!
Kids nowadays have too much homework.
Directer Pan talked to me today.
I know.
What do you think about it?
I will listen to you.
Sister Yuan.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just felt sorry for myself.
I'm unworthy.
I can understand.
It's been three years.
I drink, meet clients, go on business trips, and work overtime for them.
The business improves year after year.
But what have I got?
My husband went away with another woman.
Mengmeng gets more and more rebellious.
I'm burdened with illness. People also spread rumors about me.
Sister Yuan, everyone knows,
you gave a lot to Lubao.
So what?
I should be the sales director no matter how you evaluate it.
Why did the company do this to me?
The company...
They probably have their own plan.
What plan for me?
I'm 35 years old.
If I can't get promoted this time,
I'm done for in this life.
Sister Yuan,
no worries.
The position is definitely yours.
I won't be the team leader. No matter who is becoming the team leader, I will always be on your team.
You thought it over?
I will make it clear to Director Pan tomorrow morning.
Siyu,
thank you.
Sister Yuan.
Take it back.
We have a 7-year friendship.
Thank you.
The kid is looking at you.
Let's get in the car.
- What's the matter?  Say it.
- Where are you? It sounds very lively there.
In the bar opened by Laomeng. Are you coming?
I won't go.
Haowen, didn't you tell me that one of your friends was a headhunter earlier?
- Forward the name card to me.
- I thought you wanted to rest and enjoy life?
Li Siyu has some trouble.
I can't take a break now.
You  haven't gotten the title of husband,
but you start to work as a husband.
Don't talk like an unconcerned person.
If this happened to you, you would also do the same.
It won't happen to me.
- Did you help me to connect Gu Xiaoling?
- You are here!
Let's go drink!
Don't forget to send it to me soon!
Drink!
- You didn't heat up the food?
- It's okay.
Miao Miao's mom taught me a lesson.
She?
- Why?
- It's all because of you.
You didn't take Yuwei to take part in the activity yesterday.
They kicked me out of the group.
They said we didn't have a sense of time.
We didn't respect the rules and other people.
Is she insane?
It was definitely her that asked those kids
to exclude Yuwei.
It's good to quit the group. We don't need to contact with this kind of person in the future.
I'm afraid that Yuwei will be upset by some unkindness.
You don't need to worry about this.
It's normal for kids to change playmates.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  En...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫