Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 37]
Didn't you say you guys are busy? How come I don't see anyone working?
Everyone is recuperating and building up energy. We will be very busy at the end of the year.
Who's going to create the precinct work proposal for next year?
Li Siyu,
you work on the draft for next year's work proposal.
You can use this opportunity to familiarize yourself with the work.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
You also didn't answer my calls.
You're still mad at me for what happened that day when it was raining.
It's not like you don't know
that I'm asleep at 10:15 p.m. every night and I turn off my phone.
That's right, your life is very organized and strict, even thunder cannot disturb it.
But you're my boyfriend! Have you thought that perhaps something unexpected could have happened to me?
Have you thought that I might be scared?
That night when the thunderstorm was happening, I was already asleep.
Moreover, we still don't know about the brain activity of humans who are asleep.
Everything you say makes logical sense, but to me there's only one explanation.
You don't care about me so you don't worry about me. I'm not important in your heart.
That's incorrect.
I already decided that you're my life partner.
That clearly indicates how important you are in my heart.
But when I need you the most, I couldn't get a hold of you.
I already have a solution to that problem.
I got a phone for your sake. It turns on at 10:15 p.m. every night.
At 5:30 a.m., it turns off. This is the phone number.
You're the only one who knows this number.
However, I want to warn you.
You can only call this number for level 5 or higher emergencies.
What's are level 5 or higher emergencies?
According to all of the unexpected situations that could happen in your life,
I created a chart based on each one's degree of danger and split them into levels.
That day's situation is a level 6 emergency so you could have absolutely called.
Okay?
If you don't have any questions, we can go and eat now, right?
Today's our 100th day anniversary of meeting each other.
By looking at a comprehensive ranking and the ratings from "King of Delicious Food,"
(TN: a TV show rating food from different restaurants)
I found a restaurant that I think you'll like.
I'm pretty romantic, right?
Too romantic.
- Yuwei, come here!
- Mom!
- I'm sorry, Teacher. I've kept you from getting off work.
- It's fine, it's fine.
Say goodbye.
Sushan, bye-bye!
Yuwei, bye-bye!
Teacher Li, bye-bye!
Bye-bye, Yuwei!
We're leaving now.
Bye-bye.
It's okay. Daddy will pick you up soon.
You can keep playing for now.
Come, Yuwei.
- Hey!
- Teacher.
Is Sushan's mom not here yet?
Not yet. Her dad called and said that something suddenly came up so he'll be late.
Oh.
Do you have something to do?
My husband is away on a business trip, and my kid is alone at home so I'm a bit worried.
How about this? I was going to take Yuwei next door to eat.
Call Sushan's dad and if he agrees, then I can take her with me.
Later, we can have her dad pick her up next door.
That's too much to ask of you.
It's nothing.
Sushan, come here!
I'll call him now.
Okay?
[K Pro]
I'm coming to play with you!
Dad!
- Hey, Sushan. Have you missed me?
- Yes!
Give me a kiss.
Yuwei...
- It's you.
- What a coincidence.
How about I pay for this meal?
No need, I already paid.
Then next time.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Not yet. I just got out of a meeting.
I ordered quite a lot. Do you want to sit and eat some?
Then I won't refuse.
Do you want anything to drink?
A cup of hot Americano.
If you drink coffee this late you probably won't be able to sleep later, right?
I still have work to take care of when I get home later.
So hardworking.
Who isn't hardworking nowadays?
I'll help you get the coffee.
Thank you!
Yuwei.
Hello!
Hi!
What are you guys doing? What are you guys building?
We are building a house for the almond.
This is a house?
Yes.
- Are you full?
- I'm full.
Do you want to eat some more?
Right, right, right!
Be careful! It's going to fall.
Mom! Sushan and I are going to the kid's zone.
Go ahead! Be careful, don't fall.
Slowly.
Thank you.
Yuwei's mom,
my attitude was bad before. I'm sorry.
It's fine. We are used to it as salespeople.
Although,...
Go ahead.
I've been confused. Our company's products are pretty good
and I've put a lot of work into the sales,
so why won't you even look at it?
Hey.
Lubao's products are pretty good, but the people at Lubao...
What did I do—
Don't misunderstand. I'm not talking about you.
It's the previous salesperson.
That person didn't keep her words.
I felt extreme disdain.
You're talking about...?
She and I agreed to a small order before.
Later on, when my colleague was going over the contract, he found
that the contract to be signed was completely different from the contract that we confirmed before.
If we had signed that contract, my company would have lost hundreds of thousands yuan.
Something like that happened?
To my company, a few hundreds of thousands yuan is not a big deal,
but there's no way we can tolerate such vulgar tricks.
We'd rather have everything on the table so that we can discuss it. Even if you want to increase the price, it's fine.
I got into sales very late in life. You were the first customer I'd visited.
I'm also not very aware of what happened in the past.
Is it possible that my sales colleague didn't do it on purpose?
That she just accidentally mixed up the numbers?
She also said that.
But I said, I can't accept this kind of behavior, so let's end the contract.
However, you don't know what she did afterward.
She started spreading rumors about me.
She said that I didn't sign the contract because I accepted some other companies' money.
So that's why I didn't sign with you guys.
How can she do that?
That's exactly what she did. Isn't that going too far?
Good thing my superior trusts me or else, I, Su Lixing,
would have my principles and trustworthiness ruined by one accusation.
That really is crossing the line.
So when you came before, you happened to encounter me when I was at my angriest.
I understand.
You are you, she is she. I shouldn't have taken my anger towards her out on you.
That was very rude of me. I apologize once again to you.
No, no! I should apologize to you.
As a part of Lubao, I should apologize to you for my colleague's behavior.
This has nothing to do with you.
Mr. Su, I think I should tell my manager about this,
because this not only harmed you but also Lubao.
It seems that you are quite protective of your Lubao.
Although there are a few rotten apples,
most of our employees and our products are very good.
Can you reconsider?
Next year. Our purchases for this year have been finalized.
Next year.
Nana!
May I bother you to get this year's promotional strategy, business developments, and pricing plans?
Tomorrow.
That's what you said yesterday.
Tomorrow then.
Brother Zhai.
What is it?
Did you think that by tattling on me to the boss,
you can sit in my position?
- Ignore him. It's fine.
- When the boss sees me, he even calls me Brother Zhai.
A newcomer, who doesn't understand anything,
is actually challenging me!
Is he scolding me?
The more you react, the worse he gets. Don't say anything.
What did I do to anger him?
The takeout is here! Who is coming to get it?
That one! The newcomer! You go get it!
Let's go, let's go! I'll treat you to a milk tea.
Quickly.
Thank you.
The data for the marketing channels, internet platforms,
and customer profiles you asked for yesterday exposed Old Zhai's tricks.
Old Zhai said that he's going around doing inspections, but he's actually going out to play Mahjong.
When Manager Feng found out, he had to take care of this by fining him.
That's why Old Zhai is taking his anger out on you.
Then, why didn't you let me argue back?
Old Zhai is not the type to hold grudges. As long as you let him scold you a bit, then the situation will pass.
If you argue back, then this little incident would escalate. How would you deal with it then?
In this matter, it was clearly him who was not following the rules.
We're not children. Not everything has to go by the rules.
I think that everyone's attitude toward me is very strange.
It seems as if I have offended someone.
That's not exactly it.
It's mostly because of the work proposal. Why are you so serious about it?
You want this and that,
disrupting the peace of the whole office.
But Manager Feng assigned this to me so I can't just leave it and not do anything, right?
Do you want everyone to be your enemy then?
Of course not!
But... I can't possibly neglect
the work assigned to me.
Then you need to
slowly change your personality.
I'll try.
I have the work proposal from last year. Take it, change it up a bit, and that should be good enough.
Really?
I just found out that his daughter and my daughter are good friends in kindergarten.
Let me take care of this.
Don't tell anyone else.
By the way, did Siyu's new company collapse?
Yes.
I tried calling her, but her phone has been off this whole time.
She went back to our hometown.
She doesn't really use her old phone number anymore.
What a pity.
If there's nothing else, I'll get back to work.
Zhizhi, congratualtions on winning this month's Best Improvement award.
Keep it up!
Thank you, Director Yuan.
I'm home!
You're back?
- It's time to eat!
- Oh, okay.
You're back?
Did the people at work bully you?
How did you know?
I don't know, I'm just guessing.
Let me tell you.
Your auntie is planning to introduce a potential boyfriend to you.
Today, at home, she made a bunch of phone calls.
Why didn't you stop her?
Why should I stop her?
I didn't even stop you when you started dating at a young age, right?
You are an elder leftover woman now.
What reason would I have to stop her?
The one who started dating at a young age was Xiaoling, not me!
Xiaoling. Hey!
Now that you mention it,
Xiaoling is better than you in this department.
Dad!
What are you two father and daughter discussing?
We're talking about boyfriends.
Since you two have already started to talk about it,
Siyu, I want to advise you a bit.
Just leave the past behind. You have gotten older so use your time wisely.
I know.
I have friends with daughters your age,
and their children have already started elementary school!
Even if you are in a rush to get married,
you should at least find a boyfriend, right?
Right, right.
That Auntie Luo is going to introduce you to one.
It's a young man from a design institute. His family's conditions are quite good.
When you have the time, go and meet him.
Auntie, I just started working. I'm busy. Let's talk about it later on.
That won't do. Each day you postpone the meeting, you get older by one more day.
Isn't that a bit dramatic?
Be a good child and do as I say.
Just take it as giving Auntie Luo some face.
Who is Auntie Luo?
You don't know Auntie Luo?
In the future, if your children want to get into good schools,
then you will need Auntie Luo's help.
[Marketing Department: Work Proposal]
Don't copy the whole thing directly!
Slightly change the numbers, incorrect words, etc.
[Marketing Department: Work Proposal]
I'm begging for a response, begging for a response, begging for a response, begging for a response.
Respond to me! I'm begging you! I'm going to go insane!
At least let me confirm whether you're still alive or not, Older Sister!
Hello!
What are you guys doing?
Sorry, Sister Siyu, I'm working overtime. I'll call you later.
I'm also working overtime.
But I can still talk to you for a bit.
So jealous of you guys.
How are you doing?
Your mom has already started to help me arrange for blind dates.
Li Siyu, this is karma.
Gu Xiaoling!
It was your fault for telling mom about my situation with He Mu.
She annoyed me for three days!
You didn't even tell her about such a huge thing?
I haven't even figured it out myself, what would I tell her?
You're still not sure?
Enough, enough!  Let's not talk about me.
How are you?
Are you getting used to life there?
It's all right.
I'm okay with you coming back at any time. I still haven't put away your bed yet.
I'm not going back.
Up to you! I'm going back to work. Talk to you later!
Bye-bye.
Hi, Sushan's dad.
Hi, Yuwei's mom. Sorry for bothering you.
I... Can I ask something of you?
Go ahead.
I need to go on a business trip this weekend,
so... can you help me look after Sushan?
Not a problem.
I was going to take Yuwei to Disneyland. I can take them both.
That's great! That's great!
Sorry to bother you.
Not a bother at all.
Then this Saturday morning, I'll drop off Sushan at the entrance of your neighborhood, okay?
O-Okay. See you Saturday then!
Okay. See you Saturday. Thank you.
Listen up! As long as you can get the clients back,
I don't care what kind of methods you use, but you cannot harm the clients' interests.
If anyone breaks that rule,
then Liu Jie, who was just fired, will be your example.
How come it feels like Sister Yuan and Sister Siyu
are becoming more and more similar?
The two of them are, originally, the same type of people.
The young man is very talented. He works in a big company.
His income is very high.
He's also polite and respectful toward the elderly.
Hey! He's here.
Auntie Luo.
Siyu is here.
I'm not going to stay here and ramble. The two of you talk.
Thank you, Auntie Luo.
Grasp onto this opportunity. She's great!
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Let's talk over there.
Okay.
I'm sorry, I still have things to take care of at work. I'm leaving now.
Li Siyu, you don't remember me again?
X-Xiao Wen...
My appearance is indeed hard for people to remember.
That's not it.
I left Shanghai half a year ago.
You also came back from Shanghai?
Why did you leave?
I didn't like it and couldn't get used to it.
I... liked it a lot and was very used to it,
but I don't like the me when I was there.
What does that mean?
Today, I really do have things I need to do.
How about we meet another day?
Oh, okay. Another day then.
Which day is "another day"?
We'll figure it out later.
Can we exchange WeChats then?
Wen Xingyu?
You are the class representative of my geography class!
That was Zhang Xinyu.
I'm sorry.
It's fine. No matter where I go, I'm always the one who doesn't standout.
Try it. Try it. Why wouldn't it open?
Didn't you remember it?
What's the ending?
Dad. Mom.
I already sent the password to you guys, why are you two still standing outside the door?
Your dad didn't memorize it.
I will take them.
Watch and remember it.
I can't believe the two of you. You didn't even tell me before coming,
I could've gone to the train station to pick you guys up.
We didn't want to bother you, so we didn't tell you beforehand.
We know the address so we just took a cab here ourselves.
Son, you don't live here?
I've been working overtime lately.
This is the house you bought with 5 million yuan?
Yes.
In our hometown, you could've bought two villas with that kind of money.
Dad, this is Shanghai!
Yiming, Shanghai's housing prices aren't going to fall, are they?
How could Shanghai's housing prices possibly go down?
Is this house okay?
I called your company,
and the people said that you quit a long time ago.
Why?
Do you have a job right now?
I do have one. My friend and I started a business together.
Will the business last?
Yes, of course, it will.
We have also found people to invest in it. The company is also operating steadily now.
Then... is there no way you and Siyu can get back together?
We came
to help you talk to Siyu.
I already have a new girlfriend.
Then, what does your new girlfriend do?
Finance.
Working in finance means that her economic conditions are pretty good.
Yes, they are pretty good. Better than mine anyway.
Where is her hometown?
I don't actually know.
How old is she?
It seems like... It seems like she's a bit older than I am.
How much older?
How am I supposed to know? I-I didn't ask that clearly.
You don't even know about such important details, are you being tricked by her?
Mom, how old am I? How would I get tricked?
You broke up with Siyu for her, didn't you?
No. Siyu and I broke up because of our own reasons.
It was because she lost her original job then, wasn't it?
I was the one who decided on the job things.
Let's meet her.
Mom, Drink some hot water.
- Be careful, it's hot.
- We want to meet your girlfriend.
There's no need, is there?
Yes, there is.
The two of you came too hastily, how about next time—?
This time.
All right. I'll see when she has some free time then.
Dad, Auntie, I'm back.
Siyu, have you eaten?
Not yet.
Sit down.
How do you feel?
Do you even need to ask?
She came back without even eating, there's clearly no feelings.
I didn't ask you. I asked Siyu.
No feelings.
Such good conditions yet you have no feelings?
What conditions?
Auntie Luo said
that before coming back from Shanghai, he sold a house there.
It must be worth a few million yuan!
Are you going sell my daughter for a few million yuan?
Even if we must sell her, she's worth at least hundreds of million yuan, right?
Don't listen to your dad. Listen to me.
Get along with Xiao Wen well.
Let's forget about it.
We can't forget about it.
You need to marry someone in this lifetime, right? You're already over 30 years old.
This is your last chance.
Why would you say that?
Right now, your worth is starting to go down.
Young lads in their 30s are very popular.
They are just starting to further their careers.
Auntie, what kind of reasoning is that?
It's for your own good.
Listen to me. Don't lose him, okay?
Let's talk about it later.
This is too urgent. There's not enough time.
I need to increase Lubao's value by tenfold before the end of the year.
I contacted a few companies. They all know it's difficult and backed out.
[Mom: Your dad made a table full of dishes but you didn't come back once again.]
What's up?
[I had things to do today,]
Nothing.
[I will definitely go back to spend time with you guys tomorrow evening.]
Yiming, I need to change the situation of
Lubao's ineffective marketing planning urgently.
Let me think and see if I have any friends to recommend to you.
You can recommend Yiwen Company.
I can't comply with your wish.
Do you want some more soup? I'll help you go get it.
Let the auntie go do it.
No need. I can do it. I'll do it.
[Mom: Can we meet that girlfriend of yours tomorrow evening?]
Here.
My parents are here.
Oh.
They want to meet you.
What are you laughing about?
I just suddenly feel
like everything is so realistic.
Could it be that our relationship is not real?
That's not what I meant.
I was saying
I suddenly feel like I'm nearing the daily trifles of a family life.
Tomorrow, I might have to go on a business trip.
You decided to go on a business trip just now, didn't you?
Do you think
that it's not the right time to meet them right now?
I think that there's no need.
Do you think there's no need for that right now,
or do you think there's no need for that ever?
Our relationship is between the two of us.
It has nothing to do with other people.
T-They aren't some just other people.
They are my parents.
Yiming,
these past few days, you've been using "working overtime" as an excuse to not come back.
Did you think I wouldn't have any thoughts about that?
But I didn't ask, right?
Because I believe in your loyalty to our relationship.
I also allow you to have your privacy,
so I hope that you are like that, too. That you can respect my beliefs.
I only love you. I only want a relationship with you.
Then, what do you think
the final destination of our relationship will be?
I haven't thought about that yet.
You haven't thought about our future?
We are very happy together right now.
Why think so much?
What I want isn't just the happiness we have right now.
What else do you want?
Even though we just got together,
I want responsibility,
protection, and a lifetime.
I might not be able to give all of that to you.
Can I understand it like this?
You actually just want to date me,
but you do not want to participate in my life
nor let me participate in your life.
Yiming. Yiming!
You said that I'm your angel,
but did you know
that the failure rate of an angel's investment is 95%?
I said that I don't want to be a part of too much
because if one day, I must face failure,
then I can just be accountable to myself.
I won't have to be accountable to anyone else.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You are not allowed to go back on your move!
I'm your father!
That's still not okay.
Why are you so serious about playing Chinese chess?
It's your turn.
What is wrong with the two of you? The phone is ringing yet you two don't answer it.
Don't bother us. Don't bother us.
Hello? Who is it?
It's Xiao Wen?
Okay, okay. She has time.
Pick her up right now, all right?
Okay, okay.
Bye, okay?
Who was it?
It was Xiao Wen.
He's asking you out.
I don't want to go.
I promised him. He'll be here soon.
I have to play Chinese chess with Dad.
What's the fun in playing chess with your dad? He always goes back on his moves.
You're the one who does that.
Good girl. Go change.
Good girl.
Listen to me.
Look who's here.
Yuwei!
Sushan!
Good morning.
Come. Come to where your dad is.
Are you coming here to pick her up tonight?
My business trip was pushed to next week.
I promised Sushan that she'd get to go to Disney,
and I don't want her to be disappointed.
So... I'll go with you guys.
Sure!
Get in the car.
- We're going to Disney!
- Let's go!
Pass him.
When driving, safety is the most important.
I'm driving. We must drive safely.
What did you say?
My plan is that in 3-5 years, once I have children,
I'll switch the car to a station wagon.
It would be more convenient to take the kids out on vacations.
You've thought very far ahead.
Three to five years isn't considered far ahead, is it?
Days go by very quickly.
-  ♪ Two tigers love to dance,  ♪
-  ♪ Two tigers love to dance, ♪
-  ♪ The rabbits obediently pull the carrots ♪
-  ♪ We are little ducks learning to walk ♪
Hey, look. The tallest building there is Shanghai Center.
- That one?
- Shanghai Center?
The second tallest one is the International Financial Center.
- International Financial Center?
- That's right!
Next to it is a slightly shorter building.
It's Jinmao Tower.
- Jinmao Tower.
That's right! So smart.
Little duck.
Duck? Where is there a duck?
That's a swan.
Dad, look.
I know the story of the ugly duckling!
Please tell it to me, I'm begging you.
Okay, I will tell it to you.
A long, long time ago,
there was a female duck.
Why did you bring me here?
This is the marriage house that my parents got for me.
It's been fully paid for.
The money for construction has also been set aside. We're just waiting on the woman to decide on the design.
The two of us haven't gotten to this point yet, have we?
That's true.
I just wanted to use this way to show you that I'm not one of those unreliable people.
I want to head towards marriage with you.
If we get married, you don't need to worry about our finances.
By the way, my family has two shops in Jingye Plaza.
My mom said that the rent from those two shops is all for our kids in the future.
We no longer need to worry about the landlord increasing the rent.
We don't need to worry about the landlord selling the house anymore.
From now on, we are slaves to the house mortgage.
We have finally become house salves!
I... have had a crush on you since the first year of middle school.
What did you say?
Oh. Last time, when we met and I found out that you were still single,
I impatiently asked Auntie Luo to introduce you to me.
So that's what happened...
Siyu,
even though you don't say anything, I can feel
that in Shanghai, you definitely got hurt.
I can promise you
that as long as you are with me,
I will never let you get hurt.
Do you know why people get hurt?
Because they met bad people.
No. It's because love hurts people.
If you don't want to be hurt, then the only way is to have no love at all.
But can we do that?
I cannot.
I cannot either.
So, as long as we have the ability to love,
then we must face pain.
I keep feeling a sense of foreboding.
Xiao Wen,
let's just be normal friends.
Are you sure?
Absolutely sure.
Being with you doesn't make me feel tired
and I won't get hurt,
but...
I think...
You think it's tedious, right?
How about the two of us interact a little more? Maybe you'll be able to find that feeling.
Xiao Wen.
You have great conditions. Everyone has advised me to cherish you,
but...
you are not what I want.
Then what is it that you want?
I still want the feeling of love,
even if I get hurt again.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... Dear Myself ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫