Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 33]
- Your food.
- Okay.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Do you want some?
- Yeah.
Actually, I have some good wine in my car,
but I didn't drive today.
Y-Your wine
is pretty expensive,
I think it's probably worth more than this restaurant.
Do you understand wine?
M-My friend told me.
He said that
even if you have the money you may not necessarily be able to buy it.
I actually don't know much about wine.
But sometimes one has to pretend to understand.
- Cheers.
The boss who sold me that wine
sold me an even more expensive wine later on.
I totally forgot where I put it after I bought it.
It's called...
Luo Mandi or Luo Manshi...
I even looked it up on Baidu, but can't remember it.
Sister Ziru, you're
quite straight-forward.
Am I?
Yes, that is what I really think.
A lot of people say I'm
sly and scheming.
They say that I'm heartless and cruel, something like that.
But in my eyes you're
a very wise
calm and collected, rational, assertive,
kind-hearted...
that kind of woman.
Such a good evaluation?
Yes.
Am I really rational and calm?
However, I'm all confused when it comes to you.
Yiming, I actually have a secret.
That night,
I didn't go see a customer.
I also didn't forget about our date.
I was in the office.
Every call and every message you sent,
I actually saw all of them.
Then Sister Ziru why didn't you...
I...
I didn't have the courage to come and see you.
I was scared I wouldn't be able to control myself.
I must use many minutes just to calm down.
To calm down my emotions just so I can...
answer your one phonecall.
Sister Ziru.
Yiming,
I...it seems that
I like you.
Yiming, I know
that this shouldn't happen. I don't know why I would have these feelings.
No matter how I look at it, I shouldn't be like this.
Sister Ziru—
Yiming, I—
I'm not asking you for anything.
This is just my own
one-sided feeling.
I also...
don't need your response or reciprocation.
I also don't wish that this
will give you any pressures.
No, Sister Ziru, I...
How can I—？
Yiming,
today, I
got the courage to ask you out,
it's because I
I thought it through.
This just my one-sided feelings.
Today, saying all this out loud,
is not to start anything,
it is to end things.
After today,
I won't talk about it again.
I might still continue to love you...
deeply...
but I won't let you see it.
Sister Ziru,
I—
Yiming,
don't worry,
I won't ask anything of you.
From today on,
we are still friends.
We are still sister and brother.
We can still confide in each other.
After drinking this, this will all be in the past.
Annie.
President Wang.
Go see how Chen Yiming is doing right now.
Director Chen came here very early in the morning.
Really?
He even left this.
Did he say anything else?
He didn't say anything.
Where is he now?
He's already left.
This shouldn't be.
Go on out.
Annie.
Go find someone to find out about where Chen Yiming is
and what his plans are for the future.
Okay.
Did you apply for the reimbursement?
I didn't get it for this month yet.
I've already handed in the reimbursement form for 1 week yet it still hasn't been approved.
Don't even mention it.
The online promotion fee that I submitted 2 weeks ago still hasn't been approved.
Our company isn't having problems, is it?
That's very possible.
Don't believe in rumors. Don't spread rumors.
What does this mean?
This is the remaining balance in the company's bank account.
This is this month's employee salaries and all other expenses.
This is the debt
that we were supposed to have paid a long time time ago.
We've talked with dozens of new franchisees lately.
As long as they sign the contracts officially, then the deposits will come in.
I calculated it. We can keep going for at most one month.
Unless you can ensure that we have 10,000 new paying customers
and that must continue for 2 years.
The internet industry requires a lot of money to burn.
We won't be able to see results for another 3-5 years.
Only you and I know this, right?
Let me go talk to President Pan again.
That's our only option now.
Help me prepare all the financial statements
so I can report them to him.
Okay. Then I'll go do that.
President Pan, when are you free?
I want to report Laidianle's newest progress to you.
What's up?
Is our company out of money?
What are you talking about? We have plenty of cash.
Money from investors.
I saw that our bank account has only ¥43.
How do you know?
I hacked Sister Fan's computer.
Guan Xiaotang, there you go again!
What did you promise me?
You scared me to death. Just wait until I finish talking before you hit me.
Tell me. Are you thinking of handling it all by yourself?
I am the boss. If I don't handle it, who will?
Wait a moment.
What are you doing?
I asked what are you doing?
[¥9,420.95 was transferred to you.]
What does this mean?
From now on, I won't be getting a salary. I'm going to volunteer.
To save the company in danger.
Then what are you going to eat and drink? How are you going to pay rent?
I'll stay at my friend's place.
I can freeload for food and drinks as well as the internet.
Good job.
No, wait!  What does this mean?
I appreciate your good intentions,
but not a penny will be missing from your salary.
If you dare to refuse or return it, then you can leave right now.
You're treating me like an outsider right now. Am I an outsider?
There is no such thing as an insider or outsider at Laidianle.
You're all employees. Hurry up and accept it.
Don't force me to fire you.
I'm out of town right now. Wait for my return.
Old Bai.
Come, I want to talk to you.
- What?
- Come.
Sit.
What's so secretive?
Just now, you said that the online promotion fee hasn't been approved yet, right?
- Yeah.
- How much?
¥12,000.
Why are you asking?
Look at your phone.
[¥12,000 was transferred to you.]
This doesn't follow our finance protocols, right?
It's fine. It completely follows protocols.
Our focus is to work hard anyway.
Work hard!
Then I'm going to accept it!
[Lantian Kindergarten welcomes you.]
Teacher Dai!
Liu Yuwei, welcome back!
Susan! Xiao Xiao! Brother Hao Hao!
Yuwei, where did you go?
Yuwei, we missed you so much!
Yuwei, I found something interesting, let me take you to look at it!
Okay.
Please come with me inside.
Yuwei's kindergarten. Yuwei's kindergarten. Yuwei's kindergarten.
Yuwei's kindergarten. Yuwei's kindergarten.
Yuwei's kindergarten.
Director Su, I will come to visit you next time.
Cheers! You've worked hard.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you.
Help yourself!
Don't go.
Have some to eat!
Sister Zhizhi, you're back.
Thank you!
Come and have some snacks.
Sister Zhizihi!
Come to eat with us! Brother Xinyi bought them.
What's wrong?
Did you get kicked out again?
Your office is quite lively.
It's just today.
Ziping, bring the latest sample for President Luo.
Please wait a moment.
- Here. President Luo.
- Thank you.
Cheers to a pleasant collaboration!
Cheers to a pleasant collaboration.
Eat some pastries.
Okay.
President Luo, this is our latest battery.
This is our company's internal report.
President Luo, what's wrong?
Were there peanuts in the pastry I just ate?
- Are there peanuts?
- Is there?
Are there peanuts in this?
I think it does.
President Luo! President Luo! Are you okay?
Call the ambulance!
Call 120!
What's wrong?
Are you allergic to peanuts?
Did you bring medicine?
In my bag.
Bring his bag! Bring his bag!
The ambulance will be here soon.
How do you feel?
Better?
Thank you.
Hurry and take him to the hospital.
Slowly, slowly.
Quick, quick.
- Did you really resign?
- Yup.
Why?
I couldn't work there anymore.
Didn't you just get a promotion and raise?
It's another reason.
Tell me about it.
I haven't thought it through yet, how do I talk about it with you?
How about teaming up with me?
What?
What team? An idol group?
No singing.
The team's content will be the path to money.
Let's start a company.
Hurry!
Think about it! There is definitely a future there.
[Aunt]
Hello, Aunt?
Hey, Yiming.
Could you repay the ¥100,000 I lent you as soon as possible?
Didn't we agree that I'll repay it by the end of this year?
Well, didn't the housing prices drop recently?
Your cousin wants to buy a house. As his mom,
I should support him, right?
All right. I'll think of a way to get the money.
Okay. Could you give it to me by the end of the month?
I will try my best.
- That's it then.
- Okay. Bye.
[Your mortgage is overdue by two months and comes out to be ¥39232.95. The account ending in 1366 does not have enough funds. Please pay as soon as possible to avoid it from affecting your records.]
You guys play.
Here.
Say, is there any way for me to earn ¥10,0000 immediately?
There are lots. There is a book with ways written.
What book?
"Criminal Law."
I'm being serious.
A serious and simple way is that we do Wemedia.
(TN: Wemedia is the Chinese term for private citizen media such as blogs, forums, WeChat, etc.)
We can earn ¥1,000,000 per year. Would you still need to worry about ¥100,000 with that?
All right.
- It's settled then?
- It's settled.
I will resign once I get to work.
Come on!
You haven't left yet?
Director Yuan,
I'll be leaving soon.
By the way, how is President Luo now?
He's been discharged from the hospital already.
This illness sure does come quickly and go just as quickly.
How did you know that he was allergic to peanuts?
My daughter is also allergic to peanuts. That's why I don't dare buy snacks for her from outside.
I make them for her at home.
Well... thank you for today.
If this President Luo had any mishaps at our company,
then it would be over for all of us.
Director Yuan,
I want to ask you something.
Go ahead.
About Qijue's Director Su,
I've already visited him for nine times. I get kicked out every time.
I wanted to ask, how do I communicate with a client like this?
I actually wanted to tell you that you don't need to deal with Mr. Su anymore.
Didn't you say—
He wants to give the order to his own special clients so he has been rejecting us.
We normally just give up on this type of client.
Then this month, I...
Go meet with this client tomorrow.
He likes ping-pong. There has been an international competition recently. Buy and deliver tickets to him.
Thank you, Director Yuan.
If there is nothing else, you should go home earlier.
- Hey, Zhizhi.
- Let me help you.
- Thank you.
How come there are so many frozen foods and instant noodles in here?
I bought these for my son.
How old is he?
He's a first-year in middle school.
His body is still growing. It isn't really good for him to eat these, right?
It's better than eating takeout every day, right?
Is there no one to take care of him at home?
It's just me and my son.
You don't have it easy. You need to work hard and take care of your son.
No one has it easy. Where do you live? I'll drive you home.
No need. You should hurry home and take care of your son.
- I'll help you put these in the car.
- Okay.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes, see you tomorrow.
Lei Haowen and Chen Yiming both resigned.
They're creating a Wemedia company together.
He's also starting his own business?
Say, would you two get back together because of this?
Both of you are starting your own business at the same time, going through hardships.
You two will probably meet each other again.
That's impossible.
Hey, honestly,
you two broke up because you wanted to start a business.
Now that he's also starting a business, perhaps he will come to understand you.
I'm going to take a shower now!
[Dad]
- Hello, Dad?
- Yiming.
What's going on? Your aunt came to the house asking for the money back this morning.
She said that you borrowed ¥100,000 from her. She also said that if you do not repay it soon,
her son's house will be gone.
If he doesn't have a house, then your third cousin will not be able to get married, then things will get blown up.
I heard that you also borrowed money from your fourth older cousin.
It was because I bought a house. Right now, I don't have many extra funds to use.
Didn't you get a loan
Yiming, are you sick?
No, Mom.
You must tell me the truth. Did something happen to you?
Mom, I'm doing fine. There's really nothing going on.
Then, how is Siyu?
She's doing well.
T-Then how come you suddenly want so much money? What exactly do you need it for?
Mom, it really is for buying a house.
Then, what do you have to say about your aunt's money?
Yiming, you asked for ¥600,000 last time. I got ¥200,000 of that
from my old classmates. Your aun't ¥100,000,
we really can't help you with that.
Dad and Mom, don't worry about this.
I will take care of it myself. I'm hanging up now.
[Yiming's Dad]
Uncle.
Siyu, let me ask you something. You need to tell me the truth.
Go ahead.
What exactly happened to Yiming?
I... don't know.
How would you not know?
I really don't know.
He borrowed over ¥700,000 altogether recently.
We have already broken up.
Oh... W-When did that happen?
A few months ago.
How come? Didn't you two buy a house and were preparing to get married?
Uncle, I still have some things to do so I'm going to hang up now.
Using the name "Yiming May Not Be Amazing,"
he registered public accounts on 5-6 different platforms to talk about financial brands.
Although the topics are quite niche, the feedback is not good.
Right now, his followers and article views are growing steadily.
How is his income?
The main income is from the articles written and readers' tips.
Altogether is around ¥2,000-3,000 .
- All right. You can go now.
- Okay.
Hello? Aunt?
I transferred ¥5,000 to you just now.
Wait, how much?
Isn't it ¥100,000? Why is it just ¥5,000?
I can't get the remaining ¥95,000 right now.
Can you give me a few more days?
By the end of this month. Not a day more.
Okay. Thank you, Aunt.
- What's up?
- Haowen,
can we get an ad by the end of this month?
Don't worry. No problem!
Okay. That's it.
Bye-bye.
- Hello
- What are you doing?
- Adding water for you.
Oh, no need, thank you.
[Three best things in life: meeting someone by chance. Understanding without being told. Recovering from illness without treatment. I think reading Yiming's article is like all of the above.]
Thank you.
This car model has already stopped production. You can no longer sell it for a good price.
You should just keep and use it yourself.
Just be honest, how much is it worth?
¥50,000.
- ¥50,000?
-  Yes.
Think about it.
Hello?
Where are you right now?
I'm selling my car.
Why are you selling your car?
My relative in my hometown is pressing me to repay the debt.
I'm just going to pay back whatever I can for now.
Did you sell it yet?
I haven't yet.
Sell it to me. I give you ¥300,000.
What kind of joke is that? I'm busy right now.
[Lei Haowen transferred ¥100,000 to account ending in 1366.
Lei Haowen transferred ¥100,000 to account ending in 1366.
Lei Haowen transferred ¥100,000 to account ending in 1366.]
If you say any words of thanks, then we are not bros.
I didn't plan to thank you. I'm here to give you the car key.
I don't like your worn out car. Keep it for yourself.
I have something urgent. Catch you later.
Lei Haowen!
I'm going to go meet a client. See you later.
Hello, Dad. I will transfer you ¥300,000 right now. Let's repay our relatives and friends.
Transfer. I will transfer the money once I hang up.
Okay. Okay. It's fine.
Okay. Bye.
[Teacher Yiming, the weather has been changing often recently. Please take care of yourself.]
[Thank you. You take care as well.]
Wait a moment.
Please enjoy.
I heard that there is a new movie that is pretty good.
Shall we go and watch it after dinner?
According to our plan, after dinner today,
we will go to a book store to sit for one hour.
Then we'll take a walk around the lake for 30 mins.
- Can't we change it?
- No.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
By the way, I almost forgot.
What's this?
This is the data analysis
of all our WeChat, QQ, text, and other messages since we've known each other.
What's this for?
In this, are graphs with ratios of our words, numbers of messages,
reply time, and total time.
From these graphs, we can see that our communication is considered very smooth.
We have gotten to know each other quite well.
According to the data analysis, I think our relationship can be upgraded again.
I suggest, when we take a walk tonight,
we can have some more intimate body touches. For example, kissing.
Do you have any requirements on kissing postures?
In regards to that... I think doing it naturally is best.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫