Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 36]
Did CEO Li get funding or not?
I saw her worried look. I don't think she did.
Hey.
I heard that she's planning on selling the company.
What are you doing? Not working and spreading gossip?
Guan Xiaotang, you're the man pursuing Director Li. Did you get any information?
My information is that our company is fine.
- We got paid!
- I think even more than last month.
It's three times more than last month!
Now you guys aren't worried, right?
If Sister Li says she can get funding, she can get funding.
Everyone come here!
There must be good news.
Everyone's here, right?
Pretty much.
I gave everyone three months of salary. I believe it arrived today, right?
Yes!  Thank you, CEO Li!
Hopefully, every month will be three times our salary!
Are you asking for working overtime?
I'm announcing...
Laidianle from today on will be closed.
- No way.
- How is that possible?
I don't get it. I don't understand.
When you first joined the company,
I promised you that I would make the company grow until we IPO.
But the reality is, I don't have that ability and can't keep that promise.
The company is like this because of me. I let you all down.
Sorry.
CEO LI, we can't close the company.
Yes, CEO Li.
- How about we all think of a way together?
- Isn't it just an issue with money?
I have money.
Guan Xiaotang, stop it!
I'm serious. Sister CEO Li, how much do we need? I can help resolve it.
Thank you, everyone. I know how you feel.
But Laidianle is congenitally deficient indeed.
We don't need to continue.
- But Director Li, we can—
- Don't say anything more. I have already made the decision for you.
We all have a far journey to go. I wish our paths will cross again.
CEO LI!
What?
5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
Yay!
Let's toast to the future!
We will win!
We will be able to smile till the end!
All of the doubts have become miracles,
and the person who created these miracles
is me. Li Siyu.
Sister!
Here's the money for the office furniture.
You should keep it.
I don't need it.
I know you covered the expense before.
How did you know that?
Sister, don't worry. You still have me even though the company's closed.
What am I going to do with you?
A boyfriend! I would also be willing to be your husband.
See! I can make you laugh, right?
As much as I'm useless, I can still make you laugh. Right?
- Guan Xiaotang.
-  I am here.
Thank you.
Older Sister, if you need another website, I'll make you a bigger, better, more professional one for you!
This Director Gong is very skilled. Later, you have to introduce the business properly to him.
Do I need you to say that?
Lei Haowen!
- Hi, Director Gong.
- Hello.
This is my partner, Chen Yiming.
- Hello, Director Gong.
- Let's talk inside.
- Come on in.
This is your company?
Yes. Yiming is in charge of content primarily, and I handle business operations.
Correct.
This is what you want me to invest in?
Exactly.
You've got to be joking?
We are willing to spend ¥1,000
to rent a table in a cafe to start a business.
And when you first started your business, you couldn't even rent a table and had to work out of your single dorm.
You know me?
So handsome!
My company's philosophy is based on social media to provide virtual planning for financial institutions.
While breaking a traditional company's framework at the same time as we are breaking a traditional company's form.  Why don't we do that?
Continue talking.
Don't look down at this cafe.
The CEO of Xiaomai Company, which just launched,
at that corner, he wrote down his first line of code.
Last month, the man who entered the list of wealthiest men, Qin Geng, on this table,
wrote his first proposal.
And...
the Dufeng company which is called Community  Unicorn, also got its first investment in the cafe.
So, Director Gong, maybe the next great business tale
might happen right on this table, between the two of us.
Then... let's talk about shares.
Director Gong.
What do you want to drink?
Come take a look here.
- Sister Siyu, you're really going to leave?
- You think I'm bluffing?
- There are no issues, right?
- No, just missing home.
Older Sister.
Are you still unhappy? Let me tell you...
If you're unhappy, drink beer. I found a really good brand.
- Everyone, greet Older Sister!
- Hi!
See, Older Sister? These are all things that you never could've imagined, but nothing that you can't do! You can eat, drink,
and play video games!
Who is that?
Older Sister, really. You cannot use your heart only to think about work.
You also need to take care of your mood. If you want to play video games, then play them.
This home party place is very suitable for you who was born between 1985-1990.
I'll send you the address soon. Come later.
Guan Xiaotang?
What do you mean, "missing home," you're just trying to escape.
I can even accept that "I'm a loser." What else do I need to escape from?
If you could face it, then when Guan Xiaotang calls you, why do you shut your phone off?
If you could face it, then stay here.
If you want to be with a younger man, then be with him. If you want to earn money, then go get it.
- Xiaoling!
- Am I wrong?
I guess you are right.
Li Siyu,
in the past, when I saw you so helpless, I always felt so annoyed.
Now that you're like this, I feel even more pain in my heart.
I'm begging you, will you go back to your high-and-mighty personality?
The Li Siyu before was arrogant and eager for quick success.
In the end, I brought down GM Pan with me, disappointed all of the employees, and even harmed myself.
That was just a one time, unlucky failure.
This failure made me figure out myself.
In the past, I thought that I was so capable, better than anyone.
I could win any battle.
Now... I understand.
I am just a normal person.
I'm an ordinary normal person.
No. Sister Siyu,
in my heart, you have always been formidable. You have always been my idol.
Zhizhi, in the past, it was because I was lucky.
Now, all of my good luck has ended.
Ten thousand.
- Four cakes.
- Want it?
- I won.
- You missed one piece!
- I have this!
- Hey! You're missing a piece!
- Missing what piece?
- Why don't you count?
- You are missing a tile. This win doesn't count.
- I just put it here.
- It's yours?
Then... Then this one is mine.
I just put it here.
You are cheating.
You need to treat us if you cheated.
What do you mean, treat you? Didn't I do that a few days ago?
- Dad!
- You didn't treat the two of us.
My princess came back.
Hey, I'm not playing today. Not playing. Sorry.
You play with them!
Don't forget the treats tonight.
My guest, are you staying or eating?
- I'm coming home.
- Then you are in the right place.
Dad,
why are you still so naughty?
- Your leg. Did the old problem act up again?
- It's fine.
- Let's go, hurry home.
- Slow down, don't rush.
It's fine.
Come, come, come. Come in.
Siyu is back!
That fast?
Xiaoling called me just now. I assumed there would be another thirty minutes.
- Auntie.
- You must be hungry, right? I have two more dishes that are about to be ready.
Quickly, pour a glass of water for her.
I know, I know.
- Thank you! Go rest.
- Put your things down first.
- Dad.
- Here, drink some water first.
Sit down.
It's time to eat!
- There's more food?
- Let's eat.
We haven't eaten with you in around 200 days, of course we need to make it more luxurious.
Siyu, eat some more. Here. Eat some more.
- Thank you, Auntie.
- Here you go.
Auntie, that's enough, that's enough. I won't be able to finish it.
Look at you. Look how skinny you are? Eat some more.
- Thank you.
- I heard Xiaoling say that you resigned from your company.
Why?
I was too tired.
Then rest well this time.
- Okay.
- Are you still going to leave?
No.
That's wonderful.
The news said that the young people of the first tier city
work on a tight schedule, all work super hard. Right?
Every day, they only do three things.
They work, eat, and sleep. How could you call this living? It's just existing.
Yes. It's best.  You should have also brought Xiaoling back.
I wouldn't be able to make Xiaoling budge.
What's going on with her? It's been many months since she's contacted us.
When she finally called, and I asked her one too many questions, she got impatient with me!
- She's doing well.
- How has she been solving her personal problems?
She has a boyfriend with great conditions in every domain.
Do the two of them have a chance of being together for life?
It should be no problem.
What a big event... She didn't even tell me.
Does she still see me as her mother?
It's not that Xiaoling wasn't planning on telling you.
Of course, she sees you as her mother! It's just that she didn't think it was time to tell you yet. She will, she will.
You don't even have an office.
Not even a successful case, and got two million in investment.
Yes.
What kind of person is this investor?
What do you mean what kind of person is the investor? He's just an investor.
He also has his own business. It's not big, but the projects that he launched all have a high success rate.
Really? Wow.
So that means that he's not a lunatic.
Of course, he isn't. Not only is he not a lunatic, but he's also very smart. He's also pretty handsome as well.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then there's only one possible way to explain this.
Your creativity is very good.
Maybe he likes Le Haowen's looks and my abs. We are like a piece of abs.
- Yiming.
- Yes?
In the beginning, you were adamant that I was not allowed to invest in your company.
You don't even want me to have a look at your business plan.
I think you made me miss a wonderful opportunity.
You already invested in me though. When everyone else didn't believe in me, when even I felt suspicious of myself, it was you who gave me confidence.
Look at that.
How is this one?
I don't want it.
I didn't say it was for you.
I'll wear it.
You will wear it? This is for men.
You didn't realize that I liked wearing male suits?
Older Sister, why won't you respond to my WeChat messages?
Older Sister...
I miss you.
Older Sister? Where are you?
Older Sister, if you don't respond immediately, I'm calling the police!
Lao Li, did you see the girl by the river?
She's walking around. Will she commit suicide?
That's my daughter.
Your daughter?
Which daughter?
The one who resemble me the least.
The one who has company and is good at making money in Shanghai?
The one with the most suffering life.
She doesn't look like it.
Hi!
- Hi!
- Hi. You came back?
Yes, I came back.
Siyu, this is Uncle He.
- Hi, Uncle He.
- Hello!
I heard that you were doing well in Shanghai. We all know this!
Thank you.
It's okay. Sit.
Dad,
I came back after I lost everything.
I also lost all my money yesterday.
I broke up with Chen Yiming.
Was it his fault or your fault?
It's not someone's fault. We broke up peacefully.
Then find another one.
Don't pull a long face. It's not a big thing.
I'm already in my 30s. I have achieved nothing.
I have achieved nothing for my whole life.
But I lead a more comfortable life than anyone else.
You take things too seriously. It's not necessary.
Be careful.
Don't die early like your mom.
Dad!
It's gone.
I can go back with nothing at the worst.
Then you came here in vain.
Fishing is just for fun. The result is not so important.
It's like our life.
As long as we are happy, having achievement or not is both okay.
How old is your child?
I don't have a child.
Your husband's family didn't ask you?
I haven't gotten married.
How about your boyfriend? Didn't he come back with you?
- What does he do?
- I don't have a boyfriend either.
- Do you have any conditions? I can introduce some to you.
- Let's talk about it in the future. I need to find work first.
How is it going?
My dad's workplace is recruiting. I will go and give it a try.
I know,  the company just under the Housing Construction Bureau.
My cousin works there. He will take care of you. No problem.
No need to bother your cousin. My dad's student is in HR now. He says that I'm qualified.
You will need this. Everyone needs a strong connection in that unit.
You need to let people know you have it too or else people will bully you at work.
- Thank you.
- Siyu,
for your age now,
I'm afraid that you can only find divorced people. Are you okay with it?
Excuse me, I want to go to the restroom.
- Okay. Go.
- Thank you.
Who? You know him. It's him!
[U-likeMart]
Hi!
May I know who are you?
Li Siyu, we used to share a desk.
Did we?
The second semester of the 1st year in middle school.
Yes.
We haven't met each other for over 10 years.
That long?
We haven't met since we graduated from high school.
Actually, I come back every year for the spring festival.
I take my parents out to travel during the spring festival every year.
Then we missed each other perfectly.
Perfectly?
Nothing.
I heard that you wouldn't leave this time.
Yes. I'm looking for a job now.
Then we can meet each other often.
All right. Tell me when there are classmate gatherings.
Okay.
This juice is healthy. Give it a try.
Thank you.
I was passing by and bought some breakfast.
Eat while it's still hot.
I sent the salary to you.
- Hi.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
You paid me another ¥5,000?
What do you mean?
Boss, you want to keep me as a mistress? It's not enough.
What do you mean, Boss? Don't I need to pay ¥300,000 back to you?
Return! You must return!
But I have to pay the mortgage now.
So the money I owe you, I can only pay you back little by little.
Yiming,
actually, the ¥300,000 was not from me.
From who then?
Li Siyu.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Li Siyu didn't want me to tell you.
She left.
Where did she go?
To her hometown.
Why?
You ask her by yourself if you want to know.
Impossible! It's not her personality to go back.
She has suffered too much, so her personality has changed?
- Oh my, it's over ¥100 .
- What size?
- S.
I think it fits you well.
Everyone, stop work for a moment. Get to know our new colleague.
Hi, everyone. I'm Li Siyu.
Li Siyu?
I'm Liu Junning. We were on the same team of our high school's military training. But later we were divided into different classes.
It's you!
Since you were classmates, then you can show Li Siyu to get familiar with our working environment.
Sure.
Who can make our work plan tomorrow?
Are you still living over in Shanghai?
Nana?
I haven't finished the work you gave to me last time.
Liu Junning,
my mother-in-law and my son are both sick. I have lots to deal with in my family.
Lao Zhai?
I'm still writing this year's summary.
Where is Lao Zhang?
Lao Zhang asked for leave.
Again?
The food delivery has arrived. Who can go get it?
Let me do it.
- Food!
- Put the here! Here!
The food has arrived!
Go.
You shouldn't have taken it. Did you eat breakfast? We can share one.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Taking delivery is your job from now on.
I started to contact CC Fund.
Okay. Good.
How much can we make from your expectations?
Four to five billion.
Within one year, from 800 million to 4 billion. Nice!
President Wang is not of the common sort as expected.
Only this amount of income won't waste our efforts.
Let's look forward to the good news from President Wang.
- Yes.
- No problem.
- Okay. We'll get going.
- Okay.
I will inform you both if there is any update.
Okay. We are going.
- See you, President Wang.
- I will walk you out.
- No need to walk us, President Wang.
- It's okay.
Stay there, President Wang.
Safe journey.
President Wang, Director Gong has been waiting for you for a long time.
Let him in.
- President Wang.
- Here. Director Gong, take a seat.
Tell me what your evaluation of Chen Yiming was.
He has creativity and determination to work.
Does the virtual planning platform he's working on have value?
If he can do it well, then there is a lot of potential.
Of course, everything relies on the market.
He didn't suspect you?
I was introduced by Lei Haowen's friend, so he didn't suspect anything.
Great. Then just be a good investor.
Okay.
Mom! Mom!
- What's wrong, Yuwei?
- Mom!
Don't be afraid! Don't be afraid! Mom is here.
Don't be afraid! Don't be afraid. I am here.
Mom! I want Mom!
Don't be afraid, Mom is here. It's just rain and thunder.
Mom, I'm so scared.
Don't be afraid.
[He Mu]
Hello, the phone you are calling is powered off.
I will tell you a story, okay?
A long time ago, in a forest,
there was a female duck that was laying her eggs.
Not the Little Mermaid?
I'll tell you the story of the ugly duckling, okay?
Okay.
The little ducks got out of the eggshell one after another.
There was one duck that was different from all of the others.
It was both big and ugly.
Hey, Xiaoling? What's wrong? Missing me?
Why would I miss you? Come save me!
Sweep carefully.
Lei Haowen.
You're back? How did you sleep in the hotel? Was it good?
You didn't sleep all night?
At daybreak, I planned to doze off for a bit.
However, there was a sudden situation.
Sir, look, look!
You need to sweep all of the glass carefully!
- Keep sweeping. Look again.
- Okay.
- Be more precise.
That rat ran out.
It was rebelling against me, so I had to play the role of Tom.
Destroy his power and prestige!
You need to quickly eat this medicine. You were in the rain all night.
If you get sick, you'll blame me for not saving you quickly enough.
- Make it by yourself.
- Mr. Lei, give me a hand.
- These two pieces?
- Yes, hold them steady.
So did you catch it?
I caught them! Don't worry, I released them.
Make it secure.
Okay.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Why are you looking at me? Eat your medicine.
Xiaoling,
the way you're looking at me today is a bit flirty.
Go to hell!
You have to eat your medicine.
Right. Stick it firmly.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫