Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 35]
After the summit,
you must come to my place to sit and chat.
I still have some good tea.
-  I just know how much you like drinking tea.
- CEO Zheng!
Hi, I'm Chen Yiming from Yiwen Culture. Chief Gong told me to wait here for you.
Oh, I know.
You are the influencer of the Wemedia Lao Gong told me about. You want me to run ads on your platform.
Right.
Please take a look. This is our company's profile.
How many followers do you have now?
Our company just started, so only 60,000 followers.
60,000?
You want me to give you an ad with just 60,000?
You think too naively.
How about this? Once you have over a million followers, come talk to me.
CEO Zheng, I—
Nowadays, some people
really don't know how much they're worth yet go promote themselves everywhere.
This is the so-called "have an exaggerated opinion of his own abilities."
- Hello?
- Hello, Mr Chen. I'm the legal counsel at the bank.
Your mortgage is already six months overdue. We have already filed a litigation with the court.
I don't have money!
Just take my house! Just have the court sentence me to death!
Oh!
President Wang, did you look at the materials I gave you last time?
What do you think? How about a collaboration?
What's your company's value right now?
¥200-¥300 million!
Just ¥200-¥300 million and you want to collaborate with me?
You think too naively!
Once you're worth ¥10 billion then let's talk.
Nowadays, some people really don't know how much they're worth yet go promote themselves everywhere.
Forget it, let's go.
This is money's arrogance.
Mr. Yiming,
I'm your loyal follower. I look at your content every day.
When will I get the opportunity to collaborate with you?
Exuse me, President Wang. There is something happening with the organizing committee that needs your assistance.
I'm going inside now.
About the collaboration, I'll have my secretary—
President Wang, this way, please.
- Hello?
- Hello, Mr. Chen.
Sorry about that earlier.
Sorry about that Mr. Chen. I'm very sorry.
The bank called me just now. All of your debt has been paid off.
Who helped me pay if off?
Did you not pay them off yourself?
Mr. Chen? Mr. Chen?
Yiming!
- Yiming!
- President Wang!
Can you give me some face?
Face?
You helped pay off my mortgage, right?
Also, the replies, they were from you, right?
President Wang,
I don't need your help.
I also don't need your sympathy.
And I definitely don't need your pity.
President Wang, I beg you.
Can you please let me have some self-respect?
Don't worry, I'll repay everything that you've helped me with.
Just give me some time.
Yiming!
The only thing you can repay me with is probably money, right?
I also put out a lot of care,
worries, respect, appreciation,
and love. How would you return those to me?
You said you have your self-respect and face,
but does that mean that I don't have self-respect or face to keep?
I used all my courage to tell you how I felt.
In return, you left without a word.
I quietly got close to you and cared for you.
In return, you just say that you don't need it.
Chen Yiming, I'm also a person.
I also feel sad when I get rejected!
When I'm humiliated, I also feel sad! My heart also bleeds!
I also have pride and a sense of inferiority.
But with you, I put all my guard down.
Including all my weaknesses.
I just wish that you are well and happy.
Did I do something wrong?
Yiming,
I don't blame you.
It is I who put myself in such a low position.
It is I who gave you the right to hurt me.
I will disappear.
Disappear from your life.
I won't bother you ever again.
If it were me, I would respect what my heart's desire is.
From an economic perspective,
people socially interact just for gains.
That means that the relationships between people are all based on personal gains.
Romantic relationships are also based on personal gains.
Surviving in the workplace is quite easy, actually.
Whatever position you're in, you do what you have to do.
Don't disappoint yourself or the company.
Sister Ziru, when are you free? Let's catch up.
[All Day Brunch Bistro]
[5:00 p.m. tomorrow.]
[OK.]
Welcome.
Please take care.
Long time no see.
Your complexion does not look very good.
What would you like to drink?
How about lemon water?
Waitress, please give us a glass of lemon water.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy.
I remember when I introduced you to GM Pan back then,
the two of you spoke quite congenially.
Yes.
Then, why is the situation like this now?
You heard?
Sister Ziru,
GM Pan's temper is a bit big and a bit agitated,
but his character, core, and skills
are the best out of all the entrepreneurs that I have ever encountered.
Sometimes he's careless and isn't willing to get restricted by rules,
but he does all these not for himself.
Rather, it's for the growth of Lubao.
It's his patriotism.
You are right. I do admire him,
but...
that doesn't mean that he is the best pick for Lubao's chairman.
Then, who do you think would be better suited than him?
Me.
You don't understand batteries or new energy at all!
I know how to make money with Lubao though.
In your eyes, is Lubao just a tool to make money?
Yes.
Back then, you became friends with me
was actually because of Lubao.
Yes.
At the time, I was looking at the new energy industry,
and your appearance just so happened to give me an opportunity.
From me, you found out that Lubao was doing equity financing.
From my lips, you also got
information on Hua'an and Shanghai Bank.
When I was no longer useful to you,
you betrayed me
to prove your alliance with Fang Zhan.
I must correct you there.
I gained Fang Zhan's trust.
I always thought of you as a friend.
I also thought of you as a friend.
You were using me!
Siyu, you also gained a lot from me.
I even saved you ¥300,000 worth of car repairs.
I'm also the one who gave your ex-boyfriend a job.
I'm so stupid.
I didn't see through you.
I even recommended you to GM Pan.
It wasn't me who you couldn't see through,
it's life itself.
As an adult, you should know
that behind every slab of meat, there is a price written down.
It was I who caused GM Pan's downfall.
I sabotaged Lubao.
Don't put it all on yourself.
Lubao will only be more worthy in my hands.
President Pan may not be the president anymore, but he's still
a shareholder. He's going to gain profit.
Even more than what he's gained from the past 10 years.
Do you think money is everything?
I work with investments.
Money, to me, is everything.
If that's how it is,
then your life must be so tedious.
Because besides money,
there are a lot of things that are valuable.
Siyu, my life
is much more exciting than you imagined.
No.
You just keep learning from experience then.
My boyfriend is here to pick me up.
Sorry. I'll be leaving.
Take care.
I'm here!
How's that possible?
I'm sure!
No, you must have mistaken it.
Chen Yiming told me so himself.
Then he definitely lied to you.
We are business partners right now.
He wouldn't lie to me.
But if he does this, how can he face Li Siyu?
Please! They broke up months ago.
But Li Siyu hasn't forgotten about him; she's still thinking of getting back together with him.
How do you know that?
Li Siyu lives in the same house as me.
How can I not know?
Well, it's really not Yiming's fault.
Chen Yiming definitely with that old woman for money.
I can't allow you to say that about my brother.
I said it.
Chen Yiming is a vain and greedy gigolo.
If anyone else said the words that you just said,
then it wouldn't be a problem.
But coming out of your mouth, I don't understand.
What do you mean?
Aren't you the one who wants to marry a rich guy?
Chen Yiming has attained that dream on your behalf,
so you should be applauding him.
You should think of him as an idol.
Also, are you scolding yourself or Chen Yiming?
Moreover, Chen Yiming is not a gigolo.
The commercials that Wang Ziru offered us were all rejected by him.
He still relies on me for food.
How come you're leaving after only eating half a meal?
I'm too angry!
Today's article was very blunt.
The content must be blunt if I want to be in the top ten trending posts.
What are you writing tomorrow?
I'm writing about Lubao's contests of equities.
Okay. What side are you on?
As a bystander, I must remain neutral, of course.
I look forward to reading it.
Can I interview you for a bit?
Okay.
Since you've worked with Pan Zhiyou for a while now,
what do you think of him?
Pan Zhiyong is idealistic and has strong emotions,
but the market doesn't trust feelings and ideals.
The market trusts the law, power, and rules.
I also heard that before he left Lubao, he said some ruthless words.
He said something like..
"You group of savages. We'll see how long you can stay happy."
Yes. Acquirers are usually viewed as wolves.
It's because we prioritize returns.
Due to that goal, people who hinder the company's development
or staff who hang around and have achieved nothing,
we will definitely heartlessly fire them.
So,
people are annoyed and hate us
but the market will improve due to us.
However, from Lubao's history of development,
Pan Zhiyong is indeed a very outstanding leader.
He is not the most outstanding though.
Then, who do you think is the most outstanding?
You.
Yiming.
Are you really not going to come back and help me?
Do you know why I chose to leave Tianye?
I do.
I scared you.
No.
I... At that time, I had just gone through a breakup.
My mind really was a mess,
so I needed time and space
to peacefully figure out
exactly what my situation was.
I understand.
So, at that time,
no matter what, I had to leave Tianye.
Yiming, you have never relied on me before.
I want to keep it that way now.
No problem. I will listen to you.
I'm back!
Today was so tiring!
You came back so early today.
Yeah.
Siyu,
- there's something...
- I already know.
H-How do you know?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Siyu, listen to me.
It's fine.
The two of us broke up long ago. Who he is with has nothing to do with me.
Yes, that's right.
Are you okay?
How could I not be? Isn't it just a man?
- Yes!
- We'll just find another.
Yes, we'll find two.
No. We'll find a bunch of men.
More handsome than him!
- Better than him!
- More talented than him!
Yet I still want him.
Siyu,
if you want to cry, then go ahead.
I'm not going to cry.
There's nothing to cry about.
I have a career.
How do I have time to be distracted by this kind of thing?
Yes.
Hello, Director Zhang.
I want to ask about what your final thoughts are on investing in Laidianle.
Okay, okay.
Then... when we have good projects, I'll introduce them to you.
Okay.
He...
He isn't willing to invest.
He doesn't have good taste.
He will regret it for sure!
He isn't willing to invest!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
You'll feel better once you cry it out.
♫  The wishes that I made ♫
Don't worry, it's fine.
♫ Realize ♫
It's fine.
♫  Nights are filled with loneliness  ♫
♫  Lights are dimming  ♫
Just cry.
♫  yet I'm awake  ♫
It's fine.
♫  Love and bittersweet joys  ♫
♫  Regrets  ♫
♫  You were by my side  ♫
Oh, right.
I have something to talk to you about.
Yes?
I have been paying attention to Laidianle.
Considering its merits, I think Lubao can continue investing in it.
No.
Why?
There are two ways to start a business.
One way is to quick financing, spending, and expansion in order to occupy the whole market immediately.
The other is to steadily work and fight.
Earn profit by steadily running the business and then expand slowly.
Li Siyu, in the start, was hovering between the two,
causing her to be in this dilemma now where she cannot continue with either way.
Is there any way to turn things around then?
It's too late.
Competitors have already appeared in the market. Also, their momentum is better than hers.
She has already missed the best time for expansion.
Even if Pan Zhiyong was still the president,
Lubao's Board of Directors would not support the investment into Laidianle, right?
Then that's really a shame.
It's not a shame.
Li Siyu is a good salesperson.
Bbut when it comes to digital marketing and financing, she's like a blank piece of paper.
Also, Pan Zhiying is very self-willed and self-conceited,
he wouldn't listen to the opinions of others.
The two of them collaborating was bound to fail.
Do you still miss her?
I just don't want... don't want to see her in such a difficult situation.
Yiming,
in every other aspect, I'm pretty generous;
but when it comes to relationships, I'm petty.
I don't want you to always bring her up.
I don't want you to always miss her.
Okay?
I really can't believe that Wang Ziru is that kind of a person.
Now that I think about it, when she got close to me in the beginning,
she was not only targeting Lubao,
but also Chen Yiming.
You can't just let this go then!
What do you want?
You have to at least let Chen Yiming know what that old woman is truly like.
Xiaoling,
we broke up because of our problems.
It had nothing to do with other people.
That Wang Ziru treated you like that, are you really able to just let it go?
I can't.
Then we need to find a way to vent that anger out!
Do you know what it means to vent anger?
Yelling at her, hitting her, or even stabbing her a few times;
but trust me, these things won't dissipate my anger.
The only way I can dissipate my anger is by
steadily making Laidianle big, powerful, and going public.
Will you be able to do it?
I must do it.
All right.
You can come and take a look around at our company.
I can show you all the data on my site's back end.
Once you see it, you will know that this project is definitely promising!
Okay.
Let's keep in touch.
Come in!
Sister,
I heard that Lubao is not going to invest in us anymore.
Lubao has encountered some problems of their own.
Then is Laidianle over?
No way.
- But we—
- I have other ways to get funding.
Really?
Go back to work.
Sister,
no matter if it's to live or to die, I will stand by you.
I will definitely not die.
[Wechat Picture]
[The 1 file has been successfully trashed.]
- President Li.
- I know.
- Then...?
- Trust me, I have a plan.
President Li!
Lao Bai handed in her resignation just now.
I know.
Five staff members have already left this month.
It's fine. We can recruit ten more.
President Li, I think the problem is not with recruitment.
Everyone is panicky now. There are many rumors about
the company's future.
Everyone, come here!
Drop your work for a moment and come over here!
Hurry!
I want to officially tell everyone.
First, we have already resolved the trivial issue
regarding finances. The company has returned to normal now.
Second, since the company started,
it's always been a company that keeps creating miracles.
What do we rely on to make miracles happen?
Do we rely on the market? On funds?
No.
What we rely on is our belief that not only can we through hardship,
but we can also get past the self-blame, weakness, hesitation, and suspicion in our hearts.
We will definitely win!
We will definitely be able to smile till the end!
Seek perfection! Seek excellence!
That's right. Together, we will
seek perfection! Seek excellence!
Chen Yiming,
do you think that I don't have a heart?
That I will gracefully allow you to stand in front of me?
Let me finish.
I didn't kick you out
because I'm not willing to let my employees see me be a bitch.
Please listen to what I have to say.
I feel very disgusted already.
Don't eliminate the last bit of good feelings
between us.
I didn't come to discuss our relationship.
Do we still have a relationship?
I came here today,
to persuade you to close Laidianle.
Are you saying this with your identity as Lubao's current GM's
boyfriend?
The relationship between Sister Ziru and I is a personal matter.
I don't want to explain it.
I came here today for your sake.
I can't believe you just said that.
Are you not disgusted?
If you really want to succeed,
you must understand how to choose and learn to let go.
When you first started the business, I was watching.
You focused on the product and was very careful.
However, you suddenly started to speed up.
Afterward, perhaps because your funds were disappearing, you started to hold back.
Now, you have no guidelines at all.
Don't think that just because you work in Wemedia, you know everything!
Okay.
Let me talk about marketing planning something I understand very well.
Nowadays, for a startup
to promote an app without burning money, is very difficult.
If you have a unique creation and a clear selling point,
then it's not impossible. Did you have that though?
Let's talk about your flyer.
What's the difference between this and a shopping mall's DM flyer?
(TN: direct mail flyers)
Let's talk about your marketing highlights.
Do you bring convenience to the scooter users?
Or bring franchisees business?
You may think that both are your highlights.
But when it comes to promotions, you must have a key point.
Even if I have mistakes, it's not late for me to correct them.
You've already run out of resources.
All entrepreneurs experience the darkness before dawn.
As long as we get past it, there is light.
This is not the darkness before dawn, this is a pit of mud where you fall further and further into.
What gives you the right to say that?
In regards to the current situation of Laidianle,
I believe that you are clearer than me.
Are you here to see me make a fool of myself?
Leaving already? No need to go in such a hurry.
I want you to witness a big life event of mine.
Guan Xiaotang, what are you doing?
Sister President Li,
right now,
it is the 193451st minute since I have met you.
This number doesn't mean anything.
But what I'm want to say today means a lot.
Sister President Li,
you're the coolest girl I've ever met.
I'm willing to let you kick my ass for the rest of my life.
Aside from having a blind ex-boyfriend, you don't have any other flaws.
I love you.
Let's go! Let's go!
Sister President Li,  I have a level 200 mystical beast, a Water-Dragon.
- Wow! Level 200!
- I decided to give it to you.
What is it?
This is my username and password. Please accept it.
Stop messing around. Get up!
If you don't accept it, I'm not getting up.
Accept it! Accept it! Accept it!
Fine. I'll accept it.
Sorry.
Xiao Tang treat us to a meal!
It's 1:00 a.m., what are you doing out here not sleeping?
You are not afraid that your face will become loose?
In third grade,
I got third place for an exam.
My mom hit me brutally
as if I had gotten last place or something.
What a terrible childhood.
Later on, you came to our home.
I discovered that for every exam,
if you weren't last, then you were second to last.
But your mom never hit you.
She didn't even yell at you.
During that time, I thought,
how is it that mothers could be so different?
It's not that your mom is different from my mom,
it's that you and I are different.
You were good at studying so your mom required you to get first place for every exam.
I was not.
My mom was used to it. She accepted it.
We are actually the same.
It's the middle of the night, are you going to sleep or not?
If you're not going to sleep, I'm going to sleep.
Don't stay up so late!
♫  Just like childhood wishes ♫
♫ that I don't fulfill  ♫
♫  Nights are filled with loneliness  ♫
♫  Lights are dimming yet I'm awake  ♫
I should also accept my destiny.
♫  Love and bittersweet joys  ♫
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫