Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 38]
No!
Pink represents princesses.
You haven't called in two years now you suddenly come up with this requirement, don't you feel you've gone too far?
Princess!
I said you went too far!
Little Queen.
Here. Little Princess.
I want to eat dessert!
- Come here.
- I want an ice jelly dessert.
(T/N: relative to Korea's "patbingsu" - instead of shaved ice they use a clear jelly and toppings)
I want to eat candy!
You can't go there.
You are allergic to peanuts, so you can't eat an ice jelly dessert. Okay?
You already have cavities. You can't eat candy, okay?
Let's do this. Who can make dad laugh can have ice cream!
Okay! Okay!
Dad! Laugh!
- Laugh!
- What are you doing, Yuwei? Shanshan?
Laugh, laugh, laugh!
What are you doing? Yuwei, what are you doing?
Are you making a face?
He laughs!
Ice cream! Ice cream!
What are these two babies doing?
They want to have ice cream!
Then take them to have ice cream! Let's go!
Yeah! Go!
Ice cream!
Auntie, where is my dad?
He went to participate in the senior choir.
Okay.
I heard that you rejected that Xiao Wen?
You already know.
I saw Auntie Lou.
She said Xiao Wen took you to see a house. He is so sincere!
How can you not cherish him?
We are not the same type of people.
Are you smart or stupid?
You don't want Xiao Wen? So many people desire him!
Everyone thinks differently.
I planned this for you! You are not young.
If you don't get married soon, you can only marry those who have been divorced.
Auntie, I know you did it for my sake.
But I can handle it myself.
Look at you!  You are so smart but you just can't figure things out.
Luckily, I held back one.
Go to meet Uncle Jiang's nephew this weekend.
Also, Chairman Hong's student.
Both have good qualities.
What are you thinking about? Let's have dinner together.
- I need to accompany my parents this evening.
- You are with them every day.
You left your pretty girlfriend alone. That's dangerous.
Shut up.
She still hasn't met your parents?
No.
Liu Yang, why are you so blunt?
Can you be more poetic?
Ignore him.
Perhaps she is afraid? Your relationship is a little complicated.
You can't have her be afraid.
Women are all empowered by men.
♪ I wish you give an affirmation  ♪
♪ Then my love is meaningful  ♪
So we should sing more in a karaoke.
Go! Let's go to a karaoke tonight.
I need to take care of Yuwei.
Why do you take care of kids every day?
Zhizhi is busy. I have time.
Did you two divorce?
Should I show you my divorce certificate?
You wear your wedding ring every day and continue to be single.
How come I feel that you fell for Zhizhi more than before?
You are right. This is how I feel for Zhizhi now.
How about her?
She cares less and less about me.
That's not okay.
You need to take action.
What do you mean?
What does Zhizhi like?
Without a rose and ring,
I married you not knowing everything.
You don't like those.
Is there a woman who doesn't like these?
Right. I should make up a proposal for her!
I can plan for you.
Right. Send Yiming. He specializes in proposals. Right?
Shut up! Can you stop talking?
No. No.
Shut up, okay? Stop talking.
Okay?
I will shut up.
When a kid coughs, you shouldn't use medicine to relieve a cough first. You should reduce phlegm first.
Right? I see. Every time Sushan coughs, it lasts very long.
It seems that I didn't give her the right medicine.
I will send you some medicine that works well on Yuwei.
If Sushan coughs again, try those first.
Sounds good.
- Dad!
- What's wrong?
You made your clothes dirty.
I will do it.
Auntie will help you, okay?
Come, baby.
Take it for me, okay?
This one, too.
Take this off, okay?
Raise your arm.
Come on.
Give me the milk tea.
Thank you.
Ice cream.
You won't make your clothes dirty this way.
I want one, too.
- Here.
- Thank you!
Here.
I took the wrong one.
Thank you.
Slowly.
You know many tricks!
Just a bit of life experiences.
Uncle!
Can Sushan and I go to look at the fish near the door?
Okay, but you can't exit the main door.
- Okay, I know.
- Good girl!
I will take you there.
- Thank you.
- You are welcome.
I saw you were unhappy while answering the phone just now. Was it about work?
It was Sushan's mom.
She is going to get married again. She asked Sushan to be her flower girl.
I didn't agree and I argued a bit with her.
How long have you been divorced?
Three years. When Sushan was one year old, she left with a foreigner.
It's not easy for you to take care of a child alone.
It is hard.
I'm okay. I just feel sorry for Sushan.
As long as the child has people who love her, she won't suffer from injustice.
Do you think so?
I feel a bit comforted hearing you say this.
I often say this to myself as well.
Thank you.
How about you? Why did you divorce?
It's okay. If you don't want to talk about this. I shouldn't have brought this up.
It's okay. I'm okay to talk about it.
Seen from the outside, I broke up with her dad
because of another person.
But now I feel that we had too many problems in the marriage.
I think you are quite perfect.
At that time, I only wanted to be a good mom and a good wife wholeheartedly.
But I forgot to be the best version of myself.
Until one day, I had to face all the problems myself,
I realized how helpless I was.
I didn't have solutions. I needed to start over again.
It's not easy for you to work and take care of the child at the same time.
Yes. Work is stressful.
I was cursed by clients often as well.
I apologize to you again.
I was kidding.
You didn't feel stressed today, did you?
Today, I'm very happy.
I'm also happy.
Where are you, Li Siyu?
I miss you, Sister.
I don't have a pond.
I only have this beach.
Be the only sand sculpture on my beach
(T/N: "sand sculpture" means stupid people or behavior on Chinese internet.)
Okay?
Sand sculpture!
Li Siyu...
Li Siyu, where are you now?
I think I miss you. I miss you so much!
I miss you so much! You made me wait for so long.
Show up quickly!
Psycho!
Li Siyu,
I want to be your cold medicine.
I even prepared this for you.
When on earth will you come to hug me?
Quickly come to hug me!
You scared me.
Why are you here?
Even though Tianyuan's investment is not more than 30%,
I am willing to give you 100% of me.
What do you mean?
I don't care how you define our relationship, I want to tell you now
that I'm serious.
I'm serious without reservation. I'm so serious that I want to gain my parents' approval and blessing.
I'm so serious that I hope our relationship will last forever.
Thank you.
Me, too.
Ziru, when I am standing next to you,
in all aspects, I can't compare with you.
But there is one thing that I won't have less than you.
It's my sincerity.
No.
- I have my own problems...
- If you are worried about our age gap,
if you are worried about my parents' opinion,
I can tell you clearly now, I don't care.
Even if they are my closest persons,
they can't affect my love for you.
In a few days, my parents will leave Shanghai.
Before they leave,
I will take them to have some authentic Shanghai cuisine.
I will send you the address.
If you can come, it will be great.
But if you can't make it, it's also okay.
I respect your choice.
Okay.
I will think about it.
Hello?
You didn't work overtime today?
Am I Zhang Zhizhi? I don't work overtime every day.
What are you doing now?
Staying home alone and feeling lonely.
You are not with He Mu?
He goes to bed at 10:15. I can't disturb him.
How are you doing with Xiao Wen?
I made it clear to him.
- So quick!
- I'm always a doer.
Don't be happy too early.
I heard from my mom that
she planned bigger things for you.
You mean the birthday party of the granddaughter of Third Uncle?
Yes!
It's too difficult for me. It's annoying me.
Something can annoy Li Siyu?
I'm done.
Think of solutions for me!
If you can find a boyfriend, you will mess up my mom's plan.
Where can I find one? That's even more difficult.
Did I say you have to find a real one?
Listen to me. There will be a way to work it out.
What do you mean?
I will send Lei Haowen to you at that time.
It's easy for you to say this. Does Lei Haowen listen to you?
You don't need to worry about this.
Is this nice?
It's pretty good.
Give me one pair as well.
What?
I've just finished acting as your ex-boyfriend.
Now I have to act as Li Siyu's current boyfriend.
Can you ask someone else?
You can't only shear one sheep, right?
Your acting skill is the best.
Go away.
You are an underdog actor to win the oscar.
I'm also a popular veteran actor.
Right.
The rich second generation you acted was even more real than the real ones.
Didn't you say I'm a fake one?
You already promoted!
Come on. You are just making use of me.
Lei Haowen!
Don't be so shameless! Are you helping me or not?
Yes!
I'll remember this!
Next Friday. You show up at the birthday celebration of the Third Uncle's granddaughter.
Drive a nice car. At least over ¥500,000.
If you don't have one, go borrow one. If you don't have anyone to borrow, then rent one.
Is the Porsche from last time okay?
No! It's too flashy. My parents won't like it.
- Your parents?
- Li Siyu's parents.
Get a brand name bag. But not the ones that's everywhere.
Do you have any requirements on the brand?
Not low-key international first-tier brand.
Car. Bag. I get it.
Also, your hair and clothes, change a bit.
- Also, change your family background.
- How?
Young talent. Back from overseas.
Do I need to be more? I'm already young and talented!
Young talent.
Your mom is your mom. Li Siyu's dad is her dad. Right?
Yes.
Sit. Sit.
When will you arrive?
Feel free to sit.
In five minutes.
Sit.
Siyu!
People are all here. Dishes can be served.
Let's wait. Someone hasn't arrived.
Who?
My boyfriend.
I didn't know that.
Nor did I.
You have boyfriend?
Since when?
- Why didn't we know this?
- I didn't know as well.
Her parents didn't know as well.
Because we haven't confirmed our relationship before.
So I didn't report to you.
- Where does he from?
- What does he do?
How is his financial condition?
Is he a nice person?
He will arrive very soon.
He can answer all of your questions by himself.
Good!
We will test him well.
We will test him well as the family seniors.
- Okay.
- Siyu.
Everyone,
- let me introduce you. This is—
- Right.
Excuse me. We are late. I will introduce for Siyu,
this is...
Hi, everyone, I'm Siyu's boyfriend, Guan Xiaotang.
Nice to meet you all.
It's him! Not him!
[Yuan Yuan Restaurant]
- Okay.
- No problem.
Sit.
This is what you like.
What's this called?
I will try one.
Mom, give the bowl to me. I will give you some eel.
This is your mom's favorite.
- How can I not know this.
- Not too much, okay?
Soft heart.
- Is it called this? I ate this before.
- Did you make this up by yourself?
Soft heart.
Give me the cup. Have more soup. Drink less juice. It's sweet.
That's all right?
What's going on?
Surprised? Good?
How come it's Guan Xiaotang?
Lei Haowen's acting is too exaggerated. He is heartless. So I changed him.
I can't find someone else in such a short time.
How did you find him?
He added me on WeChat.
How did he add you on WeChat?
He is good at technology. It's easy for him to find my Wechat.
You knew I was trying to hide from him.
Why did you make him come?
I like to cross you. I was like this since I was young!
You asked me to go in the east direction, I will insist on going in the west direction.
You...
I completely tailor-made this for you according to your requirements.
Although Guan Xiaotang is young, he
is really passionate about this role.
Gu Xiaoling, don't get caught by me.
How about we do a video call? I really want to see your face now.
Aunt, this is the present I brought for you.
Thank you. I'm Xiaoling's friend.
I'm called Lei Haowen.
- You can call me Haowen.
- I got it. I got it. Surname, Lei, first name, Haowen.
Xiaotang,
what does your family do?
My dad is in the circulation of recycled materials business.
When his business expands, he started to do business in other industries as well.
Now he has business in energy, chemical engineering, food, and finance.
Amazing.
I'm Lei Haowen.
Don't go too far.
Drive.
Oh my, girls go through many changes growing up.
- You're getting pretty and prettier by the day.
- Thank you, Eldest Aunt.
You're already like the white swan princess.
Hey, Siyu, I'm begging you
to take care of the situation with your cousin.
What?
Next year, he will be graduating from college.
Help him find a good job at Xiaotang's group.
We can talk about it next year.
Hey, Siyu.
He's got such great qualities. Whatever you do, don't let him go.
I understand.
Guan Xiaotang.
- Right?
- Yes.
Xiaotang, this kid,
- How much money did my daughter use to invite you here?
- is really good.
Uncle, I did it for myself.
Don't be nervous, I won't reveal it to everyone.
I really am not an actor!
- You can't hide it from me.
- Uncle,
even if you don't trust my information,
you should at least believe in your daughter's charm.
You're not my daughter's type.
Uncle, but in life, don't you have to try them all?
Hey, these words appeal to me!
They had a good talk.
Siyu, thinking of the rain, I'll drop off Aunt and Uncle. It's quite windy.
You and Director Guan can take a walk over there.
Yes, yes, yes. Over there, nearby, is a park. You can walk around there.
- Okay, okat.
- I know.
Okay, Auntie, Uncle, the wind is very strong. Let's get going.
- Be careful.
- Siyu, then we're leaving as well.
- Okay, okay.
- We're leaving, Director Guan. Have fun.
- Stay safe.
- All right.
- Let's go have fun!
- Take a walk.
- We're leaving. Bye!
Hurry!
Uncle, be careful.
So I passed, didn't I?
Hey! Hey!
Your stick-on mustache looks way too fake.
They're not stick-on! They're authentic!
Hey!  Tell me the truth. Where did you graduate?
Don't you have my resumé?
You graduated from the Central Academy of Drama, didn't you?
You act more convincingly as a rich second generation kid than Lei Haowen does!
Who taught you?
I wasn't acting. I was being authentic.
You think I don't know you?
Who did you borrow this attire from?
And that car, how much did it cost to rent? I'll transfer the money back to you through WeChat.
- I don't want money.
- Then, what do you want?
I want you.
Go back to Shanghai. Go find yourself a young woman
and get the experience you need. Then you can come and find me.
I'm experienced, okay?
Even though I look like young, fresh meat, I'm very mature already, I am!
- Let's go.
- To do what?
I'm taking you to play in the children's playground.
Hurts!
I acted for so long for nothing??
- Yiming, will we be able to make it?
- Yes.
- Hurry.
Be careful, careful.
Make sure that's flat.
All right. If this looks okay, you should get in the car.
Get in the car.
- Good.
- Yiming? Yiming?
This is Uncle and Auntie, yes?
Uncle, Auntie, I'm Yiming's... friend.
My name is Wang Ziru.
Originally, Yiming said to have lunch with you.
But I was in a meeting and could not make it. I'm so sorry.
It's fine, it's fine.
I know that you two are going to catch the train this afternoon, so I had to come and send you off. Otherwise, I wouldn't be able to forgive myself.
It's fine. You're busy.
Uncle and Auntie, I prepared some little gifts for the two of you.
- Uncle. Auntie.
- That's too sweet of you.
- Too kind of you.
- I'm sorry. Thank you.
- Thanks.
I need to rush back to the company for a meeting.
I cannot send you to the train station.
It's fine. You can attend to your work.
Yiming, get in the car. Don't waste any more time.
- Okay. Come on, Dad and Mom.
- See you.
Bye, Uncle. Bye, Auntie.
Be careful when driving!
- We're leaving.
- Be careful.
Look!
- I can't even sit in it!
- You look like it.
What do you mean, I look like it?
Enjoy it properly, okay?
Older Sister Director Li!
Go play. Doesn't it suit you so well?
If you want me to play, then I will.
Come back to Shanghai with me.
Since I came back here, I don't plan to go back.
That's enough.
You're naturally formidable, but you've gotten bullied in the workplace.
Maybe you don't feel wronged, but I feel embarrassment for you.
I think it's nice.
Can you even do it?
When we first met, you hit and scolded me!
You can't change it!  It's your personality.
I know that in your mind, you've never been able to get past Laidianle and Lubao.
Isn't it just taking down two companies? It's fine.
Later, we can take down a few more companies then you won't feel so bad.
Are you asking to be hit again?
Look! You're so violent.
That's the true you, right?
Yiming, who was that woman?
Didn't he say already? We weren't going to discuss it.
Well, can't I at least ask? We don't have to discuss it.
If you want to ask, then ask.
Where is Xiao Wang from? What do her parents do?
Yiming, this present was sent straight to my heart.
The inscription on it is of Liquan in Jiucheng Palace.
I love this bracelet so much!
It such good quality.
It's real.
Hey, let me try it.
The inscription on it is of Liquan in Jiucheng Palace.
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
I put it on. It's nice, it's nice. Take a look!
- Just take a look. Is it good?
- Yes, it's pretty.
So nice.
This is...
How did you know what my parents liked?
I saw the pictures you sent out on WeChat moments.
Your father has many inscriptions, your mother likes jewelry.
Well, did I guess correctly?
You did.
My parents loved them and were very happy.
In truth, you had no meetings.
By using the method of sending them off,
you cut short a meeting that could have been very awkward.
At the same time, you left them a very deep impression of you.
Are you blaming me?
Yiming.
I can predict the trend of stocks.
I can also control many things.
When it comes to love, I'm useless.
I'm also uncertain.
Yiming,
It's not that I don't care...or don't want a future with you.
I just don't know what to do.
I know.
Actually talking about love,
I also have lots to fear.
We can learn together.
Make efforts together.
Okay.
Let's make efforts together.
I hope one day that we can meet them leisurely.
You should give me some time.
Yes.
Yiming,
I hope you can also lay down some unnecessary dignity.
Help me to rebrand Lubao.
Okay?
Okay.
Aunt, there is too much stuff!
- Too much! We can't eat them all.
- We can do it.
- Take back some.
- Take them!
Eat this on the way back. They are all our specialty.
This is for Xiaoling.
I will take them!
- I will take them to Xiaoling.
- Ask Xiaoling for me.
When will she bring her boyfriend back so we can see?
Since they are serious now, they should visit the father-in-law soon!
Serious?
Siyu said that man has proposed to her!
Xiaoling also said yes.
Auntie. Dad. Let's talk about Xiaoling later.
The traffic will be worse if they leave any later.
Quickly go.
Be careful on the way back.
- Drive slowly.
- We will leave.
- Take care, Auntie and Uncle!
- Be careful!
I will come back to see you again. Bye, Siyu.
Drive slowly!
Money is not the most important.
The most important is that he is nice to you.
Xiao Tang, although he is younger than you,
he knows to love you and also treat you nicely.
He is the one!
I will listen to you, Auntie.
But he is in Shanghai. You are here. What are your future plans?
Future?
We can talk about it later.
You can't!
This is a big event! What do you think—
This Guan Xiaotang...
is not mature yet.
Siyu is nice to Xiaotang.
That is acting for you to see!
What do you mean?
Tell me!
Do you still need one? Coming!
Old man!
Siyu, I think he is good.
Auntie, let's go back first.
Tell me what's going on.
- I really like that kid.
- That's great.
Brother Lei, drive slowly. Okay?
I'm afraid to die.
I'm still young, Brother Lei!
I have billions of family property to inherit!
Stop!
Let me drive.
What do you plan to do, Brother Lei?
I don't know either.
It's very urgent. You still don't know what to do?
Show your trump card.
I don't have one.
Who said?
True love is obtainable.
- Step back a little.
- A little back.
I can't do it. I'm exhausted.
You two continue.
Step a bit back.
Is it okay?
The two of them get along quite well.
Yes. It's rare.
- Yuwei's mom,
- Yes?
do you feel that...
we two get along well as well?
Perhaps it's because of the kids.
Our personalities are also similar, right?
I will go straight to my point.
Being with you,
I feel very assured and warm.
When we return from Disneyland the last time,
I've been thinking about one thing.
If we four can make a family together,
we will be very happy.
What do you think?
Sushan's dad.
You can call me Lixing in the future.
If I may, I will call you Zhizhi.
I haven't considered this.
I brought this up today, so you can have time to think it over.
-But—
- Don't rush to answer me right away.
Spend some time thinking about it, right?
Is it okay?
See you.
Xiaoling!
I almost forgot to give this to you.
What's this?
To guarantee our rights,
to guarantee our wedding can be conducted smoothly and to make sure our marriage lasts long and stable,
I drafted a prenuptial agreement.
So heavy?
Nine chapters altogether.
23 items. 347 clauses.
Including politics, economy, religion, psychological education, and so on.
It also plans different stages such as pre-marriage, the wedding, and the duration of the marriage.
Say it again?
I hope you can sign this agreement before we start to plan our wedding.
Are you getting married or establishing diplomatic relations?
Please look at it carefully.
I hope we can communicate about this agreement when we have a date next time.
Okay.
Then, I'll see you next Wednesday evening at 18:18, at the same place and the same table.
[Prenuptial agreement]
What are you doing here? You scared me!
You are getting married?
You drank alcohol?
Answer me first.
It's none of your business!
You can't marry that robot.
Why?
Because I like you.
But I don't like you.
But you don't like him at all.
Even if I don't like him,
but it's impossible between us.
Why is it impossible?
When you are down, I can drink with you.
When you get into trouble, I can solve it for you.
You can wear slippers without make-up with me.
I can make you laugh.
I'm willing to be cursed or beaten by you.
When you need me, I won't switch off my phone and go to sleep.
Do you have money?
Do you have a company that is worth hundreds of millions?
Can you make me feel secure?
I don't have money now.
But I will have in the future.
I'm tired. I want to rest.
Xiaoling.
What are you doing?
You can't leave if you don't finish today.
I don't want talk to a drunk person!
Xiaoling, if I'm not drunk, I can't say this directly to you.
Gu Xiaoling!
I love you, Gu Xiaoling.
- Can you stay together with me?
- Let me go!
But I don't love you.
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... Oh... En...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah... Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫