Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 15]
Liu Yang! Liu Yang!
- Liu Yang! What are you doing?
- Going home.
The party hasn't ended yet!
I didn't study abroad in America and I'm not a director.
My family are all farmers. I'm not good enough to attend such a party.
- I was just saying.
- You've gone beyond your means in order to be impressive.
If I don't say that, then people would look down on Yuwei.
But by saying that, where do you place me?
My director knows that mom. If he finds out about your boasting,
- then how am I supposed to face him?
- But I wasn't wrong.
You did study in America before
and you're about to be a director.
Zhang Zhizhi, can you please be more clear-headed?
We're not the same kind of people as them, yet you're forcing yourself to fit in.
You may not find it awkward, but I find it embarrassing.
Liu Yang!
The smell of the grass and soil is so nice.
Come on, baby.
You're back?
Grandma, look at the present I got!
You got a present? Let me see.
Mom, has Liu Yang come back?
Yeah, he's in your room.
- The tail can move.
- Really?
Mom, please help me give Yuwei a bath.
Okay, okay. Come on.
That was 1975.
In the countryside...
After you left,
a teacher who taught etiquette at Buckingham Palace came.
He taught all of the kids royal etiquettes.
If Yuwei didn't join this social circle,
would she be able to learn such things?
Even though we're an ordinary family,
our child must surpass us.
We must at least teach our child to motivate herself to be better.
Also, let me tell you—
Sister Siyu, the decision on how to deal with Sister Yuan is out.
- What did it say?
- She's being removed.
- Sister Siyu, you're here?
- Your complexion is so nice today.
Watch what you are saying. When has Sister Siyu's complexion ever been bed?
You two have such sweet mouths.
Sister Siyu, let's have a party to celebrate.
- Celebrate what?
-  Celebrate you becoming the sales director!
- This hasn't even happened.
- It will happen sooner or later.
Stop, stop.
Li Siyu, congratulations.
- Sister Yuan...
- Not only do I want to congratulate you on the promotion,
but I also hope that the higher you climb, the harder you fall.
Don't think that just because you've got Pan Zhiyong to back you that you don't have to fear anyone or that you can step on anyone.
Let me tell you. I may not be able to punish you,
but someone will eventually punish you.
Li Siyu, wait and see.
There will be a day when you cry.
Go away!
I said, go away!
Siyu! Siyu, GM Pan is looking for you.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Hurry and come with me.
Hurry.
Sis, give me your purse.
President Pan.
Sit.
Next Monday, Human Resources will send out a notice
to officially announce you as the sales director.
I can lay the cards out onto the table for you now.
Lubao is on the brink of death.
- But haven't we always been selling well?
- We haven't been making money though.
Why?
A few years ago, this area had bonus policies.
(T/N: policies that benefit the society such as tax cuts)
Starting from last year,
the bonus policies got canceled. Our sales have been stuck at the same level.
Technology has come to a bottleneck. Our capital chain has ruptured.
This is Lubao's current situation.
- Weren't you guys discussing equity financing?
- Yes.
But whether it be Tianyi,
Hua An, or the Shanghai Bank, they all had a condition.
They said that Lubao's sales revenue must double.
- Double?
- Yes, double.
That means that in three months, you must bring us ¥500,000,000.
That's impossible!
Fifteen years ago, I told them
that I wanted to break through the American and Japanese monopolies.
I wanted China to have their own new energy enterprise. At the time, they had also said it was impossible.
- But you did it.
- So, there's no such thing as impossible. It just a matter of whether you will give it your all or not.
Will you go all out or not?
- I will.
- Wonderful.
My judgment was correct.
Let me tell you something else.
It's very hard. It will be excruciatingly hard, but the future will definitely be wonderful.
After we get through this obstacle, Lubao's value will be limitless. Trust me!
Within five years, Lubao will definitely join enter the stock market.
Within ten years, Lubao will become China's biggest monopoly.
Within fifteen years, make Lubao the number one in the world.
- I believe that.
- I don't believe in trust.
I only believe in giving it your all!
Give it your all with me. Lubao will definitely not let us down.
Lubao can definitely go on stage in the world's top award ceremony.
At that time,
we will go on stage together, representing Chinese engineering
as well as accepting the entire world's applause
and praise!
President Pan, don't worry!
In three months, I will make that ¥500,000,000 a reality.
Mom, later,
you and Yuwei can eat first. I'm going to wait for Liu Yang to come back.
During this time, you've worked very hard. I'm not that busy anymore.
Let me take and pick up Yuwei from early education classes.
Just let me go. I don't have anything to do anyways.
Here.
Yuwei, didn't I say that you're supposed to eat on your own?
When you eat, you can't play with toys.
After you finish eating, you can play. Okay?
When you are eating, eat properly.
If she wants to play, just let her.
Mom, it's a bad habit. We can't let her develop these bad habits.
Why are you crying?
Don't you usually baby your daughter?
The person who spoils her and who scolds her are both you.
Mom, loving her isn't the same as spoiling her.
I can't let her develop these bad habits. That's real love.
Look at her, you've made my granddaughter so upset.
Go away!
What did you say?
- Go away!
- Who did you learn this from?
Okay, okay, okay. Don't cry.
Okay, don't cry. Hurry and eat.
After you eat, you still have to go to your early education classes.
I dropped her early education class.
- What?
- I dropped her early education class.
Think about it.
How much does Liu Yang make each month?
It's not good to waste it on these things.
How can you call this a waste?
How isn't it a waste?
You guys say you have no money and can't afford a second child.
If spent less on Yuwei,
not only would you have a second, you could have had a third child by now.
Mom, you—
Eat up.
- Hello, who is this?
- Hello, are you Liu Yuwei's guardian?
- Yes, I am. Who are you?
- This is Little Talent Training Institution.
Last week you made an appointment for left-brain training,
but you never brought your child.
Would you like us to help you reschedule?
I'm sorry, our family is a bit busy right now. Can I schedule training for tomorrow?
Okay, no problem. Then I'll schedule you for 7:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Okay, thank you.
Mom, you didn't even take her to the left brain training?
No.
Zhizhi, don't blame me, an old person, for butting into your business.
Yuwei's food, clothing, and items
all suppose to be good for her brain and body. How much does all of this cost? Have you calculated it?
You are taking her to so many classes. From what I see, this family will be broke because of her.
- This isn't spending money, it's investing!
- What investing?
I would say that it's a waste of money.
Mom, how can you say these things in front of her?
What's wrong with saying that? She doesn't understand anyways.
She's already four! How can she not understand?
Of course, she doesn't. How smart can she be? Besides, have I said anything wrong?
It's just a waste of money. You might not care but I care.
Mom, how can you say that? She's my daughter, my and Liu Yang's daughter.
We earned the money. We will spend however much we are willing to on her.
Enough. You're willing?
You need to ask your conscience, how much money do you make?
It's my son Liu Yang who makes money to support this family!
Yes, my husband earned the money.
When it comes to how much we spend, I am in charge.
I'm his mother. He must listen to me.
In your home, he listened to you. After marrying me, he has to listen to me.
You don't understand anything, yet he has to listen to you?
This family is a mess because of you. I cannot live life like this.
It's all because Yuwei is a girl, right?
If she was a boy, no matter how much money we spent, it would be worth it!
Yes!
What century is it?
You are still worried about girl versus boy. You're also a woman!  How can you look down on women so much?
Don't talk to me about that.
In broad daylight, all you know is how to yell.
Don't eat anymore.
Mr. Liu, we'll be leaving first.
- Mr. Liu, see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow
- Hello?
- Hello, Liu Yang.
Can you get off work on time to come home today?
What's the matter?
I can't get along with your mom anymore.
We just fought.
- What happened?
- You'll know once you get back.
Yuwei doesn't listen to me anymore.
Her behavior is getting worse.
- I thought something big happened.
- Is this considered something small?
This is your daughter. Bad habits from childhood
will last a lifetime.
You don't even know what your mom said in front of Yuwei.
In front of Yuwei, she said that I waste money on Yuwei.
Enough, enough!  Don't say anymore. I'll talk to my mom.
Okay, come home early.
Okay, got it.
- Yang.
- Hi, Mom.
I really didn't say anything.
It's a fact that every month you spend a lot of money on Yuwei,
right?
Is it easy for me? I have to raise your kid and cook food for you guys.
I also wash clothes, I do so much work.
Now you guys are nitpicking me, what's this logic?
Mom,
I still have work to do.
Stop fighting. Can you guys do that for me?
Who's fighting? It's your wife.
All right, both of you just don't say so much.
I'm still busy. I'm hanging up.
Brother Yang?
You haven't gone home yet?
I'm just staying a bit longer.
Brother Yang, look!
What is it?
Where did you get it?
The last time, when I went home, I told my family that I wanted to eat small potatoes.
My dad sent these to me.
It's been at least 10 years since I've seen this type of small potatoes.
Brother Yang, then take this box.
Have Sister-in-Law cook them for you.
Her? She won't know how to cook them.
Besides, our house doesn't have a firewood stove. We wouldn't be able to create that type of flavor.
I know a place that has one.
I'll send you the location on WeChat.
[Wife]
Little Sister Yun,
how about we go to that place with the firewood stove you mentioned tonight?
Okay!
Eat it yourself, okay?
Mom, have some dinner.
Try it.
How is it, Brother Yang?
Is this the taste that you dream of?
I have finally eaten it.
You're back?
Do you have good news?
I've been officially appointed as the sales director.
Wow, that's great!
Congratulations! Cheers!
I booked a ticket and will leave the day after tomorrow.
I just got promoted,
so I can't go back with you.
I understand.
However, communications nowadays is so advanced,
we can video chat anytime, anywhere.
A long-distance relationship is nothing.
Moreover, to get here from where I live, it takes 2 hours when there is traffic.
So, you being in your hometown and me in Shanghai
is no different from right now.
Anyways, it's not far from here.
If we want to see each other I can get on the train for a few hours and come.
Then I can see you right away.
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow ♫
♫  like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫  the days have yet to come  ♫
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights, never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But is as lost as others  ♫
♫  We love with no room for anything else  ♫
♫  Never giving each other the chance to breathe  ♫
♫  Thought that being loved by you  ♫
♫  Thought that we wouldn't age  ♫
Eat on time and take medicine on time. Don't stay up late.
Try to drink less and it's best if you don't work overtime.
You have to video chat with me three times every day.
Each session must be at least three minutes.
If you go on a business trip you have to tell me.
I'll send you off the day after tomorrow.
♫ As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫  the days have yet to come  ♫
♫  With you  ♫
In this next part, I would like to talk about the financialization of art investments.
There are six types of financialization of art investments.
Art mortgages,
art pledges, art loans,
art trusts, art funds, and art stocks.
The last time is art appreciation.
But first, we need to clarify a concept.
Why aren't you inside?
Don't you think his lecture is really boring?
Old Liu's lectures have always been like that.
He is the best at talking about something interesting in a very boring manner.
He is not only boring but also forgetful.
The assignment he gave us two weeks ago was given to us again last week.
That's nothing.
Last week, I repaid him the money I borrowed yet he asked for it again yesterday.
I heard someone say he's very stingy.
I heard when he was in his third year of university,
he treated a classmate to roujiamo
(T/N: meat in flatbread that's a popular street snack.)
and even now he's asking to be paid back.
Ridiculous.
Do you want some?
Are you also my classmate?
How come I haven't seen you before?
I don't come often.
It looks like you skip class often, too.
It's about time to go in.
- Go in now?
- I have experience in this.
If we go in now and then ask a question before class is over,
then he won't realize we skipped class.
You're a veteran at this.
Follow this veteran.
Okay, we will discuss it up to here for today's class.
I'd like everyone to read some books I recommend.
Then write a book review of no less than 3,000 characters.
Email it to me before the next class.
Do you understand?
Okay, class is over.
I'm going to go ask a question.
Professor Liu, for the two important aspects of art investment, I didn't really understand it.
- Can you teach it to me again?
- I just talked about that.
One: artwork has become an important part of financial management.
Two: artwork has become involved in credit rating and pricing for companies and individuals.
So...
- When did you get here?
- Just now.
- Are you finished? If you're finished then let's go.
- Okay. Do you have any more questions?
- No.
- Wait for me, I have to get my things together.
How are we doing things today? Going dutch?
If we're going dutch then you should pay,
since you haven't paid me back for the roujiamo from our third year of university yet.
Don't speak nonsense, everyone is waiting.
It's not nonsense, you're a big boss now so shouldn't you treat me to a meal?
Let's go. Where are we going?
- Today, we definitely have to go dutch.
- Hey!
Everyone pays for themselves.
- Are you looking for me?
- I think she's looking for me.
Professor Liu.
Oh.
Are you one of Professor Liu's classmates?
Then, why didn't you tell me just now?
- Are you very afraid I'll tell him what you said?
- I'm not afraid.
If you give me your WeChat,
then I won't sell you out.
Okay.
If I invite you out and you don't come, then I'll still rat you out.
- That's blackmail.
- Bye.
Hello, I'm from Lubao Group.
Lubao Group's Sales Director, Li Siyu.
This is Lubao's pre-approved documents.
Okay, wait a moment while I register it.
Thank you.
Brother Yang, I've submitted the pre-approved documents on behalf of Lubao.
Someone with the surname Wu accepted it.
Got it.
Please take care of us.
Siyu, are you free to have a drink tonight?
Sure.
[Yiming]
[I'll send you off the day after tomorrow.]
Xiao Wei, go ask Old Wu if he has collected all the documents from each company yet.
Okay.
I saw you barely eating anything in the canteen these days.
Is your stomach acting up again?
Yes.
You are an adult, yet you don't even know how to take care of yourself.
Take care of these boxes for me.
Just these?
Yep, just these.
What else do you want to entrust me with?
There's nothing else.
Then, you and Li Siyu...
What are you planning on doing?
For the time being, we'll just be like this.
Bro,
there aren't a lot of people who have successful long-distance relationships.
But I think you two are different.
You, how do you have so much confidence in us?
Don't tell me you two had a mishap?
When she is with me,
I often feel I can't handle her.
Not to mention the hundreds of kilometers that will be between us.
Don't tell me Li Siyu will fly away.
No, she definitely won't.
But... I might let her down.
How can that be?
Once I think of
rainy days where I can't bring her an umbrella,
when she's sick and I can't get her medicine,
or even when she's sad and needs comforting,
I can only call her.
I don't feel very optimistic about our future.
Then don't go.
If I don't go,
then she'll be even more disappointed.
You and Siyu...
Won't break up, right?
For the time being, we won't.
But who can say what will happen in a year?
Or after 2 years?
Who can say for sure what will happen then?
I won't talk with you any longer. I still haven't finished packing up at home.
I'm leaving.
What time tomorrow? I'll send you off.
I'm going alone. No one should send me off.
Siyu.
- Sister Ziru.
- Have you been waiting long?
- No, I just got here.
- Why didn't you go in?
- It's no problem
- Let's go.
I ran into GM Pan yesterday. He told me
that you're officially the sales director now.
So I was thinking that I should treat you to dinner
to celebrate with you.
Thank you, Sister Ziru.
If it wasn't for your constant support and encouragement,
I would've given up a long time ago.
No, you wouldn't have.
You're not a woman who gives up easily.
I just let you get to know yourself more clearly.
Sit, Siyu.
Sister Ziru, how was your discussion with GM Pan?
It was pretty good. The whole negotiation had been going smoothly.
Our President Pan is an extremely insightful and hardworking leader.
It will definitely be the right decision to collaborate with him.
I've felt that way already.
Our team is also especially outstanding.
Actually, GM Pan appointing you as the sales director
has brought me more confidence in Lubao's management team.
Oh right. Have you, executives,
met with the representatives of those two companies?
You mean Hua'an and Shanghai Bank?
- Yes.
- Not yet.
Well, maybe it's not the right time yet.
Eat. These are our new dishes.
- Try it.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Sister Ziru, you should eat, too.
How has Yiming been recently?
He's been pretty good.
What's wrong?
We...
might have to break up.
What? Why?
He left his original company
and he hasn't been able to find a suitable job this whole time.
His hometown just happened to have an opportunity.
So he's going back to try it out.
Have you already talked about breaking up?
No.
But I have a really bad feeling.
I feel like... we'll break up sooner or later.
Your feelings surely aren't that weak.
It's been said that
the breakup rate of long-distance relationships is over 90%.
It's a critical period for Lubao right now.
As its sales director,
I must put 200% or even 300% of my efforts into work.
I don't have the time or the experience
to manage a long-distance relationship.
This is easy.
Easy?
I remember Yiming works as a planner, right?
Yes.
My company just happens to have an empty position for a planning director.
I'm not sure if Yiming would be willing to condescend for the position or not.
The annual salary should be higher than the previous one.
But it's a newly established department.
The scale is smaller.
Sister Ziru,
you saved my relationship.
Yiming!
- What's—
- Yiming, we don't have to be separated!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫