Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 24]
[Lubao New Energy was real-named reported for alleged bribery.]
[The biggest shady deal of the new energy battery industry.]
[Lubao New Energy exposed for bribery. It's value plummets.]
[Severe crack down on bribes and crimes, will Lubao become a target of public criticism?]
[Whether it is giving or accepting bribes, there should be severe punishment!]
[This kind of enterprise should be shut down. ]
[These people and companies that take public safety as a joke are social scum. Let's collectively boycott them.]
[Letting this kind of company produce car batteries?! Isn't that putting people's lives in danger?! Or are they trying to punish civilians!]
[How are they not embarassed to say that they are the leader of new energy batteries?!]
[Last year, my car combusted because of the Lubao battery!]
[Important, will Lubao batteries that have falsified data be recalled and refunds be given?]
[Behinds the scenes, the big boss continues to not worry.]
90% are rumors!
There is 10% truth!
The 10% is not like what they wrote!
GM Pan, I suggest we find a lawyer to sue these rumor mongers.
Then we hold a press conference to clarify the truth.
You still don't think this issue is not big enough?
Li Siyu,
you must immediately,
at all costs,
reduce the impact
to the smallest.
Where are you? I need you.
I'll wait for you at the old place.
[Sorry]
President Wang, the secretary of Lubao's GM Pan called just now,
she said they are still open to discussing about the financing.
Tell her that I don't have time this week. I have to deal with a family issue.
We will meet next week.
You already know?
The new is spreading all over the internet.
You knew so many media before. Could you ask people to help control the spreading for us?
It's too late.
It's been twelve hours already since the news broke out.
It is widely spread and you already missed the best time to deal with it.
So there is no solution?
I assessed the situation before you arrived.
The main target is the public opinion of the shady dealings of the bidding.
There is almost no question about the quality of Lubao products.
It's lucky from this perspective.
But the outcome is definitely settled that your brand image and profit will be damaged.
So the only thing you can do is stop public sentiment from getting worse and out of hand.
That can reduce investors from leaving to a minimum.
This is why I came to you.
You must keep the confidence of the partners with us.
According to my planning experience for so many years...
First: you can't avoid. You can't hide.
You must take action.
Second: you should go and contact new and traditional media.
Based on the principle of communicating sincerely,
admit your mistake to the public and shoulder your responsibility.
Also, punish the related people immediately.
It's not my problem. Why should I admit it?
At least, you didn't avoid arousing suspicion.
I remember you told me at that time.
You said you must take part in the bidding. It's not only for yourself,
but also for Lubao.
Now, Lubao needs you to endure humiliation in order to
shoulder all the responsibilities.
How?
Resign.
I got it.
Siyu, there is another thing.
I think this whole thing shouldn't be a hot topic.
But it went viral like this.
I don't think it's in line with the propagation rule.
What do you mean?
- Someone is hiring people to influence public opinion.
- Who?
If you need, I can investigate it for you.
Okay.
GM Pan, go on the internet to see those comments.
We really can't delay this any longer.
If you still don't punish Li Siyu,
all the netizens will explode on the internet.
Once the company gets into trouble then the staff take the blame for the company.
This kind of irresponsible company,
how can we gain the staff's trust?
How can we ask the staff to fight and sacrifice for us?
- There should be people to take responsibility, right?
- I will!
Absolutely not!
You are the Chairman of the Board and CEO.
It's better for me to take the blame instead of you!
It has had nothing to do with you from the beginning to the end!
But Lubao has something to do with me.
I will take the blame.
But Li Siyu as the party, if she doesn't get any punishment,
then it won't make any sense.
I can take all the responsibility by myself.
I consulted an expert.
He thinks that we must open a press conference as soon as possible.
Admit the mistake to the public and shoulder the responsibility.
Also, to quiet down the public sentiment,
to calm everything down,
I should take the blame and resign.
I will go and write my resignation report now.
Wait!
Fang Zhan, go and prepare a press conference now.
I will apologize to the public in person.
I will announce that Lubao has suspended Li Siyu from her duties.
- Can the public accept this?
- That's it. Go.
As a public enterprise,
for all the wicked public influence caused by this,
we sincerely apologize to everyone.
As the chariman of the company, I feel deeply guilty and blame myself.
Now all the related staff have been suspended from their duties.
They are under investigation now. I apologize again to the public,
the supervision department, the shareholders of Lubao,
and all the friends who care for us.
We sincerely welcome the public and the media
to continue to monitor Lubao.
Finished?
♫  This city's too magical  ♫
It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
♫  The wishes I have made  ♫
♫ that I don't fulfill ♫
♫  Nights are filled with loneliness  ♫
♫  Nights are filled ♫
Let's go.
♫  Lights are dimming   ♫
♫  yet I'm awake  ♫
♫  Love and bittersweet joys  ♫
♫  Regrets  ♫
♫  You were by my side  ♫
♫  The world turns quickly  ♫
♫  Yet footsteps slow down  ♫
GM Pan has said that he just wanted me to take a break.
When the crisis finishes, I will go back.
♫  Who's shouting?  ♫
Let's not talk about it. Take a break first.
No.
I have been fighting for so many years and I've given so much to the company.
I won't give up easily.
But even though you won't give up,
you can't go back.
Why?
Think about it.
Now Lubao has announced that you were suspended from your duties,
but when the crisis finishes and you go back to your position immediately, what will the public think about Lubao?
They will definitely think that Lubao is covering up for you and taking the punishment lightly.
The public can put up with committing mistakes, but
they can't tolerate cheating.
Maybe it will cause new public sentiment at that time.
The public will forget about it quickly.
They won't even care about who becomes Lubao's sales director again.
I'm not as optimistic as you.
This is the result you hoped for, right?
I knew it.
Why do you always think about me in this way?
Am I wrong?
Yes.
I do hope you can quit.
But this is the best solution to protect you and Lubao.
Also, you can take advantage of this time to get a good rest and nurse your health.
Is it a problem?
This is what I'm thinking. Is it wrong?
Siyu,
since it has happened,
let's face it actively.
Let's turn the bad thing into a good thing.
Here.
Sister Siyu, how is it going now?
He was sacked by his work.
What?
Zhizhi, sorry.
Can we remedy it?
Is there any other way to help him?
Don't worry. It was me that started it.
I will take care of it to the end.
Zhizhi, do you still plan to divorce him?
Yes.
Yuwei!
- Are you happy today?
- Happy!
Let's go home.
President Wang, it's not easy to meet you.
No, I had to deal with a family issue.
I thought I could finish it in 2-3 days, but I was delayed for a week in the end.
Okay. Let's get down to business.
About my offer last time,
what do you think about it?
I also made an offer last time. What do you think about it now?
Your offer wasn't sincere at all.
GM Pan, the new incident to Lubao's valuation—
That little incident has no influence on Lubao.
This is the latest completion of the sales order and the purchase order.
From the data, no matter it's dealers or users, they are both confident in Lubao.
According to our latest evaluation, the valuation of Lubao
is severely damaged in this incident.
Your arithmetic is outdated now.
We believe that within the next 3 months,
the influence will fade out.
We will rebrand Lubao.
This is our rebranding plan.
The research and development of Lubao3 cost too much.
You can't make a profit in a short term unavoidably.
But the growth of Lubao3 in the market is very quick.
Also, the operating methods are mature now.
In the long run, the rate of return on an investment is very high.
We also have an evaluation of the return on investment.
Enough.
Are you all thirsty?
President Wang,
800 million, 22%.
24%.
You are looting a burning house.
800 million, 22%.
GM Pan,
24%.
Farewell.
President Wang, I think we can accept it.
We must get 23%.
It's just one point. How about we get them back and continue talking about it?
Now, the Lubao bribery crisis is starting to quiet down already.
If we linger on, once they get a new investor,
It will be more difficult to negotiate.
[Pan Zhiyong]
[22%]
[23%]
23%.
Director Chen, your letter of appointment.
Letter of appointment?
Congratulations!
Is President Wang in the office?
Yes.
- Yiming.
- President Wang.
You've received the notice?
It it too quick for me, a new person in the company?
First of all, you deserve it.
You created value for the company, so the company should reward you.
Secondly,
I need you to forge new strategic assets for Tianye Group.
Thirdly, I believe you can create more value for the company.
President Chen, your reserved parking space is there.
There is also another one in the underground parking. There is your plate number on it.
Thank you.
Director Chen.
I'm the administrative manager of Donglai investment company.
Your private office is on the 22nd floor. This is your new assistant.
- Hi, Director Chen.
- Hi.
I will take your bag. This way.
This way, Director Chen.
Director Chen, we are here. This way.
Hello, Director Chen.
Director Chen, this is your office.
I will leave first. Call me anytime when you need me.
I'll put your bag on the desk.
Thank you.
Year ten.
[Send]
[Lubao New Energy Equity Financing Signing Ceremony]
"Chen Yiming.
Deputy Director of Tianye Group Donglai Investment Co. Ltd."
GM Wang, please have a look. I plan to build another industrial park.
I will put two production lines first.
After five years, if there are ten production lines,
then half of the country's new energy industry is definitely Lubao's.
- Five years?
- That's the ideal situation.
It might take ten years.
GM Pan,
do you not want to, within one year,
increase Lubao's valuation to 20 billion?
GM Wang, to be honest,
if it were not for the equity financing,
I wouldn't be interested in valuation at all.
To be honest, in my mind,
the core technology is the top priority.
As for the valuation, I don't like this virtual concept.
Truly.
Right, young man?
Excuse me.
I reserved a restaurant. Let's meet up tonight.
[Yutiancheng Tang]
(T/N: Pharmacy of Traditional Medicine)
Hello, Xiao Zhao?
Hello? There's a meeting at 3:30 p.m. Don't forget about it.
I'm Li Siyu.
Sorry, I forgot that you've been suspended from work.
[Yu Tiancheng Tang]
Hi, I'm Li Siyu.
You're Li Siyu? I finally found you!
You are rubbish! Corruption and bribery!
You are the society's—
It's you.
I couldn't get through on the phone.
I forgot to add money to the phone.
Let's talk inside.
Let's just talk here.
How has Yuwei been lately?
She's been good.
It's time for you to pay the child support for the next quarter.
Can you...
postpone it for two days?
I'm looking for a house and need to pay the deposit.
I don't have any money to spare.
Yuwei needs to go to preschool.
Her food, drinks, and toys all need to be paid for.
I know.
It's not that I don't want to give it. Please give me two more days.
This is your responsibility as a father.
In a few days, after I get a job, I'll send you the money.
You already dragged it out for a week.
I shouldn't have kept any faith in you.
Zhizhi. Zhizhi?
Congratulations to you for getting promoted to deputy director.
You knew it?
I booked seats there.
I can't drink alcohol. I drove here.
We can find a substitute driver later.
Here.
I didn't expect that Sister Ziru thought so highly of you.
I think you can put it another way.
This is also earned by my efforts.
Okay. I said you were the best.
Now in the whole Tianye Group,
there is no one saying that I used nepotism
to get the position.
Why didn't you tell me about this earlier?
You were afraid to irritate me?
Yes.
Let me answer the phone.
Hello.
Send it to my email first. I will have a look.
Right. That's it. Bye.
Siyu,
I really have many ideas right now,
but I don't know how to tell you about them.
I was the Caixin Company's
youngest department director.
But right now, I'm
Donglai Company's youngest deputy director.
In the future, I will be the youngest deputy director of Tianye Group for sure.
Ten years. I've been fighting in the workplace for ten years.
To be honest, now I have a lot of sentiment
and thoughts but I don't have time to dwell on them.
I... I made a...
brand strategy.
In the whole financial industry, no one has practiced this before.
Now, no matter whether it's Tianye Group or Sister Ziru, they told me to just do it freely—
Hello?
What?
Tomorrow.
Yes. Come to my office tomorrow.
10:00. Around 10:00.
No. I probably don't have that much time. 15 minutes.
I just have 15 minutes of free time in the middle. We can talk about details.
Okay.
All right. See you tomorrow in the office.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Siyu,
I didn't mean anything else just now.
I just wanted to tell you
that our future is getting better and better for sure.
I'm able to take care of you now.
I can make you feel secure.
In the past, we talked about raising children and paying mortgage.
You really don't need to worry about them. They are on me now.
Just focus on being beautiful.
If I'm not beautiful and young anymore, will that mean
you won't pay for the mortgage and the kids?
See?
I knew that you were going to say that, that's why
I have been very hesitant on how I was supposed to tell you.
Hello? Yes. It's me.
Reporter? Which reporter? Oh, yes.
Hello, hello. Yes.
Okay, then send me the outline for the interview.
Yes.
My Wechat number is my phone number.
Yes. Just add me.
Okay. Then, about the interview time,
we can talk about that later.
Okay. Yes.
Goodbye.
Reporters these days have so much access to information. They caught up so quickly to me.
To tell you the truth, I'm really not willing to do interviews.
But now the company needs to do promotions, so I have no choice.
You're so busy.
Siyu,
in the future, I will get busier and busier.
So...
Hello? Director Qian?
You know this already?
That's great. Yes.
This time, we can work together and make something big.
I think we should first confirm their values.
Yes, no problem. I think my original plan was good.
We can talk about system regulations—
What?
Okay, no problem. Then we can talk about more when we see each other.
Yes. Yes.
Bye-bye.
Hello, the user you are trying to contact
is currently unavailable.Sorry—
♫  like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
♫  We once longed to wander  ♫
♫  Getting through long nights ♫
♫  Never hesitating  ♫
♫  We want to escape, far away from home  ♫
♫  But is  ♫
♫   as lost as others  ♫
♫  We love with no room for anything else  ♫
Hello, the user you are trying to contact is currently unavailable.
Sorry, the number you dialed can not be connected.
♫  Thought that being loved by you  ♫
♫  Thought that we wouldn't age  ♫
♫  Wouldn't separate  ♫
Did I say something to upset you today?
♫   I lost you  ♫
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  As I was walking, I lost you  ♫
Xiaoling said that her calls couldn't get through. She's very worried about you.
A few days ago, someone leaked my number.
So many keyboard warriors are calling me and sending insults my way, so I shut my phone off completely.
Do you want to get the police involved?
There's no need. There have been less these past few days.
Didn't you notice that I turned my phone back on?
That's good.
Have you been doing well these past few days?
Then what about Liu Yang?
He's been slacking on Yuwei's child support for over a week.
I went to find him.
He said he didn't have the money.
He doesn't have a job right now,
and he has to rent a house.
He might actually not have it.
I'm not sure if he's lying or not,
but if, at the time, I had your confidence,
I could tell him that I didn't want any of the money he owed me,
but I couldn't say it.
Zhizhi, how much do you need? Is ¥5,000 enough?
Sister Siyu, I can't take your money.
I still have some savings.
Zhizhi, this problem is partly my fault.
- Please, it will make me feel less guilty.
- Sister Siyu,
the situation with Liu Yang has nothing to do with you. Okay.
What are you planning to do now?
When he's stable,
we will go do all the paperwork.
Weren't you planning on forgiving him?
How come you're suddenly so determined to divorce?
I went to find him that day, but I found out
that he and Wei Yayun were already living together.
Then, are they still together?
I don't know.
I don't want to know.
How are you doing?
I'm going to rest for a while.
Do you have any plans?
GM Pan said
when this storm clears,
he'll let me go back.
I heard a rumor.
About what?
Director Fang
is planning to bring Yuan Huizhong back.
Back to the Sales Department?
He wants her to be Sales Director.
Mom!
Yuwei! Come.
- Are you happy today?
- Yes!
Good. What did you learn today?
Mr. Liu, hello.
We have already looked at your resumé,
do you have any other requests to join?
My one request is to be able to join immediately.
Then you can report to work next Monday.
Thank you! Thank you!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Yiming, thank you so much. I got the job.
[Wife]
I got a job.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫