Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 28]
Director Li.
Here you are.
There are some problems here.
Here. Here. And here.
Adjust a bit. Quickly finish it.
When can you finish the interaction design?
There are some logical bugs in the process design. The front end cannot solve them.
Can't solve them? It's been three days.
If there is still no result today, nobody is allowed to leave the office.
I work overtime until late night every day!
My parents both think I joined a pyramid scheme organization.
If it keeps like this, how can I find a boyfriend?
The plan you made...
Xiao Jiang, is someone here for an interview?
He arrived. I saw him come inside.
Where is he?
You should be in the general manager's office. What are you doing here?
Wait. Let me finish this round.
Are you here to play games or get a job?
Work is playing a game. Playing a game is work.
Finish!
Your office's wifi is good. I think I can stay.
You can leave now.
What do you mean?
My company doesn't need people like you.
Why don't you need someone like me?
You can leave.
You didn't even check my resume and asked me to leave.
Come on. As a general manager, can you pay me the basic respect?
Respect?
Respect is given to people who deserve it.
Right. I'm one of them! Look. You will know it after you see my resume.
You were born in 1998? No wonder...
This is the second time you looked down upon me.
How did I look down on you?
I asked for people with more than 3 years' experience.
Please continue reading.
I wanted a UI designer.
Continue reading.
Designed webpages since freshman year.
Just for fun.
Ant. Workout. Mint. Did you participate in all these?
That was when I was young.
You finished all those independently?
Do I need people to help me?
I can offer you an internship position.
Elder sister. Bye.
- What are you doing?
- Don't be nervous.
I have an idea.
Come over here.
Who are you?
- Really. I will forget it immediately!
- What?
It's related to our designing. Come on.
What are you doing?
Give it to me first.
Marker. Give me the marker.
Young hero. Respect! Amazing!
Remember, the communicative property
should be superior to aesthetics.
- Guan Xiaotang.
- Yes!
Are you offering me a position like a UI engineer?
Go back and prepare to come to work tomorrow. Coming to work late and leaving early are not allowed.
Don't play mobile games during work hours.
I can't agree to that.
You can't? Then leave.
Do you know why I came to do this interview?
Why?
On the market, among these types of companies and positions,
you offered the lowest salary.
What do you mean?
Low salary means work expectations are low as well.
I just want to find a job where I won't have to work too much and have too much pressure, and I want to find a boss who doesn't care what I do.
Do you think that there are any jobs on the market that meet your needs?
But if you want to find an employee of my skill by offering such a low salary, that's also impossible.
How about this? As long as I finish my work,
I can be late, leave work early, and play games during office hours.
As long as you finish your work, you can come late and leave early,
but you can't play games during work!
Deal!
Come to work at 9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
You just said that I was allowed to be late. I plan to come at 9:30.
Bye, Older Sister.
"Before my bed a pool of light, can it be hoarfrost on the ground?"  (T/N: A Chinese ancient poem)
"Looking up, I find the moon bright; Bowing, in homesickness I'm drowned."
Yuwei is amazing!
What's wrong?
I'm taking something from my bag.
- I will help you.
- Okay!
The teacher gave us this.
She told us to give it to our parents when we go back home.
Mom, did we run out of money again?
Who said this? We have money.
Put it back, Baby.
Let's go!
Go.
[Application for job transferring]
Too busy!
Great.
Excellent! Excellent!
LPL No. 2 seeded team. I won! I won! I won! Yes!
Does that have anything to do with you at all?
Yes! They won't give you any bonus.
This is a great day! It's upsetting to work overtime.
I will treat everyone. Barbecue plus karaoke. Who's in?
- Me! I'm in!
- Me too!
Sit. Sit. We can't go.
Don't. Don't! Let's go together!
I'm definitely not going.
Together! The more the merrier.
Director Li will kill people.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
Go back immediately!
Director Li went out on a date.
Why should we work overtime here?
Impossible! I heard her boyfriend dumped her,
- so she works like crazy to subdue her heartbreak.
- Right.
At the same time, she vents her hatred towards men like you guys.
Cut the nonsense. Let's go!
- Is this okay?
- Go! Go now!
Let's go together!
Together!
Go! Go! Go!
This will be fun.
What are all of you doing here?
We are done for the day.
- Who let you go?
- The labor law.
Go back!
This is the suggestion from the clients about a business cooperation plan.
Hand in the modified one to me tomorrow before work.
Older Sister, we need rest.
Please call me Director Li in the office.
Or Miss Li.
Older Sister... Director Li.
Did you finish your work?
According to Beijing time, I finished my work at 17:10.
You can leave now.
How about them?
They have their own work.
They have worked for 10 hours. They should be done for the day.
Guan Xiaotang, you can make no attempt to make progress. But don't influence others.
They are not others. They don't want to work overtime.
You won't understand when someone works for their dream, there is no concept like starting and finishing work.
I don't think they are working for their dream. They are working for your dream.
You are too young to understand this.
But what I can understand is Older Sister Li Siyu, the general manager,
you can't ask all the people to work overtime because of your own misfortune.
What are you talking about?
We are not your ex-boyfriend.
Don't vent your hatred about him to us, okay?
Guan Xiaotang!
Oh gosh.
Xiao Yang...
[General Manager Room]
Let's finish here today. Go back and rest.
Director Li, this plan...
Do it tomorrow.
Then?
What then?
You aren't going to announce that you're firing me?
According to this pattern,
design the user interview outline and sample again.
Hand it to me by 11:00 tomorrow morning.
Thank you for fighting for us to get one evening's rest.
Tell me. Which department do you want to transfer to?
As long as it has a higher salary, any department is okay.
I need to remind you. The department with higher salary will have higher pressure.
It won't be worse than the pressure of life.
All right. I will ask for you.
I think if I continue to work at Caijin,
I definitely won't have a future.
You had an epiphany?
Xiaoling reminded me.
She said when I retire from my job, I should be
a charming billionaire with grey hair.
What are you thinking about?
Thinking over what you just said.
No need. I have thoroughly self-reflected.
During the half of the year since I met her, we eat and drink,
chatting and have fun. But why haven't we made any progress with our relationship?
She went to have blind dates and look for a boyfriend in front of me. Why?
Because she doesn't like you.
No. Because my means of pursuing her are wrong!
It's a strategic objective.
I used tactic missiles. It for sure won't work.
I should change to a strategic missile!
What are you talking about? Can you say something that I can understand?
Gu Xiaoling is like a panini with meat and egg.
But what I can give her is a deep-fried dough stick.
So, in other words, I can't give her my heart and hope she gives me hers.
I have to get rich overnight.
I have a primary school classmate. He doesn't even know how to calculate.
Since he started to work in social media,
he upgrades his car every two months.
You want to quit your job to work on social media?
Aren't you familiar with this? I want to listen to your suggestion.
Haowen, how about this?
Don't quit now.
Give me some time. I will talk about this with you later.
Good bro!
How is Siyu?
Siyu?
She is busy with her startup.
You are still thinking of her?
How about I ask Xiaoling to ask for you?
I just asked casually.
You have such a good location but just earn ¥7000-8000 for one month? This is a big loss!
If you join "Laidianle," I can promise
that you will earn a profit of ¥150,000 in the first year. ¥300,0000 in the second year.
I will provide the brand, training, technique, and promotion.
We split the rent and the profit 50-50. I will subsidize you the installation cost.
I will subsidize you ¥200 for every new member.
I will be there to sign the contract with you.
Come on! Why do you draw back all the time?
They still have health. That's right. Right. Right.
Shoot him first! Look at me! At me!
Look at me! I'm coming!
Go! Go! Go!
Why don't you look at my position?
Guan Xiaotang! Guan Xiaotang!
I'm playing a game. Your phone!
From Director Li!
Don't report me. I didn't mean to make you lose.
Hello?
Why didn't you answer my phone?
I was pooping in the toilet.
Listen, I just talked with some franchisers. I've sent you all the materials to your email.
By tomorrow morning at 6:00, you add them to our website with
their logos in our test environment. The clients want to have a look.
Pay attention. Don't delay and make mistakes.
I get it.
I asked around. The general manager's office doesn't want people.
You can't do the jobs of the Research and Development Department and the Testing Department.
The Planning Department, GM Pan already thinks there are too many people and he wants to downsize it.
So it's impossible for them to recruit more people now.
As for the warehouse, their salary is even lower than the Admin Department. You don't want to go there for sure.
How about other departments? The Financial Department for example?
The Financial Department requires that you have a CPA.
How about the Development Department?
Your experience and qualification are not enough.
I think it's very realistic for you to stay in the Admin Department.
This is the bill from my daughter's kindergarten. I need to pay ¥9,000 for one season.
This week is the deadline of the payment.
This is my husband's receipts for hospitalization.
Apart from the insurance, we need to pay over ¥10,000 by ourselves.
We have spent all the money that we saved.
I really can't survive with the current salary.
Okay. I will ask for you one more time.
Thank you, Director Hu.
- Director Li.
- Thank you.
Director Li.
Xiao Yang!
Have we passed the pressure test?
Director Li, we've just passed the first pressure test. The second one starts from tomorrow.
Okay.
Lao Liu, the promotion plan?
I've sent you the digital version to your email.
Okay.
- Tingting.
- Yes, Director Li.
Did you modify the content layout?
- I've changed it. You can have a look by opening the testing website.
- Okay.
- Zhou Tianyu.
- Yes.
We just got several franchisees. Did Guan Xiaotang put them in yet?
I didn't see it.
Where is Guan Xiaotang?
Guan Xiaotang?
Where is the thing I asked from you?
I... I wanted to stay up to do that. I didn't even go back home.
Then?
Then I decided to play two rounds to freshen up my mind.
Then I played and I felt sleepy so I thought after I napped
I would get it done.
Then?
Then I was woken up by you.
Don't worry. I will give it to you by 12:00.
How can you hit people?
I've done all I promised. And you?
I... I just messed up.
Why wouldn't you do your work? Why would you play video games during work?
I messed up. Hey! Hey!
You can't keep your promise.
No!
Get out! Immediately!
Director Fang,
I will hand in a proposal to the board.
What about?
I want to adjust the company's business model and industrial structure from the capital's perspective.
You want to discuss about how to rebrand Lubao?
Yes. To ensure this proposal can be passed,
I would like to ask you to talk with some board members in advance.
President Wang,
actually, a few days ago, GM Pan had a chat with me.
What did you talk about?
He asked me to re-consider Lubao3's production line.
He hasn't given up?
President Wang, I was thinking if Lubao3 completely launches into the market,
it will also be good for Lubao's valuation. Right?
After we install these 2 lines, we would spend almost all of the ¥8,000,000,000.
You can make a profit of tens of millions of yuan, right?
After 3-5 years, can Lubao's valuation reach ¥5,000,000,000?
Is it fun?
But when we started Lubao,
we wanted to build China's best new energy enterprise.
If Lubao's valuation reaches ¥20,000,000,000, can you say it's not China's best energy company?
Pan Zhiyong says that he needs 5 to 10 years to realize this dream.
In my way, just one year.
But the company's valuation can't be broken away from production value and profit, right?
Then, how can you explain Tesla?
They still have a deficit but their valuation has reached over US$30,000,000,000 and it's still increasing.
One company's valuation isn't so closely related to production value and profit.
It is the operational efficiency of assets and the company's room for growth that can decide the company's valuation.
We should make use of all the capital to forge this concept
instead of the production line.
This is very different from the market which I am used to.
It is.
The time has changed.
Pan Zhiyong's way is outdated.
Lubao needs to change tracks.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
Guan Xiaotang,
weren't you fired already? Why do you still come back?
I left a cup here.
Isn't it just a cup?
It's still worthy of some money.
The ghost of poverty.
Are you still working overtime?
Isn't it the awful mess that you left me with?
Only you?
Director Li is also here.
I will go to look for my cup.
Director Liu, I have some trouble for the moment.
Can I give it to you tomorrow?
It's all my fault. I didn't finish what I promised you.
I apologize to you.
I'm really sorry.
I promise that I will definitely give it to you by 8:00 tomorrow morning.
Okay. Thank you.
Go back home to sleep. I will do it.
Didn't you already—?
Turn off your phone and take a good rest.
- Go.
- Getting my bag.
Why are you here?
Didn't I ask you to get out?
Giving a present to you before I leave.
Where is Zhou Tianyu?
I asked him to go back.
- Guan Xiaotang, you want to ruin me on purpose?
- Older Sister,
are your hormones out of whack?
What?
You are hot-tempered.
You told the client tomorrow 8:00 a.m. Okay.
I promise to show you the result by 6:00 a.m.
- Are you calling Zhou Tianyu?
- The number you have dialed, the phone has been turned off.
I asked him to turn off his phone.
Don't worry, Older Sister. I can do my work fast and well.
I don't trust you.
But you don't have anyone now. So you have to trust me.
Stop talking nonsense. Go to work!
You are like my mom watching me to do my homework when I was young.
If I was your mom,
I would have already beaten you up and left you with your skin cut open and flesh torn.
Guan Xiaotang!
Here.
Where have you been?
Buying breakfast for you.
Do you still have the mood for breakfast?
Older Sister, can you change your morning temperament?
What time is it already?
I've finished it!
- What?
- I've sent it to your email one hour ago. Don't need to thank me.
You just need to give me overtime pay.
You are reliable for one time finally.
Do I still need to get out?
Get out!
I still have to?
Go home and sleep.
Thank you, my young lord.
Dad!
Have you packed up?
Yes.
Let's go.
- Where to go?
- Leave the hospital.
Go back home!
- Are you happy to see Dad come back home?
- Happy!
Let's go.
Sit tight.
Where do we go now?
I already helped you move out of your place.
It's good.
Thank you.
You can get in the car.
Get in, Baby.
[Hand in hand]
[Shared Ride]
Mom, I want to watch TV.
Just one episode.
Liu Yang,
you sleep in this room. Yuwei and I will sleep in that room.
Here.
Zhizhi, I already come back home. Should we still be like this?
I only asked for half-day leave. I have to go back to work.
You stay with Yuwei. I will cook dinner when I come back.
Sit on me.
Three years ago was the golden age to start a new social media business.
But from last year, this great mass fervor is dropping.
Until today, social media has already become a red sea.
In other words, I am late.
To be exact, the legendary way of making money by only operating a public account,
won't show up very easily.
My way to get rich suddenly has been blocked?
That doesn't mean you don't have any opportunity.
I'm cooperating with a social media company now.
The yearly income is still over ¥1,000,000.
But they are operated by a team.
Their contents are well designed and personalized.
Also, they have a good strategy to monetize internet traffic.
All these conditions, I have none.
Then don't give up so quickly.
Of course, I have to.
Gu Xiaoling has started marriage-seeking online.
Actually for the moment within the social media industry,
there is no one working on the branding of financing institutions.
When your followers increase,
you can turn the traffic into advertisement.
And you can also turn them into clients of financial institutions.
There is a way.
If you can really setup a team,
I can help you with the contents.
You're so generous.
I know
that I still have fate to get rich overnight.
What about the thing I asked you to do?
What?
Didn't you say that you would ask Gu Xiaoling?
Siyu must live better than you now.
Look at you. So decadent.
How is her company going?
I don't know about that.
Guan Xiaotang, you want me to punch you again?
I want to see the complete one by 11:00 tomorrow.
I don't even go to bed. You want to sleep?
That's it!
Gu Xiaoling, can you mute your phone? It's very noisy.
Coming! Coming!
Let me see.
What are you up to? So busy.
A website recommends me a lot of candidates.
A lot? How many?
Several dozens.
Dozens? Can you manage to meet them all?
After the first selection, there are less than 20 left.
I will meet them in a few days.
First selection?
You make it sound like a job fair.
That's much more important.
If you hire the wrong person, you can fire him.
But if you find the wrong husband, that's a lifetime problem.
Then you will still have a first test, second test, and final competition?
You are right.
Let  me show you.
Look at this one for me.
How is he?
- Have a look!
- I'm busy!
Quick! Help me look! Look!
How is he?
What?
Take a look.
Phoenix group. Dark horse group.
Born with a silver spoon in mouth group, resurgence group.
Bingo.
Why are you grouping them?
I rated them.
According to their height, weight, look, and family background.
The most important is their financial condition.
The data could be wrong as well.
So I will select the first two of each group.
Then I will meet with them in person.
May I ask you, Miss Gu, how would you rate yourself?
Based on my perfect look, 100 points.
You are not original.
Mine has just a little adjustment.
By the way, my skin has completely recovered lately. You see I look younger, right?
Can I add 20 more points?
Look.
Here is a photo from 10 years ago?
Help me to look. Am I younger than before?
Photo.
I didn't know I had a photo of Chen Yiming and you.
When did you secretly take this? I didn't know.
When you two were just together.
My mom got to know this. So she wanted to know how he looked like quickly.
Then I took a photo secretly.
Delete it.
You said it. This is out of print.
What "out of print"?
Don't think that I don't know that you blocked all the contact information of Chen Yiming.
You deleted all the photos with him as well.
If I delete it, then you have nothing left.
Delete it.
Okay.
Don't. Send it to me.
I knew it.
This beauty needs some sleep.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫ En... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫ Ye... ♫
♫ Oh... ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫