Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 43]
Xiaoling, I made plans with my boyfriend so I won't be going in the same direction as you. I'll see you tomorrow.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye—
You don't have dyslexia.
You have symptoms of procrastination.
And procrastination often arises from the conflict in one's heart.
You are not avoiding me either.
You are hinting to me
that you want to break up with me.
I—
Let me finish first. When I realized this,
my muscle began to tic.
My breath and pulse
are all a mess.
The dopamine level in my brain was far lower than the normal level.
This directly caused me to become sad.
At the same time, it caused me to not be able to focus my attention.
My cognitive function
and memory all started to degenerate.
I didn't do anything.
Xiaoling...
You didn't do anything indeed,
it is I who fell in love with you.
All of my physical reactions
perfectly match the
pathological conditions the humans exhibit when they are heartbroken.
Logically,
Gu Xiaoling, I love you.
No one has ever
confessed their love to me like this.
I reviewed our dating data again.
I found that...
the day when you told me that your sister urgently needed ¥5,000,000
and I immediately rejected was a critical point.
From then on, you started to avoid me.
I carefully recalled everything that I said that day.
From my point of view, everything I said was correct.
However, a relationship therapist told me that
there is no right or wrong in relationships.
Xiaoling,
here is ¥5,000,000. Please accept it.
No.
I feel like my actions right now are very stupid.
It doesn't correspond to the principles I use to act by.
It also violates several articles of our prenuptial agreement.
Nevertheless,
I'm willing to make an exception for you.
You don't need to do this.
Xiaoling,
I discovered a scary truth.
I cannot accept a future without you.
Thus, I must do this.
Please accept it.
♪ How much courage do I still need ♪
♪ to give the future certainty? ♪
♪ Looking back at the road I've taken, it really wasn't ready ♪
♪ But our youth, when we could cry loudly, has long been gone ♪
♪ Swimming in the middle of the crowd ♪
Suddenly calling us to come here,
what's going on?
♪ With you by my side, even if there are days where I'm afraid ♪
Recently,
Dubu has caused me to be exhausted.
(T/N: literal translation is my head and forehead are burned)
I didn't have time to care about you.
How is the new company you're at?
♪ Do we have what supposed appearance of love? ♪
Wei Yayun is my subordinate now.
Such a small world!
♪ This life is too slow and too short ♪
If it was before, I would definitely have slapped her.
I don't know why, but now
I don't feel furious anymore.
How about her?
She apologized and repented to me.
You didn't forgive her just like that, did you?
I'm not that saintly.
I don't know why, but
when I see her try so hard to get on my good side
and her being so afraid, I pity her.
I don't know why either.
Because you are stronger than before.
♪ Looking back at the road I've taken, it really wasn't ready ♪
♪ Walking in the middle of the crowd, silence came so naturally ♪
- ♪ But our youth, when we could cry loudly,
has long been gone ♪
- Gu Xiaoling!
Gu Xiaoling!
If you continue to not talk to us, we're leaving!
♪ Living life too orderly ♪
♪ But at least my heart— ♪
I signed the prenuptial agreement.
What did you say?
I said I signed the prenuptial agreement!
You decided?
When I was eight years old, I already decided.
You don't love him at all!
You don't even like him!
But when I'm with him,
I can forever forget about that day.
Which day?
The second year after my dad died,
my mom brought me along to my uncle's to borrow money.
Then my mom had me wait for her at the door.
It was especially cold then.
It was snowing.
All the other kids are having snowball fights but I was there waiting and waiting.
Then they threw snowballs at me.
My clothes got all wet.
Then I blamed my mom.
Why didn't she let me wait inside my uncle's home?
It wasn't until later that I found out that
my mom didn't want me to see her cringingly beg people.
Then, was she able to borrow the money?
My mom wanted to borrow ¥2,000.
Then my uncle used ¥50 to dismiss her.
When my mom came out from his place,
her eyes were red.
I will never forget that moment.
Why haven't you told me this before?
From that moment, I knew that
there is nothing reliable in the world.
Brother Haowen has always liked you.
He Mu loves me a lot, too.
Then, who do you love? Who do you like?
Me?
I like money.
I want to live a stable
life where I don't need to worry about anything nor the future.
I like the feeling of buying whatever I want without checking the price tag.
Then, have you gotten what you wanted?
Yes!
So we should be happy!
Happy!
Xiaoling,
Lei Haowen has changed a lot lately.
I think you can try to see him from a different perspective.
- Maybe you will have another possible future—
- Stop trying to persuade me!
I don't want you to regret anything in the future.
No matter who I choose, there's a possibility that I'll regret it.
But at least I have money. I have money!
Here!
What's this?
He Mu gave me ¥5,000,000.
¥5,000,000!
Xiao Ling, thank you. I can't accept this money.
Take it.
Don't think I don't know.
Lately, you've been so worried, you can't even sleep.
We've already got enough money.
For now, the Dubu project doesn't need money.
Besides, even if I'm desperate,
I can't use your money.
Because I hope...
you can return this ¥5,000,000, without a penny missing,
to He Mu.
Li Siyu!
Why can't you just give me your blessing and congratulate me?!
Why do you keep thinking of breaking He Mu and I up?
Xiao Ling!
We hope that you are happy.
We hope that you are blissful.
I definitely will be!
I definitely will be happy and blissful!
Come on!
Happy.
Blissful!
Blissful.
Hey, Lei Haowen,
where have you been?
I called you but you didn't answer. I messaged you and you didn't reply.
Director Gong and I waited here for you for a long time.
I'm about to go bankrupt.
What's going on?
Dozens of Dubu's experiments have
successively failed.
If we can't find an investor to put in money right now,
my house,
and Siyu's next ten years
will all be gone.
What should I do?
Haowen's here?
Director Gong?
Hey, Director Gong.
Why didn't I think of you?
Right now, I—
No, no need. Just tell me.
Right now, there's a great project.
It's almost complete but we just need some money. Would you be interested?
Sit down and tell me.
Dubu, Professor Gao Zhengdao's membrane-less battery.
If this project is successful,
then the world of new energy will be ours.
I'm at the club.
Okay. How about in 15 minutes?
Come pick me up.
President Wang.
They are willing to transfer another 20% of the shares for ¥10,000,000.
The price is secondary. I must hold a majority of the shares for this project.
But you went to negotiate so many times already and they didn't agree to it.
They didn't say agree before because they haven't exhausted their resources (capital).
Now, should be a perfect time.
Ziru.
You can go back first.
How did you get here so quickly?
I happened to be nearby.
How long have you waited?
Not very long. Just a few minutes.
Let's go?
I think I saw the inventor of my Yiwen company just now.
You didn't recognize the wrong person, did you?
I don't think so.
That's also possible.
A lot of people in the finance industry come to that club for dinner.
You were in such a hurry to see me, did you miss me?
You are half-correct.
What about the other half?
As for the other half, I have good news.
Professor Gao's lab is starting second-round financing.
I have already given up on investing in that project of his.
Haven't you been quite interested in that project this whole time?
I have invested in two other labs
with lower risks and better prospects than his.
Got it.
Director Gong, that's everything in our lab.
Although our lab is small,
we have everything we need.
Professor Gao strictly checks every detail.
This is all of his life's hark work.
What do you think, Director Gong?
It's okay.
Director Gong, do you have any more questions?
My question is will this experiment of yours
really be successful?
I can only say that since the establishment of this lab,
today is the day we are closest to succeeding.
Excuse me, Director Gong. I'm going to answer a call.
Okay.
Let's sit down and talk, Director Gong.
Hello, Director Yang.
Are you also interested in Dubu's shares?
Hey, Haowen.
Come here.
What is it?
To be honest,
¥10,000,000 for 20% of the shares,
I absolutely cannot accept that.
Then, how much can you accept?
¥5,000,000.
¥5,000,000? That a bit too ruthless, don't you think?
60%.
You want to hold the majority of shares with just this little bit of money?
Yes. I must.
Don't say "must" just yet.
Putting money aside, Professor would never agree to you holding the majority of the shares.
If I cannot hold a majority of the shares, then this is pointless.
Director Gong.
Say, when you invested in our company,
you didn't want to hold a majority of the shares.
Why are you so interested in that for this project?
I can see the future of your company.
However, for this one, I'm really gambling here.
I can't decide on this matter myself.
I will discuss it with the partners.
Okay. You guys discuss it first.
Let me know after you all discuss it. I'm leaving now.
- I will walk you out.
- No need.
Take care.
Siyu, Director Gong is leaving!
How did it go?
The good news is that he made a counter-offer.
The bad news is that there is no way we can accept the counter-offer he made.
I don't agree.
I don't want anything else.
Just one thing. Whether Dubu succeeds or fails,
we must hold the majority of the shares.
But with the present circumstances, we have no choice.
I think Professor Gao's concerns are valid.
Dubu is about to fail before it even truly begins.
(T/N: literal translation is a fetus dying in the womb)
Is there a need to decide whose surname the child will take and what the child's name is?
Stop arguing.
Haowen, call Director Gong back.
¥5,000,000 for 49%.
If he is willing to do that, then we can immediately sign the contract.
If he is not willing to do that, then we can think of other ways.
What ways?
Worse comes to worst, I'll sell another 10 years of my labor.
49... 1.02...
6.63...
42.33...
That's not impossible.
President Wang, the reason why you want to invest and hold the majority of the shares
is the fear that if Dubu succeeds, it would threaten Lubao.
However, after going there today, I can conclude
that they won't succeed.
Why?
First, the lab is the most dilapidated lab that I've ever seen.
Second, although they seem very confident,
they are actually uncertain as well.
Then your suggestion is?
My suggestion is that there is no need for us to invest.
Let them, who are at a dead-end, give up on the project themselves.
They won't give up.
However, if they don't have money, then they must accept their fate.
Based on Gao Zhengdao's stubborn
plus Li Siyu's craziness,
they can do anything.
Sister Yuan, say, how should I take care of this?
First, why does your subordinate want to leave?
Secondly, is she worth keeping?
Figure out these two questions and you'll know what to do.
This issue is a bit complicated.
This person... in the past...
- actually was—
- Hey!
Zhizhi!
Director Wu.
Let me introduce you. This is my previous leader.
No need to introduce. I have met Director Yuan many times now.
- Long time no see.
- Yes.
Did you know? The headhunting company recommended Director Yuan to us in the beginning.
Afterward, Director Yuan strongly recommended you.
She said you were very capable, young, and have a good personality.
So I had HR to send you a message.
How is it, Director Wu? The people I recommend are not bad, right?
That's right. After she came,
sales improved a lot.
So I have to thank you!
If you want to thank me, then do so by placing an order.
No problem.
You two talk. I still have some business to tend to.
Go ahead. I will go looking for you for that order later.
- No problem!
- Bye-bye.
- Goodbye.
I have been perplexed this whole time.
How can a rookie like me, who's been in the industry for less than a year,
get this position?
Turns out that you've been helping me this whole time.
It's nothing.
Sister Yuan,
why did you recommend me?
I felt like I played a part in you leaving Lubao.
So recommending you for the job could be considered my compensation to you.
But I've never been a manager before.
Weren't you afraid that I wouldn't be competent enough for this position?
Zhizhi, you qualify for sure!
First, you are kind and gentle.
Secondly, you were able to endure my torment in the beginning. It clearly shows that you are very strong.
Third, after my tormenting,
you didn't hold a grudge against me and you still became my friend. That clearly shows that you are open-minded.
And the three points mentioned are the key features of a team leader.
Am I that great?
You, of course, have your shortcomings.
You are easily swayed by your emotions.
You are not rational enough when considering an issue.
However, you are good at learning. So by putting you in a manager position,
you can definitely overcome your own personal prejudices
in order to consider matters from a work perspective or in relation to the bigger picture.
By the way,
who's the subordinate wanting to resign that you were just talking about?
Who she is is no longer important.
I know what I should do now.
Sister Yuan, a toast to you with water in place of wine.
Thank you.
All right. It's settled then.
We're doing as you said, ¥5,000,000 for 49%.
- Let's continue.
Don't continue yet, Professor Gao.
This is our last chance. We can only succeed. We can't fail.
Did I need you to remind me?
Haowen, thank you.
If you really want to thank me, then tell Xiaoling about
my great achievement. Tell her that I,
Lei Haowen, have a reliable side.
I will definitely relay that to her.
Tell her three times, okay?
Check this. See if there are any more mistakes.
Xiao He, fill this out and sign it.
Wei Yayun. Come in for a moment.
Okay.
Sit.
I heard you want to resign.
No, I'm not.
Is it because of me?
Yes.
No! It's because I—
If it is because of me, then it's totally unnecessary.
Since I am sitting in the manager seat,
then I must consider the company's interest above all.
If you can create profit for the company,
I can absolutely put my personal grudges aside.
But...
I did that kind of thing to you,
can you really forgive me?
Indeed,
we had an unpleasant experience in the past.
But now,
I have gotten back everything I've lost,
and more.
So even though I can't forgive you for now,
I don't hate you.
Manager Zhang,
sorry.
From now on, there's no need to say that word.
When you say sorry to me,
I don't feel touched or relieved.
Because who you are sorry to
is the Zhang Zhizhi in the past.
The present me
doesn't need your apology.
I've familiarized myself with your situation.
You just joined the company for less than three months,
but you've been working hard the whole time.
As a new staff member, being able to make a deal with a big client
is considered very outstanding.
I should say that this company
and this job suits you very well.
You should cherish it well.
I also don't want to leave.
It's just...
If you must leave,
then at least get this commission first.
After all, you've worked hard for three months.
It's very difficult... working hard out in the world alone.
If you have a little more money on you, you can solve a lot of problems.
Sister Zhizhi,
I never thought that you... you would actually...
treat me like this. I—
I was wrong.
I really was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Hello.
Ms. Gu, I'm slightly raising the rent for next year.
How much are you raising it by?
I want to raise it to ¥4,200 a month.
How is that slightly? That is a huge increase!
It's just ¥200 more.
You-how is that ¥200? You're increasing it by ¥700!
If I were to increase it by ¥700,
then I would be getting ¥4,700 a month from you.
Hold up, did you get it wrong?
I have always been paying ¥3,500 a month.
Are you the one who got it wrong? I've always been charging you ¥4,000 a month.
Sis, take care. If you need anything, please come again.
Please take your banknotes.
Is it starting again?
Is there hope this time?
I don't know.
How much is left of the ¥5,000,000 that Director Gong gave?
A little over ¥30,000.
What? A little over ¥30,000?
Then if we fail this time, we're all done for?
Theoretically, that is correct.
Then, why didn't you say so earlier?
Lower your voice.
Last time, didn't you say we still had over ¥2,000,000 left?
After last time, Professor Gao changed the plan.
Everything was re-adjusted.
Is there any hope this time?
Yes.
Yes. You say that every single time.
Then, what do you hope I say?
Is there really hope this time?
What did Professor Gao say about it?
Never mind. Professor Gao's words aren't accurate nowadays. What did Liu Yang say about it?
Can you calm down a bit?
In total, ¥10,000,000 was spent on this. How am I supposed to calm down?
Even at a casino, you wouldn't spend money like that, right?
Shut up!
It's over, it's over. I'm going to lose everything.
Lei Haowen, can you please have some pride?
No wonder Gu Xiaoling didn't choose you.
That's right. Xiaoling.
Xiaoling safeguard me. Xiaoling safeguard me.
Xiao-Xiao-Xiaoling.
How has she been recently?
The same as always.
I haven't cared about her for days.
[Congratulate me. Give me your blessing.]
Did something happen to Xiaoling?
What is all this that she's posting on her WeChat Moment?
Say something. Look.
Xiaoling...
Xiaoling and He Mu signed the prenuptial agreement.
Who is it?
Xiaoling. Open the door.
Xiaoling!
Open the door! I have something to say to you!
What are you doing?!
Open the door!
What are you doing?
Wait! What are you doing?!
- You can't marry him.
- How is it any of your business?
What's so great about that He Mu?
He Mu can give me what I want!
For money, you'd sell yourself?
You don't understand anything!
Since you're selling yourself, why don't you sell yourself to me instead of him!
Fine. He Mu is offering ¥5,000,000. How much are you offering?
¥5,000,000. I'll give it to you!
Then transfer it to me right now.
I don't have money right now, but—
If you don't have money, then why are you whining?
Not having money is only temporary!
You temporarily don't have money.
You are temporarily a poor, penniless man.
Your "temporary" is actually "forever"!
Once Dubu succeeds, I'm worth ¥300,000,000!
When the time comes, you'll regret it! Just you wait!
Scram! Scram!
Gu Xiaoling, what's so great about you?!
Let me tell you, you'll regret it for sure!
You're just a bit pretty, that's all. Right?
You just have a nice body and a good temperament, that's all. Right?
I will definitely buy you!
Lei Haowen, let it go.
Maybe you and Xiaoling really aren't fated to be together.
No matter how I think about it, I can't figure out how someone just sells herself for ¥5,000,000.
You can't talk about Xiaoling like that.
He Mu has his own good attributes.
What's good about him? Doesn't he just have some stinky money?
We must succeed this time.
We will definitely succeed this time!
Let's rest for a bit. Just stop looking and go rest for a bit.
What happened?
I don't know either. Professor Gao suddenly turned off the machine.
W-W-What was the result?
He didn't say. We haven't gotten to the testing stage yet.
W-What do you think?
Are you becoming a coward now?
I, Gao Zhengdao, have never been a coward in my life.
Then why did you suddenly stop at the last moment?
In my heart, you have always repeatedly fought on despite the repeated failures.
You are the Professor Gao who can't be defeated and who is not afraid to lose.
But this time, I'm a bit afraid.
Afraid of what?
I'm afraid that if it fails, then our lab will have no choice but to close down.
What's so scary about closing down?
I'm not afraid. I've already accepted that
I'm a failure in this lifetime.
However...
However, all of these workers,
Liu Yang, you, and Haowen...
they all had so much hope.
Everyone's put so much money and time into this. Some are even going bankrupt.
If we fail this time,
then I don't know how I will be able to face them.
Before the age of 32, I had never failed either.
However, starting Laidianle caused me to lose everything.
At that time, with all my hopes crushed, I escape to my hometown.
But now that I think about it,
the thing that caused me to grow up in the quickest way and gain the most
was actually that experience of failure.
Aren't you afraid of failure?
I am, but I'm more afraid of giving up.
As long as you don't give up,
failure is just the stepping stone to success. However, if you give up,
then failure is really just failure.
If we fail this time, then we have no choice but to give up.
No.
It's just a pause. I will do everything in my power to get the lab up and running again.
There's a possibility that you'll never see the day this succeeds in this lifetime.
If we give up halfway,
then, in this life, I will definitely never be able to see the day when this succeeds.
Shall we continue?
We will continue.
Professor Gao!
When I left my hometown, my dad told me
that happiness is most important.
The joy you get from working hard is the most important.
Your dad has more wisdom than you do.
Ha. Ha.
Xiao Wu.
Professor Gao! Professor Gao!
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙) & Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh... ♫
♫  En...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious  ♫
♫  After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  Are you afraid of all the punishment given by fate?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah...  ♫
♫  Oh...  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warmth that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫