Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
[To Dear Myself]
[Episode 12]
Siyu.
It's a total of 5.1 million yuan.
I got it all back.
Lin Ling, last week, I was in a bad mood.
I shouldn't have vented my anger at you. I'm sorry.
No, Sister Siyu, I was too stupid.
Trust me, I've learned my lesson.
In the future, they will no longer be able to find my mistakes.
That's good.
5 million yuan a week?
That's good. You've almost caught up to my record.
Your record was...?
Six million yuan a week.
How did you do it?
I was also scolded by Sister Yuan and I got annoyed.
I took purchases like crazy.
Then I made my record.
You can go back to work.
You still have time to meet with Director Guo.
This is your best choice.
You should take a look.
If you don't like it, then you can go.
- Hello?
- Hi, Yiming.
I'm about to leave the house.
You don't have to go anymore.
They just informed me
that the position of copywrite planning
has already been filled.
Got it.
[Siyu]
Hello?
Zhu Xiaobai, were you looking for me?
Yiming, my father retired.
He gave me the position!
As the Wanguan Group's Chairman and General Manager,
I am officially inviting you
to come and help me.
I'll leave you the position of Vice President.
How does it sound? Come back to your hometown!
Yiming?
Yiming! Are you listening?
Hello?
Yiming? Yiming?
♫  Keep thinking that the days are long  ♫
♫  Feelings flow like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  like a small steady stream  ♫
♫  Keep thinking that we still have time  ♫
♫  Don’t fear idling away ♫
♫  The days have yet to come  ♫
Did you just say you were going back to your hometown?
Yes.
Weren't you going to go to Fenglin to do copywrite planning?
They didn't like me.
Then... Then you can go to Director Guo's company.
I have Director Guo's number.
I can't go there.
I don't understand. Why do you have so many negative feelings toward him?
Did he do anything to provoke you?
Tell me!
I just can't stand that my girlfriend
can get me a job after laughing and drinking with him.
You're so unreasonable.
♫  The memories won't let me escape  ♫
♫  Yet as I was walking, I lost you  ♫
Come, come!  Let's have another drink.
Come, come!
Eat some more.
Mr. Liu.
Sit, sit.
Brother Li always mentions you. He really admires your work capacity.
I have also admired you for a while now,
and I feel so lucky seeing you in person.
I will toast this wine to you. You can do whatever.
Here.
You flatter me.
Good drinking capacity!
Thank you.
Huizhong, Liu Yang and I have been good friends for many years.
He is really nice. You can directly ask him to do you favor.
-Then I'll say it
- Okay, go ahead.
Mr. Liu, it's like this.
Our Lubao Company wants to take part in the bid for the whole city's street lamp renovation.
And we'd like you to look after us.
Director Yuan, we haven't officially announced. How did you get to know of this?
I even know you are the team leader of the bidding.
Liu Yang, Huizhong is my sister.
She is nice and accountable for her job.
If you promise to cooperate with her, she will help you to complete your job very well.
Director Li. Director Yuan. You have the wrong person.
Although I'm the team leader, we have experts to evaluate.
I really cannot help you with this. I'm very sorry.
You told me this.
How much bidding do I attend every year?
I know how to do this.
Director Li, everything I said is true.
Brother Li!
You shouldn't bother Mr. Liu. Mr. Liu,
you do you job open and fairly.
We will cooperate with you well.
Yes, yes, yes. Public, fair, and just.
You said it well.
We've had enough alcohol, how about we go and sing?
- KTV is good!
- You guys go, I've got to get home.
Liu Yang! We haven't seen each other for over half a year.
We can't go home until we get drunk tonight!
I'm really okay today.
Come! Come! I can take my own bag.
Go! Go! Go!
[Hotel Indigo]
Mr. Liu, take my car! You guys take others!
Come! Come!
- Get in! My bag!
- I will get it.
It's okay. You get in first.
Hey, the alcohol is here.
♪ Can you not be so cruel?  ♪
Drink! Drink!
Let's drink!
Mr. Liu, to commemorate the first day of our meeting,
- I propose a toast to you.
- I can't drink anymore.
Come on, Mr. Liu.
Liu Yang!
It's okay. The beer is really light.
Together! Cheers!
Right! Right! Bottoms up!
Bottoms up!
We propose a toast to Liu Yang together!
Take your glass!
Mr. Liu!
Together! Come on!
Bottoms up.
Right! Right!
I have to go.
Director Liu, you really don't have to walk me out. It's okay.
Teacher Liu, you didn't enjoy yourself to the full!
I did. I did. I drank too much! Really.
Mr. Liu, your alcohol tolerance is really
so good. Oh! Oh!
Sorry!
Sorry, sorry.
- Sister Yun.
- Brother Yang, may  I ask you a question?
Page 13, the 2nd line. Where does this number come from?
- You're still at the office?
- Yes.
- Have you eaten?
- No, I haven't.
It's already this late, how have you not eaten yet?
I haven't had the chance.
Then what were you doing?
We have to turn in those reports early tomorrow morning,
so I'm working on them all over again.
The report is already fine, you don't need to keep working on it.
No, Brother Yang, this is a project you're in charge of.
I must finish all the work completely.
I want you to go home and rest immediately.
It's nothing, Brother Yang, you don't have to manage me.
I'll turn in the most perfect report tomorrow morning.
Brother Yang, why are you here?
I bought you some food.
There is porridge. Eat it when it's hot.
What's wrong?
Brother Yang, can you not treat me so nicely?
Is this already nice?
Sister Yun...
What are you doing?
There's never been anyone who's treated me this well.
Brother Yang...
I like you.
What's their name?
They're named...
Oh, you're back.
Did you eat?
Didn't you say you had a business dinner so you would come back late?
Back this early?
You don't feel well because of drinking too much?
Who did you go and eat with tonight?
A bunch of friends before.
Were they men or women?
There were both men and women. Why?
Why is the perfume on your jacket so strong?
I never use perfume.
Guess who organized the dinner for tonight?
Who?
Your company's Yuan Huizhong.
- What was she doing with you?
- Isn't it the bidding thing.
She asked some of her friends to ask me out.
Don't promise her.
She is the competitor of Siyu.
Even if there was no Li Siyu, I still wouldn't dare provoke them.
- What happened?
- I have firsthand knowledge of Director Yuan's personality.
- She tried to seduce me!
- Shameless.
They even made me drink. Old Li and they did too.
I assume they got some benefit. They kicked up a fuss.
I couldn't take it anymore, so I left.
I'm going to go shower.
That happened last night?
Liu Yang was terrified.
Yesterday after he got back, he was still fluttering with fear.
She also fixed her eye on this bidding.
I know now...
some rumor about her,
it was all true.
He's not usually like that.
He's surely in a bad mood because of me.
Don't worry. Liu Yang won't respond to her.
Zhizhi, you need to watch Liu Yang more closely.
I don't want the two of us to end up with
my proposal failing and your husband leaving you.
Liu Yang and I, though we have had our share of trouble,
our love and affection for each other are steady. There won't be any problems.
Brother Yang might be able to do the right thing himself,
but he can't restrain others.
Good morning, Mr. Liu.
Sister Yun,
I think you've probably misunderstood me.
All of my care for you
was because I am your leader,
teacher, and senior brother.
I had no other intentions.
I-I understand.
I just wanted to say
I... I'm not just some casual girl.
I... I've really...
I've really fallen in love with you.
I'm already married.
I have a wife and child.
I must be responsible for them.
Brother Yang, don't worry.
I don't have a covetous heart.
I won't disturb your family.
I won't disturb you either.
I just want to look at you from a distance.
I want to help you every day.
That's all.
You...
This is not good.
I swear.
What happened last night will never happen again.
I will control my emotions.
You're still young.
There are still so many possibilities ahead of you.
My future is filled with secretly pining for you.
You can't be like this!
I'll listen to you about anything else,
as long as you tell me to, no matter how hard it is, I will do it.
But to forbid me from loving you...
You can't do that.
I can't do it either.
Were you scolded by the boss?
Mr. Liu, I put the report you wanted on your desk.
Thank you.
Mr. Liu, I want to bring Wei Yayun to take a look at the Dongfeng factory at 3:00 today.
Wei Yayun did overtime work this week already.
I want to let her go home early and rest. Please pick someone else.
Okay.
Brother Dai! Brother Dai, please come with me this afternoon.
My file name is called Guangcai Engineering Construction Project.
The client representative is Liu Yang.
Sister Yuan's file is called Street Light Bidding Project.
The client representative is still to be determined.
When did she record it?
The 16th of this month.
I recorded mine on the 13th.
- Yes, that's what it says.
- Wonderful.
Yesterday, I might have been too anxious. It's possible I scared him off.
Then, what should we do moving forward?
We need to fix our rhythm.
Later, I'll send him an apology text.
In a few days, I'll arrange for Director Li to have a cup of coffee with him.
Do you need me to prepare anything?
You should go to the administration department and prepare some materials.
This time, all we will be discussing is official work business. Nothing else.
Go now.
- Hello, Xiaotang?
- What's up?
I need a copy of the company's product brochure and video.
We still have the corporate culture brochure. I'll get you one.
Doesn't Sister Yuan never give clients these kinds of things?
Don't even get me started. Last night, we met someone with a very strange way of thinking.
Sister Yuan needed to use peculiar methods.
Peculiar?
Guess what happened!
Sister Yuan didn't do anything about it?
Didn't I say? He ran away!
Zhizhi?
Don't move.
Are you unable to understand human speech or something?
Liu Jie, don't you have business to attend to?
Why would you have the spare time to stick your nose into little things like this?
Sister Yuan, I just can't help but be angry with her.
Liu Jie, just assume that her mother didn't teach her basic etiquette.
You're the one without etiquette!
What did you just say?
Apologize to me for what you just said.
You wish.
- Are you going to apologize or not?
- Let go of me!
You know what you did!
You're just an old shrew.
- You're a shameless creature!
- What are you guys doing?
What is going on?
- Siyu?
- You dared to push me?
You dared to hit Sister Yuan?
How could you hit Sister Yuan?
Stop fighting!
Those who don't want to work can all go home!
Are you finished working?
Hurry up and do it!
The approved processing results are as follows.
For Sales Team One Leader,
Yuan Huizhong, and Sales Team Two Leader,
Li Siyu, the punishment fee is ¥5,000.
The entire company condemns
Zhang Zhizhi, an employee of the Administration Department
and Sales Department employee Liu Jie.
The penalty fee is ¥1,000.
The entire company condemns them.
Understand?
Within three days, hand your respective payments to the Finance Department.
I never would have thought
that there would be a day where we got into a fistfight.
Sister Yuan, I'm sorry.
I've really failed.
It's just that when I saw the two of you gang up on Zhizhi,
I got too impulsive.
But no matter the circumstance, I still shouldn't have hit you.
I'm really sorry. I'll pay your penalty debt.
I don't need that money
and I don't accept your apology.
Then, what should I do?
If you still see me as a superior
and admit our friendship in the past,
then you will fulfill your promise,
and leave the sales director competition.
Sister Yuan, I can't.
Why not?
Because I can't let my group members down.
Because I want to be the Sales Director.
And also because...
you honestly don't really take me as your disciple.
You also don't really care about our friendship.
How could I not admit you as my disciple?
If it weren't for me, you would have been fired long ago!
For you, I carried so many burdens cleaned up so many messes, how could I possibly not value our friendship?
Li Siyu,
you're just a graceful, vengeful viper.
Sister Yuan, if I angered you today,
it was because you forced it out of me.
Li Siyu, I'm warning you.
I am determined to be the sales director.
The first thing I will do as the sales director
is fire you.
Sister Yuan,
I am also determined to be the sales director.
The first thing I will do is thank you.
Are you really going to rely on yourself and your group of incompetent idiots?
Yes.
I will rely on my skill, my ability to lead my group,
and my group of "incompetent idiots" to counterattack you.
Also, I'm about to represent Lubao in the bidding.
Guangcai Company's Renovation Project's
- total bid is 28 million.
- That's my project!
I'm sorry. My record was before yours.
GM Pan, I didn't control the sales department well enough.
I will review it with you.
The Supervision Department has already taken care of everything.
They will learn their lesson.
After giving me the sales department, something like this happened.
This responsibility, I really...
Departments with many people naturally have more problems.
It's hard to prevent such things.
In the beginning, these two groups competing was a good thing,
but this competition needs to be done in a composed manner.
During this time, these two groups,
in order to fight for clients, it has caused a whole lot of trouble.
I think we need to summarize
and rectify this situation.
Continue.
I was thinking
we should have the Consumer Department cooperate with us
and clean out our clients.
We should give the two groups their own territories,
and let them do their business within those territories.
This way, we can potentially develop more clients,
and we can prevent
this kind of vicious competition from happening again.
How should we divide them up?
Li Siyu knows a lot about the electric car market.
We should give that area to her.
It's true that Yuan Huizhong also developed many consumers there,
but generally speaking, I would say that Li Siyu is better suited there.
Would Yuan Huizhong accept that?
I can do her business.
Other than that, the toy department, home appliances, and medical equipment departments...
I also recommend them for Li Siyu.
She's very familiar with these industries.
With the same clients, others can get about 20 million
but she can make 30 million or even 40 million.
If we do it this way, it's not fair to other people in the sales department, is it?
But this way, it would limit
the exertion of the other salespersons' abilities.
For example, Yuan Huizhong.
She's very familiar with government and public relations.
We can give projects that have to do with the law to her.
Of course, she will also wonder
why should Li Siyu take charge of such a big market of scooters?
But for the company, you must sacrifice things.
I think a good competitive mechanism,
needs to mobilize all people's initiatives and potentials.
Not to sacrifice someone or help someone to achieve something.
Right?
But now the sales department is a bit messy.
The mess is the surface.
As long as the business keeps growing,
it means this mechanism works.
We'll do as follows with the previous rule.
The person who put the client on the company's records first will take care of the client.
Okay.
Sister Siyu.
I've paid your fine already.
Don't go and pay by yourself.
- I will transfer the money to you by Wechat.
- No need.
You keep your salary for Yuwei's after-school class!
How can I thank you?
Cook two nice dishes and feed me.
Okay. Tonight, you invite brother Yiming together.
You come to my place to have dinner.
- I have to work this evening.
- Meeting a client again?
Sister Siyu,
this fight you helped me with,
will it affect your competition with Yuan Huizhong?
- No.
- Really?
Don't worry about it. We can still secure our victory.
Right, has Brother Yiming found a job yet?
He wants to go back to his hometown and develop his career there.
- Then what about you?
- I definitely have to stay.
Then you'd be in different cities! That can't work!
Sister Siyu, you have to convince Brother Yiming.
I don't want to look at it anymore.
Please don't say that!
Senior Brother,
- I'm so tired.
- Who isn't?
I'm also very tired.
Do you know what I want to do most right now?
I want to regulate my body
and then peacefully eat three meals a day.
If I have time, I want to accompany my son
and help him with homework and memorizing vocabulary.
I also want to find a boyfriend and live a peaceful life.
These can all happen,
You can't relax at this critical moment.
Li Siyu's group,
they're acting like they're all crazy.
I really don't want to fight them anymore.
Why not? You must!
Huizhong, this matter,
I only told you my real intention.
Your competition with Li Siyu is related to everyone's interests.
It's also related to my destiny in Lubao.
In addition, it relates to Lubao's destiny.
We've talked about this for many times.
I don't care if I will get kicked out or not.
But I'm worried about Lubao.
Yes, Pan Zhiyong is the founder of Lubao.
But for more than a decade,
all the money, sweat, blood and youth we have give to Lubao,
is it less than Pan Zhiyong?
I can't see him ruin Lubao standing aside.
Also, Pan Zhiyong...
has never cared about the senior executives' and the staff's interest.
It is me that strived for all these equity distributions.
If I get kicked out, then he himself can decide everything.
Our interest in the future can never be guaranteed.
Even if you get the shares,
they will be diluted very quickly.
He will do this.
So, you must stick to the sales department.
The company is doing equity financing.
As long as you can persist until the new shareholders join,
we have the chance.
We have to change to turn around the situation.
Timing & Subtitles by My Dear Myself Team @Viki.com
How can I stick to my job?
According to the rule, the government project belongs Li Siyu.
Your suggestion to reform was denied by Pan Zhiyong.
If Li Siyu gets the 28 million,
I lost for sure.
[Dear Myself (亲爱的自己) by Zhu Yi Long (朱一龙), Keyso (寿君超)]
♫  How are you?  ♫
♫  Listen to me about the latest news  ♫
♫  Some sweet and some hopeless  ♫
♫  There are also some that were never said  ♫
♫  It's been so long, I've already learned to let go  ♫
♫  Let go of obsessions, of the present, and of greed  ♫
♫  Yet I've never thought of letting you go  ♫
♫  Yeah…  ♫
♫  Oh…  ♫
♫  En…  ♫
♫  Letting go…  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  In this lonely world, be cautious ♫
After we're hurt, we learn to cherish  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Use all your strength  ♫
♫  Missing the simple you from the past  ♫
♫  Turn difficulties into courage  ♫
♫  Don't back down from the crowd  ♫
♫  Growth is inevitably accompanied by setbacks  ♫
♫  The best way to overcome difficulties is to smile  ♫
♫  All the punishment given by fate, are you afraid?  ♫
♫  Let everything go, all those concerns, real or fake  ♫
♫  Cannot erase the scar, but it's just a scar  ♫
♫  We are so small yet so determined  ♫
♫  Occasionally fussy and occasionally firm  ♫
♫  If growth leaves a trace, then the trace is left be tears  ♫
♫  Your back that I've always been chasing  ♫
♫  Finally turned around to hug me tightly  ♫
♫  It's still that familiar you  ♫
♫  Yeah..  ♫
♫  Oh..  ♫
♫  Dear Myself  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  I'll give you the warm that the wind took  ♫
♫  Hugging you, hugging me  ♫
♫   Dear Myself  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫
♫  We've never been so clear-headed  ♫
♫  Looking for the past me who  ♫
♫  Ran forward without evading anything  ♫
♫  Listen to the voice inside  ♫
♫  The sky has finally cleared  ♫