[To Dear Myself]
[Ep10]
As I know, your dunners came to my house
They messed it up
I will compensate you
I just need the rent
I don't want to invite any troubles
Did you hear me?
Don't worry, I have solved it
It won't happen again
I do not care
You need to move out by the end of this month
But...
Today it's golf range
Next time I will take you to the real golf court
Over there
Over there?
Correct
Eighteen holes
Oh
Dear
I want to play more
It's your first time
Your skill will go astray if you go on playing
Ten dozens are enough
Fine
I will take you here next week if you like
Anyway, I am VIP here
I can come whenever I want
Great
A cup of coffee
Excuse me
Two cups of coffee
I have group purchase coupons
You are here to play golf?
What's the problem?
You got the outfit from the wholesale store in Qipu road, right?
Don't look down on me
It's No. 2 retail brand in the world
You rented the pole?
I forgot to bring my pole
Borrowed the car today?
I borrow it from my nanny, any problem?
Don't tell her I use the group buying coupon
A rich son needs a group buying coupon?
Thrift is my family's tradition
Two cups of coffee
Let's go to see a movie later
It's boring
Let's go shopping
Go shopping
Sucks
I like a bag
It's not expensive, only over 20,000
You can buy it for me as the anniversary
that we know each other for a week, ok?
It's the latest
It's hard to buy
Excuse me, Mr. Lei, Miss Lai
Can you give me two minutes?
Great
How do you feel today?
Very well
What about our service?
Not bad
Do you have any interest in buying a VIP card?
You are not a VIP here?
I am
Maybe I haven't come here for a long time, so it's expired
My company didn't renew it?
Mr. Lei
Can you tell me your card No.?
I can help you renew you now
Card No., let me think about it
I forgot it
I need to ask my secretary
You should let me keep the card
So you won't forget it
Miss Lai, actually you apply for a card separately
We have Liren card for female VIPs
20% discount after 20% discount after 20% discount
And you can enjoy the privilege of a VIP card of 400,000 yuan
What kind of privilege?
You can enjoy all the golf courses
facilities and hotels
You can participate in membership activities for free
Great...
I'll fill out the form for you right away
Ok
We should get one
I like the environment here
And it's close to the downtown
Then we can come here often
How much is it?
It has discount
Well, we won't buy the bag today
Is that ok?
Mr. Lei, so you will pay with credit card or Wechat or Alipay?
Vivian, leave Mr. Lei alone
He is the senior VIP
He has all our cards
Sorry, Mr. Lei
Good day
It's ok, thank you
Mr. Lei, sorry
She is new here
She doesn't know you
All my fault, I usually keep low profile
I need the Spouse card
Don't give me the Kid card
Let me ask the secretary
She is so careless
What's wrong with her?
Thank you
We are even now
Do you like that alpaca?
I like koala
You like koala
Ok, here you are
Give me the alpaca
Alpaca...
Alpaca is here
Look at me...
Alpaca
That is camel
I am very happy that you are here
Why do you buy so many things?
You are so polite
Aunt, usually I don't see you
I should do this
It costs you a lot of money, right?
Aunt can make a lot of money
Really?
Aunt bought me a lot of toys, clothes and food
Mom
My cousin can make a lot of money
She can make more money than three of us
Really?
It's nothing
Aunt
Yuwei is so smart
She is promising
What are you talking about?
Aunt, no
Now girls are more useful than boys
Really?
Look, German Chancellor Merkel
Chairman of the International Monetary Fund
And Dong Mingzhu, Tu Youyou
They are all women
I know nothing of them
Let's talk about my company
Most of the managers are women
We lead the men
Really
Except the shareholders, most of managers are female
Including sister Siyu
Still, the man leads the women
We have female shareholders
Most of my shareholders and general manager are female
So these women can't manager family well
Auntie, what are you talking about?
It's true
I'm telling the truth
What's the point of this?
Yeah
Most capable women are single now
I mean in modern society,
We have no distinction between men and women
Whoever has the power has the final say
The losers will be eliminated
Yes...
So, aunt, don't force them to have a son
Cultivate Yuwei well
She is no worse than a boy
I am no worse than a boy
Ok...
Mom, time to eat now
Ok, eat
Come. Let's eat
Come, put on your shoes
Hello
Are you off work?
Can I invite you to dinner?
No need
I don't mean anything else
I just want to show my gratitude
Ok, name the place
I will send you the place later
You freaked me out
Come, Xiaoling
You just invite me to eat this?
I saved you over 40,000 yuan
Don't underestimate the shop
They only sell fifty pots a day
The boss is my friend
Otherwise you need to wait for 3 days
Sit...
My clothes so expensive
You just let me sit here?
Gosh
Not a big deal, look
Aston Martin
Ferrari
And McLaren
Don't worry, you are not the only one
Sit down
Be careful
You should eat
Come, eat
Come...
You are back
Brother Yang
Siyu, you are here
I will reheat the dishes for you
No...
Leave it to me
Sit down
I am here to see aunt
Brother Yang, you just get off work?
Why do you work harder than me?
After he becomes the leader of tender team
he works overtime every day
He is back a little early today
Brother Yang got promoted
Congratulations
Just a team leader
But the project is more than 20 million yuan
What project?
Lighting engineering renovation in the suburbs
So can My Lubao have a chance?
Yes
This time, we need to change the old batteries
to environmentally friendly batteries
Then I'll bid on behalf of Lubao
No problem
I will tell you when we have the tender plan
Thank you, brother Yang
During the bidding process, we need your help
To be honest
I am the team leader
But I don't have a say who will have the bid in the end
You need to speak with your products
Don't worry
Lubao has the reputation in the industry
The quality is great
I won't give you any special help because we are friends
I know
Don't worry, I won't make troubles for you
We do things according to the rules
You just need to tell me your team's decision in advance
So I could be better prepared
As long as I don't violate the principles
or don't be caught for playing favouritism
and committing irregularities, I will help you
Thank you, brother Yang
Or if you come for the tender,
don't tell your company your relationship with us
I won't
My colleagues won't know our relationship
And no one knows except me and Zhizhi
So delicious
You are such a foodie
I, Lei Haowen, am the gourmand of Huangpu
I will take you to eat more delicious food in the future
Just eat
Xiaoling, thank you today
You didn't expose me and you even cooperated with me
Great
Thank you too
Help me leave a bastard
Now we eat together
So we are good, right?
Let me have a reintroduction
My name is Lei Haowen
Nice to meet you
Eat
Eat, come
Where is your girlfriend?
Why you didn't ask her here?
She is my ex-girlfriend
When?
Three hours later
She is pretty
But she is a little vulgar
Why say so?
We just meet for the second time
She told me to buy her a card and a bag
Don't you think she is vulgar?
Spend some money for her, what's wrong?
If you don't spend money for her,
why should she be your girlfriend?
Only incapable men will think women are vulgar
Yes... You are right
It's not vulgar
What is it called?
I overestimate myself
If you are my girlfriend
I will buy everything for you even if I am bankrupt
Stop it, I am not your girlfriend
I say, if
No if
No if...
Xiaoling
You should smile often
Don't pull the long face all day
Because you look at least ten years younger when you smile
You will look like at most forty
Lei Haowen
Are you on purpose?
No, I don't eat coriander
I eat green onion
No
You smash for real?
You are laughing, so great
Come
I eat too much
I went to the gym last month
Now it's all ruined
It's ok
I don't mind it even if you put on five or six catties
You take advantage of me again
I will teach you a lesson
I am sorry...
That's it
I will walk back with you
As exercise
I won't drive you back as apology
Your car?
You won't be ashamed when you drive me home?
I am a confident man
Come, goddess
Let me help you with your bag
What are you doing?
Will people think we are a happy young couple?
Lei Haowen
You are so brazen-faced
It shows I am a man of taste
I have told you
We can't be together
But I want to try
You really spend money to no avail
What if it's to some avail?
You are so brazen-faced
I will do everything I can for you
Lei Haowen
If you really want to be my boyfriend,
let's take a stroll around IFC
If you want to be my ordinary friend
we can take a stroll along the Huangpu River
IFC
Forget it
IFC, right?
You'd better invite me to the little restaurant with your little money
I want to die
Can you let me die?
I can't
Consider me, ok?
Eyes on road
10,000
Stop counting
Legs so short
You have never seen long ones
Ok, I am home
It's ok
Let me walk you to your door
No need
Ok
Thanks
If you really want to thank me, stop blacklisting me
Let me help you
What happened?
Do you have friends who rent a house?
Yeah, you ask the wrong person
One of my friends have so many houses to rent
Bragging again
No, I am not
Say it, what requirements?
It's not too far from my company
It needs to be convenient for transportation
I should be near the subway
The environment should be quiet in a bustling area
It's comfortable to live
And don't be too expensive
Ok?
Ok
That's all?
Count on me
Thank you
It's ok
Don't see me an outsider
Ok, I won't see you an outsider
From today on, you are my good buddy
You are my BFF
Bye
Go to bed early
Hello
Let's break up
Why?
I walked alongside Huangpu River just now
Don't understand?
If you don't understand, it means we are not good for each other
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Eleven
Zhizhi
Take the medicine
Mom, sister Siyu have told you a lot today
What did she say?
You don't remember?
Why should I listen to her?
You say, she is quite capable, right?
How old is she?
Yellow face and deficiency of qi and blood
Yeah, she works very hard
She is capable and can make a lot of money
What's the use?
She is 32, but still single
She doesn't have a family
She is going to get married
After getting married, she needs to have a baby
Till then she will be 34 or 35 at least
Let me tell you
Women should have a baby before 30
Otherwise it's not good for mom and baby
Today Siyu's persuasion is futile
Zhizhi
The women's capability is fake
Men's capability is true
Zhizhi, hurry
Stop it
Drink the medicine
Give me a good grandson
Drink it...
Drink
Mom, let me tell you the truth
It's not true that we don't want a son
We just can't afford another kid
What does it mean?
To be honest
Our salary is so hard to support Yuwei
We really can't afford a second child
Liu Yang has been promoted
Now he is the director or the team leader?
Mom, let me tell you this
Liu Yang's salary is 15,000
Mine is 6,000 at most
21,000 in total
House loan, 6000 one month
3000 for meals each month
Maintaining a car, 1,500
Yuwei's early education class plus kindergarten
It's 8000
Utility fee, 250
Phone fee and internet fee 150
My bus fare is 100
In total, it's 19,000
So expensive?
Liu Yang, a big man
He needs to buy some clothes
Yuwei needs toys from time to time
We need to go shopping during the weekends
All need money
We really can't afford another one
I see
How could this be?
Wake up...
I want to discuss something with you
Mom, ok
I thought about it all night last night
I had a good idea
I will take Yuwei back to hometown
Why do you take her back for nothing?
Yuwei needs to spend at least 8000 yuan each month
You will save 8000 yuan after I take her back, right?
It's enough to support a son
Mom, what do you mean?
Zhizhi told me
Yuwei spends over half of your salary at least a month
You have no money
So you can't have a second child
So this is the only thing I can do for you
What nonsense are you talking to mom?
No
Zhizhi
Zhizhi... Don't worry
Just leave Yuwei to me
I will be good to her
I will take her to early education class or interest class
The education in hometown is no better that in Shanghai
But it's cheap
120 yuan each month
Mom
You can go
But Yuwei must stay
She must receive education in Shanghai
When will you have a second child?
I can tell you
If you don't have a second child, I won't leave
I will live here forever
Your mom is determined this time
What should we do?
Don't ask me
You called her to come here
Figure a way out yourself
Brother
You are so early
According to your instructions
I told them you told me to draft up a tender contract
Then I asked them some questions
This is their reply
Xiao Xu is great
Very professional
Yang Feng is a little inexperienced
Zhang Xinyi is not bad too
Xiao Zhao
According to what he said, it's doomed
Really?
Here
It's nothing on the surface
It's fatal if something goes wrong
So he is the mole
We will know the truth after I compare the data
Put it here first
Hello, Yiming
Where are you now?
I am busy today
I can't go
What's more important than playing basketball?
It's more important than basketball
That's all
Brother, do you need to rent a house?
Exactly
I rent a house for my future girlfriend
Brother, come inside
Come in
Do you have...
Hello, Liu Yang
Yiming, sorry
I am working now
When will you come?
You just play with Haowen first
I will go after work
Ok
My two brothers stood me up
What a coincidence
My client stood me up
I will go to see you
Ok
You want to watch a movie or play video games
Or something else?
We will discuss about it later
Ok, see you in the old place
Sister Siyu
What?
This morning Liu Yang's mom told us
she won't go if we don't have a second child
What should I do?
I think aunt is too idle
You think find her a husband
Then she will have no time for you
I am serious
I am serious too
Give me another idea
President Pan
Hello, president Pan
I'm sorry
Mr. Lei
What a traffic jam
It's ok
A bit old
This is the style here
Your house is so old
Subway is around here, will we be often stuck in traffic jam?
No
Here is the bathroom
And kitchen
It's hard to find a one-room house nearby
The decoration is also very stylish
Ok
Mr. Lei, how's it?
It's ok
My future girlfriend may like the style
So you will sign the contract?
Wait
How much
4,000 a month
One month deposit and 2 months up front
4,000 a month?
You think I am an idiot?
I just live next to you
I know the price better than you
Brother, since you live nearby
you should know better
This is the price here
3,000 a month
3,000
3,000, you will have this kind of decoration?
You will have this furniture and appliances?
Enough, what decoration, furniture and appliances
What do you have here?
I still have to buy more
Let's make a compromise
3,500
Brother, the price can't be less
Let me tell you, you can't do business like this
I rent so sincerely
We both should make some compromise
3,999
What the hell
Brother, you want to a cheap one
I can show you a cheap one
Ok...
Let me tell you
My girlfriend is so beautiful
Here is only 300 meters away from my home
Otherwise I won't buy it
Fine
Brother
We should sign the contract
Wait
I can give you 3,999 yuan
But I have one condition
Ok
My girlfriend will sign the contract
She will bargain with you
You should give her the price she wants
I will make up for the rest
A deal
Check the contract
Just fabricate a agenesia certification online
But...
Where do I get one?
Just search one online
Yes
Thank you, Xiaoling
You're welcome
Ok
Bye
Doudou should quit
It's ok...
Thank you
Are you Yuwei's mother?
Yes, you are...
I'm Doudou's mother
Hello
I'm here to apologize to you
I and my husband are so busy recently
We have no time to take care of Doudou
As I know, Doudou bullies others in kindergarten
I am so sorry
It's ok...
Doudou has a little ADHD
But just a little
He doesn't need to take medicine
His ADHD will be eradicated
as long as we pay attention to code of conduct
So don't worry
Doudou won't hurt your kid
Great
I plan to quit my job
I will take care of Doudou in person
So rest assured
Doudou, he will change
I mean it
Well, as I know, many parents don't like Doudou
They even write a letter to dismiss Doudou
It's...
Actually...
Yuwei's mom
Can you give Doudou another chance?
Forgive Doudou
Doudou loves this kindergarten
He also likes playing with others
We promise he will change
I think it's normal that young boys are naughty
Thank you so much, Yuwei's mother
I...
Don't worry
If they mention this again, I will help you explain
Thank you
Well, I won't interrupt you now
I need to apologize to other parents now
Ok, don't worry
Excuse me
You are Xiaoyu's mother, right?
Exactly
I am Doudou's mother
I am here to apologize to you
My son recently...
Yiming, sorry
President Pan wants to see sister Ziru today
I am the introducer
I need to go with him
What will you do?
Can I ask?
President Wang
Which university do you graduate from?
Harvard
My major is finance
Think about when I started my business...
Everyone knows
The battery industry is currently facing a cold winter
President Wang, you want to join in now
You are so remarkably brave
Actually, I have no courage at all
I'm very timid
But I knew a sentence when I was young
If winter comes, can spring be far behind?
But...
Spring will come
But not everyone can live to that time
So who can survive this winter?
Those who have grain stock at home
What about those who have a shotgun?
You mean Lubao III ready to be on the market?
Correct
A shotgun can only guarantee food and clothing
Those who have grain stock and shotguns
will become the king of this industry
I agree
Come
So how much grain stock do you have?
It depends on the size of your warehouse
Great
Well, Mr. Pan
As I know, you have some flaws in series A financing
So you are bound hands and feet in Lubao
You know quite a lot
I think you need an ally
I don't need an ally
But a comrade in arms
Mr. Pan
This is the purpose I am here today
I have the strength and sincerity as well
Ok
For your sincerity, I will tell you a secret
You are not the only one who believes
spring will come sooner or later
or believes that the winner is king
Who else?
As I know, at least two more companies
I have competitors
I hope it's you in the end
It must be me in the end
Come
I'm almost done here
I will go to see you later