[To Dear Myself]
[Ep3]
It's midnight
What are you doing here?
Soon
What the hell
You still want to associate with them?
I have told you, just never mind them
I thought about it
We can't be impulsive
Why?
Look
Miaomiao's family
Needless to talk about it
Linda is only four years old
She can speak three languages
Xingxing's parents are postdoctoral returnees
And that William
As I know, his grandpa is from a famous family in Shanghai bund
Does it have anything to do with us?
Of course it has
Why do we spend so much money for Yuwei
to go to a good kindergarten?
All because we want her to grow up in the best environment
So we can't break away from them
Zhizhi
It's so obvious that we are not in their social circle
Don't you feel tired of kissing their ass?
I do this for Yuwei, I don't mind it
Whatever
No
You need to help me
As I know, Miaomiao's grandma also
graduated from Chiao Tung University
Tomorrow you will go to pick up Yuwei with me
I will give the cookies to Miaomiao's mom
You should get attached with Miaomiao's mom
Then let bygones be bygones
I won't go
You must go
We didn't tell them in advance that we wouldn't participate in the activity
It's our fault
We need to apologize to them
We should have chosen the ordinary kindergarten
We won't have these troubles
Liu Yang
Will ordinary kindergartens have enough hardware facilities
Will they have one-to-one tutoring?
Do they often organize the off-campus tours?
Are the teachers all senior preschool teachers?
Do they teach Go?
The tuition is just there
Before, we couldn't afford the tuition
Fortunately, we have the new policy
So she can be admitted so easily
You can go without me
For Yuwei
Are you sleeping?
Not yet
I am studying the knowledge of auto repair
Did you contact the auto spare parts agent I recommended?
Yes
I also contacted other stores
Ok, go to bed early
You too, good night
President Pan
I have thought about it
I can't be the team leader
I won't compete for the director
That's a rare opportunity
I am still young
I will have many opportunities in the future
It's not easy for sister Yuan
And with her ability and contribution
she is eligible for director
Did Yuan Huizhong say anything sensational to you?
No
It's my own decision
Li Siyu
You are good sisters
Ok, you are here to take a stand, I can understand
I get it, you can go back
I'm not here to take a stand
That's what I am thinking about
So what I told you was just a nonsense?
President Pan
I know
Competition is normal in business
I really can't do it
You can't do it
It doesn't mean that others can't do it
Understand?
You don't need to sacrifice yourself to help others
It doesn't make sense here
President Pan, I still insist
I get it
You can go now
Hello
Can you help me make an appointment again?
I am free recently
Ok, thank you very much
Ok
Please come in
How's it?
I have said I won't be the team leader
I won't compete for the director
What did Pan say?
He drove me out
So it makes no difference
Siyu
The company's appointment will ask for employees' opinion
He can't change anthing as long as you insist
I'll see him later
Ok
Come in
Sister Yuan
What happened?
Say it
We just got the latest notice
It's about...
What notice?
The board's decision is as follows
All staff in the sales department will be sorted into two teams
Yuan Huizhong will be team A's leader
Li Siyu will be team B's leader
It's a two-way selection between team leader and members
Appointed team leaders will be voluntary
Sister Yuan, I go back to work now
Where's president Pan?
He is out for a meeting
When will he come back?
No idea
You can call him if necessary
I really do not know why it becomes like this
You told president Pan that you didn't want to be the team leader?
You are doubting me?
I don't want to
But the fact is here
The fact is, I said, I don't want to be the team leader
If you don't believe it
we confront him after he comes back
Siyu
We have known each other for seven years
I see you as an apprentice and subordinate
I even see you as BFF and sister
I treat you with sincerity
You also treat me without reservations
Indeed
I shouldn't have doubted you
I really didn't...
Don't say anything
I believe you
Since president Pan trusts you
you should be the team leader
Sister Yuan
I am serious
President Pan has made the decision
We should do as he says
President Pan is so insighful
You have the potential to be the director of sales department
But you are the most suitable candidate
Sister Yuan, don't worry
I'll be second to you
I didn't see you wrong
Don't worry
After I become the director, I will protect you
Go
Look, is sister Yuan angry?
They have turned against each other, right?
They are hugging
Come
To our dear Yiming
Come...
Come, cheers
Brother
What's your next plan?
I will have some holidays
Then I will try to find if there is any suitable job
So many companies want to poach him
Many companies are lining up, right?
They line up to the Bund
More than that
They crammed the elevated freeway
Enough
Yiming
Do you remember?
Tang
Who?
President Tang
The boss in Tongli?
His company needs a planning director
They want to knwo if you are interested
Forget it
They offer a better wage and treatment
Yes, he can
Yes, we can make an appointment next time
Forget it
It's a good offer
Not interested?
You two...
I resigned from Caijin
At least, I need to go to a better company than Caijin
Yes
Haowen
What are you talking?
Say it louder
Yes, what are you muttering?
Tang of Tongli company, do you know?
Yes...
He begs Yiming to be the planning director in his company
Stop it
He won't go
Yeah, he doesn't give a damn
Yes
Of course
Tang's company is so low
Totally agree
Caijin is such a small pond for Yiming
Right?
He deserves a better salary and position in the next company
Right? -Of course
Of course
Big brother
If you find a better one,
don't forget us
Yeah
Big brother, as long as you need, we will go to work for you
Yes...
Yes
And you?
Come...
I will remember all of you if I find a better job
Ok?
Ok
We will follow big brother forever
The appointment is at four o'clock, right?
Yes
Now it's fifteen past four
She wants to cheat?
Maybe
Sorry...
I have been here for a while
I talk to the machinist and forgot the time
President Wang, you are here too
Lanke
I just talked to the machinist
Very enlightening
The loss assessment
This is Mr. Lan's loss assessment
Ok, let's have a look at Lan's loss assessment
Here
Here and here
I won't be responsible for these
What do you mean?
These have nothing to do with the accident
You have repaired it before
So I won't pay for it
And this...
Just change the parts
No need to change the whole
And this
Hardware aging is not my business
Lanke, I will repair the car
You can't make me bankrupt, right?
Who told you not to replace these?
Zhong, Zeng, and Liang
The top three here
Well, Libi
Call Zhong, Zeng and Liang here
Ok
Your bag is 90% new at most
It's very expensive now
That's in the specialty store
This is a second-hand store
It's a signature style
22,000
It's out of stock all over the country
25,000
It's the hardest color to buy
Can't be less than this
Let me see
Be gentle
Mates
You told this lady, no need to change these parts?
She is familiar with this industry
So we told her the truth
You are friends, right?
None of their business
I made up an identity
So I got all the truth out
I can understand
Your 4S stores have to make money
But you should make money in a reasonable way
I will only take my responsibility
So what's the end?
Go back
Ok, go
Mr. Lan, I think
She is right
Ok, just do as she said
Ok
At least it can save more than 70,000
And I am your VIP and I put some money in it
I will have 20% discount
At least it can save more than 10,000
What's your job?
I'm a saleswoman
Which company?
Lubao
New energy battery company?
You know?
I have heard about it
President Wang
You can call me if you need battery
I can give you a discount
Let's talk about the car first
Ok
President Wang
Your car needs to change the parts
Because they are imported
All the parts need to be shipped from Germany
I want to discuss with you
Can you choose my friend's channel?
He can give me a lower price
Don't worry about quality
I can guarantee it
I don't need you to repair my car
You don't need to pay the money
I don't think it's ok
It's my responsibility
You just need to pay his bill
I have insurance
Well, then you will have no discount for the insurance next year
Li Siyu, right?
We can be WeChat friends
Ok
Then I won't call you president Wang
I will call you sister Ziru
You are my friend now
Siyu, you are quite capable
All because of money, I have no option
But not everyone can be like you
Sign here
I'll pay you
Give me some time
The matter of car is settled
See you at the old place
On second thought
Sister, what's wrong?
Sister
Sister, we can have a talk
I have reduced it to around a hundred thousand yuan
I am so awesome
You have saved so much money
It's enough for Yuwei to finish all her education
from primary school to college
Thanks to sister Ziru's generosity
Thanks to her richness
Now you know why I need a rich boyfriend, right?
We can't be benevolent until we become rich
May I ask where your rich boyfriend is?
He is looking for me
Keep an eye on him and don't sprain your ankle
You have paid 130,000?
Here
What do you mean?
It's all because of me
But Chen Yiming started all this with the proposal
We should split up for 13,000
Do you have money?
No
So I mortgage the bag to pay you
I will redeem it after I get enough money
Be careful
I can't afford it
Keep it for yourself
Ok, I will keep it for you first
But before I redeem it,
the ownership of the bag is yours
Zhizhi is the witness
Sister Siyu
If you really need, I have some money
No need
Leave Liu Yang's bonus to Yuwei
But to be honest
Brother Yiming is so great that he helps you with compensation
Don't hesitate anymore
Just say yes when he makes proposal next time
Yes
Let me tell you
Now or never
Yiming is so great to me, I know
But I feel I am controlled
I have a lot to do
I'm afraid of losing freedom
Freedom?
Just because you want freedom
he wants to marry you earlier in case you love someone else
What?
You have to associate with your clients
What should he think of you?
The sweet and handsome man like Chen Yiming is the rigid demand
You need to cherish him
Zhizhi, just leave her alone
Once Chen Yiming dumps her, she will regret
Yiming
I'm so sorry
Two years ago, my company was expanding very quickly
I was thirsty for talents
But now the market has changed a lot
What change?
Tell you the truth
80% of the companies I opened years ago began to close
I'm still downsizing
I am sorry
It's ok, president Zhu, I can understand
How about this?
I will keep your resume
in case my friend's company may hire you
Ok
As for my company
I have to say sorry
Thank you, president Zhu
I have to go now
President Zhu, we should have lunch together
It's lunch time
I have work to do
I have ordered the dishes
I can go to urge them...
No need...
I know it's hard to book a seat here
How about this?
Invite me next time if I find a new job for you
I feel guilty if I have lunch with you today
Goodbye
Ok
I have done my work
Where should we meet?
Yinmi Fanhua restaurant
Come here directly
I'm here
Miaomiao's mom, how are you?
Come so early
I am free today
You are so beautiful today
They are here too
It's ok
Hello
Here you are
Hello, Yuwei's mom
Linda's mom
You are here so early
I made some cookies for you
Xingxing likes matcha
Here
Ok, thanks  -For Xingxing
William likes chocolate
Linda likes little bear
I have bear's mold
Thank you
Miaomiao's mom
You are losing weight
So the sugar-free for you
Here
Thank you
You are so kind
See
The little bear is so cute
This is Yuwei's father, right?
Nice to meet you
Hello
Miaomiao's mom
He is also from Chiao Tung University
He and Miaomiao's mom are alumni
I am a 2004 graduate
How about she?
My mom graduates from Cornell University
Sorry
But my grandpa graduates from Chiao Tung University
So can I ask, what's his major?
He is not a student
He is a member of the board
His reputation precedes him
You barely know his name
How can you say reputation precedes him?
Well, I can't arrange the scene alone
That party?
What's it?
We will throw a party, I love mom, next month
Ok
We want to make the party chic
But we are short of hands
I can help you
Really?
So great
We still need to discuss about it
Discuss about it
Ok...
Ok, we will discuss about it
They are coming
Coming
Where is Miaomiao?
Miaomiao's mother adds me again
I am back in the elite group
We will have a meeting tomorrow night
Discuss about party
You can't be so excited, ok?
She took full responsibility and paid with her insurance?
Yes
No
Why not?
You have promised her
you would take full responsibility
You should keep your promise
Sister Ziru offered the help
I can't decline it
So you feel it's ok that she will cover all
the insurance loss and fraud risk of next year?
We are not her relatives
You think it's ok that we owe her such a big debt?
So much money
I need to sell a lot of batteries to pay the cost
Siyu
I have told you, I will pay it
Your money doesn't come so easily
It's all because of your hard work
But at least I won't feel guilty
So much money
We should pay more attention to the technologies of the battery
Excuse me
Hello
Sister Ziru, are you free tomorrow?
What's wrong, Siyu?
I want to invite you a meal
I will pay the repair cost
Ok, I will go
But we won't talk about repairing the car
Are you free tomorrow?
Ok
Send me the address later
Ok, see you tomorrow
Your annual salary is not much
How can you say you can earn it back in one year?
Because I'm amazing
I...
I will make the company give me a pay rise
Wish you a promotion and a pay rise
Thank you
Go with me tomorrow
Ok
She have said, she would be the second to me
People can breach the contract
Not to mention it's a verbal promise
Li Siyu, she won't
Then I ask you
Today you asked her to sort out the team
Why she rejected it?
I'll be second to you
Sit
Siyu, look at this
This is personnel list of our sales department
You should choose some of them
Choose?
You are the team leader, you need to select some people
In addition to Xia Xiaotian and Liu Xiaojia
what about others?
These are working with me all along
I need them
This...
Sister Yuan
The company said, it's two-way selection
We can't select them here, right?
Let them choose
It will be so messy
In case they all choose my team or your team
First of all, they won't choose me
Besides, first come, first served
As long as you have enough staff
no one can enter if he wants to
Morning, president Pan
Morning
Sister Siyu, good morning
Sister
Lin Ling asks, if we are short of hands
She wants to join us
Lin Ling
That three-egg goddess?
Yes
Sister Yuan let her go, right?
Sister Yuan says, those who have no sales performance
for three consecutive months need to go
But now the sales department has changed
I think if you keep her, she can work here for another 3 months
Forget it
She can't do anything
Why do I need her?
Ok
I'll go tell her
Well, HR department has prepared the new office for you
Over there
Really?
Sister Siyu, morning
Morning
How's it?
Sister Siyu
They have said, you can tell them if you need some adjustment
Ok
Sister Yuan is here
I have to go now
Sister Yuan
How's it?  Everything is ready?
Tell me if you need anything
I have all you need
No need
HR department did all for me
Are you feeling better?
Much better
Do you need an infusion today?
I'll go with you after work
No need
I'll go to the hospital for the checkup later
But I have a client in Ningbo
He needs me to talk about the contract
So can you go to see him for me?
This is the last step
I only trust you
No problem, leave it to me
I will sign the contract for you
Thank you
I told Ziting to book the ten o'clock bus
Ok
What else?
Nothing
I have to go now
Ok
Our Lubao battery is the best on the market
Look
We just brought one...
After you graduate, you only work in one company Caijin?
Yeah, I am kind of nostalgic
Mr. Chen
You are Haowen's friend
Well, you are kind of my friend
I'll tell the truth
Ok
The best time for job-hopping is 3 or 5 years
Your time is a bit too long
No job-hopping for ten years
I can't recommend you to my clients
It's not what they want
The enterprises need highly loyal employees, right?
Loyalty is very important
The yearly job-hoppers are out of option
But corporate development needs dynamic talents
In addition to working years
What about other aspects?
The most sought-after talents are young and innovative
Or they can bring resources to the company
Generally, it's directors
Given your age and previous position
it's a little embarrassing
No offense
I'm a bit straightforward
It's ok
I just want to say, the salary may be not as high as you think
Then you think how much my salary should be?
200,000?
Annual salary?
Correct
Far from what I expected
Now this is the fact
Hello
Yiming
Hurry, congratulate me
What happened?
I got another order
Great
Congratulations
You are not in the company?
I am now
Your company plays the coquettish background music?
I'm in a cafe near the company
An appointment with my client
You won't work overtime tonight, right?
Don't forget
We will have dinner with sister Ziru tonight
I am going to the high-speed rail station now
I will arrive in Shanghai this afternoon
Then go to the company, that's all
You are on a business trip again?
I'm in Ningbo
As I know, you don't have a client in Ningbo
Sister Yuan's client
I am here to help her
Sister Yuan needs your help?
She has something else
Why are you silent?
Nothing
What nothing?
You want to blame me that I didn't tell you in advance again?
No
Don't be angry
It's a temporary arrangement
I didn't have the time to tell you
Come and go in a few hours
It's ok
Fine
Bye
Sister Siyu
Sister Siyu, Vice President Hu wants to see you
In HR department
Ok
Leave it to me
Thank you
Ok
Come in
Sit
You need to select your staff
Me?
It's a two-way choice, right?
Check the list first
Is this the entire sales department?
No
Sister Yuan has finished her selection
So these are leftovers
Correct
What else can I select?
Mr. Hu, I have to go now
Show me this
Come in
Sister
Here's team A's list
Huang Bibo, Kuaizi, Afu
Zhou Zhiyu, Yang Tian
And Zhang Jiaqi
I get it
As I know, after we went out today
sister Yuan talked to them in office one by one
And she let them sign to follow her
Really?
So now except you
top ten salesmen go to her team
Show me that
Sister, she did this on purpose?