[To Dear Myself]
[Ep5]
Sister Siyu
Thank you for taking me in
But I think I should go
Why?
As I know, president Pan scolded you because of me
You can go
But I was scolded for nothing
I win you a chance after being scolded
President Pan has said, as long as you can
sign a contract with a client within a week
You can end the internship and be hired offically
A week?
I can't
Lin Ling
I have faith in you
You can make it
I can make it
Among your clients, which one is most likely to sigh the contract?
Yoyo Rabbit
Why he didn't sign the contract in the end?
The company suddenly stopped production for transformation
New production line will go into operation after half a year
Till then, they need batteries
So you just give up?
I asked sister Yuan about this
Sister Yuan said, I just need to keep in touch with him
We will decide after half a year
Go
Where are we going?
Go to Yoyo Rabbit
Till have 5 months to go
You need to go out before you know where the opportunity is
Opportunities won't come when you wait here
We have to fight for them
Ok
Siyu
Sister Yuan
I want to talk to you
Wait for me
Ok
Close the door
Can you tell me in advance before you take someone in?
Otherwise they will think we are at odds
You didn't tell me in advance before you
took in elites like Huang Bibo, Kuaizi and Afu
You are still angry now?
My fault. I forgot to tell you in advance
I am sorry
No need, it's over now
All right
I will invite you to dinner
You can pick the place
I'll pick an expensive one
Ok
Fire Lin Ling
Why?
She is not the stuff for this
Why do you waste time on her?
I think she has potential in sales
You don't adopt my advice?
No
I just promised her I would help her
sign a contract within a week to end her internship
No
Why?
Siyu
To be honest
I taught her for three months
And she had no breakthrough
But if you help her sign the contract within a week
you will insult me
Sister Yuan
I'm not sure if Lin Ling can make it
But even if she signs the contract
that's because you have laid the foundation for her
Others won't think so
As long as we don't mind,
never mind the gossips
Easy for you to say
We are team leaders now
We need to care about others' opinions
Sister Yuan
Lin Ling's father is seriously ill
She needs this job
You have many ways to help her
Why do you use this to insult me?
Give a man a fish and you feed him for a day
teach a man to fish and you feed him for a lifetime
She has some foundation
It's a pity if she gives up now
You hurt our relationship by helping Lin Ling
You don't think it's a pity?
Sister Yuan
Do you think too much?
Siyu
Don't forget
You have promised me
You will be second to me
I don't think it will make any difference
just because of Lin Ling, right?
Maybe you will help more out
Sister Yuan
I have promised you
But you still don't believe me
Take precautions against me
What's the point of this?
Li Siyu
Think with your conscience
Will you have today without me?
I just ask you a little favor
But you say one thing and do another
What should I think of you?
When do I say one thing and do another?
Then fire her now
Hello
Is this Dayu investment company?
Yes
Hello, I...
Days ago, I sent an email cover letter
But I got no reply
So...
I hope you can check it for me
No reply, it means you are eliminated
Then I want to ask about the reason
I don't know
Thank...
Hello
What are you doing?
Meeting
Are you ok?
I'm fine
I just didn't have a good talk with the client
What's the matter?
Nothing
I just ask casually
Why are you all sitting there?
It's been two weeks, you still didn't fix it
So disgraceful
Sales depend on legs
In all, go to grab clients
Grab clients
Here
I didn't finish the medicine you gave me last time
Keep it just in case
Pay attention to your stomach
Lin Ling
Come here
Sister Siyu
Lin Ling
Sorry
Sister Siyu
Go through the resignation procedures in HR department
You promised me you would help me
I take my words back, ok?
I break my promise, ok?
Sister Siyu
Stop it, go out
You are a workaholic
Why are you here now?
I don't want to work today
What happened?
All about the office story
You should watch Empresses in the Palace
Then you won't have these troubles
Well
Help me say sorry to Chen Yiming
I showed no respect to his friend Lei
Lei Haowen likes bragging
An egoist man
But he is nice
Stop it
I am so curious that Chen Yiming would have a friend like him
Chen Yiming is very strange recently
He told me he went to see clients
But I didn't see one
Why are you here alone?
Where is the client?
He just left
And he is preoccupied
He checked the phone behind my back a lot
Does he have an affair?
Impossible
Lanke did all these when he had an affair
Chen Yiming won't
Why do you trust Chen Yiming so much?
If we don't have the basic trust,
why does he make a proposal?
Let me tell you
You can't take it lightly just because he makes a proposal
Actually he didn't make one
All because of you
Don't scapegoat me
All because you have gamophobia
After that, he didn't mention the proposal again
So weird
You shilly-shally all along
Just ask him
How?
Chen Yiming
When will you make a proposal again?
You are such a rookie in love
You think yourself as love expert
At least I see more two-timers than you do
Let me tell you
Some men are womanizers
They are lurking around all the time
Answer it
Xiao Jia
Sister
How to quote when I talk to Alade company?
Give them the quote of our senior clients
Ok, bye, sister
Well
Did Lin Ling go through the procedure?
Lin Ling?
She goes to Yoyo Rabbit
Why does she go to Yoyo Rabbit?
No idea
You are leaving now?
I have work to do
You need to keep an eye on Chen Yiming
Showcase
What about the booth?
At least you have a red carpet, right?
Who will use the carpet of this kind color for exhibition?
Where are you now?
Come...
So, will you come?
You have promised you would come at that point
See the backboard
The logo
Where's my Yoyo Rabbit logo?
Let me tell you
We have invited the leaders and media
Even the dealers are here
You all ruined it now
So will you open the exhibition tomorrow?
What were you saying?
What were you two talking about?
Come, tell us
Tell me what to do
Lin Ling
Sister Siyu
Mr. Jiang, calm down
Why are you here?
What's going on?
They will have a dealer conference tomorrow
But they found an unreliable PR company
Now it's a mess
What are you doing now?
I am helping...
I fired you
What are you doing here?
Sister Siyu
I want to fight for the last time
You have no chance
You have told you we can't have opportunities by waiting
We need to fight for them
You will do everything I say?
Yes
Because only you tell me I can make it
I know I am fired
But before leaving, I want to prove myself
I can make it
What? Arrive tomorrow?
Why do you tell me till now?
Ok, I get it
You can't set the tables and chairs
No guest list
You can't arrange the seats
Is there anything you can do?
What about the booth?
I told you to arrange it a month ago
Zhizhi
I need the booth when we held the exhibition
at the beginning of the year
You are good for nothing
Great
I need it now
You help me go through the application process
Thanks
Xiao Jia
Call everyone to come to help Yoyo Rabbit
Ok, sister
Everyone, listen
Sister Siyu called me just now
Later all of us need to go to Yoyo Rabbit
To help Lin Ling
This is an exhibition
You all know what you should do, right?
You know what to bring right?
Yes
Let's go
Bring the LED screen
Please come in
Sister Yuan
You leave Yoyo rabbit to me, right?
Why it goes to Lin Ling?
It can't be
You guys, get in my car
Ok
And put things in that car
I sent you Yoyo Rabbit's address
Hurry
Be careful
Sister Yuan
Li Siyu
Yoyo Rabbit is Liu Jie's client
Why is Lin Ling making a trouble?
Yoyo Rabbit belongs to Lin Ling all along
After Lin Ling was fired, I told Liu Jie to take it over
Lin Ling was not formally fired
It still belongs to Lin Ling in company's dossier
Li Siyu, don't forget how I taught you in the beginning
Sister Yuan
I did not forget
What I am doing now is what you taught me
What?
In the beginning, I had no sales performance
for two consecutive months
You didn't despise me and taught me hand by hand
So I found confidence and breakthrough
It teach Lin Ling just like the way you taught me
Sister Yuan, what did she say?
Forget it
No
I said it and I mean it
You fired her and she took her in
Now she grabs your client
She is turning against you
Go out
Where's Siyu?
In there
Hurry
I will wait for you inside
Lin Ling
Check the guest list and seats
Ok, sister
Xiao Jia
You will be responsible for printing and placement
Ok
Xiao Tian
Yes
You will handle the banners
Ok
Xiao Wu
Get the LED lights
Ok
You two
Help them with stereo
You three, come here
Come with me
You are from a PR company?
We are from Lubao company
Mr. Jiang, this is our manager Li
Manager Li, this is Mr. Jiang
Mr. Jiang
Lin Ling told me, your company is in a problem
So we are here to help you
Do not worry
We are not a professional PR company
But I have organized all Lubao's dealer activities
I can guarantee you can hold a successful activity tomorrow
Manager Li, right?
What I want to tell you is
Our company has ho plans to order batteries in the next six months
It's ok
We have no plan even after half a year
Mr. Jiang
I will help you today no matter you buy or not
Go
Hello
Hello, Liu Yang
When will you come back?
I have a little work
I will go back soon
Come back early
I need to go out later
I can't leave Yuwei at home alone
Where are you going?
I have told you
I have a meeting with Miaomiao's mom
I really don't understand why you associate with them all day?
I do this for Yuwei
Since Yuwei plays with them
she has a different vision now, you don't know?
I need to handle an urgent matter now
And I won't go home tonight
Liu Yang, hello
Little devil
Don't jump, it's dangerous
Come, sit down baby
Come, sit down
Sister Siyu
I got brother Yiming's revised plan
It's so great
Thank you
I'm busy now
That's all, bye
Aunt Mei
Xiaoling
Can you help me take care of Yuwei for a while?
Me?
I'll pick her up later
But...
I am running late
Bye
Zhizhi
Come in
Aunt Mei
Close the door
It's so great
It's a good picture
A very rich content
Yuwei's mom is so professional
Great
Flattered
Look
Our previous ones are great
What do you want to drink?
I drank too much water today
I can't drink anymore
You should order
Or have some snacks
I am on a diet recently
I can't
You should order some
You are so thin, still want to lose weight?
I am fat
Yuwei
My high heels are very expensive
All right
I won't blame you...
I will give you some food, ok?
I have only biscuits and juice
Do you want some?
Sister, look
I am painting your mouth
Zhang Zhizhi, pick up your daughter now
So you three still want to see it?
No need, still the same
She caused me more than 20,000 losses
She needs to compensate me when she grows up
I'm going crazy
Sister, look
You like painting, right?
Let me teach you
Tomorrow, Yuwei's mom and I will arrange the scene
Ok
You should split up
Well
That's all for today
Ok
Waiter, settle the bill
Yes
Hello, scan there
1672.5
Yuwei's mom
Pay the money
I paid it
Let's go first
I got it
A little sleepy
I paid too
Go...
Bye
Hello, Xiaoling
You are not at home?
Where are you now?
Ok, I am coming now
Zhizhi
Well
Where's Yuwei?
In the toilet
Toilet?
How can you let her go to the toilet alone?
She needs to be independent
What if a trafficker is lurking around?
No
Mom
Gu Xiaoling
What's going on?
Why did you do to her?
Mom, look
Yuwei likes it
Is it poisonous?
These are all famous brands
Very safe, don't worry
She is still a child
Mom, this
I dropped by and had her ears pierced
How can you do this to Yuwei?
Come
These are so pretty
My aunt said
Women should be good to ourselves
Yuwei is right
Gu Xiaoling, you are so ridiculous
Goodbye, aunt
Goodbye Yuwei
Zhang Zhizhi
Do you need me to keep an eye on Yuwei tomorrow?
Never
Hello, Haowen
Send me an email
Never mind the content
I just want to make sure there is no problem with my mailbox
Ok, hurry
Hello
Make a phone call
Stop talking nonsense
Just do as I say
Hurry
Liu Yang, drink water?
Let me help you
No, thanks
Why all of them work overtime?
They can't leave before you
Why?
You are the team leader
Tell me to get off work now
I will go home soon
All of you should go home now
Well
Nothing...
Go home now
See you tomorrow
Liu Yang, you are back
What's wrong?
I left Yuwei to Xiaoling
Now it becomes like this
How can you leave Yuwei to Gu Xiaoling?
You work overtime, I need to attend a meeting
I have to ask Xiaoling for help
So you still went to see them right?
Voice down
You are hungry, right?
I will make you a bowl of wontons
What stuffings do you want?
Three delicacies or cabbage?
Whatever
You don't adopt my advice anyway
You are the head of the family
What else do you want to eat?
I make it for you
Lin Ling
I'll go back later
I will leave here to you
Ok
Manager Li
You are here
Mr. Jiang
I want to talk to you
Ok
We have trained them
Flowers will arrive by 6 o'clock tomorrow morning
Tea and pastries will arrive by eight o'clock
I have left the phone numbers to secretary Wang
I have communicated with the moderator about the conference
Everyone knows his responsibility now
And plan B is ready, too
Thank you
Thank you so much
Come, please
Mr. Jiang, you are welcome
Client's priority is our priority
The thing is our company is not your client
A friend, at least
Friends should help each other
Manager Wang
Mr. Jiang
Draw up a contract right away
Our company need to order half a million batteries
Tell finance department to prepare advance payment
Our production line won't operate until the second half of this year
Mr. Jiang, you don't need to do so
You have said, we are friends
I see you as friends
I want to show my gratitude
It's a little sincerity of our company
But...
Yes
But sincerity must be based on reality
well, you don't believe in my strength?
Thank you Mr. Jiang
Ok
Then let's hit the iron while it's hot
Lin Ling
You should talk about the details about the contract with them
Ok
Manager Jiang, manager Wang
Are you sleeping?
I just finished my work
Me, too
Are you ok?
I am fine
No parking here
I'm sorry
I will go now
Ok...
Thank you