[To Dear Myself]
[Ep9]
Morning
The report you gave the director, you forgot the data in 2017
It's ok, I remedied it for you
Be careful next time
Thank you
It's ok
Mr. Liu
Actually, last time it's not my fault
Wu told me to do that on purpose
I even asked him if it's ok
He said, it's none of my concern
Really?
I still heard he called someone
As long as you make another mistake,
you won't be the team leader
But you begin to doubt him
So that man seizes the opportunity
Who's that man?
I don't know
Mr. Liu
Be careful
Thank you
It's ok
I want to invite you to a dinner another day
Well, ok
Hello
Yeah, it's me
Ok...
Really?
No idea
He didn't tell this to others
Really?
Come out, I have something to ask you
Mr. Liu
Why Wu didn't avoid you while making a phone call?
I cried in that corner that night out of homesickness
He thought no one in the office
Did you tell anyone else about this?
No
Why do you tell me?
Mr. Liu
You are a good guy
I don't want to see you are entrapped
Mr. Liu
Please trust me
You are so good to me
I will never lie to you
I believe you
What are you going to do?
I am revising the plan
The priority is to reverify the data
The workload...
Yes
I can't do it alone
Mr. Liu, I can help you
I can stay up late
Thank you
It's so tricky even if you help me
The most important thing is to find out Wu's traps
Xiaotian, your turn
Sister Siyu, this week...
Sister Siyu
Guys
Are you all pigs?
Look over there
Stare at me every day
You are waiting to be fed?
You think you have orders while you sit in the office?
Sales depend on legs
Go, move
Why are you standing here?
I will sack you if you can't meet this month's performance
Sister Yuan is so screwed
She is going to break down
Go out...
Of course
We have surpassed them
Don't talk about them
Xiaojia, your number
2 million this week
2.4 million
Sister Siyu
2.5 million
Sister, I can't
2.6 million
Ok
2.6 million, ok
2.6 million, come on
Lin Ling, where are you?
Why don't you come for the meeting?
Sister Siyu, help
What happened?
I have talked with the representative of Meiyi Group for 3 months
Today we are here to sign the contract
But Liu Jie also came
It's your client, why she went there?
It's a long story
You should come now
I can't handle her alone
Wait for me
Go on without me
Li Siyu didn't teach you about company rules and regulations?
Sister Yuan
What rules and regulations?
Meiyi Group is Liu Jie's client
It has nothing to do with you
But she has given up
I never said so
Ok
You said it yourself
Stop talking, go back
No
I have talked with the client for three months
Why should I give it to her now?
Not give, you should step out of this
Why?
Here you are
Sister Yuan
We should be reasonable, right?
Lin Ling picks up the client Liu Jie gives up on
She's worked on it for three months
She is going to sign the contract
Liu Jie suddenly wants to take it back
No one will accept this right?
Who said, Liu Jie gave up?
She just put it aside for a while
Sometimes we need cold treatment for the client
I have taught you this before, right?
Thank you
I remember you even taught me
to seize the opportunity firmly
So I taught Lin Ling about this
Stop it
The company has its rules and regulations
Rules and regulations must be reasonable
Director Luo
Sorry
Director Luo,  -Sorry
We made it at 15:00
I just had a meal with the mayor
So I am a bit late
It's ok
Sorry...
Director Luo, do you remember me?
You are from Lubao Group too, right?
Correct
Director Luo
I am the sales manager of Lubao Company
Li Siyu
Ok
Director Luo
I am Lubao's sales director Yuan Huizhong
So many people here today
Yes
It shows our respect and sincerity
So who should I talk to?
Talk to me
Director Luo, I have been on this all along
Only I know the details
Talk to me, you will save time
So you are not the same team
Of course we are
But if you talk to me
I can give you more convenience
Director Luo
Director Yuan is our superior
We all listen to her
Ok
Tian Siyu
Yuan Huizhong
Ok
Please... Come to my office
Come
Why not foil her lie?
It's not good for Lubao's reputation
if we argue in front of the client
What should we do now?
The order is 5 million
What's going on with this client?
During my internship, sister Yuan led me
A friend introduced director Luo to me
But at that time sister Yuan said
I was inexperienced
She told Liu Jie to lead me
Liu Jie took me to talk with director Luo several times
But he was not sincere
So we gave up
Then I go to your team
Director Luo contacted me again
This time everything goes smoothly
When we were about to sign the contract, Liu Jie came
So it's your name in the file or her name?
I don't know
I just came to the company at that time
I didn't know all this
So did she cancel the name in the file
when she gave up on the order?
It's...
No idea
Go back first
Excuse me
Where is the cold medicine?
Cough medicine is also here?
Boy, you have a cold?
Come, let me take your pulse
No, thanks
I just need some medicine
How about this?
It's your decision to make
whether you believe me or not what I say
Anyway, it will cost you nothing
Come
You have the cold because of the low temperature
Maybe I was caught in the rain days ago
You have a strong physique
I don't think you have the serious cold because of the rain
Having a cold is the superficial symptom
The left wrist is not smooth
Right hand pulse is tight and rigid
And you have some discomfort in your internal organs
You have some anxiety
What medicine should I take?
We have a lot of cold medicines
As for the discomfort and anxiety
If you can't let it go now, no medicine could work
What should I let go?
Let all your concerns go
According to Chinese medicine,
all diseases originate from the mental disease
Nowadays, all young people's diseases are because
they can't get what they want and they are afraid to lose
So let go,
you mean we don't need to work hard
Just let it go if we can't get it or we are afraid to lose it
I mean, everything needs to be based on the actual situation
Ginseng and antler are good
Many people feel refreshed after eating them
But it's also harmful for some people
Let me give you some prescription
Thank you, doctor
No need...
I'll try to let it go
Don't worry
I will pay you the consultation fee
Thank you...
Liu Jie didn't cancel
No
So what's all this?
Hello
Li Siyu
President Pan wants to see you and Lin Ling in his office
Ok, I get it
Go to president Pan's office
President Pan, vice president Fang
Li Siyu
What's going on today?
Meiyi Group?
What else could it be?
It's Lin Ling's client
I have checked it
Liu Jie is registered in the file
President Pan, vice president Fang
We need to report and file the client's name in advance
We are not allowed to grab clients
We can't lower the price for vicious competition
But Li Siyu and Lin Ling just ignore company's rules and regulations
I think it's a serious problem
The vice can't be tolerated in our company
Sister Yuan, you really want to be like this?
What's wrong?
The company's interests are above all else
I mean you can't call white black or confuse right and wrong
because of this order, right?
You are even here to denounce me here first
Li Siyu
Who call white black?
It's the company's regulations
Those who file the client's name have the order
No internal vicious competition
You encourage your subordinates to play hard for KPI
Who are you talking about?
It's you
Enough
Here is not vegetable market
It's work
Tell the truth, get to the point
Lin Ling is the first one to contact Meiyi Group
And she is also the one who gets the contract
Lin Ling has kept all the evidence of the negotiation
President Pan
I am the first to contact Meiyi Group
Director Luo is my friend for many years
Come on
He doesn't know you at all
He saw you for the first time today
I know it
I also know director Luo
At the beginning, Huizhong introduced him
It's been at least ten years
I see
President Pan
Director Luo and I have made the contract long ago
His company had some problems
So we didn't sign the contract till now
But I didn't expect Lin Ling would step in
And she even offered a lower price
Fortunately, director Luo sees me as his friend
So he accepts my price and finally we sign the contract
You sign the contract?
Yes
5 million
He will pay the deposit tomorrow
What is your offer?
My offer is higher than Lin ling's
You even said you were the sales director
Lin Ling, let me tell you
When I was a little manager
for the convenience, I even said I was vice president
President Pan also did this
To avoid being despised,
he said he was the director of an association
It's very normal
President Pan
I think it's a serious problem
If everyone grabs clients viciously,
it will ruin our company's reputation and we can't work
Meiyi Group is my client
The fact is here
You're still talking nonsense here
I'm not
I won't talk nonsense with you
I have nothing to say
I just hope president Pan, you could uphold justice for me
You're lying
Shut up
Meiyi Group is team A's client
The order of 5 million goes to team A
And Lin Ling will be fined 5,000 yuan
because of the violation of company's rules and regulations
Li Siyu, as a superior,
will be fined 10,000 yuan for the negligence
And you will be criticized in a circulated notice
Sister Siyu
You know, it's Liu Jie's filed client
Why did you do this?
I don't know
You should know
Now you lost your client
The contract is gone
And they even make a countercharge
Are we happy now?
I am sorry, sister Siyu
Siyu
Come early after you get off work
Anything wrong?
I am preparing the dinner
You find a new job?
No
Why are you so happy?
So I can't be happy?
Today I met a senior herbalist doctorr
Senior herbalist doctor?
What happened to you?
I was caught in the rain days ago
So I have a cold
I went to get some medicine
And I met him
Oh
Do you want to know what's gone on?
All ears
The senior herbalist doctor said
I am depressed
Because I think too much
I should learn to let it go
Are you there?
I am listening
So, I plan to let it go
I'll entertain myself
At least I have a good health even if I have no job
What's wrong, Siyu?
Are you ok?
Nothing, lost an order
Siyu
The sales performance is so important for you?
It decides whether I can be the director next month
So what?
I have to fight for it
Maybe this is the so-called worry
We want to get it and we are afraid to lose
What are you talking about?
The senior herbalist doctor told me this
We want to get it and we are afraid to lose
What did you say?
After I lost my job
I have been applying for a job
All the interviews and resumes
And I failed over and over again
It's just temporary
My friends told me now is the off season for job hunting
So you can't doubt yourself
I believe soon you will have good news
Siyu
I want to stop looking for a job for a while
Yiming
Do you think too much?
I think I used to run so fast
and think too little
Yeah, we can't think too little
But we have to run fast
Even if we can't get it in the end, at least we try our best
We can start over, no big deal
If we are so hesitant, we will get nothing
You never failed
Siyu
It is not so easy to start over
I have just said, I lost an order
Will you come tonight?
I will be there late
Overwork?
I have to go out
Where?
See the client
I need to get the order of 5 million back
Your words are harsh
Still, I want to thank you
Yuwei's mom, you can't dress so casually till then
I...
Yeah, you need to wear formal clothes
And your shoes and your bag
You need to change them
Otherwise it's so unsightly
Everybody
Wednesday evening at 19:30
Gather at the dessert shop
Discuss about the joint letter
Hope all the parents will come
Sorry
I have no time tomorrow night
Ok
You are back
They are sleeping?
Why are you back so late every day?
I will come back later than this in the future
Why?
Wu wants to be the team leader
He wants to nitpick me
So I need to do everything
He is so evil?
It's common to see people like this in the workplace
Yeah
After sister Siyu begins to compete for the director
she has the endless troubles
President Pan called her to his office this morning
She is fined
Now you know it's hard to work in the company, right?
So in the future, you don't go out with them
Take care of the family
So I won't be distracted
I do this all for Yuwei
Nowadays, the society values the resources and connections
I maintain the relationship with them for Yuwei
So she will have a better platform in the future
But is it too early to think about this?
Not early at all
We have the differnt starting points
We need to make an effort in advance in locker room
So people from countryside like me will have
no qualification to enter the locker room
But I am still so great
It's the past
The poor students like you still have the opportunity
It's different now
I need Yuwei to go to the elite circles since childhood
When she grows up, she will become an elite
Well, there is a parents gathering tomorrow
They will write a joint letter to kindergarten
So parents need to be there together
I have just said
The office fight is very tense
I need to work overtime
I have no time for your gathering
No
It's about Yuwei's future
Zhizhi
Neither of us are elites
You try so hard to get into that circle
Don't you feel tired?
Yes, I am
Let nature take its course
Just live a simple life, ok?
Are you hungry?
I will cook you a bowl of wontons
No need
It's ok soon
Have lunch together
I won't go if you want to eat with Li Siyu
Only two of us
Ok
Zhizhi
Sister Siyu, you're not in the company?
I am on the way to company now
How's it?
500,000
It's a small order
Sister Siyu
I find a good restaurant
Have lunch together
You should change your mood
Come
It's my treat
Ok
Gu Xiaoling won't come, right?
You want to invite her?
No, only two of us
Ok, I'll book the table now
Ok
Miss Zhang reserved the table
This way please
You two arrived before me
I have something to do, I have to go now
Eat first
I have to go now
Xiaoling
Sit...
Sit down first
Zhizhi, you don't know I break up with her?
I know
But you often break up every year
And it won't last more than a week
So it's almost a week
So I invite you two here
We won't make up this time
You said the same last time
You said the same last year
And you said the same two years ago
Two sisters
Both of you are over 30
Why are you so grumpy like kids?
Yuwei are not so grumpy now
She blacklisted me
Yes
But before that, she transferred you 110,000
Sister Siyu
Last time you were framed up and had a bad mood
No one could contact you
You don't know how anxious she was
Excuse me
I have to make it clear
If either of you leave, I will be angry
Thank you anyway
I have helped you a lot these years
But you never appreciate it
I also helped you a lot
Your dad found you write love letter to a boy
before the college entrance examination
I stood up for you
You couldn't even pass the graduation exam without me
You had no money when you first came to Shanghai
I saved my money and sent the money to you
You had no place to live in Shanghai
I shared the bed with you
I helped you every time you quarreled with Chen Yiming
Why are you arguing again?
Zhizhi
Tell us, I helped her more or she helped me more?
You have noted all down
Come, get out your notebook now
It will tell all
You have been sisters since childhood
You should help each other
You should feel grateful to have each other
In my heart, you have different styles
But you are my good sisters
Now you become like this
I want to take back my worship of you two
I admit
These years she helped me more
We have been sisters for so many years
I know
I know you have disputes sometimes
But you wish each other good?
No one can hurt your relationship
I am sorry for the bad attitude that day
It's ok
I want to thank you
Need the loo
Between these two,
add two or three light spots
Ok
Are you tired?
Let's take a break there
Ok, let's go
Sit
Ok
Come
Thank you
I know it's hard for you
It's ok
Let me see
How many steps have we taken?
20,000 steps
A piece of cake
I used to walk 20 kilometers back and forth to school
Mountain roads
You are from the countryside
Yes
Me, too
Mr. Liu
Actually we are alumni
Really?
It's not easy to be admitted to Chiao Tung University
I am the top pick in our county
Me, too
I know
It's not easy for us
Mr. Liu
Can I call you brother?
Of course
Brother
Are you used to urban life?
Not entirely
For example
Let alone others
Food, for example
I like the hometown's food
Exactly
I feel the same
In childhood, if I was hungry
I would dig some potatoes in the field
Then threw them in the wood stove
It would be cooked soon
Then I would get them out
Peel them and dip in soy sauce
Or chili powder
You know this too?
Of course
It's so fragrant
What a pity
Now even imported potatoes can't be that delicious
Well, Yayun
I have a good idea
But I need your cooperation
Ok, I will help you
Zhizhi
Do you have diarrhea?
You went to the toilet so frequently
Liu Yang's mom is here
She is here
Help you take care of Yuwei
She asked us to have a son
I need to drink two bowls of Chinese medicine for pregnancy
Now I have diarrhea
The time's changed
She still forces you to have a son?
So ridiculous
All her neighbors have sons
So she wants one
No way
So outrageous
It's so unbelievable
Yes, it's ridiculous
Shit
It's over 3,000 yuan
Here
Over 3,000?
Yes
It's hard to tell
You are a battery seller
It's weird if you know the price of clothes
Xiaoling
Can you do me a favor?
Say it
Yuwei's class will hold a party
All moms will be well dressed
You also know I only wear these clothes
No need to say more
Come to my house this weekend
Clothes, bags, shoes
You can choose whatever you want
Thank you
To you
So good to have you
Thank you
Now we make up with each other
Sister Siyu, can you have dinner tonight with us
Help me talk to Liu Yang's mom
No problem
I know you are busy
I don't want to ask you the favor
But I really can't change his mom's mind
It's ok
I haven't been to your home for a long time
Sort out this
Thank you
Sister Yuan, I will go now
Ok
How's it?
Don't worry, sister Yuan
You lead her now
How much?
1.13 million
Only 1.13 million?
I just got an order of 5 million
Correct
Plus the order of 5 million
You lead her by 1.13 million