# Google translate version for your reference #
Yuwei is asleep
I still don't believe
You are really
Broke up with Yiming
Yes indeed
Why are you suddenly
That's what happened
Life
Siyu sister
Are you too strong
Yes indeed
If you can't, just take a step back
Get married before starting a business
No big deal
This is not a matter of order
Is what he and I want most
Different
Can't it reconcile?
Reconciled to today
I'm tired
Is it possible for you to get back together?
impossible
Cry if you want
Cry happily
I don't have time to cry
There is so much work waiting for me
fortunately
I still have a job
If you really want to divide
You two have settled the bill
What account
The house they bought together
How to do
How to repay the loan
You go find him
I do not have time
This idea is good
You two can still
Take care of each other
You can live in my house to save money
But I want to tell you clearly
If i have an important date
You are going out to stay in a hotel
and also
You can't be like when you were a kid
What is forcing me every day
Memorizing words and writing
Homework
and also
Can't dress me up
Just call me a fairy
Not to give a small report to parents
I won't
Zhizhi
What did you plan
from
I heard
Liu Yang has an accident
That woman bit Liu Yang back
Liu Yang and her
This time it was really broken
So what?
some things
Once found
It is impossible to pretend
do not know anything
What's the matter
Liu Yang is a very dull
Very bored man
Not romantic
Will not take care of people
But when i see
He and Wei Yayun
When together
I just found
He will be romantic
Also take care of people
Just look to whom
The five years of marriage
Life is very hard
But I am willing
Thought he loves me
I love him too
I am willing to give everything for him
in fact
I'm deceiving myself and others
He doesn't love me at all
He didn't treat me as a lover
As a wife
All the time
He only treats me as a nanny
But you till now
I still go to the hospital every day to take care of him
Although I have treated him
Completely disappointed
But he is after all
Yuwei's father
Zhizhi, you are too kind
In marriage
Kindness
Can't exchange for sincere
Even if I get my heart
Will be pressured by life
Riddled with holes
okay
Stop talking about you two
Keep on saying that
We all become bitter women
You are
For a scum
I wasted five years of youth
It doesn't matter
The next five years
We happily live
Lose now
Win it all back
And you
Isn't it just a broken love?
I have less than half a year
I've been broken up twice
Do you see me complaining
Decadent?
Repeated defeats
To get the final victory
Pour all the wine
Upside down
Ok and mine
I declare
We have to take all the complaints
Worries
All stay today
Tomorrow is a new day
Cheers
Is she okay
well
About her business
What's going on
You don't support her either
Don't ask
She hopes
You sold that house
Repay her down payment
That house is sold
Can't buy it back
Or don't sell it
But she is really short of money now
I think of a way
I asked the agent
The house has gone up now
If sold
You have to pay her at least 800,000
Xiaoling
The house has been
It went up by 300,000
I know
and
And Siyu was altogether
Out of half a million
She was with you for five years
Shouldn't you
Compensate her
But but i now
Can't get so much money
Then you write the IOU
And me
I asked for 300 thousand more for you
Who asked you to do this
I'm helping you fight for your rights
Are you fighting for rights?
You are blackmail
Why am I blackmailed?
On the real estate certificate
Write clearly
Half of you
I want 800,000
Not too much
Say again
Youth compensation
We gotta point
I knew you were this way
I shouldn't let you go
your business
I will never care about you again
tomorrow we
To change the title certificate of the house
I can't take out 800,000
Let's talk after the formalities
it is good
You said I obviously helped her
She actually taught me a lesson
have you seen
Such an ungrateful person?
Have seen it
Last time at the gate of the art gallery
I help a woman
Escaped the clutches of the scumbag
The woman scolded me too
Who are you talking about
I said your sisters have a virtue
Don't say who
Having said that
Chen Yiming is my brother
You for nothing
Ruined 300,000 people
A bit cruel
Why am I for nothing?
He hurt Li Siyu
I help Li Siyu be fair
what happened
Isn't Chen Yiming injured?
I saw him yesterday
The whole person is too thin
Deserve it
You want me to say
This thing is really not to blame
Li Siyu is to blame
Li Siyu is a bit
Crazy
Who is crazy
You scolded someone just now
Ungrateful
I scold her
You can't scold her
All the time
You said they both
Can I get back together?
Li Siyu
It has to be changed a bit
Otherwise like last time
Score after compounding
Then do you think Chen Yiming
No need to change
Yes
Compare with me
Chen Yiming is indeed
Not enough sunshine
Not handsome enough, not interesting enough
But in general
Still quite perfect
Come, come, eat skewers, eat skewers
I can't eat spicy food for a month
why
I got an injection
The doctor said to avoid food
No way
You have grown up like this
Still use injections
Although I look so beautiful
But i will get old
What are you afraid of
Isn't there a good song?
How many people can
I love your face when you were young
Can anyone
Care about the ruthless changes of the years
How many people can
Came and paid in your life
I know I have you in my life
I'm by your side
Moved not
why
If i get old
Or only you by my side
Then I failed too much
Who will stay by your side will not fail
No matter what
Man with silver hair and personable
Retired billionaire
It's not said
Me fifty years from now
you
Why are you laughing? Look down on people
Then you should do it
Something I can afford
That `s a deal
Now house
You alone
I'll collect half a million for you first
The remaining 300,000
Within two years
I must pay it all off
This is an IOU
You owe me nothing
Siyu
I was once to our future
I have
Many ideas
but
I never thought
The result will be like this
it is my fault
I can't give you what you want
No you are not wrong
There is nothing wrong with what you want
only me
just
We might
Each has its own direction
No matter what
I really love you
I really love you too
We finally have a home
Before now after
I'm in your palm
You can always hold me
Hey
Hey Yiming
mom
Can you lend me some more money
The data on the 18th
I watched
All conditions are pretty good
But i think
A little older
I hope so
Best age
No more than forty years old
OK, I'll wait for your news
Ok
Who are you calling
My exclusive matchmaker
what
I'm on a blind date website
VIP member registered
Exclusive matchmaker one-to-one service
Don't you say
This paid tens of thousands of dollars
Really different
The person he introduced to me
It's either rich or expensive
I think you can also try
No time, no energy
Not interested
I'm serious
Even if you can't find anyone
Live together
You can find someone to partner with you to start a business
Is it right?
what happened to you
Chen Yiming transferred you 800,000
He still has a conscience
Do you have white wine in your house
I'm going to die
I'll find it for you
Find it for you
If not handling other business
Please remove the bank card in time
Yu Wei
Mom wants to talk to you
Discuss something
Ok
Let's not buy shoes
Wear the old ones first
But the teacher said
My dancing shoes are broken
Need a new one
Mom will help you make up
The kids are all wearing new dancing shoes
The old dancing shoes are patched up
Can dance
I want new dancing shoes too
Mom doesn't have enough money
Didn't you just withdraw the money?
This is my father's hospital fee
And your kindergarten tuition
And our electricity bill
Water, gas, telephone
Daddy is not
Do you have money every month
Dad is hospitalized and has no money
Is your money enough?
Don't worry about it
Mom i have money
What money do you have
I eat first today
Do exercises first
Teacher rewarded
Can be in the fairy tale house
Buy crayons buy bows
This lottery can't buy dancing shoes
I don't need dancing shoes
Mom, this money is for you to spend
Future mother
I must buy it for you
Many new dance shoes
Ok
what do you mean
Go! Go! Go
I have never seen you like this
You are simply
Let me post money to help you decorate
Twenty six five
Miss Li
You are the boss
You are such a piece of fifty cents
Bargain with me
Is this interesting
Brother, I know it's boring
I want to wave my hand boldly
OK, that's it
But the money in my hand is not allowed
Don't say it's a fifty cents
I am a penny now
I want to break the two halves of flowers
Then we have to make money
Have to eat too
Now order a decent box lunch
It's fifteen yuan each
I ate eight yuan for lunch
Miss Li
How much can you pay?
My renovation budget
Only three hundred thousand
This price
All Shanghai
No decoration company can do
lowest
Five hundred and eighty thousand
Three hundred and two thousand
I knew it
I won't come
Isn't this taking time?
Manager Chen
President Wang
Why are you staying up late lately?
No
How about Siyu
we broke up
or
How about I ask her again
You guys have a good chat
no need
It's fine now
Both of us
All relieved, all relaxed
It's not easy for you to look at
Maybe I still pay
Just not used to it
Get used to it
I'm here, Mr. Wang
Ok
Yiming
Want relief
Really let go
If you want to find someone to solve
I'm here
Thank you, sister Ziru
I go first
Here here can be finished today
Over here
Rest assured
Anyway at the end of this month
Definitely finished
Come, let me give
Boss Li
here
Siyu sister
Zhizhi
there
Speak quietly here
Cleaner
How do you dress
Same as migrant workers
I am a migrant worker now
These jobs
Don't have to do it yourself
Save money by doing it yourself
What does the decoration company do?
My money
The decoration company doesn't even make a profit
No answer
I can only find workers by myself
Lead
can you
No money
Anything
Why are you looking for me
Nothing
I just came to see you
need some help
I still have
One million funding gap
How about you make up for me
I am teasing you
Miss Li, help
coming
You go busy
Then I don't care about you
You pay attention to safety
it is good
Mr. Pan
Ok
You are looking for me
Nothing
Just sorted the cabinet
Found something
Special touch
Ok
This
look carefully
This tie is yours
mine
you forgot
At the beginning
Emerald was established soon
Going to visit a leader
You take this tie
Untie from my neck
Tie me
You still said that
Mr. Pan
You are the face of emerald
It's okay if we are sloppy
You must be glamorous
I seem to be impressed
Then the business was successful
I bought a lot of ties
But this one alone
Keep it
Reluctant to return you
It records
Your contribution to Emerald
and also
The friendship of working hard together
That seems to be
More than ten years ago
Yes, more than ten years ago
that time
I bring a technician
In the lab
Boil all night
How about you
Bring the sales team
Run across China
Have today's family business
I remember that
I went to Zhengzhou on a business trip
Before departure
Your hair is all black
Less than a month
Turned white when I came back
I also remember
Three hundred and sixty-five days a year
You have been on business for 300 days
More than sixty days left
You are working overtime most of the time
Just because of this
Your ex-wife divorced you
Right
We are
Have paid too much
Correct
We all paid too much for Emerald
But your friendship
No one can replace it
Yes
sit
We have been busy these two years
Communication is less than before
The company is getting bigger
The market has changed again
We started to disagree
Fang Zhan, it's okay
Here with me
in my heart
You have always been the best brother
Partner
Yes
It used to be so difficult
Let's all carry over
Maybe more difficult later
Let's carry it together, okay
Mr. Pan, tell the truth
I'm a little tired
why
today
Too difficult to do business
We invested hundreds of millions
All year round
Can only earn a few million
Ugly
Buy a house
Appreciation is faster than this
Fang Zhan Fang Zhan
When we invested in this industry
Is it just to make money?
If to make money
I was
It's time to sell the patent
If to make money
You could invest
Any field
We are not done
Our dream
still remember
Was it our slogan back then?
Industry Excellence
China's first
World leader
We did it
One more step
Is the number one in China
Are you going to retreat this time
I
I know Fang Zhan
I know
You have worked so hard these two years
I am anxious
Made you feel wronged
Fang Zhan
I promise you that
I will pay attention later
Own working attitude and way
I promise
Mr. Pan
Actually okay
Lvbao has come to today
Not easy
We must not give up
Let's continue
Ok
Two days later
I plan to apply to the board of directors
Discuss Emerald III again
Proposal for two more production lines
I hope you support me
same as before
Ok
How is Liu Yang
There are a few more indicators
Did not come down
The doctor said I will live for a while
I asked
This disease
Can't be anxious, can't be tired
Have to be raised slowly
How are you
Hello, Xiao Liu. Long time no see
Auntie just paid her salary
Yuwei, order whatever you want
Aunt
Do you have a lot of money
Auntie also wants
Have a lot of money
Then you share it with mom
What did Yuwei say?
When we eat fruit
The teacher said
Children who can't finish eating
Can be divided
For children who are not enough
It's not the same thing
Aren't you out of money
Yu Wei
No more
Give you another date
Let's see
Xiaoling
Who let me
I knew you when I was twelve
thank you
Thank you
It's not a big deal
Buy less clothes
Let Siyu for a while
I'll get you some too
Don't, don't tell her about it
how
You didn't find
Is she worried about money now?
Doesn't she have a lot of money?
I went to see her the other day
No wonder
She now even has hand cream
Have to rub me
Join my team
Trust me
Within three years
In the vehicle battery service market
We will be
Leading brand
Great
See you in our company next Monday
Won another talent
Where did you just say
Let me say okay today
In order today should be my please
I want to join the team
Row
Which company
OK, I get it
Ok
Okay, thank you
Siyu
My friend told me just now
During the Emerald Tender Disturbance
A company called Langfei
Spent 40,000 to buy the navy
Create public opinion unfavorable to Emerald
Come in
Mr. Chen, your takeaway
it is good
I didn't order takeaway
You ordered for me
not me
OK, you go ahead
Eat well and exercise
Take a good rest and work hard