[ To Dear Myself ]
[Ep1]
Excuse me
Coming
Get ready, everyone
Be careful
Ok, let's begin
Excuse me...
[Lyrics]
Take a knee
Flowers
I do
What are you doing?
It's...
What about my ring?
When will I give Siyu the ring?
Ring, later
It's in the drone, and it's under you control
You give me the drone
Exactly
Then I will give Siyu
Take a look
Ok
Everyone, have a break
How's it?
I have checked all data about Zhang Yanzhou
He is trustworthy and loyal to his friends
But he can't resist money
I think we still have hope
It's five million yuan
You need to get the order back
I will try my best
Sister Yuan
So, in your opinion, who leaked the price to Qiji?
No idea, but I am trying to find out
After we find out, I will beat him to hell
Don't worry
I'm tougher than you
Just win Qiji
I will invite you to spa
Ok
Sister
We have no appointment
They don't let us in
Sister, people of Feiyu went in just now
Sorry, you can't enter without an appointment
Can you...
Hello
I'm from Beijing Feiyu Battery
We have an appointment with Mr. Zhang of Qiji Group
We have a meeting at 14:00
What should we do?
Fifteen minutes to go
Data
Hello
The number you have dialed is busy now
I'm from Beijing Feiyu Battery
We have a meeting with Mr. Zhang at 14:00
My colleagues arrived ahead of me
Yes, this way please
Thank you
Can you do us a favor?
Only one time
Sorry, I can't
Just a phone call
Sorry
You can't enter without appointment
Learn the piano
Ok
The number you have dialed is busy now
Sorry
The subcriber you dialed can not be connected
Any problem?
I am here to see Mr. Zhang
You are...
I'm from Feiyu
I have told you to wait in the reception room
Mr. Zhang went to the bathroom
He will be back soon
Thank you
Wait a moment
I think this is pretty good
Brother Yiming
Where is sister Siyu?
No idea
No idea?
She went to the company at noon
She has something to do
Then she doesn't answer my call
Such an important day
Why don't you let her ask for leave?
I just want to give her a surprise
I didn't give her any hint
Haowen
What?
Siyu's sister is here
Right at the subway entrance
Help me pick her up
Recommend her to me on Wechat
Ok
I'm the best at picking up beauties
What else?
Don't make troubles
It depends on whether she is beautiful
Don't worry
Thank you
Hello there
Did you go to the wrong toilet?
Yes, I want to talk to you
Hello, Mr. Zhang
You are...
My name is Li Siyu
I'm the sales manager of Lubao Battery
We have terminated the contract
You should contact the legal department if any
Mr. Zhang, please give me 15 minutes
Thank you
Ok, make an appointment with my secretary
If I can make an appointment, I won't be here
Out of my way
Mr. Zhang
With Qiji Electric Vehicle's sales speed and profit margin
you can make 2000 yuan every minute
But if you give me fifteen minutes
I promise, I can help you make more 50 million
Listen
I won't make any deal with Lubao
Fifteen minutes later
Maybe you will change your mind
I will call a security guard now
It will take at least 10 minutes that security guards
receive a call, come up and drag me out
Ok
Mr. Zhang
Let's begin now
I never make business in the toilet
We can talk in your office
Baby, what are you doing now?
Remember to eat on time
Baby, do you miss me?
Do not be angry
You will get wrinkles
Let me tell you
I found a good food store
Little fairy
I love you the most
I'm in a meeting now
I'll go back to see you later
Be a good girl
That's all
Bye bye...
Yiming
I am speechless about your sister-in-law's appearance
She doesn't look like Li Siyu
They are sisters by law, not by blood
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I thought Li Siyu's sister would be pretty
Forget it...
I rented the sports car for nothing
Leave her alone
Otherwise, I can't explain it to Li Siyu
Don't worry
I won't need even if it's free
Alert
Talk to you later
I will have some incident with a goddess
You...
Hello
Xiaoling
You have fifteen minutes
Countdown starts
Mr. Zhang
Yunhai's contract price is 1% higher than yours
But the final strike price is 5% lower than ours
It's our sales team's practice
For the first time customers
we will give the full sales commission as thanks
It's also true for our previous cooperation
I do not care
You can't offer them the price lower than mine
This batch of batteries is only 200,000 in total
It will make no difference for your costs and product pricings
But it ruined my trust in you
This is our negligence
We should have told you before we signed with Yunhai
Enough, stop it
It's too late to apologize
Mr. Zhang
If we can shorten the delivery time, is it ok?
No need
Mr. Zhang, what if I list you as the privileged partner?
Sit still
My car is full of power
A hundred kilometers in 3.2 seconds
I didn't use this car for a long time
I put it in the club
Actually I can put it in my house
Downtown villa
You know the garage is small
It can only hold three cars
So I often drive those three cars
If you still ignore me, I will run away with someone else
Open air conditioning
Usually I don't drive this car
Lubao III?
Lubao III can be put into production ahead of schedule
And its indicators far exceed any other battery's in the market
Your research finally succeeded
If you install Lubao III ahead of them,
the output value of Qiji's full line of products will
increase by at least 50 million next year
What about the price?
I will give you the lowest price
What about Yunhai Group?
Lubao III is the new production line
Production capacity in the first three months
is only ten million
If you can buy the first order of 10 million,
we won't find another buyer
You want to get the order of five million back
You even want me to place another order of 10 million
Yes
Time's up
You can go
Mr. Zhang
Thank you Mr. Zhang
Sister Siyu, how's it?
I failed
Are you ok?  -Sister
Sit...
I am fine
Give me thirty seconds
Xiaotian
I need the earliest flight ticket to Guangzhou
Ok
Xiaojia
Contact Yunhai Group's purchasing department
Tell them I need to see them as soon as possible
Ok...
Manager Li
Mr. Zhang wants to talk to you
Li Siyu's wedding ring
So small
Xiaoling
You should take a break
I'll go, check it out
What's going on?
No idea
What happened?
What's the problem?
I don't know
Husband, go, have a look
Hi
Can you hold it for me?
Ok
Thank you
Can you?
Go
How long can you fix it?
I don't know
Let me check it out
What the hell, you know nothing
Can you do it?
Today it's his proposal
It's my brother's lifelong happiness
No
It never happened before
Check it out
Ok...
Have you tried the long-endurance?
Not yet
Check long-endurance first
If it's ok, check the operating system
If it's ok, it must be the problem of interactive system
Indeed
It's the interactive system
Can you fix it in half an hour?
At least three hours
Three hours?
It will get dark
Do you know why I aim at Yunhai?
Because Yunhai's two largest shareholders used to work for you
They stole your core technology
in an immoral way before they left
I have a batch of defective batteries
Not much, only 100,000
I hope your group can help me transfer it to them
I will reward you a million yuan as return
Mr. Zhang
You have a minute
I admire you
But not because Qiji Group's all-time high performance
or you are a ranked billionaire
But because you have said
you will have a conscientious electric car group
I often encourage myself with this
I will be a conscientious saleswoman
Well said
Conscientious saleswoman
Mr. Liu will help me see Feiyu
And I need to see all directors of each department in my office
Ok
Including manager Liu from the contract department
No problem
I will keep the previous order of five million
And I will place another order of ten million
Brother Yiming
She is in Wuxi now
Wuxi?
One of our customers cancelled the order
Our company sent her to persuade the customer
Can she come back on time?
As I know, they will arrive at Hongqiao at 16:44
Manager Li
I think we should have lunch togther
Thank you
Boyfriend is waiting for me
Ok
But I am curious about one thing
If I had rejected you
what would you do next?
Before your secretary came out,
I was booking flight ticket to Guangzhou
Go to Yunhai Group?
Yes
Sell all the batteries to them?
But as far as I know, their purchase plan of this year is done
I need to have a try
We have a good reputation after all
And your 10% liquidated damages
If I give this to them,
I think they will be interested
Manager Li
Have you considered changing the environment?
What do you mean?
Come to Qiji
You will have a satisfactory position and salary here
You want me to sell electric cars?
Yes
You are a talented saleswoman
Thank you for your compliment
But you are so greedy
You just bought our company's 15 million batteries
You even want to poach the sales manager
How about it?  Think about it
How about this?
After your purchase reaches 200 million,
we can talk about the contract
Ok, a deal
A deal
Oops, damn it
I'm sorry
I was talking with my client
Finished it?
Yes
What seems to be the problem?
Yes, it's very important
But it's all ruined
Where are you now? I will go to see you
Bye
Stomachache again
Want some medicine?
Ok
Sister, are you ok?
I am fine
Sister Siyu
You are so awesome
You can turn the table
Honestly
In our sales department
you are the best on talent, character
and work attitude
Where did you put sister Yuan?
Don't talk nonsense
I forgot it
But sister Yuan has been in charge of the sales department
on behalf of director for over half a year
But we don't know her personnel appointment
What's going on?
You guys
Stop thinking about too much
Sister Yuan becomes the director
It's a matter of time
Yes
Sister Siyu, bye
Sister Siyu, see you tomorrow
Sorry
I didn't mean it
My phone is muted
You know
Business can't be interrupted
I called you right after it's over
Wow, all my favorite
Yiming
You are so considerate
Ubuntu 15.04
Correct
Delete the upgrade system
Reinstall it
It only takes forty minutes
Really?
Have a try
Ok
If something goes wrong, you can't blame me
Great
It's all UAV's basic knowledge
What AV?
UAV
Everything is ready
We are waiting for the heroine
Ok
You are so good to me
How can I repay you?
Say it, I promise you all
I am driving
Sit still
Let's go
Let's go home now
No
I have arranged it
What arrangement?
Watch movie
Shooting a movie is better than watching a movie
It's an exclusive movie
It will be a pity if you miss it
Fine
You have a better mood now?
No
You cheated my feelings
Your phone is not muted at all
Your line was busy
Then it's completely out of touch
I was on the phone with sister Yuan
At least you could pause
And answered my phone
It's almost over
Why you didn't call me back?
I have told you
The client only gave me fifteen minutes
Really?
It's mine-clearing?
Whatever
No
I don't like it
Your phone rang
Next second, you were out of touch
A busy line
What do you want to say?
Nothing
I feel it weird
And I am worried about you
Weird or worried?
Worried
I have said it many times
I am not a kid
I know how to deal with the bad guys
Don't need to be worried
Ok...
Stop being angry
I know I am wrong
I should have texted you
Don't worry about me anymore
I will remember to reply in the future
Let me tell you
I'm worried, and that's not all
And I feel it weird
What's all this?
I have arranged everything
Then my girlfriend left on a business trip without saying a word
Went to Wuxi
You didn't answer my calls
Chen Yiming, can you stop it?
What?
You always work overtime
Your body can't stand it, ok?
You want me to resign, right?
It's a good option
I can support you
I can support myself
Why do I have to rely on you?
You can have an easy work
Enough
Am I wrong?
No, you are not worried about me at all
You just don't believe me
Don't be so ridiculous
I never mean that, ok?
Pull over
Siyu...
What's wrong with you?
Why do you lose your temper?
I'm tired
I need some rest
We haven't watched the movie yet
Not interested today
Sister Siyu
Xiaoling was having a fight
It's ok, Xiaoling
Stop it
Stop it, Xiaoling
Xiaoling...
You lied to me
Hit me?
Are you crazy?
What do you want?
Xiaoling felt bored, waiting there
So she asked someone to teach her to use a drone
So it becomes like this
I don't know it's out of control
or it's deliberate
The drone smashed Lanke's car
Then Lanke's car drove into the sister's car
Xiaoling, Lisa and Lanke fought against one another
Excuse me
Hello
Brother Yiming originally prepared the proposal for you
So romantic
Zhizhi
You should go now
It's ok. I'll stay here
Liu Yang, you should go
I'll go to see you later
Fine
Got it
Ok, I get it
Thank you
Siyu
Lawyer Liu called me
We'd better settle this in private
Lanke hit Xiaoling and pushed Zhizhi
Xiaoling attacked first
How's it?
Will you accept mediation?
Yes
She beat me like this for nothing
I won't accept
All because you stepped in
Xiaoling
Here is the police station
She's still so fierce
I will sue you today
I will sue you
Calm down
Don't stop me
Stop it
Come back
Xiaoling is Siyu's sister
You are my brother
We are a family
Of course I can't calm down
Don't mess it up?
I want to go home...
What's wrong, baby?
You send Liu Yang home first
What about Gu Xiaoling?
The kid is here
She can't stay here
Wait a while
Ok  -Come
Stop it
You want to make it worse?
Want to sue me, right?
So be it
You want to be detained?
What about your job?
How can you find a boyfriend?
Your parents-in-law will look down on you
Listen
Compensation is the best solution
No
Do you listen to me?
How?
Will you listen to me?
Lanke
I was curious why Xiaoling likes you
Finally I know now
I saw your photo on Xiaoling's phone
Pretty handsome
But today I find you are more handsome
Come, sit
Lanke
You used to date Xiaoling
So just forget this
Lanke, think
If your father knows this,
what would he think?
He is a famous entrepreneur
He hates your tidbits so much right?
Lanke is beaten like this in public
What about our reputation?
Things become like this
Xiaoling and Lanke are over
So you think, who will be Lanke's next girlfriend?
What do you mean?
It's her fault that Xiaoling hit you
But you step in between them
It's also a fact
We are just friends
The drone took the photo
Lisa
As I remember, you are a live broadcaster, right?
If someone uploads the photo online,
I wonder what your fans will think of you
Don't threaten me
No
I am thinking for you
You are an internet celebrity
If your reputation is ruined because of this,
it will be so bad
Lanke, I will do as you say
Ok, it's over
But you need the repair our cars
Ok
Are you still at the police station?
Wait for me
I will pick you up right away
Want to go for a walk?
I'll be with you tonight
Lisa
Thank you for getting rid of the garbage
Let's go, Xiaoling
I will send you back
Let's go
You should have seen this coming
Get away from me
I helped you
None of your business
Let's go, let me send you back
No need
Driver, be careful
Zhizhi, let's go
We will send you back
I'll take a taxi by myself
It's ok
We can send you back
No need
Yiming, how's it going?
Where's Xiaoling?
She went home
How can you let her go home alone?
She needs someone to be with her most now
Don't worry, she's strong
By the way, brother Haowen
Are they home?
Yes, don't worry
You have an activity, right?
Why they are home?
Yuwei is tired
She wants to go home
Liu Yang told me to send them back
Damn it
I have to go back now
What happened?
Today we had a parent meeting for an important thing
Yuwei is finally admitted to the kindergarten
She can't be despised
I see
Don't worry
Bye
Bye bye
Thank you today
You are not mad at me?
I can only be angry for two hours
No, it's my fault today
I didn't do it well
I didn't control my emotions
I also have some fault
I did not expect you would prepare such an exclusive movie
Yeah I...
I wanted to give you a surprise
Now it's a spoiler
And I turned the romance movie into an action movie
Siyu
Yiming
You won't want a midnight show, right?
I...
Siyu, actually I...
Are you really ready?
You forgot to take this
Thank you
Can I call you sister?
Sister, I'm so sorry
Your car was hit
And we wasted you so much time
You are such a good peacemaker
No, I am just reasoning
Sister, I want to add your Wechat
No need
I have your phone number
I'll call you if necessary
Ok
I will pay all damage cost for your car
Goodbye
Actually only you are not ready
I mean, it's late at night
Police station entrance
We just finished a conflict
It's a little inappropriate
And I hope it will be a romantic reminiscence
Not like this
Ok
Well...
I will pick another time
But don't worry
I will give you the best moment
Yiming, thank you
Sleeping?
Why didn't go to the parent meeting?
Yuwei is so sleepy
She will be so annoying in the parent meeting
You have to go
It's not easy to be admitted to the kindergarten
We should go
I have an important report tomorrow
If something goes wrong, nothing could make up for it
Ok...
Report...
Is Gu Xiaoling's matter resolved?
Everything can be solved when we have sister Siyu and brother Yiming
Did Chen Yiming finally make proposal?
No idea, I just left
I married you without roses or diamond ring
You don't like these
All women like these
Now these are not important
The most important now is Yuwei
Yuwei's education
Yuwei's kindergarten
We can't be absent from the parent meeting
Come again?
Ok...