[To Dear Myself]
[Ep20]
Come in
Director Li
Xiao's Group demands the shipment now
As I remember, it's next month
Yes
But their production plan changed
They hope we can cooperate with them
What does production department say?
I asked them
They said no
So I will give you the cargos that I should give General Group
General Group?
It's your client
Yes
They are my old friends
So I know them
They won't mind if the shippment is half a month late
Thank you, director Li
Well
What about Redrose battery car?
I have talked with the vice president for over a month
But I have no breakthrough yet
Wait
This is my analysis of Lubao in battery car market
I hope it can help you
This is exactly what I need
Remember to keep it secret
Ok, thank you director Li
Back to work
Sister Siyu
I worked for sister Yuan before
So I was worried if you would trust me
But I really didn't expect you didn't hold the grudge
Even, you help me a lot
I didn't like you
But now I have changed my mind
Actually I am sister Yuan's apprentice too
We have some misunderstanding in the end
But I still remember sister Yuan's help
What I do now is what I have learnt from her
Actually you have a lot in common
Of course
You have more differences
Well
What is sister Yuan doing now?
She runs a restaurant
Mind Blowing
Because she wants to give her son hot soup and rice anytime
And the restaurant is close to the school
It's convenient to communicate with teachers
Back to work
Be careful
Find a thick blood vessel
I have told you
Find a thick one
You give her so many needles
So much blood
Can you do it?
What are you doing?
Let me tell you
It's swollen
You give her three shots
It's ok
It's ok...
Sorry, lady
Tell me anything you need
We want another nurse for the injection
She has no problem with injection
She is new here, maybe a little nervous
Your cooperation is appreciated
Ok...
I am ok
It's flesh, it hurts
Change her, now
Ok, wait a minute
I'll change her
Let me see
She gave you three shots
What the hell?
I am fine
No, look
Zhizhi, recently you need to work, take care of Yuwei
You even need to take care of me
You must be tired
It's ok
I'm your liability
Mom, I'll get you some water
To cleanse your body
No...
I haven't taken a shower for days
I am smelly
I won't mind it
No
I mind it
See, my mom died young
I didn't have the time to take care of her
I want to do something
When did your mom die?
When I was 19
Sorry to hear that
I used to contradict her
So sometimes I contradict you
I hope you won't take it personally
I won't
Stop it
Come, take a seat
Talk to me
Zhizhi
Don't give up on your disease
You still have hope
Health system is very advanced now
We can go to see an expert in the famous hospital
You will be ok
Mom, you are still thinking about grandson?
Of course
It's not just for our family
It's also good for you, silly girl
Mom, boys and girls are the same important
Filial piety is the most important thing
Aunt Wang on the bed next door
She has three sons
What's the use of it? None of them are filial
Good for nothing
Yeah
We didn't have enough money to pay the surgery fee this time
Then my cousin paid the rest
Cousin?
Cousin
Liu Yang often told me, his dad died young
You raised Liu Yang and his sister alone
I think few men in this village are better than you
Mom, we are women
Why do you look down on women?
No
I didn't look down on women
I think it's better to have a son
After I came in the hospital, I thought a lot
We can't change anything after we die
Ok
From now on, you can do whatever you want
Mom
Zhizhi, I made many mistakes
Don't take it personally
Don't hate me
No, I won't
Where's Liu Yang?
I didn't see him all day
He is working
Working?
He has many female colleagues
Many young female colleagues
He worked with those little girls together all day
You
You should keep eye on him
Mom, I believe in Liu Yang
It's ok
Let me cleanse you
Fine
As I know, the leaders are discussing
about the candidates for deputy director
It's you if everything works fine
If I become the deputy director
you should take some credit
I didn't do anything
You don't have to do anything
Stay with me like this
Then things are getting a lot easier
Are you ok? Brother Yang
Nothing
Hypoglycemia, perhaps
Come, take some rest
Sit, be careful
Brother Yang
You lost some weight recently
Are you too tired?
My mom is hospitalized
I have a heavy responsibility
Of course I am tired
I really want to take care of aunt for you
Fortunately she will be discharged soon
I want to visit her today or tomorrow
I will have no chance after aunt is discharged
It's not convenient for me to visit her in your house
I met aunt once
We had a good chat
You don't want aunt to be happy?
Ok
Focus, be a good boy
Settle the bill
Yes
Good boy
53 in total
You still need to pay 3 yuan
No
It should be 50
16, 14
The prices of these two dishes have gone up
Just charge me 50
I'm so sorry
It's small business
I can't
I am here to eat every day
I think you can give me a little discount, right?
No discount, 53
I will never come again
Sister Yuan
What are you doing here?
I know you have a restaurant here
So I am here to see you
Now you are here
You can go now
I didn't eat yet
I want to order Shuangjiao noodles
It's sold out
Noodles with spicy sauce
No more
Still mad at me?
I am mad at myself
I see others wrong
Sister Yuan
We have known each other for seven years
We had the bad time in the last three months
But prior to that, you are my best mentor
We are best friends
The last three months erased all the past
Both of us have responsibility in the last three months
At least I didn't initiate it
Now we can't make it clear that who has more responsibilty
and who hurts the one more
I think we should let bygones be bygones
You become the sales director by hurting me
Now you want to let bygones be bygones?
Li Siyu
Are you too greedy?
Sister Yuan, I didn't hurt you
When I become the sales director,
we can take about let bygones be bygones
Sister Yuan
It's closed, you can go now
28%
22%
This share
It's valid within 24 hours
Otherwise we are really done talking
President Wang
Is there anything I can do?
No, you can get off work now
Ok
You are working overtime now
President Wang
Time to get off work
I have some mails
Then I will go home
Didn't have dinner yet?
I forgot to eat
I didn't eat, either
Let me invite you to dinner
Ok
Well, wait for a minute
Give Siyu a call
If it is convenient, she should come
Siyu
Siyu need to work overtime today
What a pity
As I know, leaders are discussing to
promote Liu Yang as deputy director
Wu
Now or never
Do not worry
I began to take action after Lubao won the bid
But why there is no update?
Soon
Before you came
my negotiation with Lubao reached a deadlock
But your research report broke the deadlock
You even pushed the negotiation forward
So I still played a little role
I shouldn't have invited you to dinner long ago
Thank you for what you have done for the company
President Wang, thank you
Thank you for providing me with a good platform
Thank you
Yiming
You did the latest work plan of planning department?
Yes
I have a little conflict after reading it
Tianyi Group is a bit lethargic now
But your plan subverted people's knowledge of
the traditional financial industry
Of course
If Tianyi Group does not change,
we will have no big development direction
But if we change according to your plan,
it's a bit risky
President Wang, it seems risky
Actually it will bring a huge profit
In China, the vast majority of financial institutions
didn't regard the brand as strategic asset building
So who takes this step first will be the winner of the whole market
Don't rush to convince me
I need to think about it
Ok
But one thing I am sure
It may be wrong that you are planning director
With your talents, insights and perspective
you should have a bigger platform
President Wang, I will drink this up
Drink less...
Waiter, we need more dishes
No need, president Wang
It's enough here
Siyu likes some dishes
You should take them back for her
Really no need
I tonight...
I and Siyu tonight...
We won't see each other tonight
Won't see?
You can send it to her
No need, president Wang
Actually, we lost contact for a week
Why?
Sorry
It's not the question I should ask
No...
I think...
No matter how much intimate we are
we still have the different opinions sometimes
What's wrong?
Siyu is very competitive and subjective
I gave her advice
Sometimes people will think she can
resort to every possible way for her sales performance
But she...
But she thinks I said so because of my selfishness
I had my own purpose
Pan Zhiyong gave too much pressure on her?
Yes
Mr. Pan now presses her with financing and sales performance
even Lubao's future
She is under unprecedented pressure now
But...
But no matter how much pressure,
we should have principles and bottom lines
I agree
Don't worry
Don't force her
Give her some time
Siyu is a smart girl
She will understand
Sorry, president Wang
I drank a bit more today
I talk so much
Eat
Ok
Good bye
Thank you
Don't need me to send you home?
It's ok
I will go now
See you tomorrow
I think we can reply Pan Zhiyong now
800 million, 25%
Won't
He won't let the negotiation break down
He is very short of money now
Correct
His pressure is much bigger than we thought
Ok
Hello, I'm Li Siyu, from Lubao
Mr. Tang, hello
Comparison data?
Ok, wait a minute
Manager Tang
Listen
18650 is 10.4 Wh
18650 is 11.2 Wh
21700 is 17.76 Wh
Ok, that's it
I will calll you back
Mom, your legs have some problems
So I bought you this
Tie this up
Then plug it in
It can massage you
It's heatable
How much is it?
No much money, over 300
Over 300, so expensive?
No...
I don't need it
I can massage legs with my hands
Refund the money
Don't waste money...
I...
No, it's not expensive
Liu Yang gave me the expensive vacuum cup
It's over 200
I asked for refund
But they only gave me the voucher
So I bought this with the voucher and 100 yuan
It's still over 300
It's ok as long as your legs feel better
Let's have a try
Come
How is it? Is it hot?
Yes
It's shaking
Aunty, massage?
I am here to see you with Xiaoling today
Yeah
Aunt, how are you feeling now?
I am fine, I am getting better
Thank you for coming
Bed No. 34, it's your turn
Ok...
Let me help you
Take this off
Be careful
Ok, you should talk
I have to do a little checkup
We should go with you
No need
The doctor is with me
You guys talk here
Let's go
Be careful
Bye
You guys talk here
Sit down, come...
Sit here
Come, give it to me
Aunt is under a good recovery
Yes
Come, sit
Sister Siyu
I have discussed with Liu Yang
We will pay the money in installments
I don't need it now
Take your time
After mom is discharged
I will invite you and Xiaoling to dinner with us
And brother Yiming
And your boyfriend
Why call so many people?
I will go with Xiaoling
No
Brother Yiming needs to come
I don't know if it's ok that I invite your boyfriend
I will ask Wei Shang if he has the time
You and Chen Yiming quarreled again?
Because of what?
Not a big deal
How long has it been?
The cold war for more than a week
More than a week, you think it's no big deal?
Stop talking about this
Xiaoling, I need to ask you a favor
You two are going to get married
Why are you still quarreling?
Please
Stop talking about this, ok?
Hello, Xiaoling
I'm in the company
No
You want to come here?
You are so nice, I can't quite get used to it
12:45
See you at the company gate
Don't be early or late
Ok
I will invite all of you to lunch later
Once in a lifetime
How about hairy crabs?
Ok
Thank you, brother Lei
Finally you are here
Your wife takes care of me and Yuwei
Mom
Wei, my workmate
Aunt
I come to visit you
Sit...
You are so busy
You don't need to come
I need to come no matter how busy
Aunt, you look so good
You are under a good recovery
Aunt Joe
See?
My daughter-in-law bought this for me
My daughter-in-law is nice to me
She treat me so well, she bought a lot of things for me
Great
Days ago, my son bought a vacuum cup for his wife
It's over 200 yuan
But she went to refund the money
She bought me this with extra 100 yuan
It's so warm and comfortable
It's called massager
So great
I want to have one
Aunt
I will wash you some fruit
Why do you bring her here?
She is kind so she is here to see you
You are not afraid to run into your wife?
Zhizhi is working now
You
You should broke up with her
Mom, what are you talking about?
What?
You are my son
I know you best
Mom, take a break
Zhizhi is sincere to you
But she replaced imported drugs with domestic drugs to save money
It's a fact
I can't get over it
I asked the doctor to change the imported medicine
Imported medicine is so expensive
It can't be reimbursed
You told the doctor to change it?
Yes
Zhizhi didn't know about it
Why do you give me that look?
Let me tell you
After this hospitalization, I know she is such a good wife
You have to cherish her
Break up with the little girl
You should live a simple life with Zhizhi
Mom, it's not like what you think
What do I think?
Break up with her
Completely
What?
You want to make me angry?
No, mom
Ok, I get it, sit down
Aunt, have some fruit
My mom is a little tired
You should go back first
Aunt
Have a good rest
I have to go now
Thank you for coming here
Look, beauty
What beauty?
It's goddess
What's wrong, brother Lei?
Why is she blocking here?
Who?
Come for you?
Can you stop lying?
I don't believe she knows you
She is my ex-girlfriend
I have said, I have no feeling for her anymore
But she still pesters me
We have broken up for months
Later, I will go back to the company that way
You should tell her you didn't see me
Haowen, Lei Haowen
No... Keep your voice down
The hairy crabs are great today
Next time
Here you are
You are here to see me?
Nonsense, who else should I see?
Kept you waiting
So what do you think?
It's windy outside
There is a cafe there
We can have some coffee
Lead the way
Yes, madam
Is Chen Yiming abnormal recently?
What are you doing?
Take pictures
Stop it
Look, Xiaoling
Your mouth...
Yiming?
I haven't seen him for a long time
What is he doing now?
Work, of course
He works in a new company
They are going to get married
Why are they still quarreling like this?
Who said, no one can quarrel after engagement?
It's so abnormal that they didn't talk for a week
If we two quarrel
how long do you think is normal?
It's two matters
Why?
Both, one man and one woman
Let me give you a task
Yes
You don't even ask what the task is
Selling the soul or body
I am good at both of them
Mom
You are here
How are you feeling today?
Give it to me
Pretty good
I made you fish soup
You eat now or later?
Later
I'm not hungry
Sit down
You are so tired, you need some rest
It's ok
Zhizhi, take a break
Leave it to me
I also steamed you a squab
As I know, it can treat heart disease
Squab?
It's not cheap, right?
As long as it can cure your disease
Someone came to visit you today?
Liu Yang's workmates came
I'll wash shopsticks and spoon for you
Give it to me, I will go
See, such a good wife
What else do you want?
Zhizhi
You didn't tell the doctor to change the medicine
I blamed you wrongly
Don't be angry, ok?
I'm sorry
My apology
You are so good at bullying me
Well, you can punch me as long as you want
Hello, Yayun
Are you in the company?
Wait for me after you get off work
I need to talk to you
Brother Yang
What happened to the legs?
A little pain
Maybe I walked too much recently
I'll buy you some medicine
No need
Yayun
I have something to tell you
Wait
I have a gift for you
What?
I made this by myself
I embroidered this by myself
For me?
So what do think of it?
Let me help you
It matches you well
I stayed up for several nights
Just buy one
Why bother?
No
I want to knit stitch by stitch
Embroider the stitches one by one
It's meangful
You should wear it when it's windy
Ok
Why hasn't Yiming come yet?
Here
Took you long enough
In such a hurry?
No game today, right?
So we brothers can't sit down and have a little talk?
What is our bromance?
Liu Yang's mom is still in the hospital
I am busy recently
We are here now, we should sit here for a while
Look
Such a nice man
Liu Yang
How is your mom doing now?
She is discharged
She will go back to hometown soon
Good to know
Talk about yourself
Thank you
What's happened between you and Siyu?
How did you know it?
Gu Xiaoling told me
Liu Yang
I think your company's bid
Li Siyu's approach is very problematic
What is the problem?
To avoid suspicion
she should withdraw from the bid
Yiming, you think too much about this
I am the leader of the bidding team
But I am for the logistics
Only experts have the final say
I can only be at the door when experts evaluate the bid
I can't even enter the door
But it's very risky
Risk is everywhere in our company
Unless you don't want anything
You have no desire
I think you can't blame her
I need to thank her
She paid my mom's hospitalization fee
I see
If you and Siyu quarrel because of this
Liu Yang has already expressed his opinion
It's over now
I think she can't do that
Why?
Yiming, you are great
But you are so sissy
So ridiculous
What are you talking about?
Am I wrong?
Think about the good side about Siyu
She has been with you for so many years
Did she spend your money?
She cries and laughs with you
She even pays the mortgage with you
She shares the down payment
A good girl like Siyu is so rare to see now
It's two different things
Why?
The same thing
We can't let Siyu...
Why it's us?
You...
You should make peace with her
Then you will begin a happy life
So I can give Xiaoling a good news
Tell her
You have no affair
No seven year itch
No phobia of marriage
You are just a little sissy
No, wait a moment
They think I have an affair?
Look at you
You are so abnormal recently
Their imagination is so amazing
They are women
Haowen
They didn't say anything about me, right?
You? Nothing