# Google translate version for your reference #
No way
Pink represents the princess
You connected a phone in two years
Never call
Now suddenly this request
Don't you think it's too much, I ask you
I want to be a princess
I say you are too much
Come, little queen
Come, little princess
I want ice powder
I want to eat shrimps I want to eat sugar people
Can't go
You have a peanut allergy
You can’t eat ice powder, you know?
And you
Already have cavities
Can't eat sugar
Is this good
Who of you can
Make dad laugh
Anyone can eat ice cream
it is good
Dad you smile
What are you two doing this is
Yuwei, what are you doing, Susan
what
What are you doing
I asked you what
Yuwei, what are you doing
Making faces
Smiled smiled smiled
Laughed
Ice cream ice cream
What's wrong with the two babies? This is
They want to eat ice cream
Then take them to eat ice cream
Go eat ice cream
go
ice cream
Auntie, where's my dad
To join the elderly choir
It is said that
You rejected that little news
You all know
I saw Aunt Luo
Said Xiaowen took you to the wedding room
So sincere
Why don't you cherish it so much
I am not the same person with him
Are you fine or stupid
Just sniff this condition
You do not want
Many people are rushing to get it
Everyone thinks differently
I plan for you
You are so old
Don't get married again
In the future only
Find those divorced
Aunt
I know you are doing me good
But my own business
I know
look at you
So smart
Just don't understand
Fortunately
I kept one hand
weekend
You go meet that
Uncle Jiang's nephew
and also
Student of Chairman Tong
I see
Conditions are good
What do you think
Let's eat together tonight
I want to accompany my parents tonight
Are you with your parents every day
Let the beautiful family stay alone
Lonely, empty, cold and dangerous
Just shut up you
I haven't seen your parents yet
No
Liu Yang
You speak so grounded
Can you
Let's talk something poetic
Ignore him
Maybe she is scared
After all, your two situations
Quite special
You can't make her afraid
Woman's courage
All given by men
As long as you give me an affirmation
My love has meaning
so
You should be
Sing more karaoke
Let's go
Go singing tonight
I want to bring Yuwei
How to bring children every day
Zhizhi is busy and I am free
You two
Did you get divorced?
Should I take my divorce certificate
Show it to you
You wear a wedding ring every day
Staring like this
How do I think you treat Zhizhi
I'm more concerned than before
you are right
I am right now to Zhizhi
This is how it feels
What about her to you
Less and less caring
That won't work
You have the means
What means
What does Zhizhi like
There was no rose at the beginning
No diamond ring
I'm so confused
Married you
You don't like these
How can women not like these
Yes
I should make up for her
propose
I can help you plan
Yes, let Yiming go
Yiming's proposal is the most experienced
is not it
I said if you can't speak
Can you just stop talking
I serve, I serve, I serve
Don't talk if you can't speak
Ok
Surrender
This kid coughs
Can't stop cough first
Should first resolve phlegm
right
What i said
Every time this Susan coughs
It's been a long time
It turned out that the medicine was not given
Look back
I use some Yuwei
I will send you more symptomatic medicine
If Susan coughs again
You give her a try first
That's great
father
what happened
Get the clothes on
I come i come
I go
I come
Auntie help you
Come baby
Come, help her get it
good or not
Come, take off your clothes
Come, reach out
okay
Give me milk tea
Thank you
Here, give me ice cream
So it won't
Stained clothes
Me too me too
it is good
Come
Okay, thank you
Got it wrong
Slow down
You have a good idea
Just have more life experience
Uncle, yes
Susan and I went to the door to watch the fish
sure
But can't go out
Oh, I see
Ah so good
I will take you there
Ok
Thank you
You're welcome
I just saw you answer the phone
Particularly unhappy
It's work
Yes
Susan's mother
she was
Getting married soon
Let Susan be a flower girl for her
I didn't agree. I quarreled a few words
How long have you been divorced
Three years
When Susan was one year old
She left with a foreigner
You take the kids alone
It's not easy
Very hard
I'm fine
But just think about it
A little wronged Susan
As long as the child does not lack love
Will not feel wronged
is it
What you say
I feel quite relieved
I am so relieved of myself
Thank you
how about you
Yes
Because of divorce
Nothing
It's okay if you don't want to answer
I shouldn't ask
nor
I'm not unwilling to say
On the surface
I broke up with her father
Because of the third party
But now I feel more and more
I am in marriage
There are also many problems
I think you are perfect
Me back then
I just want to be a good mother
Good wife
But i forgot
be the best you can be
until one day
All questions
You have to carry it by yourself
I just found
How powerless I am
no way
Everything has to start over
Then you alone
This is busy with work and with children
Actually it's not easy
Yes
Work pressure
Still scolded by customers
I'll apologize to you again
just kidding
Didn't stress you today?
Very happy today
Ok
I am also very happy
Li Siyu, where are you?
Sister, I miss you so much
I don't have a fish pond
I only have this beach
Do me on the beach
The only one
Is the sand sculpture good?
Sand sculpture
Li Siyu
Where is Li Siyu
do you know
I miss you so much
Miss you so much
I waited too anxiously
Li Siyu
You show up soon
Neuropathy
Li Siyu
I will be your cold spirit
I have all the materials ready for you
When are you
Come hug me
scared me
Why are you here
Although the angel investment
Rarely more than 30%
But i will
Give you 100% of mine
What do you mean
I don't care about your relationship
How is it defined
I want to tell you now
I was serious
I'm so serious
I'm serious enough to hope
Parents’ approval and blessing
I'm serious
Hope this relationship belongs
Forever
thank you
me too
Ziru
I stand with you
No matter what
I don't have any comparability
But one thing
I will never be less than you
Is my sincerity
Do not
Yes i have my problem
If you are worried
The age difference between the two of us
Worry about opinions between parents
I can now
Tell you clearly
I do not care
Even if
Is the closest person
Can't be shaken
My feelings for you
In a few days
My parents are leaving Shanghai
Before they go
I want to take them to a meal
Authentic Shanghai cuisine
I will send you the address when I arrive
It would be best if you can come
It's okay if you don't come
I respect your choice
it is good
let me see
Hey
You didn't work overtime today
Do you think I am Zhang Zhizhi
Work overtime every day
What are you doing
Keeping an empty boudoir alone, emptiness, loneliness and cold
He Mu who didn't talk to you
In one piece
People ten fifteen
Going to bed
I can't disturb people
How are you and xiaowen
Already made it clear
So fast
I have always been an activist
Don't be proud
I listened to my mother
She has arranged for you
Bigger event
Did you say
Birthday party for three uncles and granddaughters
Correct
I'm too hard, I'm so sad
And your worries about Li Siyu
old
Help me find a way
You
Really find a boyfriend
It disrupted my mom's plan
Where to find
That's harder
I didn't say really looking for it
You listen to me
There must be a way
What do you mean
By the time
I will send Lei Haowen to you
Isn't it enough?
It's easy for you
Lei Haowen listen to you
Don't care about this
Socks look good
Quite good looking
Give me a pair too
what
I just finished installing your ex boyfriend
I want to give Li Siyu again
Pretend boyfriend
Can you change someone
Wool
I can't have a lamb
is not it
Who will let you act well?
You come less
You are
The actor left behind
Oscar
I am still
What about the old drama with its own traffic
exactly
You, play rich second generation
More like a rich second generation
Didn't you say i am
Is it domestic counterfeit goods?
You already upgraded
Come on
Employing people forward, not people facing backward
Talking about people like you
Lei Haowen
Don't shame you
Are you helping me?
help
I remember
next Friday
When the third uncle and granddaughter day
You appear
Drive a good car
Start at 500,000
If you don’t have it, you can rent
Didn't that Porsche work last time?
No way, too exaggerated
Can't get past my parents
Your parents
Li Siyu's parents
You go get another one
Bag with logo
But not
The kind covered with trademarks
Is there any brand requirement
Not too low-key international first-line
Car package
remember
And your hairstyle and clothes
Also need to change a little
And your family background
Need to beautify
How to beautify
Young talents, returnees
What to beautify
I am not
Young talent
Ok
that
Your mother is your mother
Li Siyu's father is her father
right
Yes
Come, come, sit down
Sit down. Sit down
when will you arrive
Come, everyone, sit down. You're welcome
five minutes
sit down
Thinking about rain
Everyone is here, let's serve hot dishes
hold on
No one has arrived
Who else
My boyfriend
Never heard of it
That's right
You have friends
When did
Why don't we know
I don't even know
Parents don't know
Because not before
Determine the relationship
So there is no
Report to elders
Where is he from then
what does he do
How are the economic conditions?
Good person
He will be there soon
Your question
Let him answer
it is good
Then we have to take the exam
The elders will check for you
it is good
Siyu
coming
Elders
let me introduce
This is
Yes
Sorry, elders
We are late
I am thinking of rain
Grandly introduce
This is
Hello, elders
I am Siyu's boyfriend
Guan Xiaotang
First time meeting, please take care
It's him not him
Have you heard of
No no
it is good
Row
Sit down
You like to eat
What's this
I also have one
Ma, give me the bowl
I will serve you some eel
it is good
Your mother likes this dish the most
Yes i don't know
Less
it is good
Heart is too soft
It seems to be the name
Had eaten
Is it your own name?
it is good
Heart is too soft
You give me the teacup
You have more soup
Drink less drinks
Ah it's too sweet
it is good
It's gone
what happened
Surprised or not surprised
How could it be Guan Xiaotang
Lei Haowen's acting is too exaggerated
Don't worry
I changed him
I can't find anyone else temporarily
How did you find him
He added my WeChat
Why would he add you to WeChat
He is a great technologist
It’s not easy to add me to WeChat
You know i'm hiding from him
Why do you have to call him up?
Because i like to fight you
Since childhood
You let me go east, i want to go west
you
I didn't harm you either
I did exactly what you asked for
Customized
Guan Xiaotang
Although I'm a little younger
But he is
Very dedicated and passionate
Gu Xiaoling
Don't leave me
How about we video
I really want to see
Your face now
Aunty aunty
First time meeting
This is me for you
Small gift
thanks, thanks
I am Xiaoling's friend
My name is Lei Haowen
You can call me Haowen
I know, I know
My last name is Lei Haowen
Thunder billowing thunder
Xiao Tang
What does your family do
My dad does
Regenerative asset circulation business
Then after the business got bigger
Also stepping into other industries
right now
energy
Chemical industry
food
Finance is also doing
so smart
so amazing
My name is Lei Haowen
So many industries
Thunder billowing thunder
You lay it down
Hao Ran, righteous Hao
Particularly cultural
I'm telling the truth
I admire your role
True or false
Drive
Yellow hair girl eighteen changes
It's really longer and more beautiful
Thanks auntie
You are now
Princess White Swan
Siyu, your cousin's business
Then please
what
He will graduate from university next year
You help him
The group at Xiaotang's house
Find a good job
Let's talk about it next year
Siyu
Such good conditions
Don't let go
I know
Guan Xiaotang, right
Yes
Xiao Tang, this kid
How much did my daughter spend
Invited you
uncle
I am at my own expense
take it easy
I won't break through you
I'm really not an actor
You can't hide from me
Uncle, even if you are
Don't believe my infatuation
Should also believe
The charm of your daughter
You are not my daughter's food
uncle
But life is alive
Don't you have to taste it all
This word
Appetite for me
They had a good chat
Thinking of rain that
I'll give it to aunt and uncle
Go back first
Windy outside
You and Mr. Guan
You go and go around there
Right right right next door
There is a park ahead
Good good
I know
That line, uncle and aunt
It's windy outside, let's go first
Good walk around
Pay attention to safety Pay attention to safety
Thinking of rain, then we're leaving too
Good good
Don't worry, Mr. Guan.
I will give you
be careful
Go play go go around
Goodbye goodbye
Goodbye, let's go
Hurry up
Uncle, slow down
Still qualified
Your beard is too fake
Not sticky original
to be frank
Where did you graduate
Don't you have my resume
Did you graduate from Central Academy of Fine Arts?
Acting rich second generation is more like Lei Haowen
Who taught it
Not acting original
I don't know you yet
Who borrowed this outfit
And how much is the car to rent?
I turn back to WeChat to forward you
I don't need money
What do you want
I want you
Go back to shanghai
Go find a little girl
Finished the puppy love first
Come find me again
I'm an old driver
Although I look like a little fresh meat
But i have matured i
Let's go
Why go
Take you to the children's playground
I
I played for a long time in vain
Yiming, is it time?
Too late, no problem
Hurry up
it is good
Be careful, be careful
Ok
Flattened
It's okay, parents
You get in the car first
One Ming One Ming
Is this uncle and auntie?
uncle and auntie
I am Yiming
friend
My name is Wang Ziru
Originally said
I want to accompany you at noon
Have lunch
As a result, I kept meeting
Can't make it
I'm so sorry
it's okay no problem
I know you
Catching the train at noon
Said it must come
I can't explain it
It's okay, you are busy
uncle and auntie
Prepare some small gifts for you
uncle
Too polite
You are too polite
aunt
Sorry thanks
Thank you
I have to hurry back to the company
Going to a meeting
I can't give you away
Went to the train station
It's okay, you are busy, you are busy
Yiming, get in the car
Don't delay
OK, let's go, parents
Goodbye
Goodbye uncle
Goodbye aunt
Goodbye
Drive slowly
gone
Slow down
Ok
You see, I can't sit down
Looks a lot like
What looks like
Come on, enjoy it
Sister Li
Let's play, it suits you more
Just play
Come back to Shanghai with me
Since i'm back
Didn't plan to go back
Come on
You will be domineering tomorrow
But was bullied in the unit
Don't you feel wronged
I still feel embarrassed
Nice
Did you do it
We just met
You beat and scolded me
Unchangeable
That's your true shape
I know
You have been unable to make it through
I'm calling and Lubao's Kaner
Don't you just destroy the two companies?
It's ok
Let's break a few more companies later
I'm not so uncomfortable
Do you want to be beaten again?
look
Murderous
This is you
Yiming
Xiao Wang that girl is
Didn’t you say it?
Can i ask
Not talking
Just ask if you want
Where is Xiao Wang from?
What do her parents do
Yiming, this gift
But it's on my heart
The inscription on the inscription of Liquan in Jiucheng Palace
I like this bracelet so much
The condition is really good
Let me try
The inscription on the inscription of Liquan in Jiucheng Palace
I have been thinking about it for a long time
It's not bad
You look
Take a look, okay
Good-looking good-looking
that's nice
This is still
This this is the band
how do you know
My parents' preferences
I'm in your circle of friends
Look at the photos you sent
Copy Rubbings of Your Father
Your mother's jewelry is all jade
Don't know if i guessed right
you guessed right
My parents love it
Also very happy
You actually
There won't be much
The way you send them
Put a
May be awkward meeting
Become very brief
But also left them
deep impression
Are you blaming me
Yiming
I can predict
The trend of a stock
Can also control many things
But for feelings
I really don't have the ability
I'm not sure
Yiming
I don't care
I don't want to have a future with you
I don't know what to do
I know
Actually in love
I also have a lot of fear
We can learn together
work together
Ok we work hard together
I hope that one day
We can calmly
Meet them
Then you have to give me some time
it is good
Yiming
I hope you let go
Unnecessary self-esteem
Help me rebuild the Emerald brand
Alright
it is good
Auntie, take so many things
Hold hold
Too much to eat
You put it there, auntie
We do it ourselves
Take it back
You take it in the car and eat slowly
Are the characteristics of our place
This is for Xiaoling
Xiaoling, let me come, let me come
I sent it to Xiaoling
thank you
You help me ask Xiaoling
When is she
I should bring my boyfriend back
let us see
Yes, since it's set
Should have come long ago
Meet this father-in-law
Yes
deal
Siyu said
That man has already proposed
Xiaoling also agreed
Aunt dad
That one
Let's talk about Xiaoling
Stop walking in traffic jam
Yes yes yes you guys go
Be careful on the road
Drive slowly on the road
Then we go first
Uncle and aunt
Pay attention to your body
be careful
I will see you again
it is good
Bye bye thinking rain
Drive slowly
Money or not are second
The most important thing is to be nice to you
Although this Xiao Tang is a few years younger than you
But I know it hurts
Also good to you
Ok, deal
Auntie, listen to you
But he is in Shanghai
You are here
What are you going to do
In the future
Talk about it later
That won't work
This is a big deal
You said
Guan Xiaotang
Not mature yet
Siyu and that Xiao Tang are fine
That's for you
What do you mean
Tell me old man
Is it three missing one?
I'm coming i'm coming
Tell me this dead old man
Siyu, I think it's good
Auntie, let's go back first
You want to tell me what's going on
I really like this kid
You like it
Brother Lei, can you drive slowly
I'm afraid of death, Brother Lei
I'm still young, Brother Lei
I have billions of property to inherit
Lei Ge
parking
Let me drive
What are you going to do, Brother Lei
I do not know either
When is it
Don't know what to do
Bright killer
No killer
who said it
Really invincible
Take a step back
A little backward a little backward
No more no more
Play with you two
A little bit backward, win or not
The two of them can have fun
Yeah rare
Mother Yuwei
Ok
Do you think
Actually we two
Also quite agreeable
Maybe because of the child
The personality is quite similar, right?
I'll just say something
With you
I feel particularly at ease
Very warm
Last time I came back from Disney
I have been thinking about
one question
If the four of us can
If you start a family
Should be very happy
What do you think
Susan Papa
You can ask me to go
If you can
I call you Zhizhi
I
Haven't considered
this problem
The reason i am today
Ask this question
I just want to give you time to think about it
but
Don't worry about answering me
Take a moment to think about it
Enough
May I
Goodbye
Xiaoling
Almost
Forgot to give this to you
what is this
to ensure that
Our mutual rights
To ensure that the wedding goes smoothly
At the same time guarantee
Long-term stability of marriage
I made this
Prenuptial agreement
So heavy
A total of nine chapters and twenty-three items
Three hundred forty-seven entries
Includes politics, economy, religion
Emotional health education etc.
every aspect
At the same time before marriage
Stages of marriage
Planned
You say it again
I hope to be able to prepare before the wedding
Sign this agreement
Are you getting married or establishing diplomatic relations?
You take a look
I hope
On the next date
To this agreement
Communicate and communicate
Then next Wednesday night
0.2625
Still that western restaurant
See you at the old place
Ok
What are you doing
Frightened me
You are getting married
you've been drinking
you answer me first
What's up with you
you can not
Marry that robot
why
because I like you
But i don't like you
But you don't like him at all
Even if i don't like him
But it's impossible for me and you
How impossible
When you are in a bad mood
I can drink with you
You are in trouble
I can help you
You stay with me
You can wear slippers without makeup
I can make you laugh
I'll beat and scold as you like
When you need me
I won't shut down and sleep at all
Do you have money
you have
Is it a company valued at several hundred million?
Can you give me a sense of security
I have no money now
But i will have
I'm tired
I want to rest
Xiaoling
what are you doing
Don't you say today
You just can't go
I don't want to follow one
Drunk man talking
Xiaoling
Some things i don't get drunk
I can't tell you
Gu Xiaoling
I love you Gu Xiaoling
Can you be with me
You let go
But i don't love you