[To Dear Myself]
[Ep13]
Mom, listen
You should get all things, and at the entrance
You will see bus No.106 , ok?
Then mom
You need to take five stops
Only five stops
After you get off
you need to cross a zebra crossing
and cross another road
then you will get there, mom
Ok
Ok, be careful
Ok, don't worry
Yuwei
Be a good girl in class
Do you know?
Mom
I want dad to drive me there
Not today, Yuwei
I have work to do
Yuwei, be a good girl
Dad works very hard
You know?
You can't take her to school?
I want
I want to stay with you
I promised those moms
I can't stand them up
Ok, let my mom go
Ok... I will go
I'll go
Yuwei
Later I will take you to school
I will buy you some candy
Ok
Mom, Yuwei has cavities
She can't eat candy anymore
I just say it casually
If I don't say so, will she go with me later?
Be careful
I know
I have to go now, mom
Go...
Yuwei, good girl
Liu Yang
Huh?
I'll go by myself
Such a little girl
Why let her attend early education class?
Here, drink some water
Look at your dad
He used to play with dad chickens and ducks every day
He learnt nothing
Now he is a top talent
Mom
Yuwei's living environment is different from mine
What's the difference?
I think it's the same
You are wasting money
Zhizhi says, we should raise a girl in a rich way
In a rich way
She is going to drain up your money
Zhizhi
Stop frowning
Come, choose your clothes
Xiaoling, I had the fight
Will I invite troubles for sister Siyu?
You kept talking about this the moment you came in
So annoying
I'm just worried
Don't worry
Li Siyu is very resilient
Well, you need to keep an eye on Liu Yang
Zhizhi, come
Come, choose yourself
How about this?
No
Just this one
Otherwise you won't have one
Is it here?
Yes
Hello
We are here to attend class
Yeah
Here
Ok...
Come...
Follow the teacher
Hello
Hello, teacher
What's your name?
My name is Liu Yuwei
Hello, this is for you
Take it
You are...
I'm her grandma
Grandma
You need to wait in the waiting area
We are going to start class
Ok...
Yuwei, be a good girl
Don't waste money
Go
I outwear it
Harder
How's it?
Chest out
Shoulders back
Relax
Legs out
How?
Like this
Yes
Legs out
Crotch to this side
Belly in
Hurry, belly in
Remember you are not Yuwei's mom now
You are not Liu Yang's wife
Let alone the worker in Lubao
You are a beauty
Beauty
Look at the skin
So smooth
Eyes are so big and bright
Breast
Breast is not as big as mine
Waist
The waist is so slim
Long legs
Right?
Hands down
Look in the mirror
So charming
Is it me?
Of course it's you
Well
Hand down
Start learning English early
Can't be left behind from the starting line
Sure
Kids need to learn English early
How old is your kid?
Four years and a half months old
My kid is four years and eight months old
The class is so expensive
Over 20,000
So expensive
I don't know if the teachers are good
Just ask the kids
If they don't like the teacher, we will ask for refund
Ok
We can apply for refund?
Aunt, you don't know?
If we are not satisfied with the first day of class
we can ask for full refund, over 20,000
Over 20,000?
Aunt, you really won't let her finish the class?
Maybe you should ask for her opinion
No need
I have the final say, full refund
I have to go now
Ok?
Zeng, help her with the refund
Ok
Come, aunt, drink water
Ok...
Aunt, look
You pay Liu Yuwei's tuition with credit card
According to the rules, the money will return to
original account within twenty working days
So many days?
Yes, it's our rules
Fine
Ok, return the money
Ok
Don't worry
The dress, the bag and shoes
I'll return them on Monday
I just keep up appearance with them
You only need to return the dress
You can keep the bag and shoes
No
I can't take your bag
It's expensive
Not expensive
How much?
No much money
Look at my bag
58, bought on Taobao
Free delivery
Use this?
It can hold a lot
Zhizhi, if you don't care about yourself,
others won't care about you, either
You use cheap skin creams
No one will send you expensive cosmetics
So no one will send you Hermes
Who will send me?
And you really need to stop sighing
Don't say negative speech
We attract each other
You need to be positive
You are right
If we think about something bad all the time,
it will come
It's called Murphy's Law
Xiaoling
I didn't expect you to know a lot
You think I know nothing except beauty and money?
No
I never thought about it
It's ok even if you think so
When women are jealous of me,
it means I am attractive
Right?
I'll get it
Gosh
Yuwei, come here
Do you like it?
Come, drink some milk
Here is better than early classes
Aunt...
Sorry
They can't eat inside
In case they will get suffocated
I get it...
I'm sorry
Thank you...
Yuwei
Let's go over there
Is that your son?
So naughty
Yuwei
Come here
She pushes you
Why don't you push her?
Are you stupid?
Go, push her down
Go, push her
Push her...
Push her
Why does she push my daughter?
Your daughter pushed my granddaughter first
Did you see it?  Are you blind?
But you can't teach kids to fight
Who fought?
You didn't teach your daughter well
Who fights?
How can you say so?
You...
Stop it...
We are here for fun
What the hell
Stop it
You are so great?
Undereducated
Who is undereducated?
Stop it -Go
Don't play with the idiots
Right? Let's go
Forget it...
Look, so ridiculous
Forget it
Idiot
Baby, come here
You need to be fierce
Don't be a wimp like your mom
Good for nothing
Look good, right?
Miaomiao's mom, sorry we are late
It's ok
Let me tell you
I tried the dress last night
I gained weight recently
I outwear it
Really?
I am going to wear cheongsam
I am going to wear a cheongsam too
Hope we won't wear the same one
Yes
Doudou
Why is he here?
Go
Doudou, be a good boy, let's go home
The teacher told me principal told Doudou not to come ever
Really?
Our joint letter works
Yes, definitely
Doudou, let's go home
Put that down
Put that down, ok?
The more I look at them, the more annoying it becomes
It's ok...
The car is coming
Let's get in the car
Go...
You first
Help me hold this
I have got too much
Let me help you
Over there
Doudou, did you hear me?
The left one
Yeah, the left one
The door sucks
Stop it
Let's go home ok?
Come...
He is so naughty
What color is your cheongsam?
Green. What about you?
Mine is blue
But I will have a crystal brooch
Crystal...
I...
What color earrings do I use?
Golden
Golden is great
Is golden ok?
It looks great with green cheongsam
Ok, it depends on how you match
Sister Siyu
They give the tender of municipal lighting project to sister Yuan
What?
Client department told me this
Lighting project tender is mine
Why do you give it to sister Yuan?
Because she filed it first
Come on, please take a look
Obviously I filed first
I'll check it for you
Yuan Huizhong filed on 10th
It's clearly written here
Impossible
Xiaojiao
Please help me to check the filing
Which one?
Sister Yuan's street lamp tender
Sister Yuan's filing time is the tenth
Impossible
Xiaojiao
We checked it days ago
It's 16th, right?
I forgot it
You checked it for me
How can you forget?
Every day so many people come to register for file and check it
How can I remember all?
I get it
Did you find it out?
Client department says
They haven't touched any data
The network department didn't find any tampering
Security department checked all the monitorings
Everything is normal
Can I check it myself?
Is this necessary?
So she will go on behalf of our company
You think it's you?
Sister Siyu
You should have taken a picture
I didn't see this coming
Last time the reimbursement
You should know who they are
I underestimated the enemy
What are you going to do now?
I surrender
Now?
If it's only one million, I can defeat her
But if she gets the order
28 million
I will have no chance
So she will be the sales director?
I have to leave Lubao
Maybe even you have to go
Sister Siyu, listen
I have an idea
Liu Yang won't let Lubao win the tender
Yuan Huizhong won't get the order
Then you still have a chance to win
Impossible
Why?
First
President Pan needs this order
He will have an ace with this order
Second
It is unfair
Liu Yang will violate the rules
Sister
Chen
Your rent is due next month
Will you go on renting?
I need to increase the rent
How much will you increase?
Not much
Increase by 15%
Hello
Hello, how about it? Chen
So much
If you want to renew the lease,
you need to transfer me all the money for next quarter
22,000 in total
If you want to move out, I will come to collect the house next month
Ok, I get it
Brother Yiming
Siyu has some problem in the company
She has a bad mood now
You should go to see her
You didn't answer my calls
So I am here
It's ok
Since president Pan talked to me
I survived open and covert attacks and slander
I think I will be the sales director for sure
But who knows?
How to get the order
How to bring a team
I don't think I lose to sister Yuan
But in some ways
I will never be sister Yuan's opponent
I failed, but you are happy
No
Or you are laughing at me
Laughing at you?
For what?
I am a loser now
How could I laugh at you?
Then why are you laughing?
Siyu
Come back to my hometown with me
How could this be possible?
Before I came, I called Zhu Xiaobai
I told him about what happened recently
He told me he needs a sales director
Chen Yiming, what are you thinking about?
Now things become like this
After she becomes the sales director,
you will leave Lubao
I can go to other companies
With my ability and resources
I can find a job so easily
I thought so two months ago
I was as confident as you
Is that useful?
Now I even want to be a copywriter
But no company hires me
President Guo needs you
Can we stop talking about this?
Really
Only after you lose your job,
you will find the market is different from what you imagine
You are not the one as you think
Sister Ziru asked us to have dinner with her
I won't go
I have a video conference with Zhu Xiaobai
You really want to go?
The little confidence is all I have now
And a little bit of self-esteem
I want to keep them
I don't want to consume them in Shanghai
I will consume without producing
If it's the case, I should step backwards
I will have a broad sky
Right?
Xiaoling
You have so much luggage
You have over 80 pairs of shoes
Are you a centipede?
Can you wear all of them?
None of your business
I buy shoes with my money
What are you doing?
I have to get in your car
These are my treasure
I didn't promise to send you to your new home
Or you can beg me
I will help you out of kindness
Beg me...
Fine
I will help you out
Come, seat belt
I will do it myself
This is the last one
I'm exhausted
Just so little
So little?
You have 20 catties of cosmetics at least, right?
Let alone your shoes and bags
Enough
I'll invite you to dinner later
Ok?
We won't eat out, right?
We can eat here
You can cook some specialty dishes for me
Ok
My specialty is boiled water
Well, we should eat out
Ok, you can name the place, I will pay the bill
You go out first
I need to get changed
You can just get changed up there
I won't peek
I will close my eyes
Hurry, get out
Believe me
I won't peek
I need to get changed, get out
No...
If I go out now, people will think I am a stealer
You can get changed in bathroom
I helped you move out
You should be nice to me
Xiaoling
We'll go to the roadside stall later
Not Michelin
Don't wear high heels of ten centimeters
Eight centimeters will do
And don't take expensive bags
Chanel Gucci
If it gets oil, you will throw the tantrum
You go out with me like this?
What's wrong?
So casual
Usually you will do the makeups
It depends on whom I go out with
It's not necessary when it's you
Gu Xiaoling
You won't get married if you are so snobbish
None of your concern
If I don't care about you, you can't get married
Anyway, I won't marry you
Go
Let me tell you
Why are you so naughty?
Hurry
Siyu
Have a good appetite
I ordered a soup for you, it's good for your stomach
Sister Ziru
You know I have a poor stomach?
If a saleswoman has a good stomach,
her sales performance will be poor
You know me
Drink while it's warm
Siyu
I remember president Pan told me last time
Another two companies are talking about equity financing with him
What are those companies?
I just can't remember them
I am forgetful from time to time
He didn't tell you about these two companies?
We only talk about sales
He barely talks about financing with me
After we met last time
What did he tell you?
Nothing at all
Is the soup delicious?
Not bad
You don't have a good mood today
Did you contact the people on the list I gave you last time?
Three of them have cooperation intentions
Great
Your sales performance has no problem, right?
What's wrong, not enough?
It's ok
I will tell Annie to give you more
Sister Ziru, thank you
I won't need your client list
What's wrong?
My competition with sister Yuan is over now
It's three months, right?
It's not the deadline
But I have lost
Why?
Be careful
Come in, please
I need all the special dishes
Ok, what kind of hotpot condiment?
Slightly spicy
Extra spicy
Four beers
Ok
Only two of us, four bottles?
I just ordered my own beer
You need to order if you want to drink
Great
What are you looking at?
You have never seen a beauty like me?
Are you Gu Xiaoling?
What does it mean?
Oh my god
You are not the one I know
What should I be?
You are a goddess in my heart
Today you are...
Think it clearly before you say it out
Otherwise I'll stab you
I mean usually you are so aloof and detached
Why are you so unrestrained today?
Comfortable
I feel so comfortable today
Amazing
Usually I am surrounded by fair-skinned,
rich and beautiful ladies
But I don't feel a thing
Because they can't make me confortable
Stop pretending
You pretend you are a rich son every day
Aren't you tired?
Yeah, I'm very tired
You don't know how tired I am
Every day when I'm lying in bed
I need to review the past and learn the new
I need to think if there are any loopholes of the line that day
What kind of story I need to make up next day
So you say, am I tired?
Do me a favor
Can't open a beer?
Amazing
And in the field of new energy battery
almost no one can outcompete Lubao
in terms of cost and performance
So no matter who goes, our company will win the bid
Siyu, I don't think your competition with Yuan Huizhong is over
It's settled after president Pan saw me
You think I still have hope?
Everything is possible
With my experience, I won't surrender until the last moment
And I will have the chance to turn the table
Sister Ziru
What should I do?
Tell me why do you lose to her?
I don't think I am not as capable as her
I lose because I am indecisive
In fact, it is soft-hearted
Siyu
You have a wrong idea
I need to correct you
Decisiveness is vital
Right?
A little girl is soft-hearted
It's because she is kind and compassionate
She cherishes friendship
It's a good advantage
But in the workplace especially for managers
it's not an advantage
The workplace speaks by performance
And performance depends on shrewd and calm mind
And decisiveness
You mean...
I'm not professional enough
At least when competing with sister Yuan
you are so soft-hearted
Then you made a mistake
But...
People have feelings
But mature people will be more rational
You only care about your friendship
rather than company's development
You only see sisterhood
You even don't care about your subordinates' future and job
Siyu
Actually, the sensibility is not bad
But to be an excellent professional manager
you need to stay calm and decisive
For the development of the company
For career
You even need to be cold-blooded
Then you can go higher and farther
Sister Ziru
I don't know if I can make it
If you want to realize your dream
you need to work hard in this direction
You will feel painful
But in the end you will benefit from it
Surviving in the workplace is actually very simple
Do what you should
Don't fail the company
Don't fail your efforts
Need more?
Waiter, I need large intestines
Ok
What'?
Large intestines don't fit your temperament
but I like it
I can tell you
I like large intestines since childhood
You are heavy-flavored
All because of my dad
My dad took me to eat large intestines each week in childhood
I will take you to eat Shanghai's best brine intestines
But he died when I was 8
When did your mom marry Li Siyu's dad?
When I was 12
Actually my stepdad treats me and my mom well
Mainly because we used to live a poor life
We had no money
I wish I could meet you at that time
The one I wished to meet is not you
Who?
I loved Meteor Garden in childhood
I think I am Shan Cai
I wait for my Dao Mingsi every day
Guess what I watched in childhood
Doraemon
No
Young and Dangerous
The film is my dream in life
You have a dream?
Of course
I want to make big money
Be a big brother
Now I think it's so silly
But at that time I made an oath
If I succeed, I will go to Macau
I will be on a spree
Wish your dreams come true
Cheers, to dreams
Cheers
President Liang, sorry
I call you back so late
Don't worry
I will handle your shipping properly
Manager Tang
I have sealed the contract
It can be sent tomorrow
I invite you to dinner when you come to Shanghai
Mr. Xu
Sorry
I was busy yesterday
So I didn't have time to reply you
If it is convenient for you tomorrow
I will go to see you 11 o'clock in the morning
Ok, see you tomorrow morning
Zhu Xiaobai called
He asked me when we could go back
What's your decision?