[To Dear Myself]
[Ep16]
It's true
Sister Ziru told HR department about your post and salary in my presence
You just go to work
Wait...
Stop talking
Let me process
She has so many talents to choose from
Why does she choose me?
Because you are excellent
Tell me the truth
How did you beg Mr. Wang?
Did you promise her any condition?
Nothing at all
Sister Ziru admires your talent for a long time
I just told her you resigned
She immediately asked you to work in her company
That's all?
Yiming, don't worry
Sister Ziru is not stupid
If you are mediocre, she won't hire you
But I only met her twice
But your resume is great
Resume?
I have sent that resume for over 50 times
No reply
Why do I...
Not all bosses are talent scouts
Not all job seekers have girlfriends like you
I did nothing
Siyu
Thank you
Don't need to thank me
I do this also for myself
Yiming
I don't want you to go back
I don't want to have a long-distance relationship with you
I don't want to face unforeseeable future
I don't want, either
Huizhong
Sorry
It's ok, brother
I know you did your best
I have told my friends about you
They are very interested in your qualifications and abilities
So you don't need to worry about work
Brother
Thank you
But I don't want to
What will you do?
Todau Mengmeng's teacher called me
She scolded me and she said I am an unqualified parent
These teachers are so ridiculous
I feel I am a loser
I have worked for 13 years there
Finally I am fired
My apprentice turns against me
My son is the poorest student in class
Don't be discouraged
People like Li Siyu won't ride on the crest of success for too long
Lubao
Li Siyu
Just let bygones be bygones
I just want to find a simple work
I don't care about the salary
So I can take care of Mengmeng every day
I will help him with his grades
Fine
I have to go now
Mengmeng's tuition is over
I have to pick him up
Bye
Ok
Bye bye
Now even Wei Yayun can command me
What an irony
I'm no better than you
A graduate from 985 university works as a receptionist
Wu
So that's all for my life?
Of course not
We still have a chance
Chance?
Where is it?
From my experience, all bids have dirty tricks
Liu Yang drives us away deliberately
He thinks we stand in the way
But we are kicked out now
Even if there is some dirty trick, we just don't know
We don't know
We can start from the outside
I have the list of companies' paper for bid
You go to check it
I think, one of them has something to do with Liu Yang
How to check?
The Internet is so advanced now
You want me to teach you?
It's my honor to join Tianyi Group
So happy to work with you
I am confident that I will make planning department
an important department for Tianyi Group
I believe under the leadership of Mr. Chen,
planning department will go to the next level
Thank you
Mr. Chen
Your office is inside
Ok
Sit
Mr. Chen
Do you need any help?
No
I'll go back to work now
Thank you
You take me to this wilderness
What do you want?
You even inebriate me
What's your purpose?
Say it
I am happy today
I will do as you say
I have no purpose
I just want to have a little walk with you
Walk?
Ok
Be careful
Why are you so slow?
Hurry
Fireworks
These two
Let's celebrate it
Ok
Congratulations
Find your place again
You are sales director now
Your dream comes true
So in the future, every time we achieve a dream
we will light a firework to celebrate it
Ok
I think we should get a bigger one today
Come  -Ok
Drone
Take it
Siyu
Your husband accepts your offer now
Actually I should have accepted long ago
But I want to give you the best of me
A safest future
So it took so long
After these difficulties,
I have a deeper understanding about you, me and us
Siyu, don't worry
I will work hard
I will prove I am the best with the rest of my life
I am your Mr. Right
So this is proposal?
Yeah
This is my proposal
Great
So happy
What happened to you?
Nothing
Because of this painting?
Xiaoling
I have been looking for you
I'm here all along
Ten years ago
the first time I saw this painting
I cried too
Many people don't understand why
But only I know it
What touched me?
Xiaoling
We are the same kind of people
Be my girlfriend
You know me
I know you too
This exhibition includes clothing, sculpture
visual art and interactive installations, etc
As you can see, it shows
social networks's change on people's mind and behavior
And an influence
Hi, Danny
Hi, Bruce
Long time no see
Yeah
Your exhibition is great
Very nice  -Thank you...
I like painting and its history
Like it, yeah
It's great
Every moment is certain
But every next moment is uncertain
Where did you go?
Who do you send messages to?
Did you see it?
The top floor of that house
I have told you
That famous collector's apartment
Take a look
So low-key
Yeah, low-key enough
Right?
Liu Yang
Sister Siyu accepted brother Yiming's proposal
Great
Congratulations to them
I want to invite Siyu and Yiming to dinner here
First...
I'm having a meeting
So fantastic
I still don't believe it
It's too late to change your mind
Do we really get married?
You think I am kidding?
Yiming
Actually I don't know how to be a wife
You think, I know how to be a husband?
It's my first marriage, ok?
But I believe we can get used to it
and work hard together
And explore together
So what's the next step?
Next is a realistic link
Talk about dowry?
Talk about the wedding room
Siyu
I have saved about a million
It's enough for down payment of two-bedroom house
I think we should buy a three-bedroom house
One for us and one for kid
In case Zhizhi or Xiaoling has dispute with her husband
But three-bedroom house in a better location is at least 5 million
I don't have enough money for down payment now
I have half a million
No
Your money is your money
How can I use your money?
How can you like my appearance other than my money?
Siyu
We have been together for years
I know I am not good enough for you
If you pay down payment, I really can't accept it
Chen Yiming, let me tell you
Today you need to take me and money at the same time
Or you will get nothing
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Only 500,000
Remember, you need to work for me for a lifetime
Actually I win
Siyu
You can ingratiate yourself with me
As I know, you have a new director in your department
He took office last week
How's it?
Not very good
Why can he be a director?
As I know, he is a leader's son-in-law
President Wang can't refuse it
So she transfers He away to save a spot for him
No wonder He was suddenly transferred away
It's He's blessing in disguise
He is promoted to branch's boss from the planning director
Director Chen
You didn't attend the meeting?
What meeting?
Wednesday's regular meeting
All directors need to attend
Thank you
800 million has 20% stock equity
So Lubao is four billion in total
It's a good price in previous years
But now, it's not a favorable price
So what's your take?
According to the finance company 's valuation model
3 billion is ok
3 billion
I think it's a little high
Sorry
I did not receive the meeting notice
Amy
Remember to notify director Chen
Ok
Director Chen
Come sit here
It's ok
I just sit here
Director Chen
Your place is here
President Wang
So what's your take?
Let's not talk about this now
Any updates about financial openness?
We hold this meeting to evaluate Lubao, right?
We are going for the next round of negotiations
We need to get an answer today
As I know, the new policy will adjust the ratio
of indirect financing and direct financing
Any more?
President Wang
I made an appointment with a client today
We are going to talk about our company's brand image
Ok
Go
I'll go now
Ok
I'm sorry, everyone
Bye
Ok
Go on
Well
Xingxing's father likes your cookies
Really?
I love it, too
Yeah
Ok, I'll make more and bring it tomorrow
Ok
No
Make some Napoleon
I love Napoleon
I love Napoleon, too
Napoleon is delicious
Delicious
It's plain
Ok, I will make some
Thank you
Yuwei's mom
The school is over
They are coming out
Line up
Your son
Yeah, my grandson
Are you ok?
What's wrong with you?
Come...
He is not ok
Look
It's swollen
Sorry
I am so sorry
We can take him to the hospital now
Of course
Maybe it's a concussion
Ok, grandma
I will go with you
Wait a moment
He has a younger sister
We will go together after we pick her up
No, go now
Grandma, his sister is still little
No
You only care about your children
What about my grandson?
Forget it...
Go now
Grandma
Grandma, don't be angry
Go
Why are you hitting me?
I didn't harm you
What's the problem?
Serve you right
Stop it
Who told you to cut in?
None of your business
Stop it, don't be angry
Stop fighting
Stop it
Let me go
She hit me
You should stop her
Why are you stopping me?
Are you friends?
It's ok now
Come...
Come here...
Yuwei's mom
We do this for your own good
Think
The grandma is so old
If you have a conflit and hurt her by accident
you will be in a big trouble
Yes
Even if you don't hurt her
what if she deliberately extorts you?
It will invite trouble
Am I right?
Yes
Exactly
We are helping you
We let her hit you
So she could calm down
Am I wrong?
You know who his son is?
It's the principal of the international elementary school nearby
It's so hard to go to that school even if parents have money
But the principal said in the next three years
he will consider our kindergarten's kids first
Why?
All because his kid is in this kindergarten
If you irriate the grandma
they will transfer the grandson to another kindergarten
The promise will be invalid
All the kindergarten's kids won't be admitted to that elementary school
Including your Yuwei
Do you understand?
Kids are out
They are coming
Miaomiao, go...
Miaomiao
Xingxing
Come here
How's today?
Yuwei's mom
Don't forget to bring Napoleon
Let's go
Don't forget my cookies tomorrow
I want more
Go
Yuwei's mom
I drive today
Do you want me to give you ride?
Bye
Get in the car, go
Hurry
Mom
What happened to you?
Why are you crying?
Mom
What happened to you?
Liu Yang
Change this sentence
Ok
I need th loo
Hello, the subscriber you dialed is busy now
Sorry
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed is busy now
Go home
Girl
Chinese Studies Training Class
Hello
I like the houses for rent on your app
I want to make an appointment
Ok
Let's contact online
Goodbye
President Wang
Yiming
I want to explain the meeting to you
It's ok
You know we are talking
about equity financing with Lubao, right?
About Lubao's valuation
I have negotiated with president Pan for many times
I think you know Lubao's valuation best
But today's meeting
I specifically notified HR department not to tell you
I get it
You are afraid I will leak the company's secret
No
I believe in your professional ethics
You won't do that
I don't want to get you in dilemma
You and siyu
One is an executive of Tianye
One is an executive of Lubao
If Siyu asks you about Tianyi's strategy
if you tell her, you will be sorry for company
If you don't tell her, it will affect your love
So I think you don't need to know
Thank you
President Wang
Thank you for being so considerate
Hope you can understand
I can understand
Of course
Come
Who is responsible for Lubao Group's brand valuation?
Wang
But he gets off work now
I have a backup
Ok
Give me all Lubao Group's public data
Director Chen
All here?
Yes
Ok
You should get off work now
You are not sleeping?
Why you didn't answer my calls?
Did you?
I have no missed calls
You didn't WeChat me, other
Don't ask me why I called you?
You can tell me now
I want to transfer Yuwei back to bluesky kindergarten
What did you say?
I will go through the formalities tomorrow
You forget how hard we tried to transfer Yuwei out of bluesky?
Now you want to go back
So, all the money, the time, energy and debt we owe are ruined now
I will transfer her back
Yuwei was doing great in bluesky
You said, Yuwei needs to receive more elite education
So you transferred her
Now she is doing great in Jinguduo
What do you want?
I am wrong, ok?
I don't need Yuwei to receive elite education
I just need her to be an ordinary girl, ok?
What are you doing here, so noisy?
Zhizhi wants to change Yuwei' kindergarten
Is it true?
Yes
What's wrong?
I disagree
Whether you agree or not
I will transfer, tomorrow
It's late in night
Are you insane?
Yuwei is just familiar with the environment of new kindergarten
You want to transfer again
You are not afraid to leave her some psychological shadow?
And we just paid the tuition of this semester
If you transfer now, the tuition of 30,000 yuan
they will only return half of it at most
I will transfer
No
You only think about money
I was bullied today
They bullied me together
What happened?
Mom...
I am coming
Coming
All right
Yuwei, I am here...
Come
Come, go to bed
Good girl
They bullied me together
After that, they said they did that for my own good
Voice down
Don't wake Yuwei up again
Gosh
I have told you, including Miaomiao's mom
Get away from them
But you don't listen
Yuwei enters Jinguduo
You should let her finish this semester first
Snd you just need to stay away from Miaomiao's mom
Can't you think for me?
Keep your voice down
Voice down
You want to transfer Yuwei back just because of this?
Don't make a fuss, ok?
I am not
I was bullied
Can you stop being emotionally fragile?
Emotionally fragile?
Ok
You are not
I can tell you
In life and workplace, it's common
You just need to bear with it
No
If I were you, I would have resigned thousands of times
Ok, tell me your thoughts
I...
Zhizhi
We are adults
Adults should solve problems rather than avoid them
You can't just transfer her back to bluesky kindergarten
Don't make troubles for me, ok?
Anyway, Yuwei can't stay in this kindergarten
Let me ask you
If you are bullied again after
we transfer Yuwei back to bluesky kindergarten
So we still need to transfer Yuwei to another kindergarten?
No matter what, we must transfer
Whatever
I am out of this
She wastes money
You should stop her
What does this mean?
What does she want?
Yang
You should sleep in the room
I will sleep on the sofa
It's ok, mom
I will sleep here
Bloody wife
So ridiculous
It's ok, mom
Let me tell you
You can't lower your head first this time
Ok...
You can't spoil her
Go to sleep, mom
Ridiculous
Good night
How's it?  Do you like it?
Brother, sister, look
Many clients want to see the house
You should buy it now, don't hesitate
Ok, we need to take a look
Ok
We need to discuss about it
OK...
How's it?
We will buy it
I have considered this for a long time
I checked its real picture, floor plan
and panoramic video in VR
I like the location and direction
And the decoration is not bad
We just need some furniture
Then we can get married directly
Get married?
Yes
We can afford it
Wait...
I can't catch up with you
You have any plans?
I need to get mentally prepared
No more
Only buy a house
Buying a house is a lifelong event
We need to be deliberative
Yes, I am
I...
I'm discussing with you
Tell me your opinion about it
Nothing special
But maybe we will find a better one
Siyu, there is no perfect house in the world
It's our home when we move in
I think that is the best
You are right
But I want to see more
I don't want to
Just this one
I really don't want to see more
Don't be so impatient
I am impatient
I'm so anxious
I want to buy the house
Then I can marry you
Why?
You change your mind?
You don't want to marry me?
No, no, absolutely no
Why are you so picky when it comes to buying a house?
I'm not picky
Let me think about it
Brother Yang
Siyu, I just want to tell you
Lubao is shortlisted
Qualification  certification and sample testing are ok
Great
Prepare for the bidding documents
No problem
Next, expert team will intervene for evaluation
We just assist them
To avoid suspicion, we can't see each other
Don't contact each other
I know
Brother Yang
But can you tell me
What's our odds?
The only thing I can tell you is
Lubao's score is pretty high
Good luck
Thank you
Angry?
No
Still deny it
You sound so indifferent
I'm sorry
Ok?
I want to get married
I have pressure recently
I need to make five hundred million
Also, you just went to the new company
I just can't concentrate on marriage
Since you are sincere
I'm ok now
Ok
Mr. Chen?
Yes, it's me
I made an appointment before
Come in, please