# Google translate version for your reference #
High teacher high teacher
data
where to put
system
There is still data, impossible
You let go
High teacher high teacher
I
I i i
Here we are
This fails
Didn’t you say it will definitely succeed this time?
Teacher Gao
Didn't you say this time
Sure to succeed
Lei Haowen
you
Didn't you say that this time will definitely succeed
Can't do this
It's all over
Hao Wen
Too dangerous inside
Haowen Lei Haowen
The firefighter will be here in a while
I'm coming
Hao Wen
Hello there
The fire is out
Still need to check
okay
You two maintain order
You two go with me
I didn't bring the key
feelling better
I can stand it
Hao Wen
Don't know he can hold it
Hello
The number you have dial can not be reached
He turned off
He will be fine
I go find him
Xiaoling Xiaoling
It's almost done, let's go back
Over
All gone
All blown up
Go back and talk about it
Come go
You leave me alone
You will get sick after a while
Go back with me first
stand up
Go back by yourself
You are sick
Walk around
I'll tell you it's all over
Burned out
You calm down and go back first
Walk around, don't move me
go
Don't move me
Are you sick?
Hey
He's fine
Do you want to talk to him
No more
Don't tell him
I'm looking for him
Come, drink while it's hot
Don't catch a cold
It's alright
Don't you just fail once
This is not once
This is the thousandth time
What's wrong
It's a big deal to start all over again
Can't start all over again
We have no money
What about refinancing
Today's explosion
Are making local headlines
Think about it
Who would invest in us
Gu Xiaoling
Gone
Siyu, Mr. Gong is here
What are you going to do now
Mr. Gong, tell the truth
I was also hit the other day
Also thought about
Just forget it
Just spend 10 million
Bought another lesson
I understand
If you decide
I have nothing to say
But unique project
Condensed Teacher Gao
So many years of hard work
So many people paid for it
This also includes your input
I feel
I shouldn't give up easily
Right
I think it's all here
Still don't give up
How about we find a way
Refinance
Delay in financing
Correct
Because we are ready
Pause the laboratory
Teacher Gao and I
Go back through the experiment
Including before
All failed experiments
Contour teacher and Liu Yang’s
After the backtracking result comes out
Let's discuss
Next steps
When will the results come out
Three months
or
Half a year
It's okay. This is the normal state of Teacher Gao
Mr. Gong
Ok
We will definitely make a fortune
So don't lose faith
Your investment will return
Then I'll wait
Why didn't you see Lei Haowen?
His blow
Bigger than all of us
why
Hard to say
Hao Wen
otherwise
Let's ask Liu Yang to play court
Not interested in
I know
I invite you to have a big drink
how about it
Unless you drink me to death
Otherwise it will be more uncomfortable
Cheer up
not good
Even if you fail alone
Don't you still have
Is Yiwen Company?
Start a business
I'm just for her
She is going to marry now
Yiwen company for me
There's no point
You two are here
Mr. Gong
sit
Hao Wen Hao Wen
Unless you sell Yiwen Company
Can give me five million
It makes sense
What did you say
Seeing my investment
Still make some money
You are about to sell
Mr. Gong
I put Yiwen Company
All my shares are sold to you
Five million
Mr. Gong, he is broken in love
Nerves
I am not nervous
five million
Do you want
I found it again
Yes I found it
Great
Everyone is on this round of experiments
Placed great hopes
But I didn’t expect this result
even though
Failure is commonplace
But I still feel a bit
hard to accept
how about you
I'm okay
Zhizhi and Yuwei didn't go to Europe
I'm very happy
One cannot be too greedy
Can't want everything
How about siyu
Except Teacher Gao
She is the strongest
Teacher Gao said
This explosion is because
Insufficient electrolyte concentration
As long as the concentration problem is solved
We still have hope
I heard enough
Every time I said there was a small problem
Every time I say there is a breakthrough
Every time I say there is hope
Every time I say it will work next time
But every time it fails
It's real this time
Which is not true
Hao Wen
Yang brother
Siyu is here too
Hi
I'm encouraging Haowen to cheer up
Then you talk slowly
We just have to experiment again
I have been taken by your words
Miserable
I don't want to hear it again
This sentence
Moreover
Mr. Gong gave us the five million
Already spent
We have no money now
We have come this far
No reason to give up
People develop a battery
Spend hundreds of millions of dollars at every turn
We are ten million
Ten million
You just want to change the world
Stop dreaming
Hao Wen
I don't want to lie to myself
Yiming, come and play two balls
coming
Siyu
How about we invest in new green
Sell ​​it
Then we follow
But it's okay
New green is simply a dream
Our new green investment is unique
That share
Not worth at all
Since it's worthless
I can’t sell if I want to sell
If i can sell it
And the price is not bad
That's not for sale
why
Because the only step will succeed
Alone will never succeed
Will succeed
Siyu, sell it
I am the chairman of New Green Investment
And major shareholder
I said not to sell, not to sell
Haven't the labs been ruined?
How can Siyu do an experiment?
Only part of the instrument is destroyed
If you give us another million
Repurchase a batch of instruments
We can restart
Then you guys now
Has one million gone?
Don't say a million
right now we
Can't even get a thousand yuan
Why come back so late today
I happened to have something tonight
Let me do it
correct
Ok
Mr. Gao's lab, you
Have you heard
It exploded, right?
Correct
heard
You were not in stock before
And the price above
Are there big differences?
They are now hit hard
I think
Maybe you
A good opportunity to build a position at a low price
Investment is not about price
But value
As long as there is value
You can vote no matter how expensive
If it's worthless
Can't go in no matter how cheap
Their project
It can be said that it is already
Totally worthless
But i heard
They are still very promising
Say if
If you do one more experiment
May succeed
Their one more time
The last time with the gambler
almost
Totally unbelievable
If this is the case, I
I want to put my house
Sold
In your name
Put this money
Lend to Li Siyu
Help them continue to experiment
what do you mean
I didn't talk to
Does Siyu have a paragraph?
I just don't want to see her
no way no money
Just want to help her
But I don’t want others to misunderstand
Feel between us
Old love or something
and so
I think in your name
Lend her money
Is the best way
And before she
Not prejudiced against you
Is there a misunderstanding?
I think
Maybe this time
Can ease you guys
The relationship between
Yiming
You are so affectionate and righteous
I read you right
So you agree
I understand you want to help Siyu
Actually I want to help her too
But you do
Not helping her but hurting her
Why do you say that
Teacher Gao and I and Siyu
Have been in contact many times
I know the project very well
Although all rational analysis
All point to this project
Impossible to succeed
But they
Just unwilling to accept
Where's Teacher Gao
Is such a stubborn person
More than ten years
Can't hear anything
Suggestion and advice
Siyu is infected by him now
Totally obsessed with this project
Inextricable
Yes, they both do
Are quite stubborn
So my suggestion is
What they need now
Not support
But stop loss
Stop loss
Just can't
Lend them money again
That's not helping them
Is to let them in
The road of paranoia gets deeper and deeper
You really want to help them
You have to persuade them
Abandon this project
Professor Gao, you can go to me
Newly bought laboratory work
Siyu
Doesn't she like to start a business
I can work on other projects
Support her
What do you think
also
The laboratory is only temporarily closed
Everyone go back and rest for a while
And I and Mr. Gao Liu Yang
And other shareholders
We will never
Abandon this project
After the call broke down
I was bankrupt too
But less than a year
I stand up again
So i believe
This time we will be able to
stand up
Siyu sister
Now everyone outside says
Our project
Doomed to succeed
They know a fart
Correct
Our own life
Why listen
What the outsiders say
Our own life
We have the final say
I know
Many people say
Teacher Gao is stubborn and says I am paranoid
But actually
We are just pursuing
Just what I want
Even if it's waiting for us in the end
Doomed to fail
But at least
I believed it sincerely
Desperately attached
Give heartily
Even if there is no result
I have no regrets in my life
Worked hard
Siyu sister
As long as you say hello
We come back immediately
Good rest this time
Worked hard
Siyu sister, we are waiting for you
wait for me
Ok
Thank you sister
Bye bye
Goodbye Siyu sister
Feel better
Okay
A friend from the Trade and Industry Bureau notified me
Said our new green investment
One less information in the filing
Need to fill in the signatures of several shareholders
What information
Amendments to the articles of association
You signed it all
Still take a look
Gu Xiaoling next week
I got the certificate with He Mu
Let it go
Can you put down the tweet
I can't let go of you
Two of us drinking
he's drunk
Keep saying your name
Come, sign first
I'll send it first
President Wang
The kill acquisition has been completed
Got it
Li Siyu
Thank you
Password is your birthday
Is the meaning of Wang Ziru
It has nothing to do with her
This is what I mean
Where did you get so much money
I sold that house
you're so dumb
That house sold
It's hard to buy it back
But you need money
Why did you do this
Siyu
Start from our acquaintance
You have always been
Stop
Don't reminisce with me
Well
Actually I have always had a regret
If at first
I support your dream
Don't talk to me about dreams
Then let's say now
What is our relationship right now
nothing
Have
When I was desperate
You gave me 300 thousand
This house is selling fast
Didn't make much money
I repaid the loan
Returned some money from relatives and friends
Just one million and fifty thousand left
All here
You don't owe me
do not worry
After the two of us
There won't be any intersection
Chen Yiming
crazy
All crazy
We have and FCC Group
Signed an investment letter of intent
Wait now
Accountant's audit report
And due diligence report
What is the final price
Tianyi Group
Put twenty-three percent
Emerald's shares
Transferred to FCC Group
The total price is
five billion
This is great too
You must drink some wine on this matter
Celebrate
Should drink
Yes
President Wang
Zeng
Here, Mr. Zeng, Mr. Qiu
Respect the harvest season
Now it seems
No more than three months
We can and green treasure
Say goodbye
Yes
Three months later
Wait for this fund to exit
We'll be with you
Continue signing
In funding
We will increase investment
Thank you for your trust
Happy cooperation
Hope to continue to harvest
Please come in
Please sit down
Do you know Gao Zhengdao
I know what's wrong
We succeeded
Filmless battery
Scientific feat
From today we have entered
The era of membraneless batteries
Membraneless battery is the only one
From today
Coming
The comments above are all saying
Membrane battery
Only way out
Among them
Specifically mentioned green treasure
And green treasure
Companies with similar businesses
The comment area is active
It is estimated that the stock price will fall tomorrow
Then this will definitely cause
FCC attention
And will definitely understand our plan
Create a big obstacle
Will not
Two bosses, don't worry
This old man
I was prepared
His these
Will not be on our plan
Cause any trouble
Since President Wang is so sure
Then I can't say much
Ok then we are now
Just wait for these three months
The report submitted by Mr. Wang
I will not let them down
Row
it is good
Cheers
Liu Yang
Congratulations
Thank you
Why hasn't Haowen here yet?
Yes
Moments like today
How can there be no him
Hello
The number you have dial can not be reached
Phone turned off
Haowen is in a bad mood recently
Should be because
Gu Xiaoling is getting married, right?
Yiming
Li Siyu told me
Must let me do her
To toast you alone
thank you
she was
Where is she now
After the sole announcement of success
People don't know where to go
Call no answer
No reply to SMS or WeChat
President Wang, to you
Mr. Wang, I really admire you
Everything is under control
I just want to make sure
Everything is foolproof
When am i
Showdown with them
The sooner the better
understand
By the way, Mr. Gong
Didn’t you say they have three months
After half a year
Will there be new progress?
Why so fast
New action
I heard
Chen Yiming gave a sum of money
For Li Siyu
So so fast
Started a new experiment
But okay
With you, Mr. Wang has a layout