[To Dear Myself]
[Ep21]
They think I have an affair?
Look at you
You are so abnormal recently
They are women
Haowen
They didn't say anything about me, right?
You? Nothing
You
Anything wrong, right?
Nothing wrong
Something happened?
No
Nothing happened
Stop denying
Say it
We can help you analyze it
We won't tell others
It's different from what you think
What is it?
In my office, an intern
Female?
Of course
Something happened when it's a man?
Go ahead
I am clean with her
She is like a little girl, and worships me
With a little admiration
Quite dangerous
You won't fall for it, right?
I won't
But to be honest
When I am with Zhang Zhizhi
sometimes I feel tired and bored
But when I stay with her
even it's working overtime
I feel easy and happy
Things like this are all fresh in the first beginning
You will change your mind over time
I'm just talking about feeling
I didn't talk about time
Don't deny it
I am most qualified to talk about this
Your personality is not suitable for being ambiguous
Where am I ambiguous?
You are not like me
You are not as free and easy as me
You are not a philander like me
In the end you will disgrace yourself
More than that, you will disgrace her
Liu Yang, you have a family to support
If something happens to you, your family will suffer the loss
And you hold public office
From the perspective of investment,
you will have more risk than benfit
Don't have any illusions
Don't indulge yourself
And I think you have married Zhizhi for so many years
It's not easy
You should cherish it
Come
Don't be impulsive
Don't be impulsive, brother
Tomorrow is your last opportunity for assessment
If you still can't pass, my advice is
you should uy 30,000 batteries and put them at home
How to use?
For your girlfriend
I called you
But the line is busy
I texted you and you didn't reply me
I was reviling someone
I bought you some skewers and porridge
It's a little bit cold
You need to heat it before you eat
When did you come?
It's about forty minutes
I'm sorry
It's ok
I am willing to wait for you even if it's forever
You haven't talked like that for a long time
Siyu
This week of our cold war
I'm really unhappy
I'm not happy, either
I have been thinking
What's wrong between us?
But to be honest
Even till now, I still disagree
But the primary cause lies in me
I didn't do it well
So you feel insecure
So you make money so desperately
So you choose that method
Sorry
I didn't handle it well
I'm sorry
please forgive me
Yiming
Siyu
Doctor...
What?
This is Li Siyu's medical report
Thank you
She is only 32?
Correct
Nowadays, young people are so...
Look, sinus arrhythmia
Blood lipid, blood pressure, and blood sugar
are all higher than standards
Look
Gastrointestinal tract has serious problems
What should we do?
What does she do?
Saleswoman
Often drink and stay up late?
Correct
She should change her job
Or take some rest for a while
Or completely stop drinking
Then take more rest
combined with proper exercise, light diet and balanced nutrition
Maybe she will recover
Wait
You're awake
Where am I?
This is the hospital
What's wrong with me?
You fainted suddenly
Don't move
Lie down...
I will elevate the bed
Is it ok?
Yeah
Your blood pressure, lipid and blood sugar
And your uric acid
All higher than the standards
And your stomach, kidney, liver
And your thyroid
All have problems
Yiming
It might be important
It's not as important as your body
Maybe the doctor took off your ring during checkup
I'm fine
No
You have a poor stomach all the time
Take the medicine first
The doctor told me, you'd better take a long vacation
Take a good rest
Generally given your current situation
If you don't pay attention to it,
your health will break down
So serious?
Come, see it yourself
So
You need to have a good rest
Come, drink the medicine
Come
Be careful, it's hot
But now is the critical moment for Lubao's financing
Everyone is working hard
How could I take a vacation?
Unless I quit my job
It's a good idea
You want me to resign, right?
Siyu
You just want me to stand behind you
So you can work outside
Why do you think I do everything for myself?
It's the fact
Can you take a good look?
These are the facts
I tried so hard to persuade him for hours
He is fully aware of his mistake
Then he dated Li Siyu that night
And then they make up
How did you know it?
Yiming called me in the morning
He wants me to find a trustworthy buying agent
He needs to buy some health products for Li Siyu
Good to know
I have accomplished your task successfully
Well done
How do you thank me?
Say it, what do you want?
You will give me everything I want?
I want a girlfriend
Haowen
Get out of this door
Turn left and turn left
You will see a hotel
Book a room
Then have a good sleep
You will see a girlfriend in your dream
Gu Xiaoling
Remember to take the invoice
I will reimburse you
No one will help you anymore if you do so
Whatever
Great
Remember what you said today
Or I can invite you to dinner
Save it
Mom, I want to watch cartoons
You have watched today
You can't watch anymore
Grandma
Watch cartoons with me
Your mom said, don't watch
Zhizhi, put this in
Mom, this box still has some space
I'll get you some clothes Liu Yang doesn't need
You can give them to relatives
Ok...
Zhizhi
The little granddaughter of the third aunt is of your height
You can give her some clothes that you don't need
Ok
Zhizhi
What?
Nothing
Put this in there
Yuwei
What is this?
Car
This one
White Dragon Horse
White dragon horse sitting on the cart
We are going to drive
Did you finish the packing?
Almost
I will go back at four o'clock
Ok
Call me when you about to arrive
Transfer me to another department?
Yes
Did I do something wrong?
No
You did nothing wrong
It's my problem
Brother Yang
I still want to learn from you
Impossible
Why?
For your good
Also for my good
We are ordinary friends from now on
Did someone say something?
No
Why?
Does sister-in-law know something?
I can explain it to her
It has nothing to do with her
It's my own decision
That's all
I need to work now
Mom, leave it to me
Be careful
Mom, get in the car
What?
Get in the car
Where's Yuwei?
Chinese studies class
Mom's things are all packed?
Go back
Mom left
We can return to normal now
It's been so many days
My contract has been for a long time
Me too, it can't be delayed anymore
What to do?
They are urging me
I am so panic
It's the last week I guess...
Sister Siyu
Sister Siyu, sorry
You are sick
We didn't go to the hospital to see you
Sister, we are wrong
It's ok
Get down to business
Sister, I can't fix Daneng company
You need to go there in person
Sister, you need to sign it
Now the client is waiting for you
This is the fax from Ningbo
And this contract
Take a look
If there is no problem, sign it
We have received Tianyou Energy's final payment
Ok, I get it
Go back to work
Come in
Sister, your delivery
Ok, leave it to me
Thank you
Sales performance belongs to the boss
Body is your own
You are mine
Remember to take medicine and warm your stomach
Chen Yiming
First
What impact will website design have on website traffic?
This is the first point
Another point is
What kind of website design and technology will influence website traffic?
And what the influence will be?
I am in a meeting
Call you back later
Come in
Sister Siyu
Latest financial statement
We exceed our sales expectation this month
We set another record
Tell all of them
I will invite them to dinner tonight
Ok
Sister Siyu will invite us to dinner tonight
Celebrate our sales department's another record
Thank you, sister Siyu
You said, you invite me to dinner, right?
I'm hungry
Gu Xiaoling
We need to keep our promise
Please fulfill your promise
The best dishes, the best wine in the world
And the most beautiful boy in this alley
Are waiting for you
Who's there?
Me
I'm coming
It's so late, what seems to be the problem?
Talk inside
Say it here
I want to drink water
Buy it downstairs
I saw your boyfriend
Oh
The man has a problem with his face
I am here to remind you
You still know this?
Didn't you see?
He has hanging needle wrinkle on his ophryon
It will curse his wife
Really?
He is a womanizer according to physiognomy
He is the last man to be your boyfriend
So what kind of boyfriend should I have?
You should find a Cancer man,
1.80 meters tall and 70 kg heavy
And he is a passionate man with a pair
of affectionate, clean and warm eyes
You are recommending yourself, right?
Don't be so direct
Lei Haowen
I see you as a friend
Why do you still give up?
I also see you as a good friend
We need to share good things with good friends, right?
I share myself with you
Am I wrong?
Pooh
That man is problematic
He is better than you, though
Where?
Everywhere
At least I didn't send you gifts picked from refuse dump
Get out
Go...
Gu Xiaoling
Shut up
Don't come to me crying after you suffer loss
I won't go to see you even if I die
You will regret
Shut up
Zhizhi
What are you doing?
You didn't have enough rommance with colleague in office?
What do you mean?
You and Wei Yayun
What's your relationship?
Colleague
What kind of colleague?
Ordinary colleague
What's the embroidery?
You love me, I love you
Ordinary colleague?
Stop lying. Liu Yang
You're just being paranoid because of this?
This scarf belongs to Wei's boyfriend
Her boyfriend's name is Li Lei
You think L means me?
Really?
You can invite Wei's boyfriend to dinner
Then you will know
Why do you have her boyfriend's scarf?
I worked overtime too late
And I felt uncomfortable
She lent me her boyfriend's scarf
You borrowed her boyfriend's scarf?
Just need to leave it outside
Why do you put it at the bottom of the storage box?
It's packed in a gift bag
And why did you delete all your traces of your communication with her?
We are clean
You deleted it because of a guilty conscience
Whatever you say
Morning, dad
Morning
Do you like the fried dough stick?
Yes
Give me some
Really great
Bought at the new store, right?
Yuwei, do you like the soy milk?
Yes
Come, cheers
So great
Dad, you can send me to Chinese Studies class, right?
Not today
I need to work overtime today
Work overtime every day
After this period, I will take an annual leave
Then we will go to travel with mom, ok?
Great
Yeah
I have to go to work now
I'm going to work now
Be a good girl
Mom
When do we go?
Right away
Come
Wait for me
Sister in law
Is Liu Yang here?
He went to the construction site
Where's Wei Yayun?
Wei Yayun
Went to the construction site, too
Team leader Liu
Thank you
Be careful
Ok, team leader Liu
Mr. Liu
Why are you here?
I told Li to take over your work
I need to hand over some work on site
So this is the last time I am here
Where's Li?
He hasn't arrived yet
You should take some rest for a while
Wei, come here
Coming
What's the matter?  -What is this?
Here
This...
Wei
Wei Yayun
I... you are
I need to see Liu Yang
Mr. Liu Yang is over there
I will tell him now
Mr. Liu Yang
What happened?
Install that later
Why are you here?
You looked it up before going to bed yesterday
You forgot it at home
So I brought it here
I'm afraid you might need it
I will let you two talk
Wei
Did you return her scarf?
I brought it
I'll return it to her later
Wei
Days ago, you lent your boyfriend's scarf to me, right?
She is misunderstood
Thank you for the scarf
Take your boyfriend to have dinner at my house
I have to go now
Why do you have the cup?
You sent it to her?
Me?
You said, you are clean, right?
Wei, tell your sister-in-law
You bought this cup yourself
Hurry
Brother Yang
You gave me the gift
What else do you want to say?
Sister-in-law, don't blame brother Yang
Brother Yang did nothing wrong
Shut up
Sister in law
Me and brother Yang can't help ourselves
You seduce my husband
You still walk tall?
How did your parents teach you?
It's ok...
You live to be a mistress?
Zhizhi, go home
You walk tall, right?
Zhang Zhizhi
Why are you speaking the harsh words?
You still defend her
Are you insane?
You are crazy
Hello
Don't cry
What happened to you?
Where are you?
Siyu...
Zhizhi
Zhang Zhizhi, see
What are you doing?
Enough
You need to slap him back
What do you want?
Hit a woman, bloody man
You can go one-on-one with me
Enough...
Siyu, calm down
Which side are you on?
Calm down, why stop me?
Calm down
Figure out what's going on
Liu Yang
Why did you slap Zhizhi?
Stop asking nonsense
You need to apologize to Zhizhi
I am sorry for slapping her
I apologize
I treat you wholeheartedly
How can you do such a thing?
How could you?
I did not do anything
You did nothing
You say, you did nothing
Didn't you give her the thermos cup, did you?
And the scarf
She gave it to you, right?
How could you do this?
Even if I do something, you shouldn't make a fuss
What about my reputation?
Reputation?
You would not do such a thing if you care about your reputation
I have said, I did nothing
Fine...
Liu Yang
Everyone, calm down
I think you should take a stand now
You will pay attention to it in the future
Don't make Zhizhi worry about you
We should get over it, ok?
Zhizhi
I can't
I won't live with him even he can't justify himself
Divorce, no big deal
You are so ridiculous
Divorce
How can you say divorce?
I should be the first to mention divorce
How can you mention divorce?
Zhizhi
Why are you crying?
You dare to scream at Zhizhi again?
Enough...
Siyu...
Xiaoling
Go...
Go
Asshole
Ridiculous
Calm down...