# Google translate version for your reference #
Xiaoling
you've changed
I just want to understand
Although I can't change him
But i can change myself
As long as I don't pursue perfection
He is perfect
This makes sense
President Wang
I pour you water
Ok ok
traditional Chinese medicine
Then i tomorrow
Just send you the contract
it is good
She
More and more like you before
Everyone is changing
Only you are still standing still
Why do you say that
People are in love now
Who depends on age
Look at that so so so
That's too much
You say Guan Xiaotang
Yes indeed
Look at others
Be generous and sweet
The appearance is also up to standard
Also attentive and considerate
People buy you nuts
Nourish you
You actually rejected him
You are simply a treasure
the first
That's called violent things
second
I reject him, it has nothing to do with age
What does it have to do with
He is not at all
The person i want
Then who do you want
Do you still want Chen Yiming?
Xiaoling
Nothing
She said it herself just now
I'm fine
That's good
Ok
Really passed
Business
Gain or lose
Feelings
Gain and lose
There are high tides and lows in life
Everything
Nothing more normal
The key is
What's next
Then how do you go
Keep going
Continue to be myself
I go first
Sister Siyu, invite you to dinner another day
You take it and eat it on the road
it is good
Really busy
Didn't even take a sip
That's too late
did you
Isn't it like this
You are the same Zhizhi from before
More and more like
Flowers are good times
Parenting Encyclopedia
How do you even parenting
All watch
Prepare
why
no reason
I disagree
I'm not here
Asking for your opinion
I am venting with you
There must be a reason
The company is in difficulty
Layoffs are normal
Even if you cut it, you can't cut her head
She was specified to be laid off
Who are they
President Wang
She why
Can't live with Zhizhi
I do not know
Since this woman came to emerald
Break things one after another
Huizhong
You are afraid of her, i am not afraid
The big deal cuts me too
Huizhong
Have you remembered the numbers?
When I put it there
More convenient
And this, you remember
Handle with care
I understand, brother
Yang brother
came back
Been back for a few days
that
no need
You are moving
Yeah because of the laboratory
No results
The school wants Teacher Gao to change direction
Teacher Gao is not willing
So he resigned
Your experiment
Teacher Gao sold the house
continue doing
But now the money is gone
The school wants us
Free up the lab
So we can only move
how about you
I am sure
Follow Teacher Gao
Yang brother
Sorry
Blame me
If it wasn't for me
You won't lose that job
no need to say sorry
I'm fine now, really
But you and Zhizhi
But came to this point
This matter has nothing to do with you
That's all my own fault
Yang brother
I come today
The first thing is to apologize to you
Second thing
I still want to go back to my battery
So come to ask you for advice
Now the battery industry
The latest development trend
If it's this topic
You should ask Teacher Gao
He must see more comprehensively than me
But teacher Gao, you know
Sometimes thought
Different from everyone
I just want to hear something different
Siyu
President Wang
You haven't changed at all
Still the same as before
I think
You should be the same as before
Is professor Gao there
in
I have something to do with him
There please
please wait a moment
I go in
Can't make it
I said I moved it in two days
It's been three days
How long is the delay
Not finished yet
Sorry
We are moving recently
A bit messy
It's ok
Sit down
Teacher Gao
Professor Gao, hello
Hurry up
If you don't say anything, go quickly
I'm busy getting angry
I came to you last year
Do you remember
I remember 20 million
Want to buy me
60% of the shares
Good memory
How much do you plan to pay this time
Ten million
Less than last time
Professor Gao
Now and then
Two years ago
There are still many people optimistic
Without membrane battery
But now
Connect to your university
Have stopped this project
That means there are not so many people
Optimistic about this project
The project has no future
I can pay 10 million
Is already the greatest sincerity
Since there is no future
Why are you coming to me
I admire you
You must really admire me
You should give out 500 million
Teacher Gao
If this money is my own
I give out 500 million
There must be no problem
But this is shareholder's money
I can't mess around
Professor Gao, I know
You for this project
Already got in
All the savings
You are now moving the laboratory
Not because
Can't pay the rent?
Does this have anything to do with you
You have the heart to let yourself
A project with so much effort
All the work done
Professor Gao
As long as you sign
Ten million will arrive immediately
You can continue to develop
Liu Yang see off
Professor Gao
I'm sending charcoal in the snow
President Wang, you never
The master of giving charcoal in the snow
Taking advantage of the fire is your business
Siyu, are you treating me
What's the misunderstanding
misunderstanding
Others may misunderstand you
Made me misunderstand you
too difficult
understanding
Because of the matter between me and Yiming
Your heart is not happy
Chen Yiming and I
Has nothing to do
You and Chen Yiming
Has nothing to do with me
Because of emerald
You have an opinion on me, right
Siyu is like this
People
All have different identities
Just like me
I'm your friend
But me too
Lvbao's chairman and general manager
I have to be responsible to shareholders
Stop the employee
Don't stand up again
I told you if you were me
Will make the same choice
I do not know
Why haven't you left yet
Siyu
Let me teach you a lesson
Send charcoal in the snow and take advantage of the fire
indeed
The same thing
Just a different angle
I will teach you today
What is giving charcoal in the snow
Teacher Gao
I put all my savings
Donate all to your laboratory
And there are no strings attached
Are you angry with me?
Yes
I just want to suppress your limelight
Your impulsivity problem
Haven't changed
I can't change it in my life
Siyu
I tell you with the utmost kindness
You want to compare with me
Too far, too far
Just your money
Not enough people to spend money
You still invest
You still dominate my limelight
Save your life
Impulse is a price
I'm not afraid
Have you finished
Professor Gao
It seems that the timing is not good today
next time
Waiting for others
Let's talk together
Farewell
Not send
It's not you who are you
My name is Li Siyu
Is Liu Yang's friend
Hello there
I have listened to your class before
right
That one
You really want to spend this money
Donate to our laboratory
The words have been said
I found the bank card
Can it be collected back
Thank you
Great, thank you so much
Thank you so much
Great great great
This
How much is this
Over fifty thousand
Thank you
Not even the electricity bill
How much do you need
five million
Teacher Gao
Then you just
Why not promise Wang Ziru
She spent 10 million to buy me
60% of the shares
This is insulting my research
Also insulted my IQ
Five million you said
What does it mean
I have now
Found a breakthrough
As long as there are five million
I'm within a year
My membraneless battery can succeed
Teacher Gao
You take this money to pay the electricity bill
I'll help you raise the remaining five million
what do you mean
Tell me about your conditions
Teacher Gao
You know your laboratory
Why are you desperate?
You have no shortage of scientists
But lack of me
Understand battery
Understand business operations
Operational talent
I don't want salary from today
Officially join your team
Raise funds specifically for you
Escorting your experiments
but
The whole industry is not optimistic about us
The second time Wang Ziru
Come to Teacher Gao to talk about the acquisition
This woman
No smell of blood
Never shot
She opened the price so low
It proves that she knows the risks are high
Teacher Gao didn't say
Have you found a breakthrough?
In the past ten years
I have been one hundred and twenty-seven times
Found a breakthrough
But later found out
These breakthroughs are all dead ends
And this time
Also very likely
Is this result
so what
The five million you raised
It's possible to lose money
Don't you lose everything?
I haven't experienced it
Not afraid
I'll call you later
Zhizhi
Human Resources Department
Notified you
Sister Yuan
I'm not really bad
Zhizhi
You are very capable
And never
Dragged the sales department
I have been in business for more than ten years
Brought so many apprentices
Your understanding and ability
Absolutely ranked top three
Then why
No one was laid off
Only me
It is said that
This is the board
Direct instructions
Board of Directors
President Wang
Yiming
I'm not late
No time is just right
Tell everyone
President Wang has arrived
get ready
President Wang
You are going to receive two awards today
One is the top ten of the year
Power battery company
The other one is
Customer Trusted Product of the Year
After receiving the prize
There is a press conference
Then I invited almost
Thirty media reporters arrived
So much
If you want me to improve
Emerald's valuation
You have to do this
it is good
Come, give the pen to Mr. Wang
Take pictures
I look at the photo
Okay
Take the pen
I knew that Mr. Fang was here
Fang always participated in another forum
Also very important
Tell me the guest is waiting
Award recipients are waiting
Yiming, you come
I have something to tell you
what happened
I visited Gao Zhengdao today
Gao Zhengdao
Correct
Is the deviant
Famous battery expert
Yes
Guess who i met
Liu Yang
He is a student of Teacher Gao
They are in this relationship
Yeah what
You want to find Teacher Gao to cooperate
Yes, I wanted to
Bought his laboratory at a high price
But was rudely rejected
why
Because of Li Siyu
she is back
Think rain to me
There are deep prejudices
because I
How about it
I'll find Liu Yang again
Let him do it again
Teacher Gao's ideological work
Ok thank you
you are welcome
Share the worries for Party A
Is our second party
What should be done
Please prepare for admission
OK, get ready
Yiming
Suddenly
a little nervous
Share my experience with you
When nervous
Just think of something happy
Can resolve this emotion
Really
Let me think
What's so happy about recently
I love you
happy
Very happy
Let's go
Open the door
Come on
Winners please
Ms. Wang Ziru
You said
Just because i'm mom
Just because i am
Siyu's cousin fired me
This reason
This is nothing
I have been in a company before
Just because of the staff
With this boss's zodiac
Is offensive
Cut directly
But on my job
Just got better
I have to start all over again
May also be a good thing
Good thing
Company notify me
Want to send me to Europe
Work for five years
Five years
When will you leave
Hurry up
next month
It's not a few days
Yes
Zhizhi
I want to take you
Susan and Yuwei
We go together
Yuwei and I
Yes
You can bring your family members abroad
And the company every month
Will make up some living expenses
For family
The four of us are in Europe
Will live happily
This
I know
It may be difficult for you
I just learned the news
I am also very embarrassed
I know
You like your current job
I'm not so sure
Will you do it for me
And give up this job
But you see it happens right now
Didn't this happen?
that
Maybe it's God's will
God willing
God wants to fulfill both of us
Chant together
It's okay, don't think too much
Ugly duckling
Out of the bushes
Raise wings
surprisingly discover
My own wings are full of power
It flies to the middle of the lake
Look down and see my reflection
surprisingly discover
I am no longer the one
Ugly duck
But became a
Beautiful swan
The ugly duckling becomes a swan
Ok
All right
Let's read it here today
Continue tomorrow
Ok
Go to sleep
Yuwei
Mom wants to ask you
If you go to study abroad
Willing or not
Are you with Susan?
Ok
I do
Mother got it
Go to sleep
Come
you let me
Investment
Filmless battery development
Unless my head is flooded
Just five million
You always pluck a vellus hair
Came out
You still owe me three million
That's why I tried so desperately
Investing everywhere
Not Li Siyu
If this is your personal business
I can consider investing
Gao Zhengdao
Never vote
why
the first
I am
A leader in membrane batteries
I have always been clear-cut
Against membraneless batteries
second
Gao Zhengdao, just him
I am at odds with him
Guan Zhong and Bao Shuya
It's the master
But later joined forces
Achieved the great cause of Qi State
He studies that stuff
I can't even do it myself
Also achieved great cause
The light has been seen now
After every dawn
What awaits him is failure
Mr. Pan, take a look
Not going
His broken laboratory
I have been there ten years ago
Dirty messy
Behind again
I kindly say something
He even scolded me
Maybe it has changed now
Gao Zhengdao
Can't change it
Mr. Pan, go and see first
Right to help me check
Not going
Anyway, if you are idle, you are also idle
Go walk around
Maybe a plan for revenge against you
It helps
Professor Gao
More than ten years
I don't think you are making any progress
I just haven't improved
Always lead you
You put the prototype battery
Designed it
Who am i
these years
You still make progress
You finally are
Know the goods once
such
I can vote 30 million first
Based on the prototype battery
Let's try again
Solid glass electrolyte
Etc., etc
You are talking about membrane batteries
Of course
Only in this way can we solve Emerald III
Have been unable to break through
Energy density bottleneck
I spent so many years
Research results
Turned out to solve your problems
The low-end problem of low-end gadgets
As long as it can be changed
Human quality of life
There is no high-end and low-end
Understand
You know what a fart
Two great gods two great gods
We had a good chat just now
Why did you quarrel
Let's go
We are not on the same level
Come please
I want to remind you
No membrane battery has no future
You
Study for another ten and twenty years
Still like that
Gao Zhengdao, look back
Short-sighted
Have something to say
Let's not get angry
Gao Zhengdao
As long as you are willing to change direction
I invest money immediately
Liu Yang
Free dog
You
Maokeng stone
Smelly and hard
It tastes better than your copper coin
Mr. Pan, Mr. Pan, don't go
You let him go
We can
Chat again
I don't cooperate with such people
I would rather
Blackmailed by someone like Wang Ziru
I don't follow this
Self-righteous people cooperate
Mr. Pan, we have another plan
We can talk again
Hurry away hurry away
Don't let me see
what
Teacher Gao
what happened
Thirty million is gone
Not afraid
Wait for the battery to be invented
People looking for us to invest
From here to the Oriental Pearl Tower
But now the situation is
We have no money
Membraneless battery will die
Teacher Gao
Now it's us begging
You this
Your temper
I am this crazy dog ​​temper
Next time
I don't care about investment
You, you decide
alright
what
five million
Four million is fine
Three million is fine
of course
Six million best
Sister Siyu, I believe you
What you think
There must be nothing wrong
but
I really have no money
I am the most
Can only take out fifty thousand
No, do you believe her
We all have no money
I'm not talking about you
I mean people around you
thank you all
Zhizhi
What are you
You promised him
Ok
Zhizhi
in case
You are still doing sales
You will agree to his marriage proposal
Go to Europe with him
I do not know either
Sorry
Siyu, don't say that
I was laid off
Of course there is also our relationship
But it also shows
I haven't created enough value
If i can do it
Irreplaceable words
That company
Won't fire me easily
No, Zhizhi
As sales
You are already excellent
I want to thank you even more
if not you
I do not even know
I can do sales myself
Don't even know
I still have these potentials
But now you have to give up these
Why don't you think about it
What Zhizhi got
A down-to-earth husband
Stable life
Complete family
These are not for money
I don't want to repeat the old thing
What do you mean
Sister Siyu means
Before Liu Yang's accident
I also have a stable life
Complete family
People are different from people
Liu Yang and Su Su, what?
Not the same
You are different from her
She loves it by nature
Fight and kill
But don't forget
Zhizhi she said
Before meeting customers
She blushes and heartbeat
What does this show
this means
The customer is her love
Work is her love
Zhizhi's rings are all on
This is what people choose
Let go, respect
What are you doing? Let go
People choose
Ok ok ok what are you doing
Okay, stop making trouble
Stop it
Don't make trouble
Okay, don't make trouble
Ah don't make trouble
Stop making trouble with you
five million
I didn't want to
Talked to you
But she is my only sister
Did you bring the project plan?
let me see
What?
Just briefly introduce
What are the advantages of this project
This project is very promising
You also know new energy
This project has prospects again
But in this industry
Not all companies are good
My sister was in Lvbao Group
Sales for ten years
She has the resources and channels for sales
You confused the concept again
Good sales and R&D are two different things
Say again
No matter how good the sales are
Not necessarily equal to
Is a good CEO
I want her to come and talk to you
I don't think this is necessary
According to your description
Your sister
Should be a high risk appetite
She must know one thing
put all one's eggs in one basket
I was right
Your entrepreneur
Isn't it all like this?
wrong
The most important quality of entrepreneurship
Is the desire to survive
That is
Can survive
that
Then you don't invest
You treat her as family
From the perspective of family
Help her
Can you lend her this money?
right now we
No legal marriage
So i can't
Help her from a family perspective
that
If I ask you to borrow it
In the prenuptial agreement I gave you
Chapter One Part Two Article 7
Before marriage i treat you
No financial obligation
Chapter Five Part Three
One of them is after marriage
Maintained by marriage
length of time
And the number of children
You can get a fortune
Corresponding cash payment
And this sum
You can freely control
what do you mean
Not borrow
So we need
Sign an agreement before marriage
how about this
To know each other
Rights and obligations
This way
More clear and specific
Put an end to the future and the present
Cause unnecessary disputes
understood
Can i order
Ok
Susan
Dad, I want to eat ice cream
I want to eat ice cream
Dad get it for you
ice cream
Mango
Ok
it is good
Last time I sent WeChat
The thing I told you
How are you thinking about it
what's up
It's my cousin
Is your cousin's project?
If this is
If you need help
I definitely didn't hesitate
But you let me put the money
To lend it to your cousin
I think
inappropriate
why
What about this project
It's too risky
You say in case of failure
Will affect first
The love of your two sisters
Besides
Our relationship will also be out of balance
But my cousin
I'm determined to do this
I want to help her
Then you let her stop early
Look
With her qualifications, right?
To be an executive in a big company
Isn't that more than enough
Why is it so hard
But she just came out of a big company
Don't want to go back
that
Let's take 10,000 steps back
Even if she succeeds in starting a business
That as a woman
Do you think she is happy
Not so absolute
I'm talking about high probability
Think about it
A woman who has a successful career now
Part of married life
It's not perfect
so
Find a
Work locally
Find a suitable man to marry
Is this a correct answer?
What do you think
Women will eventually return to the family
is it
Can't generalize
Then tell me
You say this home
The pot can't be opened
Let's talk about return
It's not realistic
What if the family income is high
High family income
I think it’s okay to be alone
If you take care of your home full-time
Isn't it okay?
Perform their duties
Come, Susan
Come, let's come out, OK?
it is good
one two Three
Ice cream is good
Ice cream is ready
Come and ride high
Our ice cream is here
Thanks sister
You're welcome
Goodbye sister
Bye bye
Go
Dad, eat
Dad take a bite
Thank you Baby
Look at their bubbles
did you see it
Come one two three
Yu Wei
Ok
Dad ask you something
OK
Are there any uncles lately
Come find mom
No
Ok
Do you like it
Come out to play with dad
like
Do you like it
With mom and dad
Come out and play together
Also like
Then you have to learn to ask
do you know
When I come out with my mother
Call dad too
OK
Then let's talk to Susan next time
And Susan's father
Dad comes when we play together
Who is Susan's father?
It's Susan's father
that
Where's Susan's mother
never seen it
But once Susan told me
Her father asked her
Willing or not
Let my mother be her mother
Susan said yes
Say so
Susan and her father
Often with you and mom
Are you playing together
Susan is my best friend
We every week
Have to play together
And go to elementary school in Europe together
Who said you want to go to elementary school
Susan said
Susan's father said
Take my mother and me to Europe
I didn't say when
I do not know either
Anyway soon
Dad, take another bite
Read the prenuptial agreement, right?
not yet
Shouldn't
Ordinary people's reading speed
In every minute
Two hundred to four hundred words
A person who is good at reading
In six hundred words
Even if you are
Slowest reading speed
Read thirty minutes a day
Ten days should be finished
So
Do you have dyslexia
I have no dyslexia
I just watch things slowly
I've been slow to see things since I was young
Besides, I have to look and think about it
it is good
I'll give you another 30 days
Thirty days later
We enter the next program
Row
I hope within this year
We can start the wedding process
If in the prenuptial agreement
If it takes too much time
He Mu, do you love me
Why are you laughing
I still can't understand
Women for
Things with established answers
Why must
Heard through the other person’s mouth
To be sure
Did not understand
This may be between men and women
Huge difference in thinking
Also because of this difference in thinking
So that humans always keep
Curious attitude towards marriage
I feel a little sick today
Go home and rest