[To Dear Myself]
[Ep8]
Director Wang
This is tender plan?
Yes
Have you checked it?
Mr. Lu
I received it this morning
I browsed it
I didn't check it carefully
Ok
Check it carefully now
The fourth row of the third page of the attachment
Mr. Lu, I'm sorry
I stayed up late and I was muddle-headed
I mistook the numbers
And the first row on the fifth page
Mr. Lu
Sorry, I missed it
I was just browsing and found the low-level errors
I'm sorry...
The depth and quality of tender plan will determine the success
It also reflects the company's management level
Your tender plan is going to ruin our reputation
President Lu, I'm sorry
It's my negligence
We will recheck it immediately
Liu
You just said, stay up late
You want to blame me that
I didn't give you enough time?
No... President Lu
We have enough time
I didn't arrange the time well
I will give you another two weeks
If you still can't do well, I will leave it to someone else
President Lu
What's wrong with you?
It's ok...
All these are ok
All...
Wu, come with me
What's wrong, mate?
Look here
And here
What's going on?
I...
Wei Yayun
Come over
Hurry
Tell him, what you did
You did this?
Yeah
This is common sense, you don't know?
And here
Compared with the previous paper,
you just need to change the order
You can't even do this?
And here
You don't know or it's your carelessness?
Sorry, I was negligent
Just because of your negligence
the tender plan failed
You wasted his time
What's in your head?
You want to end your internship like this?
I think you should leave now
Enough...
Go back to work
Young people are so unreliable now
I was thinking it's easy
And I wanted to give young people more chances
So I left it to her
I didn't expect...
Sorry, mate
I will go to change it...
I won't make the mistake next time
No need
I'll do it myself
You don't trust me?
Wu
I am busy now
We will talk about it another time
Ok, talk about it another time
In the lineup, Doudou almost knocked Miaomiao down again
Really?
Also pushed my William
Yes
He also provoked my Xingxing
Does Doudou have ADHD?
Yes
We should say something
Our kids' class can't have an insane classmate
What should we do?
Is it a bit discriminatory?
Doudou almost bullied all the classmates
If all the parents turn blind to it,
teachers can't do anything to him
we need to do something
So what should we do now?
We can write a joint letter
Joint letter?
Ok, then we ask the parents to sign it
Yes, it's a good idea
It's ok?  Well, it's a deal
Yes...
It's almost done now
Turn on the lights
So beautiful...
Look, so beautiful
The color is so good
Beautiful
Nowadays, kids are so happy
Yes
All because you are a wonderful mother
Yeah...
Let me tell you
The party is so great
In the future, we should hold more parties like this
The color is so great
Yes, see
So pink, it's like in a fairy tale
Right?
Look
It's a good place
Yes...
We should be well dressed at the party
Of course
Of course, let me think
Earlier on, my husband bought me a nice dress in Australia
I'll wear that
Last month, I ordered a gown
I will wear the vintage dress grandma left me
Vintage dress?
I didn't see it before
Yuwei's mom
You can't dress so casually till then
I...
Yeah, Yuwei's mom
You need to wear something special
Yes
Look at your shoes and bag
You need to change it
Otherwise it will be so unsightly
I wear so because I have to do something
Yuwei's mom
Come, have some tea
After I finish this
Thank you
Which kitty is hiding in the quilt?
Let me see
You are back
Mom
You're back finally
What's wrong?
She doesn't like my storytelling
She is so naughty
I want to hear mom's The Daughter of The Sea
Ok...
Come, here
Let your mom tell you a story
Ok, I will tell you a story
Here
Come, I will tell you a story
Come
Deep under the sea live a grandma
and six beautiful princesses
They have no legs
But with a fish tail
They are mermaids
Princesses mermaid are very beautiful
Especially the youngest one
Yuwei, come
I have something to ask you
Doudou often bullies other classmates, right?
Doudou likes to provoke others
But he doesn't bully others
Did he provoke you?
He threw the grass in the garden to me today
What did you do?
I just ignored him
Did the teacher know this?
Teacher knew
Teacher criticized him and he apologized to me
But soon he became naughty again
He went to tease Miaomiao
Then Miaomiao cried
So other classmates dislike him, right?
Sometimes yes, sometimes no
Why?
Because he can play as little animals
I like it
Eighteenth century
Rococo Watteau
Boucher Fra
Boucher Fo...
Sixteen
The sun rises
The little mermaid feels she is light and transparent
She rides higher and higher on the rosy clouds
Some voice from the sky
Zhizhi
What's up? Mom
Drink it
What is this? Mom
It's good
You can have a son after you drink it
Mom
It's a bit hot
You should put it there first
I'll drink it later
You have to drink it while it's hot
Drink it
Mom, I'm a little tired
Just put it there first
Why are you so stubborn?
Drink while it's hot
Drink...
No, mom
What happened?
Mom, I...
I...
What did I do?
Are you all right?
I boiled a bowl of medicine
But she refused it
Mom is old and has a poor health
What are you doing?
Grandma, are you ok?
My hands are scalded
Mom, sorry
I didn't mean it...
Zhizhi
Blame me, I am a busybody
I do this for your own good
Don't be angry
I will drink it next time
I will drink
Don't wait for next time
Yang
Mom, what?
Get some medicine in the pot for Zhizhi
It's hot now
No, you...
Never mind my hands
Go now
Hurry
Grandma, I will blow for you
Ok, baby
Drink before it's cold
It's late at night, don't make troubles
Drink it
Who?
Help...
Help
Gu Xiaoling
You need to return my money now
I...
When do I owe you money?
Miss Gu
I have the loan contract you have signed
You...
You are from Chunfeng Company?
Yes
The deadline is next month, right?
According to the contract, you need to pay each Thursday
Impossible
See it yourself
Page 7
How could this be?
Ok
It's Friday today
According to the contract
it's one day overdue
You need to pay 6600
Give me the money
You lied to me
You still want me to give you money
Miss Gu
Don't be afraid
You should know the consequence of not repaying the money
What do you want?
Repay the money as soon as possible
Mom
Here's your favorite steamed buns
Mom lined up for half an hour to buy it this morning
Thank you, mom
Zhizhi
Drink the medicine before eating
Mom
I can't drink anymore
Why?
I got up three times last night
I didn't sleep well
That's right
Huang said, citizens have poison in the body
This medicine is to clean your poison
Come, drink it
While it's hot
Liu Yang...
I am running late
I have to go to work
It's early now
It's urgent
I have to go early
Are you full?
I am full
Ok, just go
Don't be late
Ok  -Medicine
Medicine
Yuwei, be a good girl
Ok
Zhizhi
Drink the medicine while it's hot
Be careful, it's hot
Mr. Liu
Sit
Thank you, Mr. liu
I am sorry that I said the harsh words
I hope you don't mind
No
Mr. Liu, you are right
Wu is a bit alarmist
Do not worry
As long as you work hard in the future
and don't make low-level mistakes
you will pass your internship
Thank you, Mr. liu
Don't cry
Dry the tears, let's eat
Sister Ziru, here
Why only you? Where is Yiming?
He has something to do
Overwork for Caijin's market value?
Kind of
Sister Ziru
I want to tell you something
I declared the fight with sister Yuan officially
Finally you follow your heart
Actually that's because I have no choice
I want to ask you a question
Is it possible that sister Yuan
and I will make up with each other?
Everything is possible
Let's go
Some people say Membrane-free energy storage system
can only be academic interest
It's not feasible in business
It's utter nonsense
My reason is
combine the respective advantages between
membraneless energy storage system
and hydrogen bromide chemistry
Combine these two limited systems
We will get a better result than either of them
His point of view is totally opposite to my president Pan's
Pan Zhiyong
Quiet
Traditional membrane battery's membrane, and catalyst
accounts for half of the cost
But what about this membraneless battery?
It doesn't require membrane
And it doesn't require cathode catalyst
It just needs a small amount of anode catalyst
If the research is successful, all the brands on market
like Beike, Deke, GNB and Lubao will die
He is defaming our Lubao
That's all for today
If president Pan is here, they will have a fight
I am looking forward to it
That's all
Professor Gao
I want to ask a question
Ok
If the question is too low, I will throw a tantrum
You say, membrane battery has come to an end
But do you know
Lubao's the new membrane battery Lubao III?
It is said that all the indicators of Lubao III are ranked first
In the times without a hero, it's the world of villains
So you mean the hero is your membrane-free battery?
Let me tell you
If my research is successful
Pan Zhiyong's Lubao will come to an end
When will your research succeed?
When the time comes
Professor Gao, I have another question
Play the lute to a cow
I didn't want to come
But they insisted
Sister Ziru
You want to vote his so-called invention?
I'm a little interested
You should vote Lubao rather than his battery
Our company is preparing for equity financing
Really?
President Pan said it himself
Sister Ziru
Xiaoling is in trouble
I have to go now
Do you need any help?
No
Bye
Ok
Professor Gao
New products in the new energy market are cliches
But your research is different
Your research is so revolutionary
Finally someone can understand it
Can I go to your laboratory?
Please, lead the way
Professor Gao
How much money do you need for your research?
20 million
I will make a breakthrough with 20 million
20 million is not much
I can pay the money
Great
But you need to tell the college
The donation is for my lab specifically
It's my investment
Ok
You still need to talk to the college
What if I just want to talk to you?
What do you mean?
I want to set up a company for you
You want me to leave the college
Professor Gao
As far as I know, the college has been cutting our research fund
Some of them want to close your lab
You know a lot
They have seen your research as chicken ribs
I believe they are willing to sell our previous research results
And then?
Then?
Then you will do research without concerns
in your own laboratory
You don't need to worry about the money
You must have a condition
I just want to be a shareholder
How much?
Sixty percent
20 million
With 20 million
You want 60% shares?
Professor Gao
Angel investment is no more than 30% generally
And we need to have a stipulation
We need to quintuple it in five years
But if I can do it
I won't be like this now
Yes
Actually you can't even guarantee
you will make a breakthrough with 20 million, right?
Professor Gao
People are not optimistic about your research
More than 50% people think it's futile
More than 90% people think you won't succeed
The most authoritative scientific journal predicts
It takes at least 2 decades to develop membrane-free battery
And achieve the marketization
So why are you here?
I'm an investor
I have a different understanding of risk from others
I will never accept 60%
60% sounds a bit high
But don't forget
I'm taking 99% risk
Go
Professor Gao, let me tell you
I believe no one will spend so much money and time
in investing such a risky project
I'm going to work
Work
Ok
This is my business card
If you change your mind, contact me
I just put it here for you
Bye
Don't cry
Say something
I needed money
So I borrowed 100,000 from a company
You needed money
Why didn't you tell me?
You just paid 130,000 for me
I couldn't ask more
And then?
I borrow 100,000
I need to pay 140,000 in two years
6000 per month
I don't know why I have to pay 6,000 per week
How could this happen?
When I signed the contract, I didn't check it carefully
It's such an important thing, you are so careless?
The contract is so thick
I can't read them all
Serve you right
Sister Siyu, stop scolding Xiaoling
She's sad enough
They came to ask me for money yesterday
I had no money
They just...
All my contacts received the text message
It's so disgraceful
Who are you looking for?
Miss Gu, your friends are here
Great
How's it? Can you pay today?
No
Ask a friend or relative for help
You sent a text message like that
Who would lend me money?
You are so eloquent
Let me tell you
If you don't repay today, I will be tougher on you
Why are you so rude?
We are here to help Miss Gu solve the problem
Not to scare her
Miss Gu
If you really can't repay the money, I have an idea
You can borrow money from another company
You should repay me first
It's trap loan
Don't do that
Then you can pay it for her
Great
106,000 in total
Repay the money
Miss Gu
You have seen our means
And we also gave you idea
The rest is up to you
Go
We will come tomorrow
You cheated Gu Xiaoling with the contract
She didn't know it
It's ok
But you broke in and smashed her things
You pushed in
What do you want?
I will sue you for violent debt collection, burglary
and attempted rape
Believe it or not, I will kill you
And intentional injury
You will be put in jail for ten years
Miss
You are framing me
Yeah, I frame you up
You think only you two are rogues in the world?
Zhizhi, call the police
Don't move
Xiaoling
Call for help from the window
Don't move
Come
Stop
Help  -Don't move
Help
Sorry...
We are impulsive
We apologize to you, ok?
Miss
It's our work
Why do you do this?
It's ok as long as Miss Gu returns the money
We will pay all the money with intersts off within this week
But you must apologize
And send text messages right away
To redeem her reputation
And promise not to harass her in the future
But...
It's non-negotiable
Ok...
Sorry
SMS
Right away...
You clean it up here
I...
Wu  -I...
Do it now
Ok...
Get out
Siyu, you are so awesome
Siyu
Thank you
Why do you borrow so much money for no good reason?
I want to study for the master's degree
I need to pay 100,000 yuan tuition
What do you learn?
Art appreciation and art institution management
Are you insane?
No
This is my deliberate decision
Our club starts group buying
The customers will be lower and lower
I have to change the circle
You don't need to change circles
You need to change your mind
What's wrong with me?
You suffered a big loss because of Lanke for not long
You still want to take shortcuts, why can't you learn?
Why do you think I take a shortcut?
And shortcuts could be a good option
Then why can't it be my option?
You can't take shortcuts before you have the ability
What do you have?
You think the rich men are stupid?
You can sweep the board with your face?
Li Siyu
You can't preach me just because you repay the money for me
More than that
I even help you pay off your debt
I am qualified to preach you
I can tell you
You don't need to pay the money for me
Ok
From now on, I don't need your help even if I die on the street
From now on if I care about you again, I am an idiot
Sister Siyu
Zhizhi, leave her alone
Xiaoling
Look
Sister Siyu transferred me 110,000
She wants to transfer it to you
You should pay off the loan first
Sister Siyu doesn't mean it
She is so good to you
Li Siyu
I won't bow to you just because you help me pay off the debt
I will pay you back ten times
But I don't want to see you again in my life
I prepared a great dinner for you
I am so tired today
I will go to see you another day