# Google translate version for your reference #
Mr. Pan, are you back?
came back
I have time on Friday
You come to the company to talk
it is good
how
You start to lose weight again
I want to break up with He Mu
Aren't you satisfied with him
I am quite satisfied with his net worth
It's not enough
but he
Like a robot
I think i'm with him
Almost become a robot
Do you love him
what is love
You and Chen Yiming
That was love before, right?
Don't break up
Don't mention me
So love is not important
Money is most important
Since you think money is the most important
You have already asked for benevolence
What's not satisfied
But every time I date him
I just feel
I am taking math class by myself
Every time I send him WeChat
I'm like
Same as doing math homework
for you
It's really painful
What people get when they fall in love
Cosmetics bags shoes
I harvested
Spreadsheets
Bar graph scale graph
Time is running out for me
I must break up with him
Welcome inside please
late
Today is ten minutes
Bad mood today
Yes
Proper physical exercise
music
And self-suggestion
Can relieve depression
In addition
He Mu
We are together
For a while
You feel
Are we right
What a coincidence
I also want to discuss with you
This topic
You feel it too
feel
I don't believe in feeling
I only believe in data
also
Xiaoling
In the matter of choosing a mate
I am very strict
five years ago
I give my future life partner
Formulated a
Four categories, nine projects
A total of 87 assessment indicators
Then I must have done poorly
After this period of inspection
These 87 assessment indicators
You got 60 full marks
Seven ninety points
Eight to eight points
Six and seventy points
Three sixties
Only three failed
I'm still a schoolmaster
You are far from being a schoolmaster
Sorry
But this result
Let me be sure
you
Is my future life partner
you you
What do you mean
Now that it is clear
I hope we
Future communication
Don't just stay at
Mutual understanding level
But should
Put more time and energy
To discuss
our wedding
And marriage
you
you you
Are you a proposal
You can understand
But those three failed
One is self-emotion management
I hope you will
Able to improve myself
I will also
Improve and enrich yourself
Hope in the future
We can be each other
Perfect life partner
Let's eat
Eat
I'm not here
Did you break up?
Please come in
I don't eat these. I'm losing weight
For your son
I make a cake for Yuwei
Made a copy for Mengmeng
These oils, eggs, flour
All the best
Let Mengmeng eat at ease
Thank you
I go first
Zhizhi
Meet customers
Don't come up
Let’s talk about our products first
First talk about the customer’s product
Thank you Mr. Yuan
What to do next
Put some vegetables
This is also green vegetables
There are so many vegetables here
Do you want to put them all in?
can
Put them all
All put
and then
Then hit it, right?
Hit hit hit
All right
Mom is back
Ok
Have you eaten yet
Yuwei has finished eating
I'm waiting for you
Don't wait for me anymore
Have to wait
Did you take the report?
Took
How to say
Indicators are normal
The doctor said
Just take medicine on time
Daily life and diet
Just pay attention
I can rest assured that
what does it mean
I paid my salary today
Sit down
I can't drink
So take juice instead of bar
What does this mean
Zhizhi
Think of the previous self
Really confused
So to you
Sorry
It's in the past
Zhizhi
give me one more chance
We start again
Yu Wei
Come
Mom and Dad have something to say
You go back to your room and play
it is good
Come
go with
Liu Yang
Let's divorce
Why are you angry
I broke her early
Has nothing to do with that matter
Then why
I have no love for you anymore
impossible
If you don't love me anymore
Why is it so
Take care of me without giving up
We married
You are down
sick
I take care you
It's due love
I'm better now
Also found a job
I don't have this obligation anymore
Even if you don't love me
We still have Yuwei
If we get divorced
What about Yuwei
I can take care of Yuwei
Yuwei is only four years old
Don't you think this to her
Is it too cruel
I don't want to do it for Yuwei
I'm wronged again
Zhizhi
You always said before
I am very happy
And now with me
Feel wronged
Zhizhi
We don't divorce
I swear
I won't do it again
Kind of silly thing
I must treat you well
I am not
Liu Yang before
Neither do I
The old Zhang Zhizhi
Zhizhi, otherwise
We all calm down first
Don't make decisions so quickly
I have already thought very clearly
Zhizhi
Liu Yang
If you still read me a little bit
Just fulfill me
I am in your eyes
Really that bad
Not bad with you
It doesn't matter
The old me
bad
I'm not angry
Really think so
I don't want to go back
The old me
Yuwei and me
The house belongs to me
Wait for me to save some money
I will supply you some more
You see, I finished it myself
Yuwei is awesome
Come
Dad rewards you for a sip of juice
good or not
Yu Wei
Did you do it yourself
No dad to help
Yes
Yuwei is awesome
Come
Yu Wei
Will be like this in the future
No matter what
Have to do it alone
do you know
Let's have a meal together at noon
no need
I still have it at noon
Visit a client
By the way, your stuff
I cleaned up the dormitory today
Come and move tomorrow
If you want to see Yuwei
anytime
Just tell me in advance
Goodbye
Thank you
You go ahead
Just got
Manager Zhao from the Finance Department
Isn't it Pan Zhiyong's person?
This is given to me by Xiaoqiang below
He is my recruit
Call
This boss is Li Siyu
I know
we
Do you have to get there?
We have no choice
Over the past ten years
He has always been
The soul of the emerald
Without him
There will be no green treasure today
He was right
Doesn't mean he is now and in the future
Also correct
Ok
Mr. Pan
Look at this proposal
Who proposed
Wang Ziru
What she wanna do
She only has
23% of the shares
She dare to dismiss me
She's only been here for a few days
This is my company
This is my country
The company is now at a critical time
There are many things to do
This proposal
Can you put it aside for now
right now
I'm afraid not
it is good
Then prepare to fight
Row
I'll go ahead
Eleventh gun three hundred
Insufficient balance
Brush this
Then i
pay in cash
more or less
Twenty-three
Scan WeChat
Eleven short
Ok
Yes yes
Okay, thank you
Wait a minute, give you a small ticket
Why did you sell the car?
Didn't you just give you 300,000?
Hole is too big
Dear Customer
You handled it in our bank
The mortgage has been overdue for three months
Repayment amount principal and interest
Dear teacher Yiming
Your article has become
Dear fans show love
Look at your expression
Fell in love
What nonsense are you talking about
People are a loyal reader
Yes, only loyal fans
You can't develop into online dating
So you can become
Big v
Still big v
I am very tight now
Easy to die
On the way to becoming a big V
So you have to grow up quickly
I'm fine with you
I recently talked about one
One hundred thousand yuan advertisement
If it becomes
I'm not afraid
What if the talk fails
Then I will put myself
I sold my new house
I hurry up
Hurry up and take a big deal
Inside please
right hand side
Hello inside please
Mr. Wang, hello
Inside please
Hello inside please
President Wang
Come here
Inside please inside please
Right hand side
this way please
Inside please
President Fang
Sister Yuan
Please come in
The Administration Department asked that
Li Siyu's office
Free up
Something she didn't take away
How to deal with it
Find a place to put it down first
I put it here
Yeah, put it there
I'll go out first
it is good
I refused her purchase
Later she asked her sister to buy it
Why she did this
President Yuan
Actually Siyu never did
Treat you as an enemy
She made an order
Have started with me
That's because of me
Correct
I remember
then
Liu Yang is still my husband
Sorry
I only found out later
do not be sorry
It's in the past
that time
I was too forced
So I used some
Non-flowing means
Made a sale
I also understand
sometimes
Even myself
Don't look down on me
It's not easy for you
Who is easy
Including Li Siyu
Sister Siyu Sister Siyu
Why are you back
I'm looking for Mr. Pan
sister
come
Why is Siyu back?
I do not know
Siyu sister
I'm looking for Mr. Pan
Mr. Pan is holding a shareholder meeting
It's not over yet
Um not yet
I'll wait for him for a while
Then sit there for a while
Ok
Siyu sister
If we analyze a little
The company's current business situation
And industry status
Will find
The emerald is already on the edge of the cliff
And put the company in
In this dangerous situation
It's Mr. Pan Zhiyong
For the future of the company
Also for everyone's benefit
I recommend
Remove its director
And remove its chairmanship
As a company shareholder
I agree with Mr. Wang's proposal
I respect every shareholder
According to the articles of association
Proposed motion
but
I will tell you responsibly
In the current situation
If the core team is removed
You guys here
Benefit of all
Will not be guaranteed
Hello
I want to say a few words
All these years
President Pan for
The development of our green treasure company
How much effort
Everyone can see it
And now
These play capitalists think they have money
I just want to kick Mr. Pan out of the company
Own the green treasure
We absolutely can't promise
Not agree
Why do you force President Pan to abdicate?
On the credit of Pan Zong first
In terms of shares, Mr. Pan is also number one
No turn
Speak up
Just
Everybody
These few years
The company has never paid dividends
Have you ever thought
What is the reason
This is the company strategy
Do you understand
Just
Mr. Pan
Please explain
why
Put the three million of Lvbao Group
Forwarded the call to the company
Nothing to explain
I am for the green treasure
Develop downstream products
Such a large sum of money
Without board
Did not go through the shareholders meeting
Even the group office
nothing
One of your signature
Transferred the money out
That's because i think
This investment is very cost-effective
Since it is an investment
What about the business plan
What is the return on investment
Has the risk been tested?
Project feasibility report
Where is it
Make investment
Not just looking at the report, looking at the data
Also need courage and vision
Fang Zhan
Lvbao has come to today
Don't you understand these
Then dare you tell everyone
Who is the founder of the company?
There is nothing bad to say
Li Siyu
Her talent
Everyone can see
Three million disappeared in vain
Without any explanation
This is your management
Squandering shareholders' assets
This is your guts
Serious impact on
Emerald brand people
Not only do you not severely punish
Give her a blood transfusion
This is your vision
Pan Zhiyong
Management confusion
Lack of ability
Poor character
Not worth it at all
We all continue to trust
We change chairman
Swap chairman
Change chairman
Pan Zhiyong steps down
President Pan can't step down
Do you have a conscience?
Is your conscience eaten by dogs?
President Pan can't leave Green Treasure
Siyu
This is what you left in the company
The Administration Department put it away for you
I want to apologize to you
Hasn't it been written off?
something
I'm ashamed to think about it now
If you don't apologize
Sister Yuan
That 500 yuan for overtime
Sorry
Sister Yuan
I am sorry about you too
You should work hard
Even your hard work
Threatened my position
I should work harder to deal with
Instead of below
Do some small moves
I mean
The Meiyi Group
I didn't stand up to speak for you
I believe
If not for me
Filing date of Guangcai Lighting
You will definitely stand up and help me
Siyu
that matter
I am also responsible
Sister Yuan
You will always be
My best master
I
Strive for
I will only teach you how to do
Don't teach you bad
I
Respect the shareholders meeting
Voting results
I also respect
Your last choice
But what I want to say is
You are wrong
Someday after all
You will be
Pay for today's vote
Will be your choice
And regret
President Wang just promised
She operates through capital
In a short time
Let everyone here be worth
Up four or even five times
I believe
She has this ability
She can do it
But have you ever thought
Lack of real value support
Market value inflation
How far can i go
Please come in
President Yuan, Sister Siyu
Look at the phone
what happened
President Pan was dismissed
Hard to do business
Making money is hard
But we do business
Do business
Not just to make money
We have to be in competition
Seek long-term development
In business
I'm not ashamed of words
But the profit should be the profit of the world
For a country
Industrial development
Economic boom
Industry is strong, country is strong
I insist
Innovation
And core technology
Is the right way for an enterprise
honestly
Do business without any distractions
Is the duty of an enterprise
Everything package
Hype
Will eventually become a bubble
I was defeated by barbarians today
But i believe
This must not be the final result
I will return
Because i firmly believe
My path for emerald
Although it is difficult
very slow
But will definitely go further
Mr. Pan
Sorry
do not blame you
I have some problems myself
Caused the shareholders who originally supported me
Finally, they all turned to them
But in the final analysis
I am tired of you
When talking about equity cooperation
Wang Ziru is planning today
I promised her
23% of the shares
In her arms
I still don't believe
Sister Ziru would do this
How did you know each other
An accidental crash
She didn't claim from us
Took my own insurance
She helped you so for no reason
Don't you think there is a problem
what do you mean
She contacted me
Is for the emerald
What do you think
I'm a salesperson
Which company
Green treasure
That new energy battery company
You know
I don't need you to repair my car
You don't have to pay
No way
Now it seems
That rumor is also true
What rumors
then
I and three companies at the same time
Talking about equity financing
Huaan
And Shanghai Bank withdrew halfway
I was told
Said that both of these have encountered
From Tianyi Group
Harassment and stress
I didn't believe it at the time
Because i didn't tell her
Who are the other two companies
She has no way to know
Actually Pan can always appoint
You are the sales director
Let me know the management team of Emerald
More confident
correct
You executives
With the representatives of those two companies
Have you met
You said Huaan and Shanghai Bank
she knows
Impossible how does she know
I told her
How could i have
Your stupid subordinate
President Pan, I'm sorry
Don't cry
you you
Dare you cry
I don't recognize you all my life
I do not cry
I won't admit defeat
Green treasure
I must take it back
Mr. Pan
What do you need me to do
you
You just do your own thing
correct
Called the second round of investment
I can't help
You have to find a way
do not worry
I won't admit defeat
Teacher Chen
Business cooperation plan
I have already passed
But Mr. Zheng
I want to see you and then finalize
are you free tomorrow
Available
Mr. Zheng will be at the hotel tomorrow
Will attend a meeting
A few minutes rest in between
I can just chat with you
Ok, see you tomorrow