# Google translate version for your reference #
Who
You sold the house
You still gave the money to Li Siyu
Yes
I didn't tell you
Don't do that
I just think
I should do this
I treat you so nice
Why are you going against me
I didn't fight against you
Do you still love her
I love you
Then why are you selling
Your only house
To support her
I just think i
I feel guilty for her in my heart
Okay, you feel guilty
Ziru
President Wang is gone
I want to see you
Mr. Gong
Ok
What do you want to drink? Tea or water
no need
Only you
Teacher Gao and Liu Yang
Went to the park to see the factory
Entrust me to represent them both
Row
but
Haowen can't get in touch
It doesn't matter if he comes or not
Lei Haowen can be considered
Unique shareholder
He should be there
He doesn't count
What do you mean
I summon everyone today
Just to announce
from now on
Suspend follow-up research and development
Freeze the mass production process at the same time
Mr. Gong
Do you know what i'm talking about
What you hear is what i want to say
Why are you doing this
I am now
The largest shareholder of this project
Your royal gold investment
Only 49%
New Green Investment Teacher Gao Liu Yang
Our tripartite joint holding
Fifty one percent
Mr. Gong
On a unique project
You have no right to speak
Miss Li
Did you forget
You and Lei Haowen
Has invested in new green
Sold it to me
what
New Green Investment Holdings
Unique shares
Also all transferred to
Royal Gold Investment
6.63 of New Green Investment
Plus royal gold investment
forty nine
total is
0.5563
sorry
Now I have the final say on this project
I have never signed
This contract
Did you even include your signature
Don't you recognize it?
What information
Amendments to the articles of association
You signed it all
Come, sign first
Lei Haowen
He won't answer your call
You bought him
You are also one of the investors
Prevent independent research and development
What good for you
This is the decision of our major shareholder
You just need to execute
Who
No comment
When she walked over there
The light here is going to turn on
Your music is about to start
Ok ok ah
And that tune
Take it easy, don't worry
Ok
Follow this rhythm a little bit
Follow her steps
By the time
I might also go from this direction
To this position to her
propose
Ok ok no problem
Lei Haowen, contact me immediately
Otherwise at your own risk
OK, then you guys will be busy
Ok ok
Cook the song a little bit
So good
OK, let's prepare
If you dare to hide
I let you in this life
I can't even see Gu Xiaoling
Are you crazy
Why buy it cheap
New Green Investment
Why lie to me to sign
What do you want
Siyu
I need money to save Xiaoling
You stupid
You thought you did
Will she agree to marry you?
I know you all think I'm stupid
But things are already like this
Hope you can understand
Just for your obsession
How many people’s efforts have been ruined
do you know
Sorry
You are breaking the law
You get me back right away
Xiaoling, come here soon
I have very very very
Very important thing for you
You know Lei Haowen
What did you do
Xiaoling
Last time i asked you to marry me
You want me to change the lantern to diamonds
Now i did it
There are five million
Marry me
Where did the money come from
I earn
How to earn
Investment income
You lied to Li Siyu's money
You sold off the new green investment
Siyu invested three million
I gave her six million
She didn't lose
That company is worth hundreds of millions
You sold it for 12 million
When i sell
New green is not worth a penny
Are you stupid or bad
Xiaoling
Me now
Isn't it the one you always wanted to marry
That kind of person?
the you now
Just a greed
Short-sighted bastard
I really love you
I am real
Really sick of you
I'm wrong
I can not live without you
Why are you
Ask him for the five million
You are not a good thing
Gong Jing started
Planning this
Yes
We were all cheated by him
High teacher high teacher
Teacher Gao
You have to provide sufficient evidence
Prove that you are at
In case of being cheated
Signed contract
such
Before the court
Or arbitration institution
Cancellation or modification of assignment contract
Is there any other way?
If Lei Haowen
Or Gong Jing surrendered
Admit fraud
Then things will be easier
You can call the police
Blame me
I misled him
I can only blame him for being so confused
Blame me for being too careless
If not for
Stop me from marrying He Mu
He won't betray you
It has nothing to do with you
He is an adult
Know what you are doing
Don't fight
I have all of him
Comments on social platforms
He never returned me
Lei Haowen must be found
I think you
Ideas for planning this project
And creative, really good
This cooperation is very pleasant, Mr. Chen
Hope we continue to cooperate next time
Good good
Goodbye, President Chen
Go slow
Ah goodbye bye
Hey
Xiaoling
Do you know where Lei Haowen is
I am also a long time
Didn't see him
Do you know what he did
Don't worry, Mr. Wang
I have arranged
Advance
That day, all media
Will all speak at the same time
Ok
Mr. Gong
Chen Yiming is looking for you
President Wang
Chen Yiming came to see me
See or not
Be entertained
but
What to say what not to say
You know it
I know
Let him in
Mr. Wang, I'll hang up first
Yiming
How did you come
Where is Lei Haowen
What did you say
I'm asking you
Where is Lei Haowen
how could I know
Gong Jing
I give you another chance
You either surrender
Admit fraud
You either now
Hand over Lei Haowen to me
Chen Yiming
Please pay attention to your attitude
I am your investor
Who is your major shareholder
No comment
Nothing in the contract
I can't beat you
Chen Yiming
I don't think you look good
I didn't sleep well last night
Still unwell
Ok
According to the current road conditions
I predict
In twenty-three minutes
Arrived at the Civil Affairs Bureau
Then use fifteen minutes
Complete the formalities
Spend another thirty-two minutes
Back to the company
Half past four
I happen to be able to start a video conference
Are you so anxious?
My life
Are calculated in minutes
In addition
After getting the certificate
We can start
Wedding preparation
Is there news from Lei Haowen today?
You must be within a week
Four selected
Then put
Of these four companies
Advantages and disadvantages
You make me a form
Then we decide
In the end
Which wedding company
remember
beware of the steps
what happened
He Mu
we
Can we be later
Re-certification
According to the plan
Two months ago
We should get the certificate
I'm really in a bad mood now
I feel messy
We have arrived here
An hour later
I have an important meeting
You give me a few more days
I have done
All future plans
Plan can't keep up with changes
Is a loser
Leave to myself
Winner
Never let things happen
Deviate from their expectations
I'm not a winner, okay
Xiaoling
I have treated you
Paid a lot
Can you be willful
Alright
But i today
Just don't want to get this certificate
Can you control your emotions
This is an adult
The most basic ability
You think i have no control
I tell you
From the first sight of you
I've been controlling myself
I haven't slackened for a second
This is a public place
What happened in public
public area
Will wear a mask
Is it fake?
He Mu
I hate healthy meals
I like eating junk food
I don’t like to watch Discovery Channel
I only like chasing gossip
I am to all the elegant things
No interest at all
I'm not elegant nor easy
I'm full of
Low-level fun civilian girl
This is the real me
He Mu, sorry
I do not love you
He Mu, I don't love you
I finally put this sentence
Said it
I'm so cool
what did you say
Your money back to you
From then on we owe nothing
and many more
If it's like you said
You were carefully disguised before
Show you are on me
Still attentive
Are you sure to put all your efforts
Are all in vain?
Ok
A failed person like me
Deviate from the expected track
Is a normal thing
Don't say anything, brother
High mountains and long rivers
I wish you happiness
Remember to check out
Lei Haowen
I broke up with He Mu
Where are you now
Show me up quickly
I want to see you
This royal gold investment
It's really complicated
This is invested by Emperor Jin
Shareholder situation
Nine shareholders
MH Group
89% of shares
Is the largest shareholder
This is information from MH Group
MH Group
Is a holding company invested by Langfei
Correct
This is the information of Langfei Investment
Zhilan Group
Langfei Investment
But Zhilan Group
Not the ultimate actual controller
Tianyi Group
It's from Zhilan Company
Largest shareholder
So i can be sure
Chairman of Tianyi Group
Wang Ziru
Huang Jin invested
Largest shareholder
My friend told me just now
During the Emerald Tender Disturbance
A company called Langfei
Spent 40,000 to buy the navy
Create public opinion unfavorable to Emerald
Naranfei Group
The actual controller is
Also Wang Ziru
Young and Dangerous
This film is ready
My life dream
You still have dreams
Of course
I want to make a lot of money to be the big brother
It's silly to think of it now
But at the time I made an oath
I am going to succeed
I am going to Macau
I am chic
Love is priceless
Go out
what are you doing
Don't pull me
I still have money
Don't pull me out
fast
let me go
Lei Haowen
Thunder you
Where did you die
you
Lady stop
Wife in charge of husband
Can you control
you go
you
How can you
Where did you die
Why are you missing with me
Why don't you answer my call
You are missing you
Why don't you hide
You hit it
Kill me
Anyway i am alive now
It doesn't mean anything
You made my sister miserable
You feel boring to be alive now
Do you want a face
What else can i do
My friend was cheated by me
A thousand-year-old business
I also missed
Except eating and drinking
What else can i do
Lei Haowen
Lei Haowen, look at me
I'm not married
I broke up with He Mu
what
I admit
I am superficial
vanity
I just want to marry the rich
I'm still superficial and vain now
Like money
But I found one thing
Except money
I want some more
other things
what
The dog barks when stealing fruit
When eating fatty intestines
Punch and kick
Broken high heels
Gibberish after drunk
After heavy rain
Someone help me repair the glass window
Lei Haowen
I want you
You go back to lie to me
You really can say anything
Yes
I am in front of you
Can say anything
But i haven't told lies
I hated you
Beat you, scolded you
We never met
I hurt you badly
But i never
Lied to you
but
It's today
You say everything is late
not late
I mean i'm late
I can't look back anymore
The gift I prepared for you
But it's not too late
For you
We both quarreled
I made it myself
I just knew
You want me
Be more comfortable
Help me make up the rent every month
money
I'll give you back
But your heart
I don't want to miss it anymore
But i am now
This virtuous
Why are you doing this
not worth it
Because only in front of you
So I can happily
Be the most authentic Gu Xiaoling
Hao Wen
Come back with me and surrender
Surrender
Surrendering is going to jail
You did something like this
Shouldn't you go to jail
Accept punishment
Then you said so much
You still let me go to jail
Yes i just want you to go back
Go to jail for punishment
If possible
I'll go to jail with you
But you are willing to follow one
Anyone in prison?
Lei Haowen
I want to marry
Is a responsible and dare to take responsibility
Man who knows wrong and can correct
Not a wretched and cowardly
Coward
These things i did
At least three years
Isn't it three years?
Can you wait for three years
I have been waiting for 30 years
I miss these three years
Xiaoling
You really want to be with me
Are you really willing to wait for me
I do
But my ugly words are ahead
I only waited for you for three years
I won't wait for one more day
So you go in early
You can come out earlier
Xiaoling
I am Lei Haowen
Won't let you down again
Xiaoling
Wait for me
Waiting for you
There were some twists and turns in the negotiation process
This is too normal
Yep
President Zeng President Qiu
Don't worry
Final result
Must satisfy you
Good good
Come in
It is you
it's me
Why are you coming to me
Ziru
Restart alone
A foregone conclusion
This is before me
Targeted at Dobu
Made for green treasure
Plan to enhance the brand
Even if you really restart
It will take at least three years
To market
Three years later
I believe Emerald must
Can have new products to resist
Your plan
I do not need
No you must need
Otherwise you won't instruct Gong Jing
Bribe Lei Haowen
By fraud
Got Li Siyu's signature
When did you know
We went to the club to eat before
The person i met
Is it Gong Jing?
What else do you know
Why he would invest
My company and Lei Haowen
Not because of us
How talented
But because of your instructions
I instruct him
Because i really like you
Thank you
Thank you every time
While helping me
Still cautiously
Maintain my self-esteem
Thank you
What else do you know
Li Siyu
Help Liu Yang's mother
Advance medical expenses
The navy you invited
Let the event ferment
Suppress Green Treasure's valuation
Buy low and sell high
This is my instinct
Bribery fraud
Is it your instinct?
Since i'm already
So unbearable
Why aren't you direct
Break up with me
Why are you writing this plan?
Because i want to save
Relationship between us
I'm negotiating with the FCC
Take 23% of my hand
Emerald's shares
At a price of five billion
Transfer to them
You say this time
If someone said
Emerald will be eliminated in three years
Is anyone still buying emeralds?
and so
You plan to sell the emerald
Unfreeze again
I thought so
Gong Jing messed up in the end
FCC just now
Still call me
Say
Want to reconsider
Intend to cancel this acquisition
I remember you before
When buying emeralds
Spent almost 800 million
Correct
But you are now
Forty-nine percent
Unique shares
How can the market value be
Five billion
that
Then it's yellow on the green side
You won't lose money now
Because when I bought Emerald
Increased leverage
And the investors behind
Signed a gambling agreement
A year later
Eight billion will change to three billion
So this acquisition
If it fails
I'm going to lose me
All property
And have all the shares
Turned out to be like this
I'm already standing on the edge of the cliff
The reason why I am unscrupulous
Because I also have difficulties
But you are wrong
Yes
I also regret it
Gong Jing shouldn't be allowed to do this
Are you still willing to accept me now
What are you planning next
Didn't think about it
Ziru
Now the whole thing
Not as bad as you think
I can modify the plan right away
Strive for in the shortest time
Save the public
Trust in Emerald
Yiming
thank you
But I don't think it is necessary
Yes i think it is necessary
Even if it’s the last time
I have to try again
Your method
May have little effect
But i don't want to give up
Ziru
You will always support me
This time
Let me support you
good or not
thank you
Not working in the morning
What are you doing here?
Isn't this you are back
Happy everyone
What's so happy
We have wasted
A lot of time
Stop here
Everyone, work hard
Back to their respective posts
Teacher Gao
Do you want to rest first
Are you alright
Sit down first
Liu Yang
Look at my blood pressure
And blood oxygen
And heart rate
All normal
All done
Wang Ziru suspected of hostile takeover
Destroy the real economy and
Financial management order
Has been arrested
I heard that she also failed the bet
Now in debt
Deserve it
When will Haowen come out
The lawyer is going through bail
Estimated soon
Xiaoling
It surprised me that
You finally gave up money
Marry love
who said it
I want money and love
I testify
She did not compromise
Siyu
Do you have any new plans
Fight for another ten years
Let us fight for another ten years