# Google translate version for your reference #
Come
Your meal
it is good
Please enjoy
Ok thank you
Drink some wine
Ok
Actually I still have good wine in my car
Didn't drive today
Your wine
on
Pretty expensive
I think this barbecue stall
Got it
You still know wine
My friend told me
Say that wine
You can't buy it with money
Actually I don't know alcohol
But sometimes
If you don't understand, you have to pretend to understand
Come on
Just that
The boss who sells my wine
Later I sold a bottle
More expensive wine
After i bought it
I forgot where to put it
what is it call
Romandy Romance
I also checked on Baidu
Never remembered
Sister Ziru, you
Really
Pretty straightforward
Am i honest
Yes this
This is my true feeling
Many people say me
Black belly
Say i have a plan
Say I'm cruel
But in my eyes
you're a
Very wise
Calm and rational
firm
From the bone
Exudes kindness
Such a
A female
Such a high rating
Yes
Am i calm
But i'm here with you
Messed up
Yiming
Actually I have a secret
That day
I didn't see any customers
I didn't forget
Our date
I'm in the office
Every call you make
Every WeChat you send me
Actually, actually I
I saw it all
Sister Ru Ziru, you
Why are you
I
I dare not come to see you
I'm afraid of me
Can't control myself
I have to use
Tens of minutes
Come to calm down
I can calm down
Pick you up
Sister Ziru
Yiming
I
I seem
Like you
Yiming, i know
This shouldn't
do not know
How come you feel this way
In what way
Neither should
Sister Ziru
Yiming me
I
No more demands on you
This is me personally
A one-sided emotion
Me too
Don't need your return
Don't need your response
I don't want to bring you
Any burden
No, sister Ziru, I
How am I?
Yiming
Look at me today
Have the courage to ask you out
Because of me
I figured it out
This is my unilateral emotion
I told it today
Not the beginning
Is the end
After today is over
I won't mention it again
I might later
Will continue to love you
Will love deeply
but I
Won't let you know again
Sister Ziru
Yiming
rest assured
I won't treat you
More demanding
We will
Still friends
still is
Sister and brother
Confidant
Drank this glass of wine
This matter is over
Annie
President Wang
You go take a look
What is Chen Yiming's status now
Mr. Chen came early in the morning
is it
He also handed this
He said nothing else
Said nothing
What about people now
No longer in the company
Shouldn't
Go out
Annie
You go find someone for me to find a way
Inquire about Chen Yiming's whereabouts
as well as
All his future trends
Ok
Have you reported
Not reported this month
My bill this month
Handed in for a week
Not approved yet
Don't mention it
My online promotion fee
It's been half a month and haven't approved
Our company
There won't be any problems, right
Probably
Don’t believe in rumors
What does it mean
This is on the company account
Current balance
This is the employee salary for this month
And various expenses
This is what we should have long ago
Paid for
Arrears to all parties
Recently talked about
Dozens of franchisees
As long as the formal contract
There will be a deposit
I did
Can last a month at most
Unless you can guarantee
Every month
Ten thousand paid new users
And for two consecutive years
Internet is to burn money
Don't burn for three years and five years
Surely no effect
Only you and I know this
I'll find Mr. Pan again
There is only this way
You help me prepare
All financial statements
I happened to report to him
Ok then i'll pass
President Pan, when will you be free?
I want to report to you
The latest development of the call
Problems
Is our company out of money?
What did you say
We have plenty of cash flow
Investors have money
I see on our account
Only forty-three yuan left
How did you know
I hacked Fan's computer
Guan Xiaotang
You're getting old again
What did you promise me
Scared to death
You wait for me to finish
Can you call again
Say
Do you want to carry it alone
I am the boss
I don't carry anyone
You wait
What are you doing
I asked you why
What do you mean
From now on
I don't receive salary
Voluntary labor
Saving endangered companies
What do you eat and drink
What to pay the rent
I live with my friend
Can eat and drink
You can also rub the net
now it's right
Is not
what do you mean
Thanks for your kindness
But your salary
Can't be less
If you dare to refuse
Or return
You go now
Is not
You are taking me as an outsider
Am i an outsider
There is nothing
Insider outsider
All employees
Quickly collect the money
Don't force me to fire you
I'm out of town waiting for my return
Old white
Come over and let me tell you something
Why go
go
sit
What is so mysterious
You just said that the internet promotion fee
I haven't approved it for you?
Yes
how much is it
twelve thousand
Why are you asking this
Look at the phone
This is not in line with the financial procedures
It's okay, this fits
Our focus is to work hard
Come on
I'll accept it then
Teacher Dai
Liu Yuwei welcome you back
Susan Xiaoxiao Brother Haohao
Yuwei, where have you been
Yuwei, we miss you so much
Yu Wei
I found something funny
I will take you to see
it is good
Please with me, please
Yuwei's kindergarten
President Su
I will visit you next time
Cheers
Come on, work hard
congratulations
Come
Thank you
Come, you guys eat too
Sister Zhizhi is back
Working overtime is hard
Come, eat some together
okay, see you tomorrow
Sister Zhizhi
Come here soon
Eat with us
Xinyi treats you
what happened
Got kicked out again
Sister Yuan
Your office is so lively
Just today
Sister Yuan Zi Ting
Go get our latest sample
Bring it to Mr. Luo
OK, wait a minute
Bring Mr. Luo a glass of wine.
Come on Mr. Luo
Thank you
Wish us happy cooperation
Happy cooperation
You have a snack
it is good
Ok
Mr. Luo
This is our latest battery
okay
This is our company
Internal test report
Mr. Luo, what's the matter?
In what I just ate
Is there
There are peanuts
Do you have peanuts? peanuts?
Does this have peanuts
Peanuts
Mr. Luo Mr. Luo
Are you okay, Mr. Luo
Call an ambulance call an ambulance
Call 120
what happened
Is it peanut allergy
Have you taken medicine?
In the bag
Take the bag take the bag
The ambulance will be here soon
how about it
feelling better
Thank you
Hurry to the hospital, to the hospital
Sent to hospital
Walk around, slow down
Hurry up
slower
You really resigned
Correct
why
Can't do it anymore
Isn't it just a promotion and a raise?
I have other other reasons
Tell me something
I haven't figured it out yet
How to tell you
How about you form a group with me
what
What group
You can form a boy group
Not singing
Team Content Monetization Channel
All Qi
Let's start a company
Hurry up
Think about it, it's definitely promising
Hello, auntie
Yiming
The 100,000 you borrowed last time
Can you return it to me as soon as possible
Didn't we say that the end of the year is good?
Recent prices
Isn't it lowered?
Your third cousin is going to buy a house
You say i'm a mother
I should support you
That line
Then I think of a way to get together
it is good
Can you give me before the end of that month
I'll try
Then first
OK, bye
You guys play
You say there is no way now
Can make me earn immediately
One hundred thousand yuan
More ways
There is a book
It's written in the book
what book
criminal law
I'm telling you serious
Serious and simple
It’s the two of us doing self-media together
Earned a million a year
And worry about that one hundred thousand things
it is good
deal
I'll resign when I go back
Come come
Haven't left yet
President Yuan
I am almost the same
Ready to go
By the way, how is Mr. Luo?
Already discharged
This disease comes quickly
Go fast
how do you know
He is allergic to peanuts
My daughter is also allergic to peanuts
So the pastries outside
I didn't dare to buy her
I am at home
Make it for her
That one
Thanks to you today
If this manager Luo
Something happened in our company
Then we
It's all over
that
President Yuan
I want to ask you a question
You said
That one
Mr. Su from Qijue Company
I already
Visited him nine times
Every time I get kicked out
I just want to ask
I face such customers
How should I communicate with him
I was just trying to tell you
You don't need to follow this Su
Then you said
He wants to place an order
For your own related customers
So always resist us
Customers like this
We generally give up
Then I will
So you wait
See you tomorrow
This customer
He likes table tennis
There happened to be an international competition recently
Buy a coupon and send it to him
Thank you Mr. Yuan
You can go back sooner if it's okay
Zhizhi
Let me help you
Thank you
Why is this so much
Frozen food and instant noodles
Bought for my son
how old is he
First grade
It's the long body
Don't you eat these?
It's better than eating takeaway every day, right?
Is there no one at home to take care of him?
Our home
Just me and my son
It's not easy for you
I have to work hard and bring my son
No one is easy
Where do you live, let me see you off
no need
You go back and take care of your son
I will help you put in the car
it is good
see you tomorrow
Lei Haowen and Chen Yiming
Have resigned
They both made one together
Self-media company
He also started a business
You said
Will you two make up?
The same entrepreneurs
Met and met
impossible
I'm serious
How about you two
Because you wanted to start a business
Just broke up
Now he has started his own business
maybe
He can understand you
I went to take a bath
Hello dad
Yiming, what's the matter
Your cousin today
Come to our house for money
Say you from her
Borrowed one hundred thousand yuan
Said if you don't pay it right away
Your third cousin's house
But it's so hot
No house
Your third cousin can't get married
This is a big deal
I heard that you are with the fourth brother
Also borrowed 100,000
Didn't I buy a house?
I can't turn around now
Haven't you all taken out a loan?
Yiming, are you sick?
No mom
You and Mom must tell the truth
Did you have an accident
Mom, I'm fine
Really okay
How about siyu
Not bad
What about you
Suddenly asking for so much money
What's your use
Ma, I really bought a house
What did your cousin say about the money
Yiming
You wanted the six hundred thousand last time
200,000 of them
I am still
Borrowed from an old classmate
Your cousin is 100,000
We really can't help you
Dad mom
Don't worry about this
I find a solution by myself
I'll hang up first
uncle
Siyu, let me ask you something
You must tell me the truth
You say
What happened to Yiming?
I do not know
Why don't you know
I really do not know
He in recent months
Before and after
Borrowed more than seven hundred thousand
We have broken up
When did it happen
Months ago
why
Haven't you already bought a house
Are you getting married
Uncle, I still have something
I'm going to hang up first
He is not necessarily amazing
This name
On five or six platforms
Registered your own public number
Talk about financial brands
Although the topic is relatively small
But the response was good
Now his number of fans
And reading
Are growing steadily
How is the income
His current main income
Rely on manuscript fees and rewards
Several platforms added together
It's about two to three thousand in total
OK, you go out
Ok
Hello, auntie
I transferred you five thousand yuan first
How many
Isn't it 100,000?
Why has it become five thousand
My remaining ninety-five thousand
I couldn't make it all at once
Can you first
Give me a few more days
Row
The end of the month
Can't delay a day
Ok thank you cousin
what happened
Hao Wen
Before the end of our month
Can you get an ad
Don't worry, no problem
OK, that's it first
Ok
Bye bye
Hello there
What to do
Continue water
No thanks
you are welcome
thank you
Your car now
Has been discontinued
Can't sell the price now
You should keep it for yourself
Just speak directly
How much can i give
fifty thousand
Consider yourself
Hey
Where are you
I sell a car
Why are you selling cars
I'm not a relative in my hometown
Is the debt collection tight?
I can pay it back
Just pay back a little
Did you sell it?
not yet
You sell it to me
I give you 300,000
What are you kidding
I am busy now
Do you dare to mention a word of thanks
We are not brothers
I didn't plan to say thank you
Give you the car key
I look down on your broken car
Keep it alone
I still have something urgent
See you later
Lei Haowen
I went to meet a client
See you later
Hello dad
I will transfer you 300,000 immediately
Let's put
Relatives and friends paid back
I'll turn right away
I'll transfer after I hang up
Ok
Good good okay
it is good
Bye bye
Teacher Yiming
The weather has changed recently
Please pay attention to the body
Wait
Please enjoy
I heard
Recently on a new movie
Quite good looking
Shall we go to see after dinner
As planned
After dinner today
Let's go to the bookstore first
Sit for an hour
Then go to the lake
Walk for thirty minutes
Can't it be changed
Can't
By the way, I almost forgot
what is this
This is since we met
all
WeChat QQ SMS
And communication data analysis chart
This this
What's the use of this stuff?
There are
Word count ratio Article count ratio
Response time ratio
Histogram of total time
It can be seen from these graphics
Our communication
It can be said to be relatively smooth
Also have a certain understanding of each other
Oh
After data analysis,
I think our relationship
Can be upgraded again
I recommend
While walking tonight
We can do some
More intimate physical contact
Like kissing
that
Kissing pose
do you have any requests
This one
I think casual is better