[To Dear Myself]
[Ep22]
That intern?
We have told you to break up with her, right?
I have broken up with her
Good to know
I have sacrificed my love and Wei
I am back home now
Look at Zhang Zhizhi
She still makes a fuss
You can't just blame Zhizhi, right?
All blame me?
I think both of you are responsible
Liu Yang is a candide
I didn't see this coming
I remember what you said
Every man has an asshole in his heart
I do not know
I do not know anything
For this family, I get up early and go to bed late
I don't know where I am wrong
It's ok, don't cry
According to my experience, it's no use crying
Crying could help her relax
Liu Yang
Now it's only two of us
Tell me
What's your relationship with her?
I have told you
We are clean
Then why did Zhizhi become like this?
We gave each other little gifts
So she moved your heart?
Liu Yang is timid and conservative
Combined with his performance today
And the cup, and scarf you mentioned
I think even if they fall into love with each other,
now it's just the beginning
No
We can't wait
I am experienced relatively
I think, everyone should calm down
You need to figure out what to do in the future
Instead of being angry here
What's your take?
She is very simple and kind
Also very hard-working
We both come from the countryside
So no matter what I say
she knows everything
I feel relaxed when I am with her
It's like I am back to the carefree times in college
But no matter how good she is
you are married, right?
As a married man, I think I did nothing wrong to my family
Besides house and car loans,
I need to support daughter and wife
I get up early and go to bed late
I have to please others in work
After going home, I need to tolerate my wife's complaints
I have to tolerate in work and at home
My only fault is I am not a robot
I'm tired, bored
Yes, it's not easy for you
Suddenly one day someone appeared
I can smile in front of her
I can forget office politics
I can forget the boredom of the family
Yiming
If you were me, you wouldn't be touched?
What are you going to do?
Zhizhi
You have sacrificed yourself for so many years
Liu Yang is going to be the director
If you divorce now, they will take the advantage of it
Zhizhi, no matter what you choose
we will support you
I won't be with Wie
But Zhizhi makes such a big trouble today
I really don't want to live with her
You won't divorce, right?
Zhizhi
Think it over
What kind of result you want?
Do you want to divorce?
If we really divorce, what about Yuwei?
So I and Zhizhi won't divorce
I won't divorce
If only all of you pick me up from class every day
Goodbye, Yuwei
Bye bye
Zhizhi
Call me if you need help
Liu Yang
After going home, be nice to Zhizhi
Make confession or something
Be a good girl
Come, baby
Go in and play by yourself
Are you ok?
Fine
Every time Xiaoling or Zhizhi gets in trouble,
you will lose your mind, why?
So horrible
What are you afraid of?
I didn't do that to you
I'm not afraid
I just think we need to calm down
Especially their family affairs
If we are too radical, they will have no leeway
I'm so angry
He slapped his wife
He even betrayed her
It's wrong that he slapped his wife
But we don't know what's going on
I think there must be some reason
You know him so well?
No
I think, we have various problems as long as we are human beings
Just solve the problems
All will be over
We won't have this problem, right?
What are you thinking about?
Our problem now is...
When will you resign?
You need to take care of your body
I need to think about it
Now you still have the mood to surf online?
Well, what do you want?
It can't be over so easily
I have apologized
What do you want?
You need to break up with her
We did
I need you to break up with her in my presence
What are you doing?
Call her
No
I will
What's wrong with you?
Give me
What are you doing, Zhang Zhizhi?
No, give me the phone
Zhang Zhizhi
Zhang Zhizhi, open the door
No
Open the door
Zhizhi
Zhizhi, can we have a good talk?
Open the door
No
I am going to break in now
Hello, brother Yang
Are you ok?
Stop harassing Liu Yang
Leave him alone
Are you crazy?
I can tell you
You can't call my mom
I will go to your office
I will let them know she is a bitch
She can't work there anymore
If you go there, we will divorce, I can guarantee you
You threaten me
You dare to threaten me
This is my bottom line
You have a bottom line?
What do you want?
Put it down
Are you crazy?
You bastard
Bastard
Stop crying
It's ok...
Hello, mom
Hello, Zhizhi
You called me just now?
No, I called the wrong number
Are you ok?
I'm fine, mom
How are you doing?
I'm fine
After coming back, the fresh water
and clean air are good for my health
Ok, that's all
I'm going to dance now
Brother Yang, are you there?
Sister-in-law called and scolded me
It's ok
For you I don't care
I am not afraid even if the whole world scolds me
I haven't finished the medicine you bought for me
Your words are still lingering in my ear
I can still feel your kiss
Brother Yang
Even if we can't be together
I will never forget the love you give me
She keeps jumping
Just like the witch said
Every step she jumps is like
walking on the tip of a knife
Mom
Isn't the little mermaid afraid of pain?
Everyone is afraid of pain
But if you love someone
you will not be afraid of pain
you will feel more painful
Dad is back
It's our neighbor
But she is willing to endure pain
She wants to stay by prince's side even if she walks like a bubble
You want to chase me away?
I don't want to see you again
I move out
Dad
Aunts
Good girl
Yuwei is so great
Yuwei
Let me see, you are more beautiful now
So lovely
Look, what I have brought you
Like it?
And nuts
You will get smarter after you eat them
No peanuts
And your favorite
What is it?
Like it?
Yes
Take it
Here, can you take it all?
Yes
Go to play
What happened?
He refused to apologize to me
Refused to break up with her
And they are still in contact
Asshole
But you kicked him out
So stupid you are
Why?
If that woman really steps in, it's too late to regret
Mom
Yeah
What?
Why do you pull me?
My new clothes
It's very expensive
Why do you always persuade her to make up?
She can't decide for herself?
Li Siyu
Can you stop thinking in your perspective?
Zhizhi is not you
Not me, either
This family is her life
She can't live without it
Zhizhi was very independent in childhood
She becomes like this after she marries Liu Yang
So you can get her back to her childhood?
She doesn't need to rely on him
Maybe it's a good option to divorce him
What about the kid?
I can help her
Don't be whimsical
You think you can?
You let Yuwei have box lunch or order takeaway with you?
Zhizhi, do you want to divorce Liu Yang?
I don't know
If you don't want to divorce, you should call him back
Siyu slapped him for you
I believe he won't hurt you anymore
Yiming tells me, before you find this out, they have broken up
I saw that woman wechat him again
Stop thinking about this now
Just ask yourself if you want to live with Liu Yang
To tell the truth
You have never seen the world
Liu Yang is just a rookie
If you want to live with Liu Yang
you should stop now and it's a lesson for him
If you really don't want to live with him,
you should make your decision
Sister Siyu
Should I forgive him?
You have Yuwei
You need to think over what kind of life you want
If you want a happy family
you should let bygones be bygones
We have persuaded them
Why did they live apart?
You should ask Liu Yang
Actually Liu Yang is not a bad guy
He is just too tired
You think he is not bad after this?
To be fair
Zhizhi didn't save face for Liu Yang
So in your view, what Zhizhi should do?
She should understand him?
Forgive his affair?
Even she needs to reflect herself?
Forget it
You are a patient
We are done talking
Liu Yang bullies Zhizhi so
Zhizhi still doesn't get a divorce, why?
Why?
Because the family can't do without Liu Yang
Zhizhi and Yuwei can't live without Liu Yang
What do you want to say on earth?
I want to say
You want me to resign
Did I say like that?
Did I mention resign?
You mean it, I just know it
Chen Yiming, let me tell you
I am afraid one day I will encounter the same thing like Zhizhi
I am not Liu Yang
But you are also a man
You can't think I am like him just because I am a man
No one can guarantee this
Yes, it cannot be guaranteed
But that is the future
I'm talking about the present
The present is the beginning of the future
I must have my own business
I want to be independent
I know
You wish me good
But if you really consider for me
stop talking about it
I won't want to talk about marriage before Lubao's equity financing
Bye
Waiter
More beer
Ok
Right away
President Wang
I saw you over there
It's really you
Why are you here?
Sit...
President Wang, sit down
Why are you here alone?
Where is Siyu?
Siyu, she works overtime
Overtime again?
Correct
Pan Zhiyong
Siyu is such a good employee
President Wang, have some skewers
Ok
I didn't eat lunch and dinner, yet
Really?
Your beer  -Ok, thank you
It's great
Really?
Dude
Help me heat this up
And I need more skewers
Ok, no problem
Thank you
Wait a moment, you're welcome
It's cold?
Don't eat it
Ok
Eat the hot skewers
Want some beer?
Ok
I have good wine in my car
It's better with skewers
Great
Waiter
Two more cups
Ok
Wang
Bring a bottle of wine here
From the car
Your cup
Open it
I don't need cups
Ok
Thank you  -Have a good appetite
You're welcome
Smells good
Just give it to me
Thank you
Wait a moment
Tell me if it's enough
Enough...
Thank you
To coincidence
Do you like the wine?
Yeah
It has a different flavor
What kind of wine is this?
Not important
The important thing is
The mood
You have a good mood today
Outside the company
Just call me sister Ziru
Sister Ziru
Why are you drinking here alone?
Yeah
Quarreled with Siyu again?
No
We just have different views
So serious?
What's the matter?
Two days ago
She fainted suddenly
I sent her to the hospital
Then she went to do the checkup in the hospital
According to the medical report,
her body indicators are higher than the standards
I persuaded her to have some rest
But she thinks I am trying to force her to resign
Actually, I didn't mean that
But she antagonizes me
Resignation is a big deal
Yes, but I
I didn't mean to force her to resign
I think she should take some rest first
After recuperating
she can go back to work
Right?
But she just can't understand me
Sister Ziru, I really...
I really don't understand
I find, the longer we stay together,
the less we understand each other
According to my experience
It's easy to accept someone
But mutual understanding is difficult
Let alone the new lovers,
It's hard to imagine that the couple can understand each other
Sister Ziru
You mean, I should let it go
I mean you still need to have more understandings
Understanding?
Yes
Of course
Understanding is the hardest
Sister Ziru, I...
With all due respect
I just want to ask
Why women are so competitive?
Not necessarily
It depends
Yes...
Previously, I thought she was generous, resilient and responsible
She is very independent
She is so good in every way
But now I feel she can't be so emulative in every way
Especially in life
She can't have only career, right?
I am the woman who has only career
No, sister Ziru, I...
Yiming
You are right
We can't just have a career
Just like the way I came just now
Actually I am lonely
I feel everything is boring
I feel suffocated, surrounded by loneliness
I feel so desperate
Actually I saw your Moment
I know you are alone
So I came
Because I'm afraid
I'm afraid I'm alone tonight again
See a movie alone
In their stories, cry and smile
And then go home alone
It's a long night again
Sister Ziru
If you need someome to talk to in the future
you can tell me
I will be there
Hello
Where are you now?
Siyu
If you don't want to resign
So be it
But I only have one request
Just don't be too tired, don't push yourself so hard
Don't ruin your health
If you don't want to get married now
It's up to you
But I still only have one request
If you want to get married, I must be your groom
Yiming
Siyu
I will try my best to think from your perspective
I will try my best to understand you
I will work hard
I will work harder
Until you have no concerns about the future