# Google translate version for your reference #
He Mu, do you love me
I feel a little sick today
Go home and rest
Welcome next time
Send a position
Lixing, where is the soy sauce?
Inside the cabinet
Find it yourself
Lixing
Do you have a larger bowl
Find it yourself
Stop busy
Time to eat in a while
time to eat
Ok yeah
Susan, let's eat
Hungry
it is good
Let's go eat
Come
Sit down
Wait
Before eating
Didn't I tell you
Wipe your hands clean
Otherwise there will be bacteria
I forgot
Come, dad will wipe it for you
Another
Ok clean
Eat
Just do a little
Quickly taste the noodles
how about it
This is what i have eaten
The best noodles
Really
right
The best one, eat more
Try it soon
This is the life I want most
I'm working hard outside
Where are you at home
Do housework and take care of children
After i come back every day
can be seen
Susan this cute smiley
There is also a bowl of hot noodle soup
Is it tomorrow weekend?
Ok
You didn't arrange it
If there is no arrangement
You morning help me take Susan
Send to training class
My company
Something to deal with
Estimated to be in the company for one day
Workers will come in the afternoon
You come back to look after
And the kids are abroad
It's easy to get upset
If you pass by the pharmacy
Go buy some medicine for kids
I'm afraid she will get sick and catch a cold or something
Come
Some greens
I thought
You don't care about me anymore
I don't want to answer you either
I can't stand it
The temptation of fat intestines
I want to break with you too
But I thought
Can't just lose like this
What are you thinking about then?
You haven't got married yet
Even if you are married
Isn't it possible to divorce?
Even if you stay
In case you want to make one
Extramarital affairs or something
I still have hope
Lei Haowen
If you still want
Be friends with me
Since then you have died this heart
Otherwise I will leave now
Never see you again
It's okay
Don't be angry
Sit down
Watching
You
Have to give me some time
right
Have to make my little heart
Die slowly
Can only be friends
Friends drink
Come on, my favorite sausage
Lei Haowen
If i borrow 5 million from you
Will you lend me
The premise is that you have so much money
I borrow
I might not make it
Then borrow
Don't ask me what to do with the money
Do not ask
I'm not afraid of doing bad things
Don't i know you yet
thank you
You're welcome
Just your brain capacity
Apart from buying bags and clothes
What else can you save
Don't do it again
So excited why
It's alright
Young couple young couple arguing
You still said
Answer the phone
in argument
none of your business
Right right right
If you can really get five million
Enough
Why do you want so much money
not me
It's Li Siyu's prodigal daughter
Why she wants so much money
What kind of project is she working on recently
To invest
I'm going crazy these two days
Why are you blowing on your face?
See who's coming
mom
Did you have fun with dad today?
Happy
I have something to tell you
Just so I have something to tell you
be careful
Ok
Siyu is starting a business again
Still cooperate with your laboratory
Is this reliable?
What do you mean by reliable
Will the experiment succeed?
still have
Zero percent
Zero one hope
So low
Sister Na Siyu is too risky
I understand her
Can do what you like
The adventure is worth it
This is what you want to do
Yes
When graduates graduate
I just want to continue
Do research work
But reason tells me
Have to find a good job
This life
Can sit back and relax
So I got in
The previous unit
You stayed there for ten years
Actually in those ten years
I have moved countless times
Want to change career
But dare not start again
Just think about it
Then now
Is it what you wanted?
of course
Although the income is very low now
But every day is fulfilling
Although the experiment keeps failing
But for
For those engaged in R&D
failure
Too normal
In case
Finally failed
What is the last
Only success is the last
As long as it fails
Not the end
You never did this before
You always seek stability
That was when I was young
Poor family conditions
No cost to make mistakes
So every step
Have to walk safely
But these two years
Experienced these things
I just found
Life is full of accidents
Be cautious
At last
Still fall into the pit
and so
Not so much looking forward and backward
Better choose one
What I like
Throw in
You really changed
You also changed
before
We never talk like this
You never ask
Unexpectedly after the divorce
We can still chat like this
It seems
Divorced
I thought about it
Give it back to you
You decided
what
Yuwei told me
Then you went to Europe with him
Still working
The welfare of their company is very good
After going
Don't need me to work
Do not worry
He treats Yuwei well
Also good for me
Zhizhi
I'm actually quite happy
I have no money
Not capable
If you stay with me
Still work
Too hard
But Susan's father
It's completely different
You follow him
You can live without worry
very good
Liu Yang
I never
I thought you had no money
I know
Zhizhi
You are a good wife
The best wife in the world
I'm not worthy
in fact
I like work
Do it if you like
Don't let yourself be frustrated
You should keep this
I always owe you
I am back
What are you doing
I checked
These bags
It’s more suitable to sell on pollen
A lot more money than a second-hand store
Xiaoling
These ones
It's all your heart
It's annoying to see you
Can you be refreshed
Row
Wait for me to make money
I bought it all for you
double
Double
Deal
Answer the phone
Hey
Xiaoling, let's eat together tonight
Go to that house
Your favorite french restaurant
Today is not our date
I have an appointment with the client
So time is free
We can just meet
A guest from my house
I can not go
Can you see if
Move the time
We didn't meet last week
Can't move
She will leave Shanghai tomorrow
Ok
I wish you all
have fun
in argument
I just want to be able to fight
What's going on
I asked him to borrow money
Not only does he not borrow
Let's go, let's talk about me
Xiaoling
About borrowing money
Borrowing is affection, not borrowing is duty
I think He Mu’s approach
Nothing wrong
But you are my sister
And I asked him to borrow
So what?
the first
You two are not married yet
second
Even married
He has no obligation to help me either
He is so boring
Why should i marry him
Is it because he is rich
Now I need it
Not only did he stand by and watch him
What am i getting married
Xiaoling
Break up with He Mu
Not because
He doesn't want to lend me money
But because
The sentence you just said
Which sentence
You married him for money
What's wrong
Nothing is wrong
But happy marriage
Must be because of love
Not because of money
You still believe in love
I always believe
You love Chen Yiming so much
Don't break up
I broke up with Chen Yiming
It just happens that the love is not deep enough
You two are engaged
Still love enough
Maybe our relationship
Just enough to get engaged
Think of it now
Two people are really together
Need to sacrifice a little bit of self
More need to be brave enough
Face the pressure of reality
And these
I'm not ready
when will you
Want to understand these
Call
After failure
That day
I look at myself in the mirror
anxiety
impetuous
Paranoid
Quick success
Defiant
Such a woman
I hate myself
Why should I ask others
Come to love me
what about now
right now
Don't you think i'm cute
that
If there is another person now
How would you love
I will definitely still
Devote yourself
I hit my head and bleed
Still do not repent
Broke my blood
Can't change
Just in case you hit twice
The wall fell
This world is mine
I wish you happiness
Xiaoling
I wish you happiness too
Don't because of money
Go to marry someone
Only love will starve to death
Let go
I can't tell you
Think quickly
What else can I sell
You see how much my bag is worth
More than a thousand
Let's sell it together
How did I forget Guan Xiaotang
Look at the super heroine I made
Wonderful
Will she sit with me
Zhizhi
Sorry
I didn't keep you
President Yuan
You have tried your best
to be frank
Emerald is no longer
The previous emerald
I don't even know
How long can I stay in Lubao
How old is Yuwei this year
Five years old
When i divorced
Mengmeng is also five years old
President Yuan
Ok
I can ask you
Personal question
Just ask
You are alone
Is it very difficult
Of course
Have you ever thought about
Get back with Mengmeng's father
or
Find another person to marry
Do you think
Two people live together
Must be better than
Living alone is easy
Ordinary people like us
Nothing is easy
Since it's so difficult
Then we pick one
Reward yourself the highest thing
What is the highest reward
Stronger self
Ok
All these years
I am alone with Meng Meng
Encountered countless problems
No reliance, no retreat
I can only face myself
Over time
I am sick myself
Fame
Also not good
But i gained abilities
Gained confidence
And only this
Belongs to me
Wealth that no one can take away
Yes
Before my divorce
Never thought of myself
Can sell
After divorce
I actually did
The backbone of the sales department
Speaking of here
President Yuan, to you
Thank you for taking me in
no need to thank me
I used to be so harsh on you
Don't hold grudges
I have to thank you even more
Fortunately, you forced me
Otherwise there is no me today
Thank you if you want
You are not relying on me today
By yourself
thank you
Thank you dear myself too
Remember
We can lose everything
Just can't lose yourself
remember
Come
I say two
Are you two full?
I'm full I'm full
Do you want to eat more
No thanks
no need
Xiao Tang
Do you want this computer?
Don't want me to move
Move away
You want to like
I'll give you the computer chair
Thanks
Xiao Tang
This drinking fountain belongs to me
Like to dismantle it yourself
Xiao Tang
I took these two lamps
Take it away
Take what you want
Your company
It collapses faster than a call
Sister, I want to hug you
Hug
Lift up
do not move
Motionless
Sister, why are you here?
Do you miss me
You're on the hook
Going to have a
Talk about love
What's going on
Broke down
Yes sister
What do you like
You take whatever
but
I think
It's best for you to take me away
The least valuable here
It's you
Why are you so ignorant?
I am looking for you
You say
How much money do you have
I have no cash
I see
I Alipay
Seventy-three yuan
Yes i still have card
This
This one is half a million
But there seems to be three dollars left
This this seems to be left
More than thirty dollars
This is frozen
This also doesn't work
correct
I still have it in WeChat
There are more than 30 yuan
Why so little
I have always been a pauper
You don't know
Where's your car
Arrived at my friend
Over a million
Look at this
Open a company to burn money
You haven't burned
Had known
What's wrong, sister
You are short of money
Yes
How much do you lack
five million
Trivial
What a trivial thing you are doing like this
I have no money
But Laoguan has
Your dad
Yes indeed
You can find him to invest in this project
Wrap me
Guan Xiaotang
Let me tell you clearly
This is a business
Nothing else involved
You are afraid of me
Use money to coerce you with me
To shut up
It's ok
Doesn't exist
its me
I will use money at best to blackmail you
Be my girlfriend
Never let you and me
To shut up
No, both of us
You say I will beat you
You beat me again, beat me, beat me
Beat me beat me
I don't believe it today
What are you doing
broom
Broom, where is the broom
Broom me
Need to take off pants
Let you hit me
Wait a while wait a while
You spank first
You spank me first
I call my dad
Don't always slap your face
It's okay, just hit and hit
The user you dialed
Temporarily unavailable
Don't answer the phone
Sorry
I'll call Miying
You hit
It's okay it's okay it's okay
You don't hit me
Hello, Miyoung
What about my dad
okay, I get it
Fight or not
I've been lying here for a long time
If you can't fight, you can leave
where to
Go to Laoguan for money
Go
You see it beautiful
let go
As long as your dad
Can give me thirty minutes
I can convince him to invest
Not so troublesome
Tell him it will definitely make money
He must vote
I'm really not sure
That's okay
Isn't it five million?
to him
Don't lose to you
I have to blame others
Your dad often loses money
Last year
Seems to be normal
Above
Meiying
How did you come
I am looking for my dad in a hurry
He invited people to eat in there
I will bring this wine in first
How much did he drink
four people
Have drunk four bottles
Now this is the fifth bottle
Then you send it in
sit
I know his drinking capacity
Let him drink another bottle
100% of your thing
give
Wine is coming wine is coming
it is good
Why is this wine again
I'm happy to drink with elder brother
Laoguan
You have a bad stomach
Drink it again, it's going to bleed again
Can drink with elder brother
Don't talk about stomach bleeding
It turns out that your dad also has stomach problems
Can't drink
He has stomach problems
I do not know
Come, come, brother
I will do it first
President Wang
You can drink more today
thanks, thanks
Not bad right
That one
Bank loan
I have to trouble you a lot to help
Laoguan
It's not that big brother won't help you
It's really you
Company can't make it
You and the company
Be accommodating
Yes, brother
You bother
How about you first
The 30 million in front is repaid
These five million
I will approve you immediately
If you lend me this five million
Let me turn around
Don't say the thirty million
50 million just before that
I can definitely pay it back
Can't make it
Big brother
Let me be honest with you
Now my company
Just a breath away
Just let me catch my breath
I can do anything
Really not good
These five million won't work
That that
Then three million
two millions
As long as you can give me
Loan this money
My company will survive
Brother, I beg you
Laoguan for decades
Who have you asked for?
I will kneel for you
Laoguan Laoguan Laoguan
Laoguan
Woke up
Get up
OK, I promise you
thanks, thanks
accepted
Get up, laoguan
Thank you brother thank you
Thanks big brother
You really
Saved the lives of our family
Xiao Tang
I
I always thought he was easy
Actually it's not easy for anyone
My Father
For millions
I knelt down
I still burn money like this
I really i really
It's useless if you beat yourself to death
Guan Xiaotang, look at me
You look at me
Guan Xiaotang
Now is the hardest time for your dad
If you want to help him
Just walk in generously
Toast some uncles
You have to be sensible
Very capable and confident
Let uncle see
Someone in your family
Business has hope and future
I can get the money I borrowed
They readily lend money to your dad
But your business
You don't care about me
Sister, I have a way
This one
This should be worth some money
Should be able to help your dad
sister
Sorry
Xiao Tang
If you can accompany your dad this time
Get over this difficulty
You are truly mature
Then at that time
Would you still consider me
Your family is in turmoil
Don't love your children
Now your dad needs you
Hurry in
Wipe away tears
dad
uncle
Come come
Come here my son
How much did you drink
Call Uncle Li
Li Shu Li Shu
Come, my respect
Where is Li Siyu
Already inside
Li Siyu
boss Zhang
Position of Group Sales Director
Keep it for you
Conditions are the same
Thank you Mr. Zhang for your love
how about it
When do you plan to start
Come, come and sit
boss Zhang
I have something else to come today
What's the matter
I think
Borrow money from you
How much to borrow
five million
doing what
Research and development of membraneless batteries
That's the one
Gao Zhengdao
The one who has been doing research
You also know him
I heard about it
But this project
Seems to have been
Not going well
The prospects are not too optimistic
All funds are withdrawn
Does this matter
So i came to you
You need to know
Everyone is not optimistic about this project
Everyone is optimistic
It's not my turn
boss Zhang
Five million for a year
I'll pay you 5.8 million when it's due
Then
What do you use as collateral
All my assets including the car
All cast in
Called on that item
Now is a negative generation
There is nothing to mortgage
If there is no mortgage
This matter
I really can't accept it
in case
I use myself as a mortgage
what do you mean
Didn't you always want me
Join Qiji?
If one year expires
I can't pay the money yet
I joined Qiji Group
Work for you for ten years for free
What you said
I really can't refuse
but
I can only lend you three million
Four million in a year
Also use you
Ten-year labor contract as mortgage
Can you accept it
Zhang Yanzhou
You old fox
You know
I accept
Deal
Brother, I'm not free this afternoon
Correct
Cancel the appointment
See you next time
Advance
President Su
Have a courier for you
Just put it on the table for me
it is good
What is it
Sorry