# Google translate version for your reference #
I'm tired
I want to rest
Xiaoling
what are you doing
Today you can't leave without saying
I don't want to follow one
Drunk man talking
Xiaoling
Some things i don't get drunk
I can't tell you
Gu Xiaoling
I love you Gu Xiaoling
Can you be with me
You let go
But i don't love you
I know
I know you do not love me
You don't love me
in your heart
There is no place for me
Not before
Not now
There won't be in the future
Hao Wen
I always think of you as
My most important friend
What do i have
Can't tell boyfriend
But i will tell you
You in my heart
Not insignificant
But i want to marry
What kind of person
You always know
He Mu
I am married
Come in
Manager Feng
what's up
Next year's work plan
Finished so soon
I referenced
The department's work plan for the past few years
Then made a slight adjustment
The goal set next year is
Revenue from scenic spots increased by 5%
Not bad, good work
What is this again
Talking to the travel agency online platform
Offline promotion channels
After research
I made another one
New work plan
Made two
If you reintegrate the marketing market
I am sure
Revenue from scenic spots next year
At least 80% increase
You are going to make
Everyone in the department runs the channel
I recommend
Everyone is responsible for a section
Also have night tours
I recommend
Xiaoding
Notify everyone of the afternoon meeting
Discuss what Li Siyu did
Department's work plan for next year
To everyone
Then I will print a few more copies
No no no
still is
Print this
This is old
Let's discuss this
why
According to the plan of the head office
And our own future development
While developing
Consideration of balance
Take this into consideration
Five-Year Plan Ten-Year Plan
Also take this into consideration
Between employees and the company
Balanced interest
Also consider
How to mobilize the enthusiasm of employees
so
Considering this
Continuity of work
Us
Still discuss this
Thinking about rain
You are very enthusiastic
But ah
Too immature
Then why let me
Make this useless plan
Just to make you
Mature as soon as possible
Hurry up and print it
you
Li Siyu
I take it
Why did Siyu come back so early?
All right
Nothing
Thinking about rain
Go fishing with me
Don't want to go
must go
Go
Dad, wait a moment, I'll come
okay
Come
Slow down
Ok
Are you wronged in the unit?
No
I know that our unit
Then you stayed for a lifetime
That suits me right
Your character, you can't
Definitely can't stand it
I put
Manager Feng is offended
You kid
You really don't look like me
Like your mother
I was scared of my mother when I was young
I am also afraid
I don't want
Like her
But in your bones
Still more like her
So strong
Combative love is true
Actually I'm back this time
Just don't want
Be yourself again
This can't be for you
A person born
What kind of character
Can't change
When you were young
Once the Olympiad took third place
Your mother beat you
And punished you not to eat
I love you
I'll take you out to eat noodles secretly
let me tell you
I won’t read Olympiad in the future
You refuse me with one bite
Crying and calling your mother cruel
And swear to me
next time
I must take the first place
There is this
Kid like you
Even if it is by someone
Beaten up
Pain of course it hurts
But if I don’t let you play
I won't let you fight
You hurt more
what do you mean
I should still work hard
I didn't say what should be
I just said
What environment is your personality suitable for
Let's go back
Go back to shanghai
I can work hard here too
Two days ago
I just invited Lao Zhai to dinner
These two days it looks like
I'm going to invite Lao Feng to dinner again
You
Fighting like you
Love more true character
You stay two more days
The good character that I have accumulated all my life
Good popularity
I lost you all
dad
Let's be one
Big fart
See you when you look up
If you offend someone
I will go out with your aunt
Met someone
Are embarrassed to say hello
Shanghai is different
The size of Shanghai
This one
If you offend someone
Xuhui District can't wait anymore
Let's go to Jing'an District
Can't wait in Jing'an District
Let's go to Huangpu District
Pudong New Area
Never see forever
But I want to accompany you more
Ok
If you can change your character
Stop fighting
Like me
I'm happy with anyone
Can stay with me every day
Of course i am happy
But you can't change it
Sulking every day
Unhappy every day
I feel bad for you
Me, me, I can explain it
I didn't mean to rush you
I hope you can find one
More suitable for your character
Living place
That way you will be happy
Thanks dad
I know
I got goose bumps
Why are you polite to me
dad
Ok
I want to ask you a question
Uh you say
Have you loved my mom
Your mother is so good
Who doesn't love
Then why
After my mom left
Only a few months
You are married again
When your mom left
You are only twelve years old
It is the most in need of care
Age most in need of guidance
At that time
I really do not know
How to teach you
Just happen to others
Introduced me to your aunt
I remember the first time I met
She asked me
What flavor do you like
I made a lot of food for you later
Let me bring you
I decided
This woman
Will be nice to you
So you are for me
That's not all
Also for myself
Your aunt
It's the opposite of your mom
She didn't ask me at all
Thinking about rain
I love you mom
But really
Your aunt
Maybe more suitable for me
dad
You actually understand everything
I'm not stupid
I just don't want to make progress
Actually
I have never forgotten your mother
But life has to go on
Come back
We are back
How are the results
Eat fish at night eat fish eat fish
Great
None
You kid
You dead old man
Thinking about rain
Your Uncle Zhou called
Say if you are in the marketing department
Unhappy
Change your department
No need, auntie
I am going back to Shanghai
Back to shanghai
Don't look at me
Not my idea
She wants to leave
Come come come give me
Because of Xiao Tang
No, I just want to go back
What's wrong at home
Everywhere at home
But in shanghai
I am more open
You say you don't want to go
Yes, I thought
Don't go
But now i finally know
Who I am and what do I want
Where is better for me
Let her go
You can't keep her
I understand the truth
but
Aunt
Thank you for taking care of me for so many years
Take care of my dad
What is this
Wait a few more years when I go back
Save enough money to buy a big house
Just pick you up with my dad
To Shanghai together
At that time
You can see me every day
See Xiaoling
Good good
mom
daughter
dad
Ok
I will go back tomorrow
it is good
child
If your mother is here
She would definitely say
Go go fight
But i want to say
Don't care too much about success or failure
And result
Don't care how much money you make
What size house did you buy
Happiness is the most important thing
enjoy it
The process of struggle
Savor the joy of struggle
This is the most important
I understand
Be careful
Come
Zhizhi, wait a minute
Niuniu
Niuniu mom, help me take a look
For you
what is this
You open it in a while
Just know
it is good
gone
be careful
Ok
Hey
What is my proposal to you before
You never have
Reply me formally
I'm afraid you think
I just said it casually
and so
Bought this gift
Are you proposing
Yes
Zhizhi
Please marry me
Be my wife
Be Susan's mother
You make me think
good. I'll wait for you
it is good
came back
Yu Wei
It's father and mother
Zhizhi
Sorry
Remember the first time I saw you
I feel you are so pure
Very warm
I thought
If I can live with you forever
I will feel at ease and happy
My dream come true
Marry you
I was too poor then
No wedding no wedding reception
Even a wedding photo
I can't give you
But you don't have a complaint
Instead tell me
You are satisfied and happy
One year later
You gave me another one
The cutest daughter in the world
You make me a lot more
New experience
Also make my life
More complete
Is this me
however
I don't know the blessing
I only see myself running
Ignore your fatigue
I only feel my pressure
I can't see your contribution
at last
One day i committed
Wrong
On the day of losing
I just knew
I used to
What kind of happiness have you had
Zhizhi
I dare not beg your forgiveness
I just hope
Can have a chance
Let me make up
The neglect and hurt you have been
I dare not expect
Can go back to the past with you
But i hope
Able to work harder
Give you one
A sunny future
father
Zhizhi
Although long long ago
We met
But until today
I really understand you
Also understand myself
Zhizhi
Please marry me again
Mom, promise dad quickly
Hurry up
Liu Yang, stand up first
How bad is it to let Yuwei see
Dad love mom
What's so bad about this
I just started working now
Busy everyday
Really don't think about it
what do you mean
let me
Give you some more time
that
I leave this first
Zhizhi
You can think about it as long as you want
I'm waiting for you
Regardless of the results you consider
What is it
I accept both
Then you can rest early
Yu Wei
That dad is gone
Goodbye dad
Listen to mother
mom
Why don't you promise dad
Mother doesn't know
Two men
Propose to you on the same day
Zhizhi
Charismatic
I have never experienced anything like this
at the very beginning
My heart beats
Can't breathe
I dong dong dong
Flustered
Who are you going to choose?
What do you think
Who diamond election
but
Liu Yang is Yuwei's father
This is a bonus item
But
I don't want to choose
why
I think i am
pretty good
Although I'm a little tired from work
But my heart is quiet
I don't want to change
that
You have to put these two diamonds
All back
What a pity
I will earn money later
Buy for yourself
That's also a proposal
Then why can't He Mu
Send me diamonds
What did he give you
Sleep aid
what
Just this stuff
Hypnotic effect is good
Turn to the fifth page every time
I must be unconscious
Xiaoling
Do you really think
Is he suitable
He has what i want
I also have what he wants
A match made in heaven
Didn't you pick me up
Where's the person? Where's the car
I have something temporarily
You are too unreliable
I called you Didi
number plate
Shanghai WN1400
I saw
sister
What a coincidence, sister
What a coincidence, a coincidence, I will help you
Gu Xiaoling
Are you addicted to betraying me?
I was given a set of Lancome
I can't refuse
Gu Xiaoling
Have a surprise
You a poor boy
A set of Lancome
You're brainless
Just like this
You haven't beaten me for too long
I'm all itchy
Hit me twice more quickly
You can't blame me
Who told you not to reply me
You have this money, buy a set
Better clothes won't work
You can't have a better meal
Can't you rent a bigger room?
sister
Why are you all day long
It's money money money
You are so vulgar
You have time to spend on me
Will I die if I fill up?
You find a better job
Will die
But no love
Will die too, sister
Then look for someone your age
You waste time with me
Waste of money
If you don't hurt my heart
I just like challenges
Difficult like you
Where did you take me
Coming soon
General Guan
You haven't returned this car
Where to go
Car rental company
sister
Although you are a post-eighth-five
Why is it windy like a
After five or five
I
Guan Xiaotang
Where are you taking me
I'll be here soon, sister
You wait
Just above
Arrived
Mr. Guanhao
introduce
This is Mr. Li from our company
Manager Li
Here
what's the situation
Come here
Look here first
This is the pantry, how about
And this wallpaper
I chose for a long time
I spent all my energy this time
All spent on decoration
What about this company
It’s just been renovated in two days
I didn’t hire many people
The main business is undecided
Anyway all
Waiting for you to knock on the board
What are you doing
Everyone, stop
introduce
This is Mr. Li from our company
Mr. Li
Come here
Go here
how about it
This is
Our two offices
You can choose any of these two desks
Choose
What the hell are you doing
you forgot
I said
I want to make a website for you
Guan Xiaotang
Where did you get so much money
Did you borrow usury
I do not have
It's all my dad's pocket money
Your dad collects the rags
How much money can be
Last month's annual report
Several hundred million
RMB
USD
He doesn't have that strength
You and my relatives
While eating
What is said is true
Ok
I never lied to you
Are you with your grandpa
Grew up picking up tatters
Yes
my mother
Remarry
When i was two years old
My dad just give it to me
To my grandpa
I'm just with my grandpa
Pick up the tatters together
Did not you say
Did your dad have a car accident?
My dad went out to start a business
Haven't come back for many years
I just think he is gone
When he gets older
Take me to him
I am more than ten years old
The one with a broken arm
Transformers
Correct
I picked it up and put it together
The car downstairs
When i was eighteen
Birthday gift from my dad
Then why do you go to work by bus
I like
Why at my friend's house
Eat and drink
I like it
sister
Sister, are you angry?
I don't like others to lie to me
I never lied to you
You make me feel stupid
You are so cute
it is good
If you don't like this company
Tell me what you like
I can give it to you
What if i want
I will make my own
I just want to give you a gift
Make you happy
Do you know when i
Happiest
When working hard
I am happiest
Repeated defeats
When clenching your teeth
I am happiest
Go through hardships
When finally winning
I am happiest
Understand
I know
I like to surpass others
The feeling of conquering yourself
Understand
Understand i understand
You understand
Start a company like you
Like buying a toy
Rich second generation
Never understand
Sister, what are you doing
Menopause
Guan Xiaotang
This is not what i think
it is good
Even if I did it wrong
Then I love you
We two are not suitable
I think we two
Quite appropriate
I am so much older than you
If you are the same age as me
I still think you
What about a superficial wayward idiot
But I think you are now
Superficial Wayward Idiot
I will grow up
Perhaps
But i have no confidence
I have no patience to wait for you to grow up
If I mature as soon as possible
Will you fall in love with me
People are always there again and again
Mature in injury
Xiao Tang
I'm afraid you don't have this chance
Don't you think
Am i hurting right now
If this is all called injury
Then you really
So young
Li Siyu
Don't look down on people
I must be familiar to you
You wait
This day will not be too late
Not too late
How did you come
I came over to talk to the publicity department of Lubao
Get in touch
They said you are here
I'll come and have a look
How is it going well
Okay
But the same as you said
Now emerald
Brand promotion
Also used
Routines more than ten years ago
With the current situation
Already a bit out of touch
Yiming
I support you whatever you do
What I want is the final result
But this is not an easy job
Otherwise I won't
I beg you to shoot five times
I will not let you down
Thank you
I should thank you
Why are you so polite
okay
I have to hurry back to the company
I'll go now
Row
what happened
I'll be fine
Just want to look at you again
Okay, don't hide
I'm leaving
Ok
Brother Yiming
Zhizhi
How did you come
I happen to be here to do something
How are you doing now
pretty good
That one
It's nothing
OK, that's good
I'll go now
Ok ok
See you later
OK, um, bye
Zhizhi
Ok
You're thin but energetic
is it
Ok
Your complexion
Also much better than before
Watch me watch me watch me
how about it
Am I better than before
Looks younger
You will always be
The youngest and beautiful
What a pity
Except for my beauty
Nothing
I don't drink sweet
Hypocritical
Siyu sister
I have another appointment
I have to go first in a while
okay
Zhizhi
Ok
Did you date that
Mr. Su
Zhizhi
You have a boyfriend
It doesn't count
It doesn't count if you have proposed
I promised nothing
How are others
A good person
that
Do you love him
What is love
You can ask me down
Chen Yiming and I
When we first started together
meeting
Heartbeat
Sweaty palms
I only see customers
So my heartbeat will increase
Sweaty palms
Where's Su Lixing and I
Like an old couple
Not annoying to meet
Separate
Miss
very good already
He Mu and I are separated from each other
Tired of meeting
Then you have to marry him
of course
Although he is rigid and boring
But other conditions
All excellent
You told me
Don't be too picky
I decided to listen to you this time
Xiaoling
you've changed
I just want to understand
Although I can't change him
But i can change myself
As long as I don't pursue perfection
He is perfect
This makes sense