# Google translate version for your reference #
The message I got is
President Pan opposed
Keep waiting for you
President Fang didn't say anything
But there are many middle-level cadres
Joint letter
I want to invite Yuan Huizhong back
What do you say at the end
The board must vote
By the way, the board of directors has a newcomer
Is also the company’s new shareholder
Sister Ziru
or
You go find Mr. Pan
Talk to him
Let him reinstate you in advance
So Fang and Yuan Huizhong
Just give up
Voting next week
Are you sure
There are nine people on the board
Lao Feng Lao Qin and me
Will definitely vote for you
Pan Zhiyong
Finance Department R&D Department
Will definitely vote for Li Siyu
There are three more votes
Ma Chao Shi Xin
And the new shareholder
New shareholder
What kind of person
Investment
When signing a contract before
Met once
But no formal communication
If she doesn't know the situation
Then she must listen to Pan Zhiyong
Vote for Li Siyu
I'm private
Talked with Ma Chao and Shi Xin
But their attitude
unclear
since
It's Pan Zhiyong
Suggest a vote
He must be fully sure
Sister Ziru
Yiming won't let me drink
I will use tea instead of wine
congratulation
Speaking of
Thank you for this
Without your matchmaking
Nor will there be
Tianyi and Lubao are married
Have you heard about me?
heard
After signing the contract
Mr. Pan takes the ins and outs
Told me all
Siyu, you're doing it for the company
The loyalty to the king
Mr. Pan treats me well
I'm back for the company
It should be
I am now a shareholder of Emerald
thank you too
Thank you Ziru for understanding
Sister Ziru
I heard a news
Say company board
Ready to discuss
New sales director candidates
Yes, we will meet next week
How did you think about this?
I am now
Lvbao’s shareholders
Of course it’s beneficial to Emerald
I think about it
The most suitable candidate
It's me
Personal performance
Team performance
I'm the sales director
Records set in recent months
Can prove my ability
But Mr. Fang nominated Yuan Huizhong
Other executives are also very supportive
Sister Yuan and I half a year ago
Have already separated
Heard you say
One more thing
do not know
Did Mr. Pan tell you?
He suspended me
Just a stopgap
His plan is
Wait till the situation subsides
Just let me return to my original post
He said
From my suspension till now
It has been a long time
No one mentions that online
And the sales of Emerald
I can't keep it without anyone
So I think
I am reinstated now
The best chance
Sister Ziru
If the board discusses
In public to private, in sentiment to reason
I hope you can support me
Siyu
The earliest i know
The most exposed green treasure
You are the one
I am on you
I saw the temperament of the emerald
Also saw the future of Emerald
I was determined
Decide to invest
Do you understand what i mean
Sister Ziru, thank you
father
What's wrong with me
You fainted on the street
Kind people take you to the hospital
Doctor's diagnosis
Diabetic Nephropathy Stage III
What is this disease
Can it be cured
The doctor said it is early
Kidney damage
In a reversible stage
only
Treatment cycle
May be longer
If you recover well
You can still work and live as usual
restore
Don't think about anything
Treat first
Zhizhi
did not expect
You will come to see me
after all
You are Yuwei's father
How is the sales department recently?
not too good
Quite a lot
Everyone's heart is gone
But we
What's the original
What it is now
Sister, we know
You will come back sooner or later
So few of us
Never let up
Count you smart
Siyu sister
When are you coming back
Wait for the board to open
Just know
When will the board of directors be opened?
Just two days
Siyu sister
Only you back
We are all at ease
Ok
Can't wait
I'm coming back this time
Intend to re
Adjust the sales department
You are all a little psychologically prepared
Good good
First look
Any comments or suggestions
Communicate with me anytime
President Wang
You find me
Yiming, come sit down
it is good
Something
I hope you help me out
You say
Siyu found me two days ago
She wants me
On the board of Emerald
Support her reinstatement
She hasn't given up on this idea
I understand this
She is fighting for the sales director
This post
Paid a lot
Of course I don't want to give up easily
But she
She is a little obsessed now
Yiming
Yu Gong
Siyu's contribution to Lvbao
For all to see
And she can do it
Sales Director this position
Yu Shi
There is a friendship between me and her
That support her
I am obliged
I would like to hear your views
I heard Mr. Pan say
After the last Emerald accident
A series of public relations response
It's all from your handwriting
Yes
I suggested
Siyu took the blame and resigned
But President Pan
To think of rain
value
I changed my resignation to suspension
From the perspective of crisis public relations
Do you think siyu now
Is it suitable for reinstatement?
Very unsuitable
I remember I heard you say
Siyu is not in good health now
Ok
You also hope she quit
Or change one
Easier work
Yes this is me now
I'm more concerned about
I was like this last week
Persuade her to come
Na Yiming
Should i
Vote her against
President Wang
As your subordinate
A member of Tianyi Group
I would definitely recommend you
Voted against
But as a rainy
Unmarried fiance
I am really contradictory
On the one hand
I hope she can be happy
could do
What I like to do
Able to realize their dreams
But on the other hand
If she keeps doing
Message from Sales Director
That to her body
The feelings between us two
Maybe even
To our future family
It's not a good thing
You gave me a problem
President Wang
Don’t you often talk about roles?
I think now you are back
In your role
Just don't care
What i just said
Choose whatever you choose
I am to Li Siyu
Without any prejudice
On ability
She is also impeccable
But she just committed
Such a big thing
If she can reinstate her officer
Other employees of that company
how to think
What will customers think
How will the public evaluate
But don't forget
This Yuan Huizhong
Have committed even bigger things
The truth of that matter has been revealed
The police some time ago
Just solved the case
According to the liar
He and Yuan Huizhong
It doesn't matter
That to the company
Economic loss
I can't find it
Ke Yuan Huizhong
Did not discredit the company's image
I feel so too
Yuan Huizhong's ability
Comparable with Li Siyu
And there is no risk in public relations
She is more suitable
Be the sales director
Li Siyu's ability
Still better than Yuan Huizhong
Stronger
Actually these two candidates
All very good
To be honest
My own vote
I don't know who to vote for
But as a director
Not only represent yourself
Also represents all the shareholders of Lvbao
And all employees
So please everyone
Not from your own perspective
think abut
Try to stand taller
See far
Since Mr. Fang mentioned
All shareholders
All employees
Me here
Need to remind
office
Received one a few days ago
Company executives
Joint letter
They all appeal together
To ask Yuan Huizhong to return to the company to reinstate
How many people have co-branded
Eighteen people
Are the backbone of the company
President Wang
Ok
Total Emerald
652 employees
Ok
The letter is here
Everyone take a look
No need to watch
I have another meeting
Manager Wang is also busy
Or the old rules
Vote for decision
That line
In front of everyone
There are two boxes
Red represents Li Siyu
Green represents Yuan Huizhong
Who do you agree with
Acting as sales director
Put the pencil in front of you
Cast into the corresponding box
President Wang hasn't voted yet
President Wang, hurry up
Ok
Li Siyu four votes
Yuan Huizhong five votes
According to the voting results
The sales director should be Yuan Huizhong
I still have something
President Wang
President Fang
This sales department has no leader
it's been a while
I recommend
This news has been announced
it is good
Ok
Siyu
Board of Directors
Voting results are out
Yes
Yuan Huizhong
Siyu
this matter
The board has made a decision
Siyu
Hello, Siyu
This result
Is it still possible to change
How could it be such a result
That's it in a short period of time
I can't
Back to Green Treasure
How did that happen
I do all this
All for the green treasure
Mr. Pan, you promised me
I promised you
But things have changed
Emerald is not
Are you alone
Li Siyu
Please calm down, okay
I am not the only member of the board
Nine in total
but
You calm down first
Something
I have to tell you
On today's board
Between you and Yuan Huizhong
Wang Ziru cast
Key vote
What do you mean
She voted for Yuan Huizhong
impossible
I calculated before the meeting
Even if Wang Ziru doesn't help you
She will help me too
Because we are
When signing the agreement
She promised me
On the board
Will unconditionally be consistent with me
That's why I decided
Cut the mess
Proposal to vote
I did not expect this result
Why she did this
Yeah why
You should ask her yourself
Thank you brother
You don't need to thank me
I do
Also for everyone
Also for the green treasure
I finished the chores at hand
Report back to Lubao as soon as possible
After returning to the company
Meet the new shareholder Wang Ziru
You have to pay more attention
Tianyi Group
You can come back
The most critical vote
She voted
Did not you say
She and Li Siyu have a good relationship
Still Li Siyu
Did you introduce her to Lao Pan?
so
I think she is weird
she was
There will be no other attempts, right?
do not know
President Wang
Li Siyu is downstairs now
She wants to see you
Where is Chen Yiming now
Ok ok
Miss Li, Mr. Wang, please
Please
Miss Li is here
Inside please
Mr. Wang, Miss Li is here
Thinking rain is coming
Come sit here
come
Your first time
Come to my office
I want to know why
What do you mean
You promised me
Want to support me
Why did you turn back
Did I say this?
Don't you even admit this
Think about it
What did i say
Siyu
The earliest i know
The most exposed green treasure
You are the one
I am on you
I saw the temperament of the emerald
Also saw the future of Emerald
I was determined
Decide to invest
It seems that I misunderstood
Siyu
I approve of you
but
It doesn't mean you are
The best candidate for sales director
That is in your eyes
Yuan Huizhong is more suitable than me
Actually you two are suitable
but
Consider other reasons
I voted for her
what reason
You really shouldn't ask me about this
Then who should i ask
Our first installment
Almost four million
Chen Yiming
Why did you do that
President Chen, I can't stop her
It's okay. Go out first
what happened
Why are you
Deprive me of the right to work
Siyu, this is the office
Calm down
Let's go out and talk
I originally had my own office
But because of you
I have nothing now
what are you saying
Don't pretend
You just want what you want
You never cared about my feelings
I am working right now
Shall we talk about it when we go home?
You don't touch me
Do you think you're upset
My sales director
I'll follow you home obediently
Married to you
Be a housewife for you
I tell you it's impossible
Siyu
let's breakup
Sorry
A little personal matter
Let's continue
Where did we just talk
Four million for the first phase
Yes, the first phase of 4 million
Let's go
go
Yiming
President Wang
Siyu came to me just now
Correct
She just got out from me
Emerald Sales Director's ticket
I voted for Yuan Hui
She just came to question me
I accidentally
Just tell you
I got it
I'm so sorry
do not
Mr. Wang, you don't have to apologize to me
It has nothing to do with you
this is
Me and Siyu
Problem between two people
Doesn't affect your relationship?
She just told me to break up
How about I go and persuade her
no need
You don't have to persuade her
She should know
You are good for her
She can't understand now
How could this be
What i thought was
Wait for her to get better
In our company
Find one for her
Work easier
President Wang
You don't make arrangements like this
You for the two of us
Have done enough
Really
Then I'll give you three days off
Go and accompany her
Explain to her
No need to
I don't want to explain anymore
you guys
Won't really break up
do not know
Ok
Yiming
If you need help
Or talk
I'm here
okay
Thank you, sister Ziru
slower
Stop drinking, give it to me
Can't you drink
You still drink
you give me
I'm so broken
Can't use wine to sorrow
Yiming did this
Also for you
The most selfish words in the world
It's me for your good
is it
you know
The subtext of these words
What is it
Just
I'm right
You are all wrong
You have to listen to me
Must follow my plan
Live what i like
Brother Yiming will not
So domineering
That's what he did
No matter how much i like
That job
But because he doesn't like it
Let me resign
He is not selfish, right
He might really be
Good for you
If others think it’s good, it’s not good
Only I feel good
That's really good
Do you think
I should be beautiful at home
Do not
I'm going to fight outside
Do you think
I can't be a sales director
I'm gonna be
What do you want to do
I not only want to be the sales director
I want to be the general manager
Chairman
I want all of them
Regret today's decision
All right
how about it
much better
This is what Zhizhi made for you
Yes
To take care of you every day
You say you
Zhizhi used to be like this
Like Zhizhi
What a wonderful wife
Can you not mention this
OK, don't talk
You
Take care of your body now
I'm discharged from the hospital, looking for a job
From then on
Live with Ren Zhizhi
Eat
I think so
Just don't know
What does Zhizhi think?
She must think so too
Why are people stupid?
I cook for you every day
Come take care of you
Don't talk about me
What's wrong with Yiming
Why are you so decadent
Siyu broke up with him
What? Break up
Siyu and Yiming broke up
how is this possible
Yiming
You wake up wake up wake up wake up
Tell me what's going on
Why did you split up
speak
Maybe we both
Is not suitable for marriage at all
You can't say this casually
Isn't that it
We both had a look before
You can understand
What she wants now
I don't recognize
What i do
She doesn't understand
Then you two try to go back to the past
It's easy for you
Why don't i work hard
Don't i keep working hard
But she found
She is breaking up with me now
Even if she mentioned
You can't just let go
I'm your lesson
But this time
This time i am real
Feeling a bit tired
No matter how tired you are, you have to follow Siyu
Communicate well
I remember you said a word
You are a man
You have to take the initiative
Yes
You are a man, you have to take the initiative
Talk to Siyu
Something went wrong
You won't come back
You and I might not be considered
Best man bridesmaid
I'm going to change the ticket
Will be back tomorrow
how about it
Although I am not completely well yet
But now standing in front of you
It was Gu Xiaoling ten years ago
Let's go
How about Zhizhi
say something
I've only been away for half a month
There are so many moths
It seems i am
The three of us
The one in the town house
Yes, not only the town house
Evacuate
How are you going to catch me
I booked you a restaurant
Just the two of us
Zhizhi is going to the hospital to see Liu Yang
Too late
Come in
President Fang, you sign
Thank you Mr. Fang
President Fang
I'm at Hanhai Club
Booked a private room
Think about the future development of Lubao
Ask for questions
Waiting, Wang Ziru
I go to the toilet first
Ok
I'm here
I have come in
Correct
Where are you
Left hand side left
I hung up
Haowen asked me over
how about it
It's pretty delicious here
A lot of delicious
Go slowly behind
Environment is also good
You really know how to find food
That is
Can the God of Cookery recommend something wrong?
Come have a drink
What to see
Never seen beauty
Have seen
But I have never seen you so beautiful
You say you are old
Still beautiful
Lei Haowen
Do you want to break up
May I break up
How is it
Lei Haowen
Don't don't
Wrong wrong wrong
Don't say anymore
Never say again
Come, fat intestines
Your favorite
Have you been thinking about it for a long time?
It's still delicious
You say they two
What's the situation now
Based on my understanding of Chen Yiming
He should apologize first and reflect first
Based on my understanding of Li Siyu
She will soften
and then
Say two affectionate words again
Then Li Siyu's tears
Can't control it
Two of them
Hug together
Vow never to separate
They reunited
You and I match up with both swords
Boundless merit
Come celebrate the best man and bridesmaid
Re-employed
I did not expect
Lost the position of sales director
Will hit you so hard
I should
To comfort you in time
But at that time
Not from your perspective
Think about this question
it is my fault
Sorry
I was also impulsive that day
No matter what the antecedent is
I shouldn't
Go to your office
Siyu
I think about this
I need to explain
Sister Ziru
Really asked me
Asked my opinion
but
I also said
I didn't want to reinstate you
But i'm really not
Just for myself
I
I really love you
In the hospital at that time
I looked at your inspection report
You know i was
What's your mood
You have been with me for more than five years
You did so many things for me
I didn't take care of you
If in the future
I connect your body
If it's not good enough
I want my husband
What's the use
Siyu
We don't break up
good or not
Let me take care of you
I know
You want your own business
No problem i support you
but
Our priority
To restore your body
I know my body
What do you know
Tell me what you know
Then the doctor has the final say
The doctor said
You are fully recovered
Then I am at any time
I will let you out and work hard anytime
When will it get
One year two years
It's not a matter of time
As long as you get better
anytime
And we can
Borrow this time
Take our lifelong events
Solved
But my career is very likely
I'm so delayed
But you, now you want
Want to continue working but
You can't get back the emerald
I don't have to go back to the green treasure
I have many things to do
What do you want to do
I want to start my own business
Start a business
that
Good business
But that is not
Is it ok anytime
But a real opportunity
Are fleeting
Why are you so anxious?
That's not after
Will there be a more suitable time
because
Because i'm over thirty
I just lost
Everything in Emerald
So I
So I can't help but worry
Siyu
Why don't you understand
After we two are together
You are not alone
You still have me
My everything
All yours
You believe me
Trust me
I must have this ability
Go take all your things
Take care of everything
Let's get married first
Then adjust your body
And other things
We one by one
Solve slowly