# Google translate version for your reference #
Did Mr. Li get the money?
I think sister Fan has a sad face
Semi-suspended
I heard
President Li intends to put the company
sold
Why
Don't work here and spread rumors
Guan Xiaotang
You are the one who begged for love with President Li
Tell me something
My message is
Our company is fine
Paid
Seems more than last month
Twice as much as last month
You are fine now
Worry about it
Sister Li said that I can get money
You can get money
Everyone come here
There must be good news announced
Everyone is here
Almost all
I sent everyone
Three months' salary
Should all be paid
Here
Thank you Mr. Li
I hope to get three times the salary every month
Work overtime, you
Work hard you
Don't think about something good for you
Go to work well
I declare
Called the company
From today
Formally dissolved
what's the situation
When you joined the company
I promised
Will take you
Make the company bigger and stronger
Get listed
But the truth is
I am not capable enough
Can't keep promise
The company ended up like this
it's all my fault
I let you down
Sorry
President Li, can't disband
Yes, that's a pity
Can't dissolve
How about we all
Think of a solution together
Yes yes
Isn't it a question of money?
I have got
Guan Xiaotang, stop making trouble
I'm serious
Sister Li
I'll fix it
thank you all
I know your mood
But there is a call
There are indeed inherent shortcomings
There is no need to continue
Not Mr. Li
We can
Don't say anything, everyone
I have decided
Jianghu Road Far
Hope to see you
Not Mr. Li, Mr. Li
President Li
five four three two one
We respect the future together
Respect the future
We can win
Sure to have the last laugh
All doubts
All become miracles
And the creator of this miracle
It's me Li Siyu
sister
Sell
Money for office furniture
You keep it
I do not need
You paid for the previous online promotion fee
How did you know
sister
It's ok
The company is gone, you still have me
What do i do with you
Boyfriend
Husband is fine
Look, you laughed
I'm useless
At least can make you smile
Guan Xiaotang
Concubine
thank you
sister
You have to like to make a website
I make a bigger
More professional for you
Mr. Gong
Still very powerful
You'll be fine in a while
Introduce the business to others
I still need you to say
Lei Haowen
Mr. Gong
Hello there
This is my partner
Chen Yiming
Hello, Mr. Gong, hello
Let's talk inside
Come, come in
This is your company
Yes
Yiming is mainly responsible for content
I am in charge of business
Correct
You want me to invest
This company
Yes
What a joke
Mr. Gong
Stay in step
We are at least willing
Spend a thousand dollars
In the creative cafe
Rent a table
When Mr. Gong started his business
Because I can't rent an office
Can only put the company
Set in a singles dormitory
You know me
So handsome
The purpose of our company
Is based on new media as the main port
Make a
Serving financial institutions
Virtual planning platform
We are breaking a
While the framework of a traditional company
Break one
Form of traditional company
It's okay
go on
Don't underestimate
This cafe
Just listed
CEO of Wheat Company
In that corner
Wrote the first line of code
last month
Qin Deng on the wealth list
Right on this table
Completed the first planning book
Also known as
The Wind Company of Community Unicorns
Also in this cafe
Got the first investment
So, Mr. Gong
Maybe the next wealth legend
Happened on this table
Between you and me
that
Let's talk about share
Mr. Gong
Something to drink
No need to
Come, take a look
Siyu sister, really want to leave
Do you think I am a show
All right
It's okay, I just miss home
I want to go back and see
sister
Are you still unhappy?
I tell you
You have to drink if you are not happy
I found one
Great party
Come, say hello to sister
See sister
There is only you can't think of it
Nothing you can't do
Can eat and drink
Can also play games
Come take a look
Who
Sister really
You can't just think about work
Need to mediate
Own mood
Want to play games
Really
This party hall is particularly suitable
You were healed after 1985
I'll send you a location in a while
You come right away
Guan Xiaotang
What homesick
You simply escape
I'm even a waste of wood
All accepted
What can be avoided
If you can face it
Guan Xiaotang called you
Why are you shutting down
If you can face
You just stay
You should be entangled with little fresh meat
Should earn money
Make excuses to go home
What's going on
Xiaoling
Where did i say wrong
Even if it is
Li Siyu
I looked at you before
Omnipotent
I really bother you so much
But i see you now
I feel more uncomfortable
I beg you
Can you go back
Bullish
Arrogant
Li Siyu before
Eager for quick success
Finally hurt Mr. Pan
Delayed all employees
Ended up hurting myself
You are
Accidental failure
Failed this time
Let me see myself thoroughly
I always felt
I am amazing
Better than anyone
Can win any battle
but now
I know
I am an ordinary person
One
Mediocre ordinary people
No, Sister Siyu
in my heart
You have always been excellent
Has always been my idol
Zhizhi
I previously
Because of good luck
And now
My good luck ran out
Ten thousand
Four cakes
Want it
Reconciled
Why are there fewer cards?
Single hoist
Less cards
What brand is missing
You count
Six
This six
Accidentally touched
I just called
is yours
That, this one is mine
I just shot this one
You are called fraud
What kind of fraud
Yes, fraud and peace are for a treat
What guest to invite
I didn't invite you two days ago
dad
We didn't invite
Our family is here
Don't play today, don't go don't go
Don't slip away, don't play today
You always shame
Old Zhao
Zhao, play with them
Don’t forget the evening treat
Guest officer
Are you coming to stay or eat
I go home
Then you are in the right place
dad
Why are you so indifferent?
Can't change it Can't change it
You have this old problem again
Nothing
Go home quickly
You slow down, don't worry
it's okay no problem
Come in come in come in
Siyu is back
So fast
Xiaoling called
I guess
You still have half an hour
Aunt
Hungry
There are two more dishes, ready soon
Ok
Pour her saliva quickly
I know I know
Put your things down first and rest
Ok
dad
Come, take a drink first
Sit down
Have a meal
There are vegetables
Eat dinner
Come eat
We are more than 200 days
Didn't eat with you
Of course it’s important
Siyu, eat more
Come, eat more
Thanks auntie
Come come
Auntie, enough is enough
Can't eat
look at you
How thin is it
Eat
Thanks auntie
Listen to Xiaoling
You quit your job
Ok
why
too tired
Come back this time
Take a good rest
it is good
Are you still leaving?
Not going
Great
In the news
Young people in first-tier cities
All six six nine
Even zero zero seven is it
Only do three things every day
Go to work, eat, sleep
What is life
This can only be called
Alive
Yes
It's best to take our Xiaoling
Also call back
Xiaoling, I can't call it
How is she now
No news for the whole month
Finally got a call
Ask her a few more words
She was impatient with me
She is fine
How is her personal problem
Have a boyfriend
All conditions are good
Can it be done this time
should be no problem
Such a big thing
Don't tell me
Do you still have my mother in your eyes?
Xiaoling didn't say anything
Of course there is
She just feels
It's not time to tell you
Can say it can say it
Ok
You don't even have an office
Not even a successful case
Got 2 million investment
Yes indeed
Who is this investor?
What kind of person is it
He is an investor
Own company
Although not very big
But those projects he invested
The success rate is quite high
is it
Yes indeed
Say so
This person is not a crazy person anymore
Of course they are not crazy
Not just neuropathy
And also very smart
Looks pretty handsome
is it
Yes indeed
That this thing
Only one explanation
Your creativity is very good
Maybe people value it
It's Lei Haowen's face
And my abs
A piece of abs
Yiming
You said you started
Must not let me invest
your company
Don't even let me read the plan
I think you made me miss
A good opportunity
You have invested in me
No one is optimistic about me
Even myself
When I doubt myself
You gave me confidence
Look at that
How about this one
I do not want
Didn't say buy it for you
I wear
you wear
This is for men
You didn't find
Do i like to wear menswear
sister
Why don't you reply to my WeChat
I miss you
Sister, where are you
sister
If you don't return
I went to the police
Lao Li
You see a girl over there
Walking around by the river
Isn't it about jumping into the river?
That is my daughter
Your daughter
Which daughter
The one that is least like me
I'm the boss in Shanghai
The one who can make money
The hardest one
Doesn't seem like hey
Hello there
came back
Siyu
Uncle Ho
He Bobohao
Hello
I heard you did a good job in Shanghai
We all know
Thank you
It's all right, sit down
dad
I lost it all
Coming back
I also took the money from me yesterday
All lost
I broke up with Chen Yiming
Is he sorry for you
You still apologize to him
No one sorry anyone
Just broke up peacefully
Then find another one
Don't be frowning
It's not a big deal
Almost thirty
Accomplish nothing
I have never achieved anything in my life
But I live more comfortably than anyone
You
Big nails
See bigger than slap
No need
be careful
Don't be like your mother
Die early
dad
Have had
Ran
Big deal empty-handed
Then you are not fishing for nothing today
This fishing
Mainly a happy
It doesn't matter if there are fish
Just like being a human
Just be happy
It can be done or not
How old is your child
I have no children yet
Didn't your husband rush at home?
I'm not married either
What about your boyfriend
Didn't he come back with you?
What are you doing
I don't have a boyfriend either
Do you have any conditions
I see if it is suitable
Introduce you
I'll talk about this later
I will implement the work first
Is that interesting?
Where my dad used to be
Hiring
I plan to try
I know
Just under the Housing Construction Bureau
That company
My cousin will take care of that piece now
Give you a green light
Guaranteed no problem
Don't bother your cousin
My dad's former apprentice
Now in charge of personnel
He said I have enough conditions
needs
let me tell you
Everyone has a background in that kind of unit
You have to let people know that you too
So as not to be bullied by others
thank you
Siyu
Your age now
I'm afraid I can only find divorced
Don't you dislike it
Sorry
I want to go to the bathroom
Ok go
Thank you
Who
You know him
This person
You see, i have seen it before
Hi
Are you
Li Siyu
We've been at the same table
is it
First semester
Yes Yes Yes
We have to have
It's been more than ten years
So long
After graduating from high school
Never seen
Actually, every Spring Festival
All come back
My every spring festival
Took my parents out to play
Perfect miss
Nothing nothing
It is said that
You won't leave this time
Is looking for a job
I can get together often
Okay
I'll be called in after class reunions
it is good
This juice is healthy
Taste
Okay, thank you
Reserved breakfast
Drop by
Eat while it's hot
Salary paid
Hello there
Thank you
You're welcome
Gave me another five thousand yuan
what does it mean
boss
Want to support me
This little money is not enough
What do you mean, boss
I owed you that 300,000
No need to pay back
Still still have to return
But I still have to pay the mortgage
So I owe you that 300,000
I can only pay a little
Yiming
Ok
Actually that 300,000
I didn't borrow it from you
Who borrowed it
Li Siyu
Why didn't you say it earlier, you
Li Siyu won't let me tell you
she left
Where did she go
Back home
why
You want to know if you ask yourself
impossible
Home this time
Not Li Siyu's character
May be hit too hard
Personality change
Oh my god, more than a hundred dollars
What size
S
But I think it suits you
Yes, I'll wait to send you the link
The red one is nice to see
Everyone's work
Let it go
Our department
A new colleague
Everyone get to know
Hello everyone, my name is Li Siyu
Li Siyu
I'm Liu Junning
Let's train a platoon in the first grade
Then you went to a class
I went to class three
So it's you
Since it's an old classmate
Then you take Li Siyu
Get familiar
The working environment of our department
Leave it to me
Come sit next to me
correct
Next year in our scenic spot
Who will do the work plan
You still live
Over there in shanghai
Nana
I moved back
What you gave me last time
Not over yet
Liu Junning
My mother-in-law recently
Can't breathe
Son is sick again
A bunch of things at home
Lao Di
Ni Yi and I are still writing
This year's summary
Where's Lao Zhang?
Lao Zhang asked for leave
Ask for leave again
You say you guys
The takeaway is here
Who of you go to the door to get it
I'll go
Takeaway
Put here put here
Let's go
You shouldn't get it
Have you eaten breakfast
Let's have one if you didn't eat it
what happened
Nothing
Just go get it
It will be your job from now on
People already with CC Fund
Started early contact
it is good
You expect
How much can we earn this time
Between four and five billion
Row
One year
800 million becomes 4 billion, not bad
President Wang made a move
It really is extraordinary
Only this income
Can you not waste our pains
Then we
Just look forward to the good news from Mr. Wang
Correct
no problem
OK, let's go ahead
Row
That has the latest development
I will inform you two more
it is good
Let's go first
Goodbye, Mr. Wang
Send you
Ok
Stay here, Mr. Wang
it's okay no problem
President Wang, don't give it away
Mr. Zeng walks slowly
Mr. Qiu walks slowly
President Wang
Mr. Gong has been waiting for you for a long time
Ok
Let him in
President Wang
Mr. Gong, sit down
Talk about
Your judgment on Chen Yiming
he
have a thought
Aggressive
The one he got
Is a virtual planning platform valuable
If it can be done
Still very promising
of course
Everything needs to be tested by the market
He didn't doubt you
I am a friend of Lei Haowen
Introduce the past
He didn't doubt
OK then you
Be an investor well
Ok
Mommy mommy
mom
What's wrong, Yuwei
Don't be afraid
Mother is here, don't be afraid
Mom is here mom is here
Dad i want dad
Don't be afraid, mom is here
It's just thunder and rain
Mom, I'm so scared
Don't be afraid
Hello
The number you have dial can not be reached
Mom tells you a story
good or not
a long long time ago
In a forest
A female duck is brooding her eggs
Isn't it Hai's daughter?
Mom tells you today
The story of the ugly duckling
good or not
Little ducks one by one
Crawl out of the eggshell
There is a little duck
With other ducks
Look different
It's big and ugly
Hello, Xiaoling
What's wrong
I miss you
Hurry up and save me
Scan carefully, Master
Lei Haowen
came back
How is the hotel sleeping
Okay
You didn't sleep all night
When daybreak
I planned to squint for a while
As a result, there was a sudden situation
master
Take a look take a look
You glass slag
You have to clean it up
Scan over there again
Take another look
it is good
Be careful
okay
Just that mouse
Ran out
It protested with me
I can only play Tom
Destroy its power
Yes medicine
Take the medicine quickly
Rained all night
You have a cold again
I'm going to blame me for not being able to drive in time
Soak yourself
Come, Mr. Lei, help
These two pieces, right
Help me hold these two pieces
it is good
Are you holding it?
I caught
Do not worry
I also released it
Master, make it firm
okay
What do you see me doing
Take medicine
Xiaoling
The way you look at me today
A bit slick
Color, color you
You hurry up and take medicine
Right, right, just be firm