[To Dear Myself]
[Ep23]
It's not so tidy, hope you won't mind
It's ok
I will clean it up later
No, I can do it myself
Let me help you
Come
Just sit here
Come, Yuwei, come
Wait
Wait a minute
Mom
Why dad hasn't come back yet?
Dad is on a business trip
He will come back soon
Oh
Brother Yang, come to eat
Sit
Yayun, thank you
No need
I am here to warm you up
Well
You will like it
Little potatoes
I made it for you
Yayun
You are so good to me
Brother Yang
I want to be nice to you forever
Hello
Do you need a loan?
No, thank you
Mom, I want to play with the phone
Only ten minutes
Ok
This is mom
This is me
This is dad
Mom
When will dad be back?
Hello, mom
It's me
Zhizhi
How are you doing?
Can you hear me?
Mom
Liu Yang has an affair
His colleague Wei, right?
Mom, you know?
I need to talk to Yang
I will scold him
Mom
He moved out
Yang is so ridiculous
Zhizhi, don't worry
I will stand on your side
He will break up with that woman
I will tell him to come home and apologize to you
Mom
You are so nice
Zhizhi, but I need to tell you
After he comes back,
don't quarrel with him
Otherwise, he will go to see that woman again
Did you hear me?
Ok, I will listen to you
That's all
Bye
You are stupid
If you lose Zhizhi, you will regret
I know how to handle it
If you don't do as I say
you are not my son
Mom
Today you need to go home
But Zhizhi
Yang, Zhizhi promised me
As long as you go home, it's over
She won't mention it
I need to think about it
Think about what?
Do as I say
Ok
I have to work now
Brother Yang
Don't push yourself so hard
Watch a movie tonight
Come
Great
I want to play...
I still want to play
Ok... Come...
Come...
Come up
I still want to play
One
Let's take a break
Your aunt is tired
I still want to play
Zhizhi
Yang, he wants to go home
He also said he was wrong
And he has promised he won't do it again
Really?
He told me in person
But he didn't call me till now
No text
It's all because of male chauvinist
Zhizhi, you should call him
Or pick him up from the office
Tired?
Yes
So tiring to caretake a kid
Tough work
I'm tired too
You?
I need to fight against gravity and age
You think it's easy?
So you think you can win the gravity and age?
I can't win
But I will fight to the last minute
Piss off
Piss off to you
What did she say?
Can you help me find where Liu Yang lives now?
What do you want to do?
I want to give him an out
Did he confess?
He confessed to his mom
And I also have some responsibility
Really forgive him?
For Yuwei
I am willing to forgive him
Fine
1. 2, 3
All right
How's it?
Great
What are you up to this weekend?
Gaze at you
We should have a meal with your parents
They need to go out on the weekend
Your spurned my last invitation because they went to Europe
Prior to that, they went to Thailand
Prior to that...
Xiaoling
I think it's not the time
So when is the come?
You know what
According to the tradition of our family
Seeing parents means marriage
So you mean, you don't want to marry me?
I think we are not old enough to get married
I see
Actually I enjoy the current status
We can enjoy the sweetness of love
without the trivialities of marriage
Then you are not afraid I will run away with someone else?
Yes
But I know
You won't
Coming
So fast?
I just placed the order
Coming
Xiaoling
Wait a minute
Lei Haowen, what are you doing?
You hide a man in the house?
I need to get changed
In a moment
Open the door
I am going to leave if you don't open the door now
I am coming...
Please come in
How do you know my house?
So easy
Do me a favor
You have said, you won't aske me
for help even if you die, right?
Let me go
I was kidding
I am so happy to see you here
Sit...
Come
Orange juice
Open it
You hurt me so deeply
I can't even talk about it?
Say it, what favor?
I can do everything for you as long as I can
Be my ex boyfriend
What?
I am even not your boyfriend
Bloody ex-boyfriend
Will you help me?
Sorry, I can't
I want to be your current boyfriend, ok?
Current boyfriend
Be gentle...
Will you help me?
Ok...
You are so cruel
Remember
Do according to my plan strictly
What's your plan?
First
Drive your cabriolet
You need to figure out to use it first
Second
Make a proposal to me with a ring and a bouquet
Then Wei Shang will be jealous
Then he will stimulated to make a proposal to me
Understand?
Yes
We should set the time
Wait
I have to think about it
What?
The role is so important
I need to think about how to get into it
Thank you
What are you looking at?
Nothing
The menu
What else do you want?
Where are you? What's going on?
What you want to eat?
Immediately
Come to my face in five minutes
Otherwise, you need to disappear from my world in the future
Xiaoling
He is calling you
Really?
Gu Xiaoling
Please
Give me one more chance
Lei Haowen, get up
I won't if you don't promise me
We have broken up
But I can't live without you Gu Xiaoling
Gu Xiaoling
Marry me, Gu Xiaoling
We can't be together
I have a boyfriend
It doesn't matter
As long as you are not married
I still have a chance, Xiaoling
I can give you everything
I can buy you bags and lipsticks
And a big villa
I can give you whatever you want
Xiaoling, marry me
I can give you happiness, Xiaoling
This is my fiance
We are getting married soon
Impossible
Xiaoling, impossible
It's your excuse, Xiaoling
Marry me, Xiaoling
Dude
Come, get up
You break taboos the moment you came in
Proposal is a big deal
Look at you, disheveled
Like a refugee
And the bouquet
Yeah, you spent some thougts on it
You need to get flowers tidy ok?
And your kneeling
It's a proposal, not new year call
You need to take a knee
And the most important...
At this moment, bags, lipsticks,
villas and sports car are useless
The most important is sincerity
Come, let me show you
Dear
Will you marry me?
I...
Got that?
You should be like this
Come, have a try
Me?
Take it, try
Come on
I will take a picture for you
You can check it out and make some improvement
Ok...
Forget it
Xiaoling
It's not too late to propose
I am not ready this time
I will come again when I am ready
You are not angry at all?
Xiaoling
Sit down
Sit
Men become at a loss only in front of his love
Xiaoling
My advice is, you should consider his request
What about us?
Us...
I like you very much
But you can just be my girlfriend
Why?
I am afraid my parents can't accept you
Your parents barely see me
How can they refuse me?
My parents won't allow me to
marry a girl three years older than me
Am I older than you just today?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
And they won't know if they don't see my ID card
My parents can tell
Xiaoling
As long as we don't talk about marriage or see parents
we can go on dating
Asshole
I have told you
He is an asshole
But you don't believe me
Cheer up
It's a good thing that you break up with him
It's so miserable if you go on dating him like this
Cheer up
Happy for you
Do you think I am a loser?
No
Next year I will be 33
What's wrong with it?
I am 34
33, 34, 35, 36, 37
Age is not a problem
Or I can tell Chen Yiming to introduce you another one
He knows many elites
Or you can try blind date website
Maybe I will end my life like this
No
We should follow the normal process
I have to fight for another ten years
Fight for another ten years
Zhizhi
This is Liu Yang's address
Thank you Xiaoling
I went abroad today
Take care of yourself during this time
Go abroad?
Plastic surgery?
I will be ten years younger
Gosh
Keep in touch
Hello
May I ask where block 3, lane 62 is?
Over there, enter the gate and turn left
Thank you
Go
Come
Come, baby
Wait
Come home
Yuwei
What are you going to say when we see dad?
Dad, I miss you so much
Mom misses you too
Come home with us
What if dad doesn't go home?
I will be like this
Brother Yang
Buy flowers?
Which one do you want?
I like this
Come, Yuwei
WeChat Pay?
Yes
Ok, bye
Thank you
Thank you, brother Yang
Brother Yang
Come up
Sister Siyu
What happened?
I want to divorce
You are going to...
Divorce
I will support your decision
It's ok, you have me
Sister Siyu
Why so flustered?
Supervision Department
You need to go to meeting room
Now
Wait here
Liu Yang, right?
Sit
We received real-name reports from
Dayue Group and Sanke Group
In this tender, you are suspected of favoritism
So we are here to investigate it
Miss Li
What is your relationship with Liu Yang?
My cousin's husband
During this bidding, did he tell you any info about the experts?
I have never done this
I didn't send the email
You can investigate it
Do you remember this email?
Before the bidding, I received the email
Not over yet?
Not yet
But I deleted it immediately
And I haven't contacted any expert on the list
You can investigate this
So did Liu Yang send this email to you?
I don't know
I don't know the one who sent the email
So, guess, who sent this email to you?
I do not know
What is your relationship with Liu Yang?
He...
He is my team leader
Anything more?
I'm just an intern
I just do as he says
As I know, you and him are not just intern and leader
No
We have no other relationship
Do you know Li Siyu, from Lubao company?
She is Liu Yang's wife's cousin?
Take it
Don't worry
We have enough money
Zhizhi's cousin paid the rest for us
As far as you know
Liu Yang and Li Siyu
Did they have benefit-based relationships?
Now it's still your internship?
I remember it
Liu Yang told me she had a cousin
Is it Li Siyu?
Ok, to be more specific
Miss Li
This is your signature, right?
Yes
You went to pay the hospitalization fee
the second day you received the list of experts
Two days later, Lubao won the bid
My aunt had heart attack
I just wanted to save her life
It has nothing to do with bidding
It's at most the help between relatives or friends
Throughout the bidding process,
I didn't break any rules
It's just a coincidence of time
Really?
Indeed
I should have told my leader Li Siyu is Zhang Zhizhi's cousin
It's my mistake
But I didn't play favouritism and commit irregularities
I didn't get any money from Li Siyu illegally
And I believe Li Siyu didn't break the law
President Wang
I know this from information department
The two companies that lost the bid has launched
a real-name report against Lubao online
Before bid opening
Lubao has the list of experts of the bid evaluation committee
Does it go viral now?
So what will it be in the end?
No idea
Prepare for the worst result
The government will cancel the bidding contract we sigened?
It's ok if they just cancel the contract
What's the worst?
Today I should see a new client to talk about financing
He seems to know this
He cancelled the appointment
Just wait for the result
Director
I want to appeal
It's useless
Even if you can prove
that email has nothing to do with you
But Li Siyu is your cousin
Li Siyu paid the money
And Lubao company finally won the bid
It's all facts
They have side witnesses
You really care about Lubao company
I even heard you say don't meet, at special stage
Something like these
Of course
They will do further investigation
You may prove your innoncence
It may relate to legal issues
Hard to tell
But anyway, our reputation will suffer the loss
So to protect yourself
You need to consider the company's reputation
Director Li
We decide to cancel all the contracts with you
And we will remain the right to hold you accountable
Due to company business adjustment
The following personnel will resign automatically
Liu Yang and more
That's all
Brother Yang
I just received your director's call
I know
Is there anything we can do?
No
You...
I am fired
Brother Yang
Sorry
All my fault
I didn't expect this
I thought...
Siyu
Why didn't you tell me the moment you received the email?
I thought you sent it to me
Impossible
You told me
Don't meet during that time
Don't contact, either
So...
Brother Yang
President Pan
Li Siyu
Check it out online immediately
Check it out online now