# Google translate version for your reference #
Chen Xinyi
No. 1 in performance this month
Congratulations
Treat
no problem
Liu Jie
The worst landslide
Old rules fine
President Yuan, I agree
Cai Yihui
Congratulations
This month is not the last
Someone is worse than Cai Yihui
Cai Yihui Five hundred and twenty thousand
Zhang Zhizhi
zero
I'm not
Did you give you a client
What about the order
The client kicked me out
and then
Then you never contacted
This customer
You are so arrogant
Rejected by the client
Never contact again
So arrogant
Should be the chairman
What salesperson
Zhang Zhizhi
I limit you this month
Must win this client
Can't hold
Leave by yourself
Cai Yihui
You should be the entire sales department
The one who doesn't want her to leave
As long as she is
You are not the last one
Be merciful
You have become kind
All right
One more good news
Tell everyone
This month our sales department
Won the Team Excellence Award
Congratulations everyone
Everyone, keep working hard
Come on
Zhizhi Zhizhi
Are you OK
Paid
Every month
Isn't it all paid today?
Base salary
Plus various subsidies from the sales department
Plus the bonus of the excellent team
In the administration department than I was before
30% more
But next month
You are leaving
I must stay here
Hit someone to lose money
fraud company
Manager Li
Big brother, scam company
Have something to say
Where's the boss
Tell me your boss
Where's your boss
I am
Call your boss out
Your guy beat my husband
Still not willing to lose money
what
Big brother
Guan Xiaotang, are you okay?
Can't hurt people
Why are you losing money
let me go
Can you get up
Take away
Be honest
Let us go let me go
Let us go
let me go
It's okay
All right
Nothing
my husband
The user they called
Her husband
At the service point we called
Rent a new battery
All returned are scrap batteries
Was discovered by our employees
Fight on the spot
My husband was seriously injured by him
Medical expenses are several thousand yuan a day
They won't pay a penny
The beating employee has been
Detained by the local police station
This employee and franchisee
Built between them
Is a labor contract relationship
This matter
Should be borne by the franchisee
Joint liability
And we called
And franchisees
We are an independent civil subject
So this matter
Shouldn't we call
Responsible
You say yes
He still doesn't make sense
My husband is like this
Unwilling to pay a penny
Does it make sense?
Is there a king?
Let's listen to comrades from the police
it's OK
okay
This is the police station
Comrade Police
My husband is lying now
In the intensive care unit
Waiting for money to help
We can't help it
But if you seek compensation
Should go to that franchisee
but now
You hit someone
Employee who called
Smashed other people's things
Already constituted a crime
how about it
Whether you both accept mediation
Mediation works
But with conditions
the first
Apologize
second
Compensate us for calling the company
All losses
what
You want us to lose you money
Big brother
This is a list of property losses
Including decoration, furniture, labor
This is an estimate
More than 20,000 yuan
Nothing less
Little girl
Can you take less money?
When you hit my company
Why didn't you expect
One less hammer
Not little sister
My elder brother
Really not intentional
It's just a momentary rush
I apologize to you now
Sorry girl
please
Forget it
I won't let you lose
But you have to
Write a written guarantee
Stop harassing our company
Not because
Your fight with franchisees
Come to trouble our company
This
Alright
Make a decision quickly
I write
Manager Li
I was worried before
Our company's brand
Because of the fight
did not expect
These few words today
Our company this time
I'm completely out of it
Am I too cold-blooded
Ok
Cold-blooded and cool
You go to contact
Franchisees over there
Let them as soon as possible
Pay the medical bill
I asked them
they said
How much the court sentenced them to pay
They just lose
But now the court hasn’t judged
They don't pay a penny
Xiao Lu, what do you want to say
Manager Li
Before we have a few
Service point staff
I haven't had time to train
Go online
This is one of them
Do you think it’s because of insufficient training
Led to this fight
how can that be possible
Take scrap batteries
Change our new battery
Want me to beat him too
I do not know either
I suddenly remembered
Only the three of us know this
Not allowed to spread
Ok
The other employees have not
Service points that have time for training
service paused
Until all employees are qualified
OK, let me prepare
I'm leaving
You really don't have to go to the hospital
No need to
Does it still hurt?
got used to
You get beaten often
My last time
Got spanked
You too
Hit the hammer
Don't know how to hide
It's okay to smash the back
What should I do if I hit the head?
I didn't think so much at the time
I think they want to do something with you
I'm definitely not happy
I'm anxious
You are stupid
I'm not stupid
This this is called love
what did you say
I, I announce
Guan Xiaotang fell in love with Li Siyu
Thirty-three days now
Zero five hours
Forty-eight minutes and seven seconds
You little kid
Understand what love is
I am an early adult
I put aside feudal society
Now there are groups of early wives and concubines
Children are piled up
You figure it out. I'm your boss
Boss, I can't make it either
Can't
I can
Let me tell you
You spanked me
You harassed me
You are responsible for harassing me
Are you sick
I want to be sick
You are medicine
Who do you fall
Li Siyu, let me tell you
You have to face this
you
what happened to you
Why don't you hit me to death
What happened to you
pain
It hurts
Walk around
Go to the hospital go to the hospital
Stop, stop, wait
Slowly
Doctor, is it serious?
Two rib fractures
Fortunately there is no misalignment
Are you stupid
Two broken ribs
I don't even know
Me me me me
Many fractures
It was only a slight pain at first
Coupled with different individual sensitivity
so
It's normal not to know
Need to be hospitalized
Don't need this
Chest strap external fixation
Then usually
Don't do strenuous exercise
Must rest quietly
Check it out regularly
Just two months
Should be able to return to normal
Thank you
You take this
Don't come to the company during this time
Rest at home
You are so good to me suddenly
Go over there
That what
Let's go see
What are they plotting
Is not
What if it's bad for our company
go
Look
Brother, think of a solution
The hospital urged so many times
What can I do if I don't pay?
Younger siblings
Listen to my advice
This is the only way
Brother, the doctor said
He is getting better
Maybe in a few days
He is out of danger
I borrowed everything that should be borrowed
I also borrowed things that shouldn't be borrowed
I am now
Can't think of a way
Where to get money
But there is a little way
I won't come up with
This idea comes
You don't think about yourself
Not for the two babies at home
Are there four old people in mind?
Let's go
The hateful must have pity
Are you OK
it's all my fault
sister
It has nothing to do with you
I was too eager to get it
no
If the training is in place
They can't fight
Sister, don't think so
This matter has nothing to do with us
in case
It’s not that I pursue speed
If I can train employees
Implement all
This thing won't happen
President Su
I will visit you next time
Mom is back
Ok
came back
You did it
I watch the video online
Learned from the chef
You never enter the kitchen before
You work so tired every day
I am a person who eats leisurely at home
Have to do something
Help you share it
Yuwei, have dinner
Come
Sit down
The dishes are cold in a while
You don't care you don't care
I went to the vegetable market today to buy vegetables
just got it
Food is so expensive now
The living expenses of our family
Just that
Not bad at all
How are you arrogant
Simple to say
Some dishes to buy in the morning
cheaper
Some dishes
20% off after 8pm
little more
Was killed online
All learning
Come
Try this
Dad, give me the refrigerator
Which is the refrigerator
That one
this is for you
Zhizhi, come on
you go for rest
Yu Wei
Clothes changed in the morning
Where did you go
I washed it
And your underwear
I washed all of them
father
Tell me one more
The story of a scientist
Scientist's story
Let me tell you
Do not
I want my father to tell me
Dad knows many scientists
I've only been with dad for a few days
Just hate me
No, I want my father to tell me
Good good
Dad washed the dishes first
Then tell a story to Yuwei
good or not
it is good
Yu Wei
Remembered
Can't eat this
Because there are peanuts in it
Will make you sick
do you know
Know there are peanuts in it
Buy it for her
I bought this for you
Dad will finish the dishes in a while
Come find you
There are not only peanuts
And red dates
I want you to make up
Fell asleep
My junior wants to go back home
Want me
Go to teacher Gao's office
Replace him
Can the body work?
No problem working in the laboratory
I asked
Because of the laboratory
No results
So the salary is relatively low
Can only be half of the previous
But this home
I can't always rely on you
the first
You can't afford
second
I'm sorry
Zhizhi
After this time
I've been a lesson
do not worry
When i get back to work
I will repay you
I believe in our home
Will be the same as before
What do you say
Sister Fan
Manager Li
You go to the hospital
Take the medical expenses of the wounded
Paid in advance
Our cash flow is not abundant
But if the money is not given
I can't feel at ease in my life
Ok
Too decent you
Okay, so handsome
Guan Xiaotang
Chest chest chest chest
Come to my office
come on, come on, come on
Go fast go fast go
Go go go go
Come on, brother
come on, come on, come on
Today I
I won't break your ribs
My last name is not Li
you you you
Span if you want
You still want to wall
Don't you think
Do we two match well
Match your size
I am sincere
If it wasn't for the website, you still need
I will drive you now
I have the right to love
Whoever you love has nothing to do with me
If you dare to hack my computer
Fix my photo
Get off now
If you don't like it
I will change another way next time
It's no use changing anything
do not like you
do you like me
It has nothing to do with me
I like you enough
Get out of me
I'm never ending with you
roll
Come in
Mr. Chen just received the notice
Ten o'clock to open the Genting project
Second Demonstration Meeting
Ok
At the head office
correct
I'll go now
Wait
Genting project
Mr. Zhou also participated
You should ask Mr. Zhou to come over
Row
Forget it, let me go by myself
never mind
You go out first
OK
Manager Chen
Ok
President Wang
Manager Chen
President Chen is here
Then we all get ready to start
President Wang hasn't arrived yet
Today's meeting
President Wang is not participating
it is good
Today, please come here
Mainly our project
Now has one
new progress
According to our internal relationship
Now this blue cloud project
Structure pattern
We have got it
Come, let's take a look
Report of this analysis
The third page
We all come
Focus on
It this
Is the survey results and analysis
This is particularly important
Because of it
Is for customer groups
An analysis
this project
We have to discuss
Manager Chen
Today they this
this thing
Let's go down and take a look
Row
Inside it
Very well analyzed
it is good
Ok
I'll go there first
Annie
Is Mr. Wang at the company today?
in
it is good
Do you want her
No
Annie
I want to ask again
President Wang this week
Some night have time
Available after Wednesday
I get it, thank you
Sister Ziru
Are you free on Thursday night
I want to treat you to dinner, Mr. Chen
Ok
OK
But why? Mr. Chenhao
I have something on my mind that you need to solve
The old place at seven o'clock in the evening
See you at the barbecue stall
Ok
Xiaoling
congratulations
Finally found one
Handsome and rich boyfriend
What's wrong with you
What is this?
Good everywhere
Just boring
Is it too demanding?
I also advised myself
It's thirty-two
Past this village
There is no such village head
Bear with it
correct
Report to you
I transferred to the sales department
Sales
Sister Yuan's men
Ok
I always think
What you said to me before
You said that women must be independent
must
I can take care of myself
Zhizhi
I have been busy lately
About the call
No time to find you
Is something wrong with you
I'll give you if you need money
I have it here too
You guys have helped me a lot
I really appreciate you
I can't ask for your money anymore
Or you come to my company
This way
I'm not relying on you
Relying on Liu Yang
Recently experienced
So many things
I also understand
Can't rely on others anymore
I must rely on myself
So this time
I must stand up by myself
this road
Not easy
Which way is easy
look at you
Become chairman
Still get beaten
And Xiaoling
Looks so pretty
Find a boyfriend
Not completely satisfied
If you figure it out
I will give you two words
Come on
Do not worry
Me this time
I won't be knocked down
For Yuwei
Ok
Come
I'll open the door
Ok
Hello, Li Siyu's express
it is good
mine
Such a big box
You bought something
Sister Siyu, such a big express
what is this
I'll tear it down
what
What did you buy
I didn't buy it
A box of money
G
What is it
be careful
what
Have card
Li Siyu, accept me
Explain to me quickly
what happened
Are you so rascal now?
Sister, did you receive the gift?
Like it
Guan Xiaotang
If you dare to harass me
Get off now
Take a look
Throw it away
You do not want
You don't like
I want to see you off again
Why don't you throw it away
You don't want me
This is very expensive, look
Who the hell is it
Company kid
How small
Ninety-eight
So small
Ok
Actually not very small
Does he like you
I think he is sick
You will make a big move
Don't think too much
I have nothing with him
Yeah
You still have to find a reliable one
Or it's a waste of time
Have to find one
Someone better than you to take care of you
Actually, you can also try
Anyway, idle is idle
You let me follow one
You can call me auntie's child
fall in love
Although this kid can't live
But he can warm you
You just put him
As a shot of hyaluronic acid
Ha ha
What you said prove again
We are not the same
Even if we are not the same kind of people
But we can also
Encourage each other
All the way
Xiaoling, come
Wish you always have hyaluronic acid
Siyu, wish you a prosperous career
Zhizhi, I wish you stronger and stronger
Sorry, handsome guy
Keep you waiting
Your wine is here
Okay, thank you
Please slow down
Um thanks
Xiao Liu, this table is over
That table
Collect it at that time
it is good
Boss, my skewers
Wait a moment
it is good
Sister Ziru, I've arrived
Don't worry, take your time
Xiao Liu took the table away
Hello Annie
I am Chen Yiming
excuse me, may I ask
Where is President Wang tonight
do not know
President Wang has no arrangements tonight
Ok thank you
President Wang
Chen Yiming, President Chen is looking for you
Where are you now
Hello, Master Wang
You are at home
That king
Good good
okay I know
Ok
Okay, thank you
Hey
Sister Ziru, are you okay?
I'm fine. What's wrong
If you don't answer the phone
I'm going to call the police
Yiming, I'm so sorry
I forgot
We have a date today
I'm still having a meeting here
It's okay i
I know you are fine
I am in the office
Another customer
Waiting for me
I may not be able to live today
Then I'll make up for you another day
Ok i have no problem
Then let's change the appointment again
OK, that's it first
Goodbye
If you want to find someone to solve
I'm here
President Wang
Just got off work
Yes, just got off work
I'm sorry that day
No, nothing trivial
Shall I make up for you today?
No need Mr. Wang
Didn't you say something is on your mind
Do you want me to solve
Have been resolved
But I have something on my mind today
Need you to solve