[To Dear Myself]
[Ep11]
The letter is ready
It's written in Chinese and English
Only one theme
To ensure a happy environment for our kids
the kindergarten must dismiss Doudou
Are you back home?
Parent Association
Any problems?
Ok, you go on
Brother
You haven't left yet?
The latest developments in the three districts
So fast?
Mr. Liu
You can give me two more districts
Thank you
It's ok
Leave it to me
Is Zhao a mole?
I have checked the data
I find all the errors come from Zhao's part?
I am sure, he is the mole
Mr. Liu
What should we do next?
I need to think about it
Go home early
I should go too
Ok
Doudou's mom apologized to me
She is going to resign and take care of Doudou at home
She promises me that Doudou will change
So should we give her more time?
No
I can't bear it anymore
This is not the first time that Doudou's parents apologize
Has Doudou changed?
Just ignore them
Yes
Doudou's mom is very sincere
What's the use of her sincerity?
I just think if we force the boy to drop out
will it affect his psychology?
You are so compassionate
You even think for Doudou's psychology
He is a bully
He is so overbearing all day
Think
How much psychological impact he caused for our kids
I asked Yuwei
Doudou is naughty and annoying
But he is not a bully
Yes...
My daughter Linda told me, actually Doudou has some advantages
He can take initiative to help teachers in the kindergarten
My son William said
He often walks back and forth in class
It affects other kids' learning
Yes
And he blocked other kids at the door of the toilet
In the end, Xingxing shat in pants
Do you know what happened yesterday?
He was so ridiculous yesterday
Doudou put a worm on Miaomiao's dress
Miaomiao is so freaked out and she cried
Yes
It's just kids' little prank
I don't mind it if it's a low kindergarten, 1,000 yuan a month
But now why do we spend so much money for our kids?
We just hope our kids could grow up healthily and safely
Correct
We can't make a mistake in education
Yes...
Yuwei's mom
We don't mind if you want to be a good person
Anyway, I will drive away Doudou
I want to give Miaomiao a safe and good environment
I sign first
Yuwei's mom
So you will sign or not?
I...
Sign it
All right
Well
My daughter Miaomiao's birthday is coming on the 20th
We are going to throw a big birthday party
for her at the Star Equestrian Club
You should come till then
Ok
Ok, I will go
My son William, likes riding horses best
Tell your son William to teach my daughter Linda
Ok, no problem
My daughter wants to invite Yuwei
Yuwei's mom
You daughter will come, right?
Ok...
Great
I like the cake
The cake is delicious
Yiming
Finally
I just finish my work
Come
I need to get changed first
Ok
President Pan, bye  -President Wang
See her off
Please
Goodbye
Goodbye, Siyu
Brother Yang
Siyu
Yiming, I love you
So great that he has you
I just arrived here
Brother Yang
I hope recently you can often play basketball with him
What's wrong?
He is gloomy recently
He often says he wants to be alone
Then he just stays at home alone
I am afraid if he goes on like this, he will become a decadent
He will get better when he finds a job
Yes
He needs to find a job as soon as possible
Brother Yang
How's the tender?
Next week, we will make the announcement with the tender plan
I will notify you in advance
Ok
I have filed it in our company
I'll bid on behalf of our company
Just ignore others
What do you mean? Who else?
Now the competition in our company is fierce
As I know, you are framed up
More than that
They nitpick me in every way possible
How do you face?
Nothing special
Just retaliate them back
Some people are just like mosquitoes
The more you hide, the more aggressive they get
Just swat them
Then the whole world is quiet
You are right
Come
I had to sign under that circumstance
But after that, I feel so bad
So be it
Yes
I can go to visit equestrian club
Great
Wu, I told you last time
He is getting more ridiculous
Originally, I wanted to make concessions
Now I have to fight back
How?
They hold the birthday party in equestrian club
What gift should I prepare?
A six-year-old girl's birthday
Why bother?
Your priority is to persuade mom
Xiaoling today gave me an idea
Can you get down to business?
Yuwei's business is not business?
The second child is not a business?
Xiaoling gave me an idea
Just tell your mom
You have no fertility
Your mom won't tell us to have a son
No, are you kidding me?
If people know this, I will be so disgraced
Your mom keeps nagging
You don't feel it's annoying?
We need to solve it
But we can't solve it like this
What should we do?
It can't be my problem anyway
Birthday present
It can't be less than 500 yuan
Sleep
Come, Yuwei
Open your mouth, eat more
You need to grow tall like your dad
Yang
Yesterday I called aunt Liu
Which aunt Liu?
On the east, Liu Erguai's wife
She hugged you when you were a baby
Oh
Aunt Liu says, it's all because Yuwei is not a good name
Yuwei has the underlying meaning of water, it's not for her brother
So you can't have a son
No, mom
Why do you believe this?
If you think so, my name means more water
So I have to change my name?
It has nothing to do with you
All because of Yuwei
She has to change her name
Dad, I won't change my name
You won't change
Why you don't believe me?
Yang
You are not like this before
Mom, I am full
What are you looking at?
Eat...
We should get a medical certificate
You have changed your mind?
Yes I have changed my mind
But it's your infertility certification
Otherwise it's so disgraceful
Ok
Zhao
Mr. Liu
Sit down
I have checked your data
It's very informative
It saves me a lot of time
Thank you
I am busy recently
Please help me with this paper
Make it into a formal bidding paper
Ok
Thank you
Come
That's it
I have told you I have many friends
I find this one according to your requirements
Come, shoe covers
Look
If you don't like it, we can find another one
Come, come in
Come
Have a look
This is the bathroom
This is the kitchen
Now the one-bedroom house...
Look here
The environment
Very stylish
It's very suitable for girls like you
I have seen many houses like this
My friend said, this is the best for my girlfriend
Future girlfriend
Look at the balcony
Here is the best
Do you feel it's like old Shanghai?
The house is so old
The house is old
But it's newly decorated
The most important thing is location
This location is downtown
It's quiet in a bustling area
It's so close to the subway
Will it be noisy?
Listen
Do you hear the noise?
Do you know why?
The subway station is in north
We are in the south
But there is a snack street nearby
People come and go
No, that snack street is great
If you are hungry at night, you can eat downstairs
So convenient
Then I will get fat easily
You won't
I have thought about it for you
There are three gyms over there
You will have discount if you apply for a VIP card now
You are an intermediary or he is?
He is
Come...
Introduce here to her
Miss Gu, how's it?
Do you like it?
How much a month?
4,500 a month
One month deposit and two months up front
So expensive?
Not expensive
You are an intermediary or he is?
It's him
Shut up
My current apartment is 3,8000
You...
3,800, a deal
Really?
Then I will re-bargain, 3,500
No...
Look
We should be trustworthy, right?
You said, it's 3,800
You get some rebate, right?
Heaven forbid
How can I shortchange you?
Do I take the rebate?
Then why do you defend for him?
If you really don't believe me
I can show you my heart
Look
Smelly, get away from me
Miss Gu
So can we sign the contract, now?
3,500
Can you make some compromise?
Show your sincerity
Deal
Can I move tomorrow?
I'll give you the key right after we sign the contract
Ok
Deal
So great that you like it
See around
Great
You cost me 500 yuan
Brother
Your girlfriend is so beautiful
Let alone 500
it's worth it even if it's 5,000
Go away...
Your bed  -Don't sit on my bed
No... The bed
It's very comfortable to lie on it
You should lie down
Director, the new tender scenario
How's it?
No mistake this time, right?
If you make another mistake, I can't explain to president Lu
Ok, just leave it here
I will check it out
If there is no problem, I will give it to president Lu
There will be no problems
If we purchase according to this scenario
we will waste 8,000,000 yuan
Liu Yang
What do you mean?
Director
The tender scenario in your hands is made by Zhao and Wu
I have another one here
This one, I checked and verified all the data
The biggest difference is
several chapters in the first scenario are made by Zhao and Wu
Their budget plan will waste a lot of money
And the waste won't happen in the second scenario
Look at this
Come
Yes  -This...
Put this in the attachment
Ok
Have lunch together
For the celebration
Wu, Zhao
Director wants to see you
Braised pork
Thank you
Let me tell you
In my presence, director Wang didn't say anything
But then he transferred Wu to receive and send files
And transferred Zhao to be the receptionist
So great
Well, director Wang agreed
You are one of my team now for this tender project
Really?
So I can learn something from you
After the tender is completed, I will tell director Wang to hire you formally
Thank you, brother Yang
No, brother
I'm sorry
I don't know why I call you brother Yang
Whatever you like
If I call you brother Yang,
so what will you call me?
I will call you sister Yun in the future
Ok
Come, sister Yun
Thank you
Without you, god knows what will happen
Brother Yang
Don't say like that
With your talent and ability
those villains can't touch your foundation
But it's so annoying
Brother Yang
I'll follow you from now on
Is it true?
My uncle works there
They are making the tender scenario now
What's the total money?
More than 20 million
How about Li Siyu?
We only lead them by 300,000
We got Daneng's order of 5,000,000, right?
We didn't sign the contract
Sister Yuan negotiated with them for more than three months
They found a new supplier
I don't know the specifics
We need to take the project
Yes, sister Yuan will be the director after we get the tender
Go ask your uncle
who is in charge of tender
I need to know his personal hobbies and social connections
Ok
Mr. Guo
It's so hard to make an appointment with you
I tried so hard to make an appointment with you
So we can't leave unless we drink up the wine
Mr. Guo
I have a stomach problem recently
I can't drink
Drink one glass
I really didn't lie to you
Let me show you
See, all stomach medicine
Ok...
I will drink alone, ok?
Next time
Excuse me
Hello
I know
Keep an eye on that
Education, age
Not a problem
I just needs talents
Yes, ok
Thank you
Goodbye
Mr. Guo
Your company is recruiting people?
We need a director for publicity department
I can recommend one for you
Great
Pass on
Yes, get in
Ok, great
It's close
So dangerous
Come, Yiming
Drink
No water, drink beer
I drive today, no beer
I will drink with you another day
Ok
Yiming
As I know, you are looking for a job recently
Fenglin company is recruiting a copywriter
Are you interested?
I can recommend you
Mind your language
He was the planning director
You tell him to apply for copywriter
Are you insane?
Don't listen to Haowen
I just want to take a break recently
I don't think about the job now
Ok, I get it
Thank you
It's ok
Come, drink
Come...
Send me your latest resume
Yeah
Come, drink
Bravo
Hurry, I am waiting
Which company?
What post?
Mr. Guo
I have sent the resume to you
Ok
Yeah, I got it
I willl transfer it to the HR director
Mr. Guo, thank you
Let me propose a toast to you
You can't drink, right?
I am happy today
Ok
Sit down...
Come
Where are you now?
With whom?
Sister, look
We have cooperated with each other happily for so many years
All because you are so kind
He wants to ask Mr. Chen Yiming to have an interview tomorrow
Sure
No problem, when tomorrow?
Ten o'clock in the morning
I tell him now
Mr. Guo
Thank you so much
To you again
No wine
We can have another bottle
One more bottle
Waiter, wine
Haowen, I need to make a call now
Excuse me
Mr. Guo, I need to answer the call
Go
Waiter
Bring me another bottle of wine
Ok
Hello, Siyu
Yiming, good news
10 o'clock tomorrow morning
You will have an interview at the company
I have sent the address
You are drunk?
You told me, you won't drink today, right?
I have good news today
I just signed a contract
Also helped you find a job
Send me the location
I am coming to pick you up now
Can it be cured?
Obstruction of fallopian tubes, it can't be cured
What if the doctor makes a mistake?
It's the director of obstetrics and gynecology
It's true
I went with Zhizhi
The expert is famous
We can't register if we don't have connection
Mom...
Are you all right?
Let me process
Mom
It works
I am a little worried now
I am afraid my mom can't take the blow
Her disease will relapse
She will be a little disappointed at most
We and Yuwei should talk to her more
She will be ok, right?
Hope so
Let me help you
It's ok
Ok
The car is there
The car is here
Ok...
Let me help you
Be careful
Mr. Guo, to be honest
The interviewee tomorrow is my boyfriend
Really?
He is very excellent
Otherwise I won't love him
Yeah, it's true
Let me tell you
Your boyfriend is not an ordinary man
You will not regret if you hire him
Well
No need to have the interview
Just tell him
He just comes to work tomorrow
Really?
Yes
Mr. Guo, thank you so much
Thank you for giving me such a talent
Don't worry, I won't shortchange him
Thank you so much
Don't be so polite
I won't
I'm afraid you drink too much
It's ok, girl, don't worry
I will keep an eye on him for you
Thank you, big brother
Ok, that's all, bye
Bye
Be careful
Go
Yiming
Why don't you come earlier?
You almost could see president Guo
What happened?
Smile
Yiming
Sir
A kiss
Honey water
Drink some honey water
Nailed it
President Guo said
You will work directly without interview tomorrow
Director of publicity department
It's your profession
I won't go
Why?
Sit well
Yiming
You want to take some break and think
Ok, I support you
But you can't think endlessly
You can't stay at home forever
You will be a decadent if you go on like this
You need to go work
I have found a job
Found a job?
Which company?
Fenglin Industry
Is the company big?
Just so so
What do you do?
Copywriter
You are the director of publicity department in president Guo's company
His company is not big
But it's very stable in the industry
And last year, it's top Ten in China
Forget it
I will go to Fenglin
Why?
No why
Because they give you high salary
or you will have more opportunities in that company?
Neither
Yiming, I don't understand
Normal people will choose president Guo's company
I am an abnormal man
What happened?
Tell me the truth
I don't want you to suffer because of me
It's not a big deal
I just drink some wine with president Guo
You won't be unhappy just because I drink with the client?
I won't
Then why?
Tomorrow you should go to president Guo's company
Ten o'clock in the morning
I have told you
I won't go
You...
Are you sober?
Go to bed early
Why it becomes like this?
Why?