# Google translate version for your reference #
Ok ok
Ok
I'll be there on time tomorrow
I haven't gotten through your call
I'm sorry
Have been busy
I think twice
I think we
The gap is still big
I think we two
Very good chat
And two kids
Also get along
We get along very well
but
But i don't want to get married
Because I can't let go of Liu Yang
Has nothing to do with him
Why is that
I want to continue working
I don't want to go back
Go on the old road of husband and child
Is it because
What did i say that day
Hurt you
Right, Zhizhi
I don't have any
Look down on you
I really like you
I care about you
I don't want you to suffer
I know
Thank you Lixing
But an easy life
Might make me feel
Insecure
Instead I'm a little tired
I feel more at ease
More satisfied
I can't figure it out
You like to live a hard life
I just switched to sales
Those days
In my life
The hardest day
Scolded by the boss every day
Cold face by customers
Laughed at by colleagues
Take care of the children
But during that time
Is my fastest growing
a period of time
This is
To be honest with you
With you when I first met
compared to
You can do much
Also more confident
seriously
I used to think
If my husband is good, I'll be good
Now i found out
It's really good to be good
and so
I can't go with you
I can't let go
I just found myself
But don't you want Yuwei
Get a better education
A confident and excellent mother
Is the best education for children
It looks like
You have made a decision
Lixing
Actually you are a
Very nice person
It's also worthy of women to rely on
just
I don't want to rely on you
I want to rely on myself
So
I was sent a good person card
Or else
Let's each
Busy with their respective businesses
Waiting for you back from europe
Let's see if there is fate
I have a hunch
You won't wait for me in place
I will keep going
it is good
Then
Bless you and Yuwei
Everything is fine
Also wish you and Susan happiness
Will do
What are you muttering
Talk to me
When electrochemical energy storage equipment
After generating hydrobromic acid internally
Will damage the isolation membrane
Stop, stop, stop
I can understand this chat
How many scores did you score in the college entrance examination chemistry
College Entrance Exam Chemistry
Sixty points
Still pass
Full score of 150
Tell you this
Current high capacity
Electrochemical energy storage device
Mostly rely on
Hydroxide reaction
Don't tell me so professional
Just tell me
Let's make that membraneless battery
How awesome is it
Once successful
Ok
Can change the world today
Energy pattern
Amazing
That last time
Change the world energy pattern
What is it
oil
Buffett
There are three companies now
Willing to ask me
but I do not know
Which one to go
Talk about the situation of these three companies
One is a big company
A high basic salary and high commission
There is another company
Is a new company
But willing to give me
Position of Sales Manager
Plus one more
Seven-person team
Choose a third company
Can i do it
I have been in the industry for less than a year
I haven't done it
Mom, you can
Don't be afraid
You can also become a swan
Siyu sister
I go to the third house
You must do it
Okay, thank you Sister Siyu
Yu Wei
We become swans together
good or not
it is good
Let's go
twinkle Twinkle Little Star
All over the sky
It's Little Star
Hang in the sky
Where are you two million
I treat my parents
Leave me that house
Mortgaged
You are crazy
In 1999
Yingke to Tencent
Invested 1.1 million dollars
Sold in the second year
$12.6 million
And spent
The owner who bought
Eighteen years later
Made more than 100 billion
I was thinking
Maybe you
Next legend
it is me
Don't forget
The person sitting across from you
Spent nearly five million to start a business
In the end, you won't have any points left
But this person
Dare to take one's own future ten years
To invest
What am i afraid of
I still want to remind you
this project
Success is just in case
failure
It's ninety-nine ninety-nine
I know
But I still want to bet
You are for Xiaoling
Just bet this one
Yes
I always say I love her
I'm always talking
let me see
I'm not down to earth
Did one thing for her
I know she likes money so much
But I didn’t think of a way
Make me rich
She always laughs at her material things and worships money
I think about it
Actually I don't love her at all
Always want to take advantage of her
Xiaoling said
She is happy with you
Yes
But i hope
She is with me
Not just happy
But peace of mind
So relieved that she would marry me
I heard
Your company's performance
Grow well
You don't have to take this risk
But i
I can't hold back Gu Xiaoling now
She hates marrying
I'm worried
In case my business is unsuccessful
What if Gu Xiaoling is going to marry
Siyu
I have to catch
This opportunity
Hao Wen
We will succeed
We must succeed
First I declare
By me and Lei Haowen
As a shareholder
New Green Investment Co., Ltd.
Officially established
Why is it called Xinlu
No reason i'm wayward
No culture
I like it
OK OK
New Green Investment
Invested with 5 million cash
The patent that Mr. Gao is developing
No membrane battery alone
Invincible in the world
Good name
Greener than yours
Much more interesting
Okay
According to what we said before
Unique project
Teacher Gao as a natural person
87% shareholding
New Green Investment holds shares in the company
13% of shares
Let me correct
I personally hold shares
Eighty-five percent
And Liu Yang holds shares
Two percent
Teacher Gao
You follow me
Eat less
Scolded
Where's the money
Not earning much
As a teacher
I am ashamed
I have nothing
Return to you
Can only
Give you a little hope
Thanks teacher Gao
Can i do this
Stockholder
Write my daughter's name Liu Yuwei
Let Zhang Zhizhi take care of her
To whom you love
I can't control this
Thanks teacher Gao
If everyone has no objection
That `s a deal
Ok, deal
Let us all work together
Dominate the world
Come come
I brought wine
Happy cooperation
The guests just opened
Good sign
I gonna go see
Mr. Wu
Ok
Introduce to everyone
This is our department
New sales manager
Zhang Zhizhi
Hello everyone
I am Zhang Zhizhi
starting today
I will fight with everyone
welcome
long time no see
You body
How's your body
Much better than before
That's good
Are you ok
I'm good
I'm fine, how about you
pretty good
Yiming, why are you here?
I come to find you
Come in quickly
Yiming
Sit and talk about something
Liu Yang
I come today
I want to have teacher Gao with you
Have a chat
Invest in your laboratory
On behalf of Wang Ziru
Yes
Wang Ziru told me before
For your project
Very interested
Then she and Teacher Gao
Talked twice
Not too smooth
and so
I come today
Just want to know
Gao's psychological expectations
My side
You can also put the situation of Wang Ziru
Tell you something
You are late
Haowen and I invested
The unique matter of membraneless batteries
With Teacher Gao and Liu Yang
Just signed
then you
Then you still accept
Other investors
Then you have to talk to me
I am now a unique project
Chief Executive Officer
If you want to continue to invest alone
What are the requirements
right now we
No other investment required
OK, I get it
You two buddies
Don't you plan to give me a gift
Send send send send
What's the matter with you two
Such a big deal
Don't tell me in advance
Especially you
I want to tell you
But I have no chance
You are too busy now
You count
We have met several times this week
Yiming is like this
You are with Wang Ziru every day
How do we tell you
Yes
Can we say
Partner with your ex-girlfriend
Compete with your current girlfriend
Is this true?
What do you think
Cooperation with Li Siyu
This this
Xiaoling is not thinking about rain
Half sister?
You know
I am to Xiaoling
Keep giving up
I'll change one
The purpose of saving the country
Talk about this project
Is the only thing i can get
Opportunity to get rich overnight
I can't miss
Your project
Can it really succeed?
There is still hope
Actually, there is one thing I don’t understand
Why are you guys
Would rather want five million here
Don’t want Prince Ru’s 10 million
Then we only need new green investment
13% of the shares
Your prince ru
I want sixty percent
I can understand
Actually, regardless of Wang Ziru
What price
Teacher Gao won't cooperate with her
why
Because of Li Siyu
Li Siyu
Nothing at all
I was there last time she came
She couldn't talk to Teacher Gao
Not because of shares
Because of her attitude
For her
This is a business
But for Teacher Gao
This is his life's hard work
Wang Ziru is an investor
Teacher Gao is a scientist
Then they treat
Knowledge of the same thing
There must be differences
Teacher Gao said
Wang Ziru takes money too seriously
Too precise
Sit here
The sales department in the first three months
I'm in charge
I'll leave it to you next
Lay off or add
You have the final say
I only have one request
Do this sales as soon as possible
Okay, Mr. Wu
Ok
How about these seven employees
they
They all just graduated
Little experience
But very hard
Where's Wei Yayun
She's pretty down to earth
Recently talking about a client
Pretty smooth
I asked her two days ago
She said she could win
You are not usually
Do you like this best
Why didn't you eat a bite today?
not in a good mood
Watching dad
what happened
Susan is gone
We parted
She went to europe
Didn't you say that
Want to go together
Mom said we won't go
Stay here
Really
Dad, you still laugh
I have no good friends anymore
That's all right
Can't dad
Be your good friend
good or not
it is good
Come
Eat happily, OK?
Ok
Not leaving yet
Why are you leaving
I'm going to resign
why
personal reason
You stupid
Finally, the customer prepares to sign the order
You resigned
It’s not a waste of effort
You want to resign
Wait for the customer to sign the order
You take the commission before leaving
At least one month later
A month passed in a blink of an eye
I am leaving
Come ring the doorbell
Mom, this is for you
Why spend this money
I said this is delicious
Dad said to buy one for you
Thank you
Or come in and sit for a while
OK
When did this light break
Why don't you say a word
Encounter something like this in the future
Just give me a call
Send a WeChat
I'm here
Guess I am at the new company today
Who did you meet
Help me drive
All right
thank you
Thank you
I heard Yuwei say
You are not going
Ok
Zhizhi
do not worry
I won't let you down
Don't think too much
I am not staying for others
For myself
but
I still have a chance
is not it
I just arrived at the new company
The pressure is really great
No time to think about this
I know
Liu Yang
Let's go with the flow
understand
You just said
Who did you meet at the new company
No one
One
Someone you don't know
You are finally willing to come to see me
What's the matter
I'm still busy
We have been three weeks
Did not meet
These three weeks
We talked six times in total
Time per call
No more than thirty-five seconds
I took the initiative to send you
Seventeen times WeChat
Thirty-five words
But you only replied to me thirteen times
You never gave me
Actively sent WeChat
What do you want to say
You are hiding from me
Who is hiding from you
I'm just busy at the gallery
Your gallery
What can be busy
My gallery is adjusting recently
it is good
I believe you for this reason
What else do you have
prenuptial agreement
How are you looking
Too long, I haven't finished it yet
I gave you two months
You haven't finished watching
ok I admit it
I have dyslexia
Then why didn't you talk about it before
Ok i'm sick
And I lied
Only five million
Correct
But only accounted for
13% of the shares
No wonder
But one thing I don’t understand
General angel investment
Rarely more than 30%
Why are you
Must be 60%
I asked an expert to evaluate
Their project
It won't succeed at all
No investment value
Then why do you still vote
Even if they fail completely
But their early
Research data is still valuable
Ten million sixty percent
I happen to be fine
Besides
What if they succeed
That value is immeasurable
So no matter what happens
You will be invincible
I believe in Graham's
Two investment principles
the first
Don't lose money
second
Don't forget the first
You are an expert in investment
but
Are you kind of
Too fine
Yiming
I also want to boldly
Spend a lot of money
But I have shareholders
There are employees below
my position
Don't allow me to do this
understand
Ten fifty in the morning
Till 11:45
President's Communication Meeting
Twelve five
Till one fifteen in the afternoon
Lunch with Mr. Smith
1:30 to three in the afternoon
Headquarters park planning meeting
3:15 to 5:30
Investment Group Annual Closed Meeting
5:45 to 7:00
Property Group Closed Meeting
And then rushed to Xihua University
Your speech
Will start around 7:20
I know
If nothing happens
We go out first
Change this to a presentation
Okay, Mr. He
This one
Gu Xiaoling has dyslexia
I haven't finished it for two months
Change this to a presentation
Give her another chance
Mr. He
Miss Gu I am afraid not
Dyslexia
What do you mean
Follow me to you
Statistics of dating data
I think she wants to break up with you
This explains
Why for more than two months
She never did
Sign this agreement
I know
You go out first
Ok
Sister Zhizhi early
early
Good morning, sister Zhizhi
Sister Zhizhi
This is the client
Latest feedback information
Ready to place an order
it is good
Sister Zhizhi, you sign
Manager Zhang, I have a pen here
Manager Zhang
I have wiped the tables and chairs
The green plants are also watered
This cup of health tea on your table
Just soaked
You are a little haggard recently
Can replenish qi
No more
I can do it myself
You work so busy every day
I will share some of the burden for you
It should be
No matter how much you do
Will not change
My opinion of you
Sister Zhizhi
I'm wrong
I
Sorry
If i am not
Be your boss
You will tell me
Sorry?
I always wanted to apologize to you
Confess to you
but I
I
I have no face to see you
This half a year
I have a bad time
My parents almost followed me
Sever relationship
but me
And my friends
Also point to me
I really regret it
I am confused for a while
I hurt others and I hurt myself
My sister Zhizhi
Don't call me sister Zhizhi
Call me manager Zhang
Go out without much
Give me the sample
This
This this this
Failed again
normal
Edison
It took ten years
Failed more than 25,000 times
Invented the battery
So far
How many times have you failed
Since I entered the laboratory
Almost fifty times
In the past ten years, Mr. Gao
Almost failed
Thousands of times
Wrong so many times
No reflection, no progress
You are a pig
Pigs are smarter than you
I don't deserve to stand here
Who is he scolding
Scold himself
Siyu
We are on the account now
How much money is left
Three hundred and three thousand
What? Three hundred thousand
Five million is 300,000
So say this experiment
Is our last time
Did an experiment
not enough
An experiment
At least half a million
Are you kidding me?
correct
Are we out of money?
Teacher Gao, why are you asking this?
I found another breakthrough
I want next month
Do another experiment
Can it succeed
Hope is great, i have confidence
Five at a time
All the way
Teacher Gao, be yours
Don't worry about money
Subsequent second round of financing
We are already talking
Next month at the latest
Additional funds will be in place
Really
Do you really treat Lei Haowen
When our team eats free meals
it is good
We are
Walk around
Do an experiment of 500,000
Keep your voice down
We are 300,000
Where am i going
Make so much money
No, I ask you
I do not know how
What about the second round of financing
You heard it just now
Teacher Gao's next experiment
Have great hopes
We have no reason
Give up at this time
So at the end of this month
We must
Raise a sum of money in
Guarantee Gao
Finish the next experiment
Where am i going
I'll raise this money for you
Aren't you from Shanghai
Aren't you rich second generation
Don't you claim to be well-connected
Yes but
Lei Haowen, if you want
Take your two million back
Hurry to find money
Without you
Think Gu Xiaoling
OK OK OK
I really don't know
Shen Nanpeng
You always know Li Kaifu, right?
Haowen
Your project
Can't see the future at all
Where is Qiming's Gan Jianping?
Where is Bertelsmann's Long Yu
I just entered the industry for two months
You ask me to know
China's top 20
Top investor
Are you embarrassing me?
Zhou Zong
You know why
Can't see the future?
Because now
Is the darkness before dawn
It's dawn as soon as you come in
Find someone else
No, Mr. Zhou
If you want
Take your two million back
Hurry to find money
Think Gu Xiaoling
Do you want to
Introduce me one
Reliable investor
I'm sorry
You read martial arts novels in class
Found by the teacher
The pot i topped for you
Add this person to WeChat
Just say I made a kid
What is this person
His uncle's ex-wife
Cousin's second husband
Be a driver in Huaxing
Ah what do you want
Gagaga
Please come in
Sister Zhizhi
This is Wei Yayun's contract
Please review
What's going on
Let her do it again
it is good
Sister Zhizhi
Did she do it on purpose?
What deliberately
Someone told me
Wei Yayun is leaving
If she really wants to leave
We have to cut the mess quickly
Lest she be half-hearted
Harm the company's interests
Ok i got it
Go out
what's wrong with you
You look
Such a low-level error
You want to kill me
You can change it yourself