[To Dear Myself]
[Ep17]
My virile roommate called his dad after he went back
He said
Dad, my classmates go to lecture by subway
Only I drive Ferrari
His dad was so furious
His dad said
Hello, son
No way
We can't let Europeans look down on us
How much is the subway?
I will transfer you 100 million now
Is it enough?
Really?
Of course it's fake
Xiaoling, to be honest
Foreign upstarts' lifestyle is so unbelievale
for Chinese upstarts like me
Really?
My goal now is to make more money
In the future I will buy a subway for my son
Xiaoling
You look like Duffy Sheridan's girls when you smile
A bit of art
Aloof and unrestrained
And a bit cunning
Really?
I have a present for you
What?
This morning, in the park, the leaf fell on my shoulder for no reason
I thought
It looked so like you
For no reason
You break into my heart
So I decide to give it to you
Thank you
I will treasure the gift
Hello, sir
You are here to buy a car?
Yeah
Come in, please
Ok
Do you have humanity?
I was dumped
I thought I would pick Gu Xiaoling up
Now she ignores me
Say something
Do you have any sympathy?
It's ok
Sir, it's the latest new energy car
It uses Lubao's battery
With a long battery life
It can reach 410 kilometers
Fast charge
It only needs an hour
Here is the production process for charging and discharging
Put the plate of the battery in sink first after assembly
Then it will charge and discharge
Compared with the previous external chemical production process
It is more eco-friendly
President Wang
Yiming
What's this?
Lubao's valuation offer is too high
The main reason is they are optimistic
about Lubao III's future market prospects
Lubao III hasn't reached a mass market yet
I have made surveys on customer trials
I think these data might be helpful for you to
reassess Lubao III's future market prospects
Why do you think of the survey?
Because I think you will need it in the next negotiation
I also checked planning department's previous evaluation
I don't think it is very accurate
So I reevaluate it with my experience
This is my evaluation report
Yiming
I have told you
You don't need to participate in this project
But I want to tell everyone in the group
I am planning director in Tianyi Group now
I have responsibilities and obligations
to prove my ability and my professional ethics to my company
I have studied Lubao group's A round of investment
I made a roughl analysis on Pan Zhiyong's character
and his psychological construction
Look
I think it may help you negotiate with him
Yiming
You are competent
And you have exceeded my expectation
Thank you, president Wang
I'll go back to work now
Ok
Come
Thank you, everyone
To all of you
Liu
After the bidding, you will be promoted as vice director, right?
Yes  -Absolutely
So what are we waiting for?
Let's congratulate on Liu now
Come...
Congratulations
It's not confirmed yet
Drink first
Liu
Yes, drink it
I will
But you can't talk nonsense to others
Ok
Bottom up
Great... Cheers
Cheers
It's so late
Why Liu Yang isn't back?
Mom, he's an adult
He knows what he should do
Don't worry
Or...
You should call him
He will call me if necessary
Mom, I need to work tomorrow
Good night
Bidding is not over yet
We need to fight till the last moment
Liu
Ok
Drink
Come
Brother Yang, drink less
You call him brother Yang?
You two are so close
Let me tell you
Wei Yayun
Is my sister
None of you are allowed to bully her
Won't...
Yayun
Drink with me
Come, drink
Closer
Come...
Drink
Sister Yun
Thank you
Brother Yang
Wait...
Cross-cupped wine
I have told you
You can't bully her
Cross-cupped wine
Come, bottom up
Bottom up
Cross-cupped wine
Sorry, the subscriber you dialed can not be connected
Yayun, are you ok?
I'm fine...
I will leave Liu to you
Don't worry, bye
Brother Yang
Brother Yang, are you ok?
I'm sorry
Brother Yang
What are you talking about?
Be careful
Brother Yang, sit down for a while
Sister Yun
You know what
Today, I just want to celebrate with you alone
You should take the big credit for the bidding
Brother Yang
You are welcome
Brother Yang, you...
Why are you looking at me like this?
Sister Yun
You are so beautiful
Phone number 6745 grabbed the car?
Phone number 6745
Yes
Let's go
Brother Yang, be careful
Finally
Hello
Aunt
I'm Liu Yang's colleague
He's drunk
I am taking him home by taxi
Ok...
Thank you...
It's ok...
Aunt, please tell me the address
No. 85, South Garden,  Jincheng Avenue
Thank you
It's ok
Almost get there
Why are you so drunk?
Aunt  -Mom
Oh my God
Be careful
We had a celebration
Mr. Liu Yang is happy so he gets drunk
Ok
He needs some honey water
And he can't catch cold at night
Ok, thank you
Mom, let me introduce to you
My colleague Yayun
She is very nice
Thank you
Be careful
Be careful, brother Yang  -It's okay
Let me help you
No need, it's ok
No need
Look, your clothes get dirty now
Come upstairs to wash it
No need
I need to go back
This...
Mr. Liu Yang's bag and phone
I have to go now, aunt
Ok...
I won't see you off
It's ok
Next time we will celebrate it, only two of us
Ok
Brother Yang, good night
Stop it, go home
Goodbye aunt
Bye
Goodbye, brother Yang
Thank you
It's ok
Let's go...
Bye
Why do you drink so much?
I am happy
Happy?
How will you explain to her?
What's wrong?
Come, give me a hand
How much did you drink?
Come...
Be careful
Mom, water
Get him some water
Zhang Zhizhi
I will be promoted to deputy director soon
You will be Mrs. deputy director
Yang, you are going to be promoted to deputy director?
Brilliant
Hurry, he needs water
Do you know?
How much long-suffering I have been through these years?
How much torture I have taken?
But now I have made it
I get what I desire
You should stop being mentally fragile
Stop making a fuss
Try to be a good wife
Yuwei...
What are you doing?
I want to tell the good news to Yuwei
She is sleeping
Just wake her up
Don't be so ridiculous
What's wrong?
Did I do something wrong?
I can tell you
I am the most capable dad in the world
I am the most capable husband in the whole world
I am the most capable son in the whole world
What do you want?
I just want to ask Yuwei
if I am the best dad in the world
I ask her
I am...
Be your director
Mom
What?  Go on sleeping, baby
I want dad  -Come
Dad is not back yet
Wash
Bloody wife
Ridiculous
Don't know to take care of the husband
Look
Come...
Son, come, sit well
Look
Liu Yang
Brother Yang
When you were kissing me, you catptured my heart
Full?
Let's go
Come
Goodbye, grandma, dad
Ok, good bye
Be careful
I need to go to work now
Wait
Sit down
What's wrong?
Who is the woman that sent you back last night?
Colleague
I think she cares about you
An ordinary colleague
Let me tell you
I'm not satisfied with Zhizhi
But she is your wife, after all
You have Yuwei
You need to be upright
You can't do anything wrong to her
Did you hear me?
Yes
I need to go for work now
I don't know what I did last night
Did I do something wrong to you?
No, brother Yang
On the contrary, I feel very happy
I finally know your heart and my heart are the same
No... you may
Maybe you have some misunderstandings
As long as you allow me to love you
I don't care
Impossible
I have a family
For you
I am willing to do anything
So many people are watching us in office
We...
I can understand
I know
Don't worry
You can call me brother Yang
I can call you sister Yun
That's all
This is the limit
You are on diet, right?
Why do you eat so much?
The nuts are low-fat and delicious
I eat it as breakfast in the morning
I will play basketball with Liu Yang
Will you come?
Is there anything you want to tell him?
I'm with Zhizhi now
No need
He is an art curator
He also has art investment company
I think he is very rich
But we have known each other for more than a month
He sends me only leaf and stone
Even more, he gave me a button
Button?
He took it off from his old shirt
He says the button knows his heartbeat
So he sends it to me
Very romantic
But I am not interested in romance
I need something practical or fashionable
Or things that could keep value
Or something vulgar
So is there anything to enlighten him?
Just be straightforward
No
I am a chic female artist now
Why do you get so many drinks?
Can you drink them all?
It's just like fresh juice
I will drink them all
Artists like me need it
I love money so much
But I have to look nonchalant
It's not easy for me
I think you should expose your mammonism properly
I'm afraid to scare him away
If he is rich, he won't be scared away
If he is scared away, it means he is not rich
Makes sense
Hello, do you have VIP card?
Zhizhi, vip card
Zhizhi
Did Liu Yang bully you recently?
Are you ok?
I pick up Yuwei every day
I feel so sick of them
I feel so bad
So ridiculous
Zhizhi, you're such a wimp
Gu Xiaoling, shut up
But Zhizhi
We must transfer
Liu Yang firmly opposed
He thinks I am mentally fragile
Thinks I am making a fuss and waste money
It has nothing to do with money
It's not mental fragility
It's about your dignity
Yes, that's what I mean
Sister Siyu
I just don't understand
Why you don't understand?
You're a wimp
You just don't...
The kindergarten is so snobbish inside and out
What can Yuwei learn from them?
Zhizhi
No offense
I think it's wrong you transferred
Yuwei to the expensive kindergarten
I was thinking as a mom, I should give her a better environment
I just want to send her to a higher class
Have you ever thought if they will accept you?
Transfer Yuwei back
Even if you lose half of the tuition,
that kindergarten is much cheaper
I think you should remember
More importantly
No one will look down on you
No one will bully you
You don't have to kiss anyone's ass
I'll go through the transfer procedures tomorrow
I think, Liu Yang has a problem
Stop it
What's wrong?
His wife was so bullied
He could tolerate it?
Just don't get bullied
All of them are so snobbish
I just do not understand
I have convinced Gu Xiaoling to move to alley nearby my house
Psychologically, I am her BFF
Why does she date a curator?
Generally speaking, if you are her BFF
you won't have her forever
Why?
Pass it
Being her boyfriend is like lay-up shot
Male BFF is different
Male BFF is long shot
It's a little far from the backboard
But I may get three points
I think you should give up
Why should I give up?
She looks so pretty
Haowen
Don't indulge in appearance
You should know a girl's inner
Her superficial inner heart deserves
my flamboyant personality
What are you sighing?
Come
Xiaoling is right
What makes me sad the most
is I have sacrificed so much for the family and Yuwei
It's ok that he doesn't appreciate it
When I feel bad, he doesn't care about me
doesn't support me
He even think it's not a problem
You ask for it
Xiaoling
Look at you
You don't buy clothes
You use the cheapest skincare products
You barely take taxi
You don't take yourself seriously
How can you let a man see you as treasure?
Enough is enough
It's also hard for Liu Yang
He needs to be cautious in office
He needs to have good performance
At the same time, he needs to please everyone
He doesn't make much money
but he needs to solve a lot of problems
Xiaoling is also right
Women can't sacrifice for men
You need to think for yourself
From now on, don't care about anything
Don't care about Liu Yang or Yuwei
You just need to get well dressed and do the makeups
I can guarantee, Liu Yang will follow you everywhere
Yuwei is still a child
I need to take care of her
After having a family, I don't know why I have so many problems
Don't listen to her
It's no use being purely beautiful
We need to have a career
So we won't be despised by husband
I understand
I want to be well-dressed
And I want to have a career
But after I have a family and a daughter
I can't do anything
Anything is possible as long as you want
You can write an application tomorrow
You can work in the sales department with me tomorrow
Let me think
You just don't understand why she thinks so
A simple reason
She just doesn't understand
I worked very hard every day
She is so annoying after I go home
She either argues with my mom,
or have a cold war with me
Now I would work overtime rather than go home
I recently read a book
Its main idea is we can't reason with wives
We need to affect them emotionally
How?
For example
Be more considerate
Think what she thinks
You just do what she wants
Gu Xiaoling
She needs money
I can't
So you and Gu Xiaoling can't be together
Liu Yang
Don't listen to him
It's a critical moment for you now
You are going to be promoted
You can't get in any trouble in your family
Otherwise all your efforts will be ruined
Yiming and Siyu are so great
Like-minded
You fight together
You have many common topics
Actually, Siyu and I have many problems
What problems?
We hold different ideas
Take a break
So I am right that I don't get married so soon
You are different
Brother Yiming loves you so much
Don't talk about you and Liu Yang
I want to talk about my dad and my mom
They married because of love
But my dad got remarried several months after my mom's death
Your dad and my mom lived very happily, right?
Yes
I am also happy for him
But just because he is very happy now
I feel bad for my mom
You hurt me so much
Mentally fragile
You are...
So obvious
If aunt were still alive, she would live a happy life with uncle
But my aunt is gone
You can't stop uncle having a new life
But he started so fast
I almost think his love for mom is fake
So now you think Chen Yiming's love for you is fake, too
No
Yiming loves me truely
But we don't know whether in the future he will...
You are so ridiculous
Who can predict the future?
It's possible that Chen Yiming becomes a womanizer or
Liu Yang has an affair in the future
You can't deny the true love now because of the uncertain future
Now we are talking
That's not all
You say, it's hard for Liu Yang
Chen Yiming flatters you and tries so hard to marry you
You think it's easy for him?
I didn't say I won't get married
You don't fear marriage now?
I fear
But I need to overcome it by marriage
Hello
Yiming
Tomorrow we should sign house purchasing contract with the agency
You need to think about it, right?
No need, I want to buy it
Ok
Come
Brilliant
Thermos mug is on sale
Brother, buy one for your love
Brother, it's getting cold
Buy one, it's very cheap
Thermos mug is on sale
Sir
How much is it?
Look
It's made in German
Usually it costs 300 or 400 yuan
Today it's on sale, 268
Yes, that's right
Write ten times, ok?
Ok
Mom
I throw it in the trash
I picked it up
This has expired and we can't eat it
It's ok
Just a few days after the expiration date
No
I will eat
We are not rich
Throw everything
Ridiculous
Let me see, write
Yang, you are back
You are back early today
Come, give it to me
Come, eat
It's still hot
Sit...
Dad
My pen has no ink
I have a pen in bag, take it yourself
Mom, look
What is this?
Thermos cup
Such a beautiful thermos cup
For whom?
Bought for Zhizhi
It's not enough for you
I'll make you some sour pork
Ok
The vegetable price has gone up again
Yesterday the potato was 2.99 half a kilo
Today it's 3.59
Mom says her leg is painful
I want to buy a kneecap of magnet therapy for mom
I find a suitable one
It's going to be on sale
Why don't you use the mug I bought for you?
I grudge it
It's just over 200 yuan
So expensive
Where did you buy it?
The mall in front of the subway station
Where is the invoice?
I threw it away
That mall is much more expensive than online
Just use it
Well
I have gone through Yuwei's transferring kindergarten procedures
It is my fault this time
We wasted some money
Fortunately, we correct it timely
I know I am wrong
It won't happen again
You are right
We are not in a circle
In the end, I answer for the consequences
It's ok
As long as you figure it out
And one more thing
Sister Siyu wants me to work in sales department
No
Why?
Think, soon I will be deputy director
I will be busier than now
If you work in the sales department
who will take care of Yuwei?
Leave her to mom?
You are not worried?
And I know Siyu's situation
Even Chen Yiming often says he can't stand it
Not to mention us
You are right
I think HR department is suitable for you
The salary is not high
But it's easy and regular
You don't have to worry about making money
You have me
But women should have careers
I am your career
Yuwei is your career
Stop thinking
We should live a life down to earth
Ok
Wu...
I have checked all the shortlisted companies
Guess what
Say it
The husband of my junior high school classmate
works in the R&D department of Lubao
I found a photo in his Moment
Anything wrong?
The same one
Liu Yang's wife
Correct
Her name is Zhang Zhizhi
Works in HR department of Lubao
As I know, director Li who comes for bid is her cousin
Great
Wu
We should tell director about this early tomorrow morning
This time Liu Yang is doomed
Don't worry
Let me process
What if Liu Yang told the director about this relationship in advance?
Even if he didn't
Liu Yang is just in charge of preliminary work
Only experts have the final say in the bid
Liu Yang can still prove his innocence
Then we should make water dirty
Zhao, you finally have learned
I don't want to be the receptionist
We must take the previous lessons
We can't fail again