[To Dear Myself]
[Ep12]
Come in
5.1 million in total
I got the order I lost last week back
Lin Ling
I was in a bad mood last week
I shouldn't have thrown a tantrum
Sorry
No, sister Siyu
I'm so stupid
Don't worry
I will learn the lesson
I won't let them find my mistakes in the future
Great
5 million a week
So great
It almost catches up with my past record
Your past record is...
6 million a week
How did you make it?
Sister Yuan scolded me
Then I looked for orders crazily out of anger
And I set a record
Back to work
You still have the time to go to president Guo's company
This is your best choice
You should go to have a look
You can leave if you are not satisfied
Hello
Hello, Yiming
I'm coming now
You don't need to go now
Sorry to tell you, they have found a suitable man
I get it
Ok
Hello
Zhu Xiaobai
Anything wrong?
Yiming
My dad retired
And now I take his place
As the president and general manager of Wanguan Group
I want to give you an official invitation
Come to assist me
You will be my premier and vice president
How's it? Come back
Hello
Yiming
Yiming, are you there?
Hello
Yiming
You want to go back to hometown?
Correct
You are going to be copywriter of Fenglin Company, right?
They barely give me an interview
You can go to work for president Guo
I call president Guo now
I won't go to his company
I just do not understand
Why do you resist it so?
Did he do anything wrong to you?
Say it
I can't accept it
My girlfriend sells her smile to find a job for me
You are so unreasonable
Come, cheers
Come...
Come, Liu Yang
Good wine
Eat
It's good
Mr. Liu
Sit down please...
Brother Li often mentions you
He admires your ability
I have long admired you too
Such an honor to see you today
I will drink it up
Come
Flattered
Great...
Great
Thank you
Huizhong
Liu Yang has been my good friend for years
He is very nice
Just say it if you need any help
Ok, I will be straightforward
Ok
Mr. Liu
Our company Lubao wants to compete for the tender
of city's street lamp renovation
Your help is much appreciated
Manager Yuan
We haven't announced it yet
How did you get the news?
I even know you are the leader of the tender team
Liu Yang, Huizhong is my sister
She is a good girl and trustworthy
You can leave the project to her
Manager Li, manager Yuan
You find the wrong person
I am the team leader
But we have experts for bid evaluation
I really have no say in this
Sorry I can't help you
You tell me this?
I attend so many bids each year
I understand the process
Mr. Li, what I said is true
Brother Li
Don't make it difficult for Mr. Liu
Mr. Liu, you just need to do your part, fairly and openly
We will cooperate with you
Come, cheers
Exactly
Open, fair and just
Great
That's all for drinking
We should go to KTV now
Great...
Come, go to KTV
No, I have to go home now
Liu Yang
We haven't seen each other for over half a year
Let's get hammered tonight
Did you hear it? Come
I have to go home now
Come...
Give me my bag
Come, go...
Give me the bag
It's late now
Mr. Liu, let's go
Another day, ok?
Another day
Mr. Liu, I can drive you home
The rest of you, go to take another car
Ok...
Sit here, come...
Get in  -My bag
Leave it to me
Get in...
[Lyrics]
Come... Beer
Mr. Liu
To commemorate the first day we meet
I want to propose another toast to you
I can't drink anymore
I really can't  -Come
Mr. Liu
Liu Yang
It's ok
It's beer, you won't get drunk
Come
Come...
To you
Cheers
Come, drink
Great, cheers
Bottom up...
To Liu Yang
To him
Come, Liu Yang
Come
Raise the glass
Come, Mr. Liu
Drink
Liu Yang, come
I'll drink it up
Bottom up
That's the spirit
Great, come...
Great
I have to go now
Mr. Liu
Manager Yuan, really
You don't need to send me out
Mr. Liu
You didn't have fun today
I have fun
I drank too much, it's true
Mr. Liu
You are such a drinker
Sorry
Sorry...
Sister Yun
Brother Yang
I want to ask you a question
Where do you know the data on the second line of page 13?
You are still in the office?
Yes
Did you have dinner?
Not yet
What time is this?
Why you didn't have dinner?
I didn't have the time
What are you doing?
I am working on the reports you need tomorrow morning
Those reports are great
Don't need to waste your time
No
Brother Yang
You are responsible for the project
I need to make it perfect
I need you to go home now
It's ok, brother Yang
Never mind me
I will give you the most perfect report tomorrow morning
Brother Yang, why are you here?
I bought you some food
And porridge. Eat while it's warm
What's wrong?
Brother Yang, please don't be so good to me
Don't think too much
Sister Yun
You...
No one is so good to me
Brother Yang
I love you
What is her name?
Her name is...
Yang, you are back
Did you have dinner?
Social engagement, I know you would come back late
Come back so early?
Drink too much and now feel uncomfortable?
With whom did you have dinner?
Old friends
Men or women?
Men and women, what's the matter?
The perfume on your clothes is so thick
I never use perfume
Guess, who organized the dinner tonight?
Who?
Yuan Huizhong of your company
Why it's her?
All about the tender
She invites her friends and her friends invite me
Stay away from her
She is Siyu's rival
Even without Li Siyu, I will still stay away from her
Why?
Your manager Yuan is so unbelievable
She runs directly into my arms
Bitch
She even tried to get me drunk
Li and others are ridiculous too
I think they get some benefits
They help her inebriate me
Then I slipped away
I need to take a shower now
It happened last night?
Liu Yang was terrified
He still had lingering fears after he came home
She wants to get the tender, too
Now I know the rumors about her are true
Usually she won't do this
She pushes herself so hard probably because of me
Don't worry
Liu Yang will stay away from her
Zhizhi
You should keep an eye on Liu Yang
Otherwise in the end, I will lose the order
and you will lose your husband
I and Liu Yang have many bumps these years
We won't have any problem
I trust brother Yang
But he just can't resist her temptation
Morning
Sister Yun
I think you have some misunderstandings about me
I care about you
Because I am your leader
teacher and brother
I mean nothing else
I know
But what I want to say is...
I...
I am not a casual girl
I really...
I really fall in love with you
I am married
I have a wife and a daughter
I have to be responsible for my family
Brother Yang, don't worry
I mean no harm
I will never disturb your family
I won't disturb you, either
I just want to look at you from a distance
I want to help you every day
That's all
You...
It's not ok
I promise
What happened last night will never happen again
I will contain myself
You are young
You have many possibilities in the future
My future is to love you silently
You can't do that
I will do as you say
No matter how hard it is
But you can't stop me loving you
You can't do it
I can't even do it myself
Liu scolded you?
Liu
I put the report you want on your table
Thank you
Liu
Three o'clock in the afternoon
I want to see around Dongfeng factory with Wei Yayun
Wei Yayun worked overtime yesterday
She needs to go home early today
You should go with someone else
Ok
Brother Dai
Come with me this afternoon
My filing name is
the tender of Guangcai Engineering
Construction Company's lighting project
Customer representative is Liu Yang
Sister Yuan's filing name is
tender of street light
customer representative is to be determined
When did she file it?
16th of this month
I filed on the 13th
Correct
It's 13th
Great
I was too impatient yesterday
I scared him
What should we do next?
Let's adjust the rhythm
Later I will send him an apology with SMS
Days later, we will tell Mr. Li to invite him a cup of coffee
What should I prepare?
Get some materials in administrative department
Only talk about business this time
Go
Xiao Tang
What?
I need the product brochures and videos
And the set of corporate culture introduction
Wait a moment, I'll get it for you
Sister Yuan never gives client this kind of stuff, right?
Don't mention it
Last night we met a strange person
Desperate times, desperate measures
Strange
Guess what
Really?
He ran away
Sister Yuan failed in the end?
Yeah, he ran away
Zhizhi
Stop
Are you deaf?
Liu Jie, you have nothing to do?
You have the time for this?
Sister Yuan, I'm angry
Liu Jie
Her mom didn't teach her decorum and the sense of shame
Never mind her
You have no sense of shame
What are you talking about?
Apologize to me
No way
Will you apologize?
Let me go
You know what you are doing?
You shrew
Come here
You shameless
What?
What are you doing?
Li Siyu  -Sister Yuan
You push me
You hit sister Yuan
Come here, sister Yuan
How can you hit Sister yuan?
Sister Yuan, listen to me
Hit me?
Stop
Go home if you don't work
Have you finished your work?
Go
The final decision is as follows
Team leaders Yuan Huizhong and Li Siyu will be fined 5,000 yuan
and be criticized in a circulated notice
Zhang Zhizhi and Liu Jie will be fined 1,000
All clear?
Give your fines to finance department in three days
I didn't expect we would have a fight
Sister Yuan, sorry
I am such a loser
I saw you two fight against Zhizhi
So I was impulsive
But anyway, I shouldn't have fought against you
I want to apologize to you
I'll pay your fine
I don't need your money
I don't accept your apology either
So what can I do?
If you still see me as your teacher and
still remember our previous friendship
you need to fulfill your promise
You won't compete against me for the director
Sister Yuan
I can't
Why?
Because I can't fail team members
Because I want to be sales director
Also because
You don't see me as an apprentice
You don't care about our friendship
Why I don't see you as an apprentice?
Without me, you should have been fired long ago
I have cleaned your mess a lot
Why I don't care about our friendship?
Li Siyu
We are so like The Farmer and the Snake
Sister Yuan
If I make you unhappy, that's because you force me to do so
Li Siyu, let me tell you
I will be the sales director
The first thing I do when I become the sales director
is to fire you
Sister Yuan
I will be the sales director
The first thing after I become the director is to thank you
Just you and your waste?
Yes
Just with my strength
and with my ability to lead the team
and my dark horses
Well
I am preparing for a tender on behalf of our company
Guangcai company lighting project renovation
Total bid of 28 million
It's my project
Sorry
This time I filed first
President Pan, I am sorry for the misbehavior of the sales department
Supervision department happened this before
Learn from the lesson, hope it won't happen again
You leave sales department to me
I can't shirk the respon...
The more people we have, the more conflict we have
It's inevitable
It's a good thing that two teams compete with each other
But they need to have a rule
In order to grab clients, they have many troubles
I think we should do something
Go on
I think we should ask client department for cooperation
We should divide the section for the two teams
Then they will work in their own area
Which can develop the client's potential
and vicious competition can be avoided
So how to divide the section?
Li Siyu knows about electric car market well
We should leave it to her
Yuan Huizhong has some great clients
But for the company's overall situation
I think we should leave it to Li Siyu
Will Yuan Huizhong agree?
I will persuade her
I think we should leave toy market, small appliances
and medical equipment to Li Siyu too
Because she is so familiar with these industries
Same client
Others can only get about 20 million
But she can make 30 million or even 40 million
Is it unfair to other salesmen?
It can develop others' sales performance wiht maximum limit
For example, Yuan Huizhong
She is very familiar with government public relations
We can leave government-related projects to her
Of course she will think
Electric car market is a large one
Why should we leave it to Li Siyu?
But for the company, she needs to sacrifice when time comes
I think a good competition mechanism
is to mobilize all people's enthusiasm and potential
Not to sacrifice one for the other
But now the sales department is a bit messy
It's only the appearance
As long as performance continues to grow
it shows the mechanism is effective
According to the previous rules
Whoever files first will have the client
Ok
Sister Siyu
I have paid the fine for you
You don't need to pay it
I will transfer the money to you
No need
You should save the salary for Yuwei
How can I thank you?
I want to eat your dishes
Ok, you and brother Yiming come to eat at my home
I have to work overtime tonight
See the client?
Sister Siyu
You fought against them for me
Will it affect your competition with Yuan Huizhong?
No
Really?
Do not worry
I will win this time
Well
Did Yiming get a job?
He plans to work in his hometown
How about you?
I will stay here
You will be separated
No way
Sister Siyu
You should persuade brother Yiming
I want to quit
Don't say like that
Brother, I'm so tired
Who is not tired?
I am tired too
Do you know what I want to do most?
First of all, I want to take care of my body
Then I will eat three simple meals a day
Then I will stay with my son and see him do homework
Then I will find a boyfriend
I will lead a regular life
All these can be achieved
But you can't give up now
Li Siyu's team is going crazy
I really don't want to compete with them
Why not? You must
Huizhong
I only told you about this
Whether you defeat Li Siyu will influence all people's interests
It will also influence my survival in Lubao
Moreover, it's about the survival of Lubao
We have talked about this many times
I don't care if I get out
But I am worried about Lubao
Yes, Pan Zhiyong is the founder of Lubao
But over the past ten years
we sacrifice less blood, youth, sweat than Pan Zhiyong?
We can't see him destroy Lubao
And Pan Zhiyong never cares about benefits
of executives and employees
I tried so hard to get equity allocations
If I am out, he will have the final say
In the future, our interests won't be guaranteed
Including your shares
He can do it
So we need to win sales department
The company is preparing for equity financing
As long as you can persist till the new shareholders come
we have a chance
Then we will turn the table
But how can I persist?
According to rules
The government project is Li Siyu's
Pan Zhiyong denied your reform proposal
If Li Siyu gets 28 million, I am sure to lose