# Google translate version for your reference #
Then you can watch
I have these few models
This one compares
More European and American
Look at these
Then the following words
Just a little more modern
This is our company
Several recently designed
Mobile phone software mode
You can see for yourself
Like European and American style etc.
Both have
Actually the style of mobile phone software
Directly affect the user experience
Actually this is very popular now
flat design
What about the flat design?
Looks very simple and generous
What about the following models
Is more modern
Including the back
A bit more archaic
You think you like it better
Which style
OK, I almost understand
okay
During use
If you encounter any problems
You can also give us feedback in time
It depends on everyone
I'm sorry
Hey
Do you like European style modern style
Retro style or simple style
Simple style
understood
Why are you asking this suddenly
Keep secret
By the way, what are you doing now
Just keep it simple
Row
Simple style
Ah, concise style
You can take a look at these
it is good
Just order this set
Wedding photos
I ordered the love of Nice
Is the best package, look
I booked the hotel
Yuehua Hotel
look
Although it is far from the city
A little further
But its external environment
The internal environment is pretty good
Honeymoon
I choose Maldives
Look
This is a travel agency
Recommend some of our islands
What's the situation
I happen to be relatively empty recently
I want to take advantage of this time
Got our wedding
But i still have
More important things to do
What's the matter
Is it more important than marriage
I want to build one
Shared platform for battery rental
I want to do mobile new energy service
just now
This idea
I have been brewing for a long time
Now exactly
Best time to start
What do you think
China's electric bicycles today
Ownership
Has exceeded 300 million
But the battery is charging
But it has always been a problem
And the platform I built
Users only need to download one
mobile apps
You can go anytime
Any service outlet
Make a lease replacement
That is similar to
The kind of shared power bank
Right
Yes
But that one is too pediatric
Are billed in milliamperes
My
It’s a kilowatt-hour
E-bike business
After spreading
I also want to make an electric car
Provide battery rental service
The one that moves is
The entire battery industry
Your advantage in doing this
what is it then
I'm in this line
Worked hard for seven or eight years
For the battery industry
It can be said to be very knowledgeable
But you don't understand the internet at all
I can study
I can hire professional people
Do professional things
then you
Profitable model
Have you considered it clearly
Profit mainly depends on
User's rent and deposit
In other cities
You can also charge an initial fee
And as long as the platform is built
I can get the investment
Those shared power banks
The angel wheel took tens of millions
What about the cost
I do the calculation
The initial phase
About four million
Which includes
Platform construction cost
Build one hundred physical service outlets
And the cost of buying batteries
I also contacted a few
Battery manufacturer
They are willing
Give me the best price
What about the cost of promotion
Also included
Not enough
As long as the platform is running
I can get the investment
Just get the investment
Follow-up costs are not a problem
Siyu
I listen to it now
I think
Do you think about it
A little too simple
No i know
It must be difficult
But i have to do
And do it soon
I think this
You still have to think twice
After thinking twice
It's likely to be preempted by others
We have nothing
Now this market
It does not lack opportunities
But but now
Now i hope
You should still stop
I can't stop
I want to regain lost ground
I think still
Let's get married first
Get married
But i have a condition
What condition
I need capital to start a business
Shall we sell the house
what
and
I need a chief operating officer
Yiming
You quit
We start a business together
Are you crazy you
What does this mean
Siyu
I think you should
Calm down
Yiming
I need your support
Siyu
I can't support you now
You don't support me
I won't get married
Are you at the company now
I want to talk to you again
The system architecture problem
OK, let me go
President Wang
Mr. Fang, please come in
Hello
Please sit down
Never had a chance before
Communicate with Mr. Fang
Hope today we can
Speak freely
Be honest with each other
Ok
President Fang
Before I decided to invest in Emerald
From entrepreneurship to the present
All reports
I researched it all
I found a problem
The fastest growing years for Green Treasure
It just so happens that Mr. Pan is only in charge of R&D
And you
Responsible for the overall work years
Mr. Wang, you praised
Green treasure can have today
Not an individual
The miracle of alone
But everyone
The result of working together
President Fang is quite humble
Tell the truth
Probably from last year
National policy has been adjusted again
This industry has entered a cold winter
I noticed that
Fang's strategy is to shrink
My style has always been more pragmatic
I agree very much
Didn't Buffett say
I am not trying to cross
Seven foot high railing
What i'm looking for is
I can cross
One foot high railing
President Fang, Pan Zhiyong told me
He has a plan
Said it was within two years
Three more Lvbao three production lines
Thanks to Tianyi Group
800 million invested
Let Pan's plan
No more rice-free cooking
I also want to ask you
Right now
Market environment
Need to expand production
Is this a bit risky?
this problem
I have communicated with Mr. Pan
he thinks
This is a good opportunity to overtake a corner
I have been capital for so many years
Successful overtaking
I haven't seen a few
Overturned
See a lot
I also want to ask Mr. Wang
Based on your experience
What is the safest thing to do on a curve
why
Must be on the curve
Not directly on the runway
aircraft runway
Do you mean
President Fang
If I remember correctly
Emerald's profit last year
Is it more than one billion
Last year's cash flow was too tight
Have you joined this year
We hope to be able
More than 200 million
Too little
We are in the industry
That performance
It's very good
If I do it for me
I can guarantee
within one year
The valuation of Emerald
From 3.5 billion to 20 billion
20 billion
That net profit
To add more than one billion
Calculate backwards
At least ten production lines
Not needed
No need to expand capacity
Just need to repack
President Fang, you worked so hard
Make profit make market value
Isn't it for company valuation?
Then why not directly
Work hard on company valuation
If Emerald’s valuation
20 billion
The 800 million you invested today
But it becomes four billion
Fang Zong and other executives
Hard work
There will be great returns
The production line of Emerald III
Still on
Money should be spent on the blade
Pan Zhiyong won't agree
What he decided to do
No one can change
Not always
He didn't want to make Li Siyu
Are you the sales director?
Isn't it impossible?
Green treasure is our green treasure
Not someone's emerald
To our green treasure
Sister Yuan is back
Sister Yuan
You are finally back
Sister Yuan, you are back
long time no see
You haven't changed at all
Sister Yuan wants to kill us
Sister Yuan, I knew
You will be back
Ok
Sister Yuan, you look so good today
Sister Yuan, your office
All cleaned up for you
Come take a look
smell good
Sister Yuan, I'm looking forward to you back
We all miss you
Just
Sister Yuan
how
Is Li Siyu
Suppress you
Yes
Sister Yuan, don't you know
You can't talk nonsense about this
Sister Siyu, for you
Three trips to Changsha
Final commission and commission
It's all to you
Why she did that
she says
You helped her like that back then
She is behind
You must have said bad things about me
Really not
She always says it's a pity
I ended up making trouble with you
Hope to have a chance to reconcile with you
Sister Yuan, tell the truth
Li Siyu
Very atmospheric
Comparable to you
No no no
Still a bit worse than you
Mr. Yuanhao
Advance
Hello brother
This time
Declining sales
Need you to turn the tide
understand
In addition
Who should the sales department open
Give me the list as soon as possible
Sales
Why open a man
Li Siyu's men
You keep them
I'll add a stumbling block to you
The people I left behind when I left
Li Siyu didn't open any of them
Now I come back
The one she left behind opened
That doesn't appear
Is my temperament not as good as her
You are going to keep them all
I took a look
Those few people are very good at fighting
I don't just want to stay
Still want to reuse
and also
Li Siyu later introduced some
Sales rebate policy
Also very practical
I also want to continue to use
You lost to her
Because your heart is too soft
You always think my heart is too soft
Caused today's situation
Think in reverse
If my heart is softer
Could it be another result
boss Zhang
You only need to invest four million
The project can start
Three million is fine
Two million
I promise you that
As long as the number of users goes up
Cash flow is not a problem
OK, contact again
Hello lady
When can i serve
Wait a moment
OK
Hello, the user you are calling
Temporarily unavailable
Sorry
Hello, the user you are calling
Temporarily unavailable
Sorry for the user you called
Siyu sister
I'm sorry, the meeting is over
It's all right, sit down
Why are you alone
How many of them
Mr. Yuan said that the meeting was late today
Please have a meal
Xiaojia, Xiaotian and the others
Also eat Mr. Yuan's rice
Mr. Yuan still respects them
Siyu, don't be angry
What's so angry about this
I brought them out
Can be valued by the new leader
I should be happy
Why didn't you go
I think you come to me
There must be something very important
No matter what
Come to you first
President Yuan didn't embarrass you, right
Everyone said
President Yuan has changed a little this time
Where has changed
I can't tell
It feels much more peaceful than before
Siyu sister
Actually everyone misses you
One day Xiaojia said
Maybe Mr. Yuan will leave someday
You're back to be the director
Director
I can't look down on it now
I want to be
At least
General Manager Chairman
Siyu sister, you can definitely do
Okay, stop talking
Lin Ling, I plan to start my own business
Project is particularly good
After five years of running
Go to market
I now officially invite you to join
Then I have to resign from Lubao
Of course
Project start-up stage
We have to invest 24 hours
but
You believe me
Everything I like
Nothing impossible
I have repeatedly demonstrated this project
Will only succeed
Never fail
This is my business plan
You will understand
Siyu sister
Sorry
I just got familiar with battery sales
You know my dad's situation
I think
I'd better be steady
This is a golden opportunity
but I
I may not be suitable
Did not you say
Have you set me up in this life?
I mean
I'll follow you as long as I'm in Emerald
I understand
Siyu sister
I promised Mr. Yuan
Finish things late
I still have to go to her
If you have nothing else here
I'll go first
You go
Come, let's come
Come
Ok
Yes, but I only paid a deposit
Theme clothing or something
Wait for you
I can ask for leave this afternoon
it is good
I think today
Discharged
The doctor said
There are several indicators
Did not come down
Buy some medicine and take it home
I have already paid the operation fee
You don't care about me
I still have to work
Put the rice here for you
eat by yourself
You slow down
Thank you
I met Lin Ling at the company
She said you want to start a business
Yes
What item
Item is called
Is an
Shared battery rental platform
New ideas
Where is it
I already plan to give up
why
Heard my idea
Everyone said yes
but
Unable to invest
No one wants to join
How much does it cost to start up
four million
How much did you raise
If you add the money for selling the house
About one million
Green treasure invests 3 million
Mr. Pan
This is my project plan
Ok
Very good, no need to read
I only look at people
Mr. Pan, I use tea instead of wine
do not worry
I will live up to you
Ok
I want to see results in half a year
for sure
Mr. Pan
How about emerald now
not good
why
I am going to take two
Emerald III's production line
Wang Ziru and Fang Zhan
Vetoed
They two join hands
I suspect now
She was
Vote for Yuan Huizhong
It's a certificate dedicated to Fang Zhan
I asked Sister Ziru about this
Why she voted so
Because of Chen Yiming's request
Chen Yiming
He doesn't want me to go out and work hard
He wants me to go home
Li Siyu
Do you believe
it is true
For this
Chen Yiming and I got into trouble
Almost broke up
Wang Ziru this woman
For a request from a subordinate
Involved again
With so many benefits
Finally for the sake of subordinates
I do not believe
What do you think
I think her vote
Must be well thought out
Besides now
She and Fang Zhan are in such a tacit understanding
Must be with that vote
Closely related
No way
I should hold
That 22%
I don't quite understand
You don't need to understand
Just do this well
I can handle the company
Xiaohan, this is Li Siyu
I wanted to be in your park before
Starting a company
Paused later
Now i plan to restart
No problem, Mr. Li
Can you
Apply now
just now
Today is our park
The last day of the promotion
If you apply again today
What was the previous rent discount?
Just can't enjoy it
I'll come over now
Hello, Siyu
Where are you now
I'm almost there
Yiming, sorry
Suddenly something happened to me
Otherwise, let's cancel today
What's the matter
I'm going to the park
Submit an application to start a company
You haven't given up
What about your business plan
The situation has changed a bit
I think
You come right now
Let's order the wedding photos first
Yiming
Can we take it off today
Can't
I really can't walk away here
Siyu
I'm here now
The entrance of the bridal shop
I wait for you
Manager Li
This is our project introduction
Take a look
Now every year
5% tax reduction
This is ours
Hello, this is the information you want
thanks, thanks
You're welcome
Manager Li
This is our preferential policy
Positioning of investment purposes
Regional Advantage Product Support
Thank you so much today
You're Mr. Li
We should
Then, Mr. Li, I won't send you off
thank you
Goodbye
Hello
How can I help you
Mr. Chen
My boyfriend
Made an appointment to try in the afternoon
He seems to have just left
thank you
It's ok
Hey
Hello, Mr. Chen
Miss Li's phone is always busy
I can only call you
what happened
Your house
I took a look
What now
Can sell for 5.2 million
But transaction tax suffers a bit
Who told you
We are going to sell the house
Miss Li told me
She asked me to help her settle the accounts
Hey
Where are you now
Project architecture and system architecture
Already formed
What i need now is
I'll call you later
You are going to sell the house
Yes
Li Siyu
Are you really crazy about you
I'm not crazy
This is the argument I asked experts to do
The expert's conclusion is
This project is perfectly solved
Pain points for battery owners
And any kind
Business model success
definitely is
Efficient solution to market pain points
Can i now
Don't listen to you
Why don't you listen
This is the evaluation of industry leaders
They all said that this project is
New energy and Internet
Joint innovation
Is leading the people to travel
Another revolution
enough
Is enough
President Pan decided
Invest me three million
Plus more than 1 million sold
The start-up funds are all resolved
Mr. Pan
Li Siyu
I see you already
Is he completely brainwashed?
three million
This is not brainwashing
This is called recognition
You can let go
I have nothing now
I have got three million
What reason do i have to let go
Because of you now
Has lost his mind
Lost judgment
Chen Yiming
Everyone said
This is a rare occasion
Entrepreneurial opportunities
You said I lost my judgment
Everyone says this is a good time
You say i lose my mind
There are too many good projects
You have to see if it suits
Yes yes need need time
But you have to watch
Do you have the conditions
Conditions can be created
But the time waits for no one
Then you can't do anything wrong
Then what do you think is nonsense
For example
Such as getting married?
Chen Yiming
I'll tell you again
I'm over 30
Still nothing
And you know
I just got caught
Defeated
I can't give up
it is good
Then do as you said
Do you still want to marry me
Why don't you understand me
I want to counterattack
I want to win back
I want to fight for this tone
I will ask you now
Do you still want to marry me
I would rather not get married
I want to continue
If that is the case
Then we can only break up
Siyu
That was not what I meant
I agree
let's break up