[To Dear Myself]
[Ep15]
Liu Yang...
Liu Yang, what are you doing?
Go home
The party is not over yet
I didn't study in the U.S.
I'm not the director, either
I am from a rural party
I don't deserve to attend this kind of party
I just say it casually
It's all your vanity
If I don't say like that
they will look down on Yuwei
But do you consider my feelings?
She knows our director
What if our director knows this?
What I said is correct
You studied in the U.S.
And you will be the director soon
Zhang Zhizhi
Wake up
We are not in the same circle with them
You still want to kiss their ass
You don't feel a thing
But I am sick of it
Liu Yang
Come, baby
You are back
Grandma, look
I got the present today
You got a present? Let me see
Mom, is Liu Yang back?
Yes, in his room
Its tail can move
Really?
Mom
Help her take a shower
Ok...
Come...
After you left
we met a teacher of etiquette in Buckingham Palace
She teaches all kids about royal etiquette
If Yuwei doesn't come to the circle,
she will never learn this
We are an ordinary family
But our daughter should be better than us
At least we should motivate our daughter from childhood
And, let me tell you...
She asked for it
Sister Siyu
We know sister Yuan's punishment
What?
Fire her
Sister Siyu, you are here
Sister Siyu
You look so good today
What are you talking about?
Sister Siyu looks good every day
You two are so honey-mouthed
Sister Siyu
Let's have a party to celebrate it
Celebrate what?
You are sales director now
No
It's a matter of time
No...
Li Siyu
Congratulations
Sister Yuan
Congratulate you on your promotion
And I hope the higher you climb, the worse you fall
Pan Zhiyong backs you up
So you think you have nothing to fear?
I can tell you
I can't teach you a lesson
Someone will
Li Siyu
You will see
You will cry one day
Go away
Get away from me
Siyu
Siyu, president Pan wants to see you
Now?
Yes
Come with me
Hurry
Sister, leave the bag to me
Thank you
President Pan
Sit
Next Monday, HR department will announce officially
you will be the sales director
Now I have to tell you the secret
Our company has reached a point where its very existence is at stake
We are selling well, right?
But we make no much money
Why?
Because years ago, we have dividends of policy in this area
Since last year, they have cancelled it
Our sales is in stalemate
And technology hits a bottleneck
We are facing capital chain rupture
This is the status quo of Lubao
You are preparing for equity financing, right?
Yes
But Tianyi, Huaan and Shanghai Bank
They all have a request
We need to double Lubao's sales revenue
Double?
Yes, double
In other words, in three months
we need to make 500 million
Impossible
Fifteen years ago
I told them
I want to break U.S. and Japanese monopoly
I want to be China's own new energy enterprise
They also said it was impossible
But you made it
So anything is possible
It depends on wheher you fight or not
Siyu, will you fight or not?
Yes, I will
Very well
I see you right
Tell you more
It's hard now
Really really hard
But the future is beautiful
Lubao's valuation is unlimited after this
Believe me
Within five years, Lubao will be listed
Within ten years, Lubao will be No.1
Within fifteen years, Lubao will be No. 1 in the world
I believe
I don't believe believe
I only believe in hard work, Siyu
Fight with me
Lubao will never let us down
We will be top 1 in the world
Till then, we will go on stage
and accept the applause and reward
from all over the world together
on behalf of Chinese manufacture
President Pan, don't worry
I will make 500 million in three months
Mom
Later you and Yuwei eat first
I will wait for Liu Yang to come back
Ok
It's so hard for you during this time
I have the time now
I will pick up Yuwei for early education class
I'll go
I don't want to idle around anyway
Come
Yuwei
I have told you, you need to eat by yourself
Come
Don't play with toys while eating
Play after lunch
Eat
Just let her play
Mom, it's a bad habit
She needs to get rid of it
Why are you crying?
You love your daughter dearly, right?
You spoil and yell at her at the same time
Mom
I love her but I will not spoil her
She can't have this bad problem
This is true love
My granddaughter is so angry
Go
What did you say?
You go
From whom do you learn this?
Ok...
Stop crying...
Ok, don't cry
Eat
You need to attend class later
Come
I let her drop out from the early education class
What?
I cancelled the early education class
How much money does Liu Yang make a month?
We can't waste money on this
It's not waste
It's waste
You tell me, you have no money and can't afford a second child
Spend less money on Yuwei
Let alone second child
You will have the third kid
Mom, you...
Eat
Hello
Is it Liu Yuwei's parent?
Yes, I am
Who are you?
This is Little Talent Training Organization
You made an appointment of left brain
development training last week
But you didn't come
So do you need to make another appointment?
Sorry
I am busy now
Can I make an appointment for tomorrow?
Ok, no problem
Let's make it 19:00 tomorrow
Ok, thank you
Mom, you didn't take her to left brain training class, either
I didn't
Zhizhi
Don't blame me for being troublesome
Yuwei's food, clothes and nutrition
It costs so much money
Do you have any idea?
You let her attend all kinds of classes
She will make the family bankrupt
It's not spending money
It's investment
What?
I think, you spend money for nothing
Mom, how can you say so in front of her?
What's wrong?
She doesn't understand
She is four years old
She understands
She doesn't understand
She is not so smart
Besides, am I wrong?
You spend the money for nothing
I don't like it
Mom
How can you say like this?
She is my daughter
Liu Yang's daughter
We make money for her
Stop it
Ask your own conscience
How much money do you make?
My son Liu Yang supports this family
Yes, my husband makes the money
But I have the final say on how much money he spends
I'm his mom, he has to listen to me
Yeah
But he has to listen to me after he marries me
You don't understand anything
He still listens to you?
You messed up the family
I am so sick of it
All because Yuwei is a girl, right?
If I had a son, you wouldn't mind how much money I spend
Correct
What times now?
Boys and girls
You are a woman, too
Why do you despise women so?
Don't talk about this
So noisy
Ridiculous
Stop eating
Mr. Liu
Bye
Mr. Liu, see you tomorrow
See you tomorrow
Hello
Hello, Liu Yang
Can you come home early today?
What happened?
I can't get along with your mom
I just quarreled with her
Why?
You'll know when you come back
Yuwei doesn't listen to me now
She picks up the bad habits
Not a big deal
Not a big deal?
It's your daughter
The bad habits die hard
You don't know what your mom said in front of Yuwei
In front of Yuwei, she said I wasted money on her
Ok, stop it
I will talk to my mom
Ok, come back early
Ok
Yang
Mom
Let me tell you
I didn't say anything
It's a fact that Yuwei spends much money
Right?
I need to take care of your daughter and cook for you
I even do the laundry
I do so much work
Now she even nitpicks me
Ridiculous
Ma, I need to work
Stop quarrelling, ok?
For me, ok?
Who quarrelled?
All because of your wife
Ok, it's enough
I'm busy now
Bye
Brother Yang
You still didn't go home?
I want to stay here a while
Brother Yang, look
What?
Where did you get this?
After I went home, I told my family I wanted to eat small potatoes
My dad sent this to me
I haven't seen small potatoes for at least ten years
Brother Yang, take this back
Let your wife cook it for you
She?
She can't do it
We can't make it without firewood stove
I know a place, it has the stove
I will send you the address
Ok
Sister Yun
Can you take me to firewood stove tonight?
Ok
Eat it yourself
Mom, time for dinner
Have a try
How's it? Brother Yang
Is this what you want?
Finally
You are back
A good news?
I am the sales director from now on
Great
Come, congratulations
Cheers
I booked a ticket and I will leave the day after tomorrow
I just got promoted
I am sorry that I can't go back with you
I can understand
But communication is so advanced
We can make video calls anytime, anywhere
Long distance relationship is not a big deal
And on the way to office,
I will be stuck in traffic jam for one hour or two
So it makes no difference between here and hometown
It's not far away from here
If I miss you, I will come here by train
Then we will meet each other
Eat on time and take medicine on time
Don't stay up late
Drink less
Don't work overtime too often
We need to have video calls every day
Three times a day
No less than three minutes each time
Tell me if you are on a business trip
I will send you off the day after tomorrow
Next
I want to talk about
Financialization of art investment
Financialization of art investment has six forms
Mortgage, pledge, loan and trust of artwork
Art Fund
Art stock
The last is the appreciation of art
But first
We have to clarify a concept
For appreciation of artwork
I hope all of you can trust your instincts
Get immersed
Then mobilize your experience and background to understand it
The term is created in the early twentieth century
It emphasizes artist's inner feelings
We can understand art better after we know technical terms
Why don't you go in?
His lectures are boring, don't you think so?
Liu's lectures are just like this
He is a boring buy
More than that, he is very forgetful
He reassigned two weeks ago's homework last week
More than that
I paid his money back last week
He asked me for money again yesterday
As I know, he is very stingy
As I know, when he was a junior
he invited his classmate to a Rougamo
Now he even asked him for money
Ridiculous
Eat one
Travel through time and space
Have a dialogue with the artist
Are you my classmate?
Why I didn't notice you before?
I don't come often
You often skip classes
This is his true intention of works
We should go in now
Go in now?
I have experience for this
We go in now
And then ask a question before the class is over
Then he won't know we skip the class
Brilliant
Keep up
That's all for today
You should read these books
Then you should write a review
Send it to my mailbox before next class
Do you understand?
Ok, dismiss
I will go to ask a question
Teacher Liu
What are the two important features of art financial investment?
I didn't catch it
Can you tell me now?
I said it just now
Look
The artwork has become an important object of
financial institution asset management
Second, the artwork has become the object of
credit rating and asset pricing for individuals and companies
So...
When are you here?
Just arrived
Is it over?
Let's go
Ok
Do you still have questions?
No
Wait for me a while
So how about today?
Go dutch?
If you want to go dutch
you need to pay the money
You didn't pay me the money of Rougamo yet
Stop talking nonsense
Brothers are waiting
Hurry
Not nonsense
You are a big boss
You should invite me to a meal
Gosh
Where will we go?
Today we will go dutch
I have said...
You...
Me?
I think she comes for me
You?
Teacher Liu
You are his classmate?
Why did not you tell me earlier?
You fear I will tell him the truth?
No
If you add my WeChat
I won't betray you
All right
If you decline my invitation,
I will still tell him
It's blackmail
Goodbye
Hello, I'm from Lubao Group
Sales Director
Li Siyu
Lubao Group's paper for the tender
Ok, I will register it
Thank you
Brother Yang
I have submitted the paper for tender on behalf of Lubao
Wu accepted it
Ok
Much appreciated
Siyu
I want to invite you a drink tonight, I wonder if you have the time
Ok
Xiawei, go ask Wu if he has collected all the bidders' papers
You eat little in the cafeteria
Your stomachache comes again?
Yes
You are an adult, but don't know how to take care of yourself
You keep these boxes for me
Come
Only these?
Yeah, that's all
What else?
No
So what about you and Li Siyu?
Leave it be for the time being
Bro
It's unlikely that long-distance relationship has a happy ending
But I think you two are different
Why are you so confident in us?
Why you don't think so?
I often feel I can't control her even if she is by my side
Not to mention now we are hundreds of kilometers away
Li Siyu can fly?
She can't fly
But I might let her down
Impossible
When I think I can't send her an umbrella when it rains
I can't give her medicine when she is sick
When she needs comfort
I can only call her
I am not optimistic about our future
Don't go
If I don't go, she will be more disappointed
You and Siyu won't break up, right?
Not for now
But who knows one year later...
Two years later...
No one knows for sure
That's all
I didn't finish packing
Bye
What time tomorrow?  I will see you off
No need, I'll go by myself
Siyu
Sister Ziru
Kept you waiting
No, I just arrived
Why don't you go in?
It's ok
Go
Yesterday, I met president Pan
He told me you are sales director now
So I want to celebrate it for you
Thank you, sister Ziru
Without your support and encouragement
I might have given up long ago
You won't
You won't give up so easily
I just let you recognize yourself
Sit, Siyu
Feel at ease
Sister Ziru
How's your talk with president Pan?
Pretty good
The whole negotiation is smooth
President Pan has gumption and broad mind
It's right that you cooperate with him
I know this
Our team is very good, too
Actually after you are sales director,
I am more confident in Lubao's management
Well
Have you seen the representatives of those two companies?
You mean Huaan and Shanghai Bank?
Correct
Not yet
Maybe it's not the time
Eat
This is the new dish
Have a try
Ok
Thank you
Sister Ziru, you should eat
How is Yiming?
Pretty good
What happened?
We may break up
Why?
He resigned
And he didn't find a suitable job
He finds a chance in his hometown
So he wants to go back and try
You have talked about breaking up?
Not yet
But I have a bad hunch
I think we will break up sooner or later
Your love won't be so fragile
Long-distance relationship's breakup rate is over 90%
Now Lubao is facing the most critical stage
I am the sales director
I need to work whole-heartedly
I have no time or energy for a long distance relationship
It's simple
Simple?
As I know, Yiming does the planning, right?
Yes
My company has a vacancy of planning director
I don't know if Yiming has any interest
We will offer a higher salary
But it's a new department
The scale is relatively small
Sister Ziru
You are saving my love
Yiming
Why?
Yiming, we won't be separated