# Google translate version for your reference #
Don't you all say it's busy?
Why did not I see
Someone is working
Everyone is reserving energy
Busy at the end of the year
Next year that
Scenic work plan
Who will do it
Li Siyu
Next year's plan
It's up to you to draft
Take advantage of this opportunity
Get acquainted
Work at hand
Why don't you answer my call
You didn't answer my call
You are still working for
Blame me for the heavy rain that day
You don't know
I every night
Fall asleep on time at a quarter past ten
Phone will also shut down
Yes, your life is extremely regular
Thunderous
But you are my boyfriend
Have you ever thought
What might happen that day
Unexpected things
Have you ever thought
I might be scared
That evening
When a thunderstorm occurs
I'm asleep
Not to mention when people fall asleep
Brain activity
Still unsolved mystery
You have a point
But in my opinion
There is only one explanation
You don't care about me
So you don't care about me
I have no weight in your heart
This is wrong
I have determined
You are my life partner
This is enough to explain
Your weight in my heart
But when I need it most
I can't get through your phone
this problem
I already have a solution
I gave you a cell phone
every night
10:15 Separate Machine
Shut down at 5:30 in the morning
This is the phone number
only you know
But what I want to remind you is
This call
Only occurs above level 5
In critical situations
Can call
What is
Critical situation above grade 5
According to your daily life
Possible unexpected situation
According to criticality
Made a table
And divided into levels
The situation that day
Belongs to the sixth level
Can call
Alright
If it's ok
Can we go eat
Today is us
Recognize the 100-day anniversary
According to the overall ranking
The scoring situation with the gourmet king
I found you a restaurant
You should like it
I'm still quite romantic, right
So romantic
Yuwei, come on
mom
Come, Yuwei
Teacher, sorry
it does not matter
Delayed your get off work
it's okay no problem
Say goodbye
Goodbye susan
Goodbye Yuwei
Goodbye teacher li
Bye bye Yuwei
Gone, bye
Goodbye
Ok
It's okay
Dad will pick you up in a while
Then play yours
Come, Yuwei
teacher
Susan's mother hasn't come to pick her up yet
Still not here
Her father made a call
Said it was temporary
Maybe a little later
Are you okay?
My husband is on a business trip
Then the child is at home alone
I am a bit
A little worried about him
How about this
I happen to take Yuwei
Go to the fast food restaurant
You call Susan's father
If he agrees
I took Susan with me
Let her father
Just pick her up nearby
That's too much trouble for you
Nothing
Susan, come on
I'll call now
come on
Guoguo, I'm here to play with you
father
Susan miss dad?
miss you
kiss Me
Thank you
Yu Wei
Come
It is you
What a coincidence
I'll treat this meal today
No need to
I have already paid
Then next time I invite
Haven't eaten tonight?
Didn't eat yet? Just after the meeting
I ordered a lot today
Do you want to sit down and eat
You're welcome
What do you want to drink
A cup of hot American
Drinking coffee so late
Can't sleep
Go back in a while
There is still work to be done
So hard
Now you say
Who doesn't work hard
I will buy coffee for you
Um thanks
Yu Wei
Hello, a cup of hot American
What are you doing
What to take
We are taking almond's home
This is a home, right
Haven't eaten enough, Susan
I am full
Do you want to eat more
Yes yes yes
Yes this
Be careful, be careful
Fell down for a while.
mom
Susan and I went to the children's playground
Go
Be safe and don't fall
Ok
Slow down
thank you
Mother Yuwei
What happened before
My attitude is not very good
Sorry
It's okay to do sales
It's all commonplace
Ok
but
You said
I always have a doubt
Our company's products are also good
I am in sales
Also took a lot of thought
Why is
Can't get into your eyes
What about your emerald products
not bad
Just your emerald people
Am I not doing well?
Don't don't you misunderstand
I'm not talking about you
I docked with me before
That salesman
This person
Too bad faith
I am very very disdainful
You mean
Before me and her
Talked about a small list
What about my colleagues later
I found out during the contract review
Contract that requires a seal
Before us
Confirmed version
Is totally different
As long as this chapter goes on
Our company paid more than 100,000 yuan
There will be such a thing
For our company
Pay more than 100,000
Not a big number
But this low-level method
I can't stand it, can't tolerate it
I would rather you take everything
All on the table to talk
right
It's okay if you add money
I did sales very late
You are my visit
First customer
I am about the previous
Not very clear
is it possible
Is my former sales colleague
She didn't mean it
She just accidentally
Got this data wrong
What about her
That's what you told me
But it doesn't matter
I said that
I can't accept this behavior
Can't tolerate
Then terminate the contract
But you don't know your colleague
What did later
She started making my rumors outside
Say why she
Can't sign this order
Because I accepted
Money from other battery companies
That's why I didn't sign with her
How could she do this
She did it
Too much
Fortunately my leader
I still believe in me
Otherwise, I'm Su Lixing
Principles that have been adhered to for so many years
And the accumulated reputation
Not all ruined
Did she put her mouth on one?
This is too much
So when you came before
Just caught up with me
I understand
You are you she is her
I shouldn't be angry
Sprinkle on your head
This is very rude
I
Apologize to you again
No no no
I should apologize to you
As a member of Emerald
I should act for my colleague
I'm sorry to tell you
It has nothing to do with you
Mr. Su
I think i should
Take this matter
Report to our manager
Because of this
It’s not just you that hurt
Also our green treasure
It looks like
You pretty much protect your emerald
Although the damaging horse
But our company
Most employees
And our company's products
Are still excellent
Can you think about it again
next year
This year's purchase is over
Understand more
next year
Nana
Ok
Trouble you
Marketing strategy this year
market expansion
There are price plans
tomorrow
You said yesterday
Then tomorrow
Brother Zhai
how
Thought in front of the boss
Hit me small report
Can sit in my place
Ignore him, it's okay
Boss met me
You have to call Brother Zhai
A new one
I don't know how high the sky is
Actually challenged me
He berated me
The more you care about him, the more angry he gets
Stop talking, ignore him
I provoke him
do not
Who will get the takeaway?
That just came
You go get it
I'll buy you milk tea
It's okay, okay, go quickly
Thank you
What did you want yesterday
Marketing Channel Network Platform
Customer profile data
To tear through Lao Zhai's tricks
Lao Zhai said he was going to inspect
Actually go to play mahjong
Let Manager Feng know
Don't fine any money
So Lao Zhai angered you
Then why are you
Don't let me go back
Lao Zhai has no grudges
You let him say a few words
It's over
Then you have to go back
Small things become big things
Where in the future
This is clearly
He doesn't make sense
Not a kid
Everything has to be reasonable
I think
Everyone's attitude towards me
All weird
As if i offended someone
That's not it
Mainly this work plan
Why are you so serious
Want this and that
Take the whole office
Uneasy
But Manager Feng told me
I can't just perfunctory
Do you want to make enemies?
I do not want
But leave it to me
I can't neglect
Then you have to
Slowly change your character
Let me try
Ok
Where i am
Have last year's work plan
You take it and modify it slightly
Hand it in
really
I just learned
His daughter and my daughter
Is a good friend of kindergarten
Let me deal with this problem
Stop telling others
correct
Siyu's new company
collapsed
Yes
I call her cellphone
Always shut down
She's back home
Previous phone number
Not much use anymore
it's a pity
I'll go out first
Zhizhi
Congratulations
Got it this month
Most Progress Award
Keep going
Thank you Mr. Yuan
I am back
came back
time to eat
it is good
Siyu is back
Got angry in the unit
How do you know
I don't know, guessing
I tell you
Your aunt
I want to introduce you a boyfriend
At home today
Made a phone call
Then why don't you stop her?
Why should i stop her
I didn't stop you from falling in love
right
Are now older leftover women
What reason do i stop
Xiaoling is the one who fell in love with me, not me
Xiaoling
Don't you say
Xiaoling is better than you in this respect
dad
What are you father and daughter talking about
Talk about boyfriend
Since you all talked up here
Siyu, Auntie wants to persuade you
The past is over
You are not young anymore
Hurry up
I know
Those friends around me
Daughter as old as you
Their children are in elementary school
Us
Even if you don't worry about getting married
Also have to talk about one first
dont you agree
Yes yes yes
Aunt Luo
Introduced you one
The guy from the design institute
Family conditions are pretty good
Take time to meet you
Auntie, I just went to work
Busy
Wait two days
No no no
You can delay the day
Not so much
Obedient obedient
Be that Aunt Luo
Give her a face
Who is Aunt Luo?
Aunt Luo, don't you know
Your child in the future
If you go to a good school
That can be all pointed
Aunt Luo helped
Don't copy it all
Data wording
Slightly modified
Answering reasoning
Take care of me
I beg, I'm going crazy
At least let me confirm
Your life and death
sister
Hello
What are you doing
Sorry, sister Siyu
I'm working overtime
Contact later
I am also working overtime
But i can
Have a few words with you
I really envy you
How are you
Your mom has started
Arranged a blind date for me
Li Siyu, you also have today
Gu Xiaoling
Who told you to tell mom
He Mu's business
She annoyed me for three days
Such a big thing
You don't tell your mother
I didn't think about it myself
What did i tell her
You haven't thought about it
It's OK, don't talk about me
How are you
Are you still used to going back?
Okay
You want to come back anytime
I'm fine
Your bed
I haven't collected it for you yet
I won't go back
whatever
I'm busy, I won't tell you
Bye bye
Susan Papa
Mother Yuwei
Sorry to disturb you
I can i
Please one thing
You said
I'm going on business for two days this weekend
and so
Can you help me
Help me take care of susan
no problem
I am preparing to take Yuwei
To Disney
Then i just happen to
Take them together
That's great, great
Thank you
Not hard
Then this Saturday morning
I put Susan
Deliver it to your gate, okay
Good good
See you on Saturday
Ok see you on saturday
Thank you
Listen up
As long as you can get the customer back
I don't care what method you use
But absolutely not
Harm the interests of customers
Whoever violates
Liu Jie expelled
Is your lesson
How i feel
Sister Yuan and Sister Siyu
More and more like
They are the same kind
The guy is excellent
Work in a big company
His income is very high
Also polite and respectful to the elderly
Coming
Aunt Luo
Thinking rain is coming
I won't instigate
Chat with you two
Thank you Aunt Luo
Hurry up, very good
Goodbye
Let's talk here
it is good
Sorry
I still have something to do
Go ahead
Li Siyu
You don't remember me anymore
Small news
My features
It's really not easy to remember
Nor is it
I left Shanghai six months ago
You also came back from shanghai
Why leave shanghai
Dislike not used to
How about you
I
Like very much
But i don't like myself there
What does this mean
I really have something to do today
How about we make an appointment another day
Good another day
Another day
What day is it
talk later
Row
Can you add a WeChat?
Wen Xingyu
You are the representative of our geography class
That is Zhang Xinyu
Sorry
It's ok
Where did I go anyway
Are the most inconspicuous
Try again
Why can't it open?
Didn't you say you remembered you
What is after 179
Dad, mom, really
I did not put the password
Did you send it to you?
Why are you still at the door
Your dad didn't remember
Come come here i come
Old age
Watch and remember
You said you guys are too
Don't tell me in advance
I'll pick you up at the station
Just don't want to trouble you
So I didn't tell you in advance
Know the address
Just come by your own car
Son, you don't live here
I worked overtime these two days
This is
The house you bought for five million
Yes
This must be in my hometown
Can buy two villas
Dad, this is Shanghai
Yiming
House prices in Shanghai will not fall
How can Shanghai's house prices fall
Okay, this house
Ok
I called your company
The company said you stopped doing it long ago
why
Do you have a job now
I have it now
Me and my friend
Closed a company
Can it work
Yes of course
We have found the investment
Then the company is on track
Then you and Siyu
There is no way to save it
We come this time
I also want to help you and Siyu
Have a good talk
I already have a new girlfriend
Then your new girlfriend
What is it for
Financial
Economic conditions are OK
Really good
Anyway better than me
Where is her home
I really don't know this
how old are you
just like
Seems to be a bit older than me
How big
Where do i know where to go
I didn't ask so clearly
Such an important thing
You don't even know
Are you deceived by her?
No mom
How old am i
Why am I being deceived
You are for her
Did you break up with Siyu?
Is not
I broke up with Siyu
It's our two own reasons
That's because of her
Lost your original job
Things at work
It's my decision
Let's meet that person
Come mom
Drink some hot water
Ok
Be careful
it is good
We want to meet your girlfriend
No need
Needed
No this time
Mainly came too anxious
Or next time, next time I
Just this time
Row
Let me check the time
Dad, auntie, I'm back
Siyu, have you eaten yet?
Nope
Sit down
how do you feel
I need to ask
Came back without eating
Definitely not feeling it
I didn't ask you, I asked Siyu
no feelings
Such good conditions
You don't feel it
What condition
Aunt Nalu said
Before this little news comes back
Sold a house in Shanghai
Worth millions
Millions
You sell your sons and daughters
Even if we want to sell our daughter
How can it be hundreds of millions?
Don't listen to your dad, listen to me
Get in with that little smell
forget it
Don't count
You have to marry in your life
You are over thirty
This is your last chance
Why do you say that
Your value is starting to fall
The 30-year-old guy
So popular
Just started to pull up
Auntie, what is your theory?
I'm for your good
Auntie, don’t lose it
talk later
Too urgent
Time is not enough
I need before the end of the year
The brand value of Emerald
Tenfold
Contacted several companies
They all retreated
what happened
Nothing
Yiming
I desperately need to reverse
Emerald's unprofitable situation
I wonder if I have any friends
Can recommend
You can recommend Yiwen Company
Forgive me
Do you want some soup
I will help you Sheng
Let auntie go
No, I'll come here
Let me do it
Come
Ok
My parents are here
They want to see you
Why are you laughing
I just suddenly felt
So real
Isn't it true between us
do not mean that
I mean
Suddenly feel
Chai, rice, oil and salt are so close to me
tomorrow I will
May have to travel
You just thought about going on a business trip
Do you think
It's not appropriate at this time
I don't think it is necessary
Do you think it is unnecessary now
Still not necessary in the future
Feelings are our business
Has nothing to do with other people
They they are not
Anyone else
They are my parents
Yiming
Recently
You have an excuse to work overtime
did not return
Do you think i'm out of ideas
But I didn’t ask, right?
Because i believe
Your loyalty to feelings
I also allow
You have your own private space
So i hope you are the same
You can also respect my ideas
I only love you
Just want to be with you
What do you think
Our relationship
What is the final attribution
I haven't thought about this
You never thought about our future
We are together now
Very happy
Why do you want so much
If i want
It's not just happiness now
What else do you want
Although we are just together
But what I want is responsibility
Is guardian
For a lifetime
I may not be able to give you these
Can i understand
You actually just want
Have a love with me
Don't want to participate in my life
Don't want me
Participate in your life
Yiming
You say i am your angel
But do you know
Angel round investment failure rate
Is 95%
I said I don't want to participate too much
Because of
If one day
I have to
When facing failure
I can just explain to myself
No need to tell anyone else
and many more
Wait, wait, wait
No regrets
I am your father
That's not OK
Why are you so serious about playing chess?
It's your turn
What did you two do
The phone rang and did not answer
Don't bother
Hey
Who
Is it a little smell
She's free
You come pick her up now
Good good
Goodbye
Who
It's Xiao Wen
He asked you out
I do not want to go
I can agree
He will be there soon
I want to play chess with my dad
Play chess with your dad
What's the point
Laohuiqi
You regret playing chess
Be good, go and change clothes
Obediently
obedient
See who's here
Yu Wei
Susan
early
Come here, dad
Come here to pick her up tonight
My business trip is postponed to next week
I promised Susan before
Said to go to Disney
I don't want her to be disappointed
and so
I'll accompany you
Okay
boarding
Go to Disney
Let's go let's go
Super him
Drive
Safety first
I drive
Safe driving
what did you say
What i plan is
Have a child after three or five years
Change to the travel version
Good to take the kids
Travel or something
You think so far
Three to five years are not far away
Life goes fast
Arrived
Two tigers love to dance
The little rabbit pulls the radish obediently
I learn to walk
You see
The tallest building
Is Shanghai Center
Is that one?
Shanghai Center
The second highest one is
World Financial Center
Correct
There is another building next to it
Slightly shorter
That is Jin Mao Tower
Jin Mao Building
Yes smart
Little duck
Ducks where are ducks
That is swan
let me see
I know the story of the ugly duckling
Tell me one
I beg you
Ok i will tell you
a long long time ago
There is a female duck
Why are you bringing me here
This is my parents
Wedding room for me
The room payment was paid in full
The decoration money is ready
Just wait for the lady to decide on the decoration style
Let's not reach this point yet
Yes
I just want to use this way
Tell you
I'm not the kind of unreliable person
I went to get married with you
If we get married
Economically
You don't have to worry about the future
correct
Our home is in Jinye Square
There are two pavements
My mom said
The rent for those two shops
Will be used by children in the future
No longer have to be afraid
The landlord has increased the price
No need to worry anymore
The landlord is going to sell the house
Since then became a house slave
Finally became a house slave
I
I have a crush on you since the first grade
what did you say
Since I saw you last time
Know you are still single
I can't wait
Auntie Luo
Let her introduce you to me
Turned out to be like this
Siyu
Although you don't say anything
But i can feel
You must be injured in Shanghai
I can assure you
As long as you stay with me
I will never hurt you
you know
Why do people get hurt
Because I met a bad guy
Do not
Be hurt because of love
If you don't want to be hurt
Just not love
But can we do it
I can not do it
I can't do it
so
As long as we still have the instinct of love
You have to face the hurt
How do i have a
Ominous premonition
Small news
We still
Just be ordinary friends
you sure
Very sure
be with you
I won't feel tired
Won't hurt
but
I think
Boring isn't it
or
Let's go everywhere
Maybe you can find the feeling
Small news
Your conditions are good
Everyone advised me to cherish
but
You are not what i want
What do you want
I still want that
The feeling of love
Even if it will hurt again