# Google translate version for your reference #
Ninety percent are rumors
Ten percent is true
That ten percent
It's not what they wrote
Mr. Pan, I suggest looking for a lawyer
Prosecute these rumors
Then hold a press conference
To clarify the facts
You still have trouble
Is it not big enough?
Li Siyu
You must right away
at all costs
Take the impact of this matter
drop to lowest
where are you
I need you
Waiting for you in the old place
President Wang
Mr. Pan’s secretary just now
Call and say
About financing
Can talk more
Tell him
I'm not free this week
I have something at home
Make an appointment next week
Ok
You all know
The whole network has been spread
You know so multimedia
Can someone please
Help us control the impact
That's too late
From your related news
Exposed till now
Twelve hours have passed
The entire incident spread
Already missed
Best disposal period
Is there no way?
Before you come
I have been on the whole incident
Made an assessment
The main target of public opinion now
Aimed at the shady of investment
On the contrary, the quality of Lubao products
Rarely questioned
In fact, at this point
Lucky
But the brand image is damaged
Damage to the interests of
This is a foregone conclusion
So you guys now
The only thing you can do
Is to keep public opinion from escalating
Don't expand
Then let the investors lose
drop to lowest
That's why i'm looking for you
Be sure to let partners
Have confidence in us
Take me for many years
In terms of planning experience
the first
You can't avoid
Can't hide
You must act now
Second, you should
Proactively contact new media
Including traditional media
Based on the principle of sincere communication
Admit the mistake to the public
Take responsibility
and
Deal with relevant responsible persons immediately
That's not my problem at all
Why should I admit my mistake
At least you didn't avoid it, right
I remember you told me
You said you must bid
Not only for yourself
More for the green treasure
Now emerald
I need you to bear the burden
To take all the responsibilities
How to bear
Resign
I understand
Siyu
There is another thing
Now the whole thing
I don't think it has a hot spot effect
But fermented into the way it is now
I think
It does not conform to the law of transmission
What do you mean
Someone hired a navy behind
Who hired
If you need
I can check it for you
it is good
Mr. Pan
Go online
Leave those comments and comments
This matter really can't be delayed
Don't deal with Li Siyu again
This netizen is going to fry the pan
Let the employees take the blame when something goes wrong
Irresponsible
And there is no company in charge
Why do employees trust you
Why do employees work hard for you
Dedicated to you
Someone has to be responsible
I am responsible
That will never work
You are the chairman and general manager
Instead of letting you take responsibility
Why not come here
this matter
From beginning to end
It has nothing to do with you
But Green Treasure has something to do with me
I'll take care of this
But Li Siyu as a party
Don't deal with it at all
Definitely not justified
Can't take Li Siyu
I can handle this alone
I consulted an expert
He thinks we must
Hold a press conference
Admit the mistake to the public
Take responsibility
and
And for
Calm public sentiment
Calm things down
I should take the blame and resign
I'm going to write a resignation report
and many more
Fang Zhan, right away
To prepare for the press conference
I personally apologize to the public
And announced
Li Siyu
Temporary suspension
Can the public accept it?
That's it, let's go
As a public enterprise
To the resulting
Bad public opinion influence
We sincerely
Apologize to the public
As the chairman of the company
I feel so guilty
Feel guilty
Related employees currently involved
Has been suspended immediately
Under investigation
I once again to the public
Regulatory authorities
Lvbao's shareholders
And all the friends who care about us
Apologize
Sincerely welcome the public and media
Continue to supervise Emerald
ended
OK OK
All right
Nothing
It's okay, I'm here
OK OK
Let's go
go
Mr. Pan said
Just let me rest for a while
I'll go back when the storm is over
Let's not talk about this
Take a good rest first
Do not
I have struggled for so many years
I give so much
I will never give up easily
But even if you don't give up
Can't go back
why
Think about it
Emerald now announces that you have been suspended
Waiting to be processed
As a result, wait for the storm to pass
You will be reinstated immediately
What will the public think
They will feel
Emerald is sheltering
Is perfunctory
The public can tolerate mistakes
But deception must not be tolerated
Maybe then
Will trigger new public opinion
public
The public will soon
Forget about it
They don't even care
Who is back
Emerald's Sales Director
I am not so optimistic
This is the result you most hope for
I knew it
Why are you
Always look at me like that
Is not it
Yes
I hope you resign
But this is protecting you now
The best way to protect Emerald
And you take advantage of this time
have a good rest
Condition your body
What's the problem with this?
That's what I think
What's wrong
Siyu
Now that it has happened
Then we will actively
Face it
We take bad things
Turned into a good thing
Right here
Siyu, what's the situation now?
He was removed from the company
what
Zhizhi, sorry
Can it be remedied now?
Is there any other way
Can help him
do not worry
I caused this
I will take care of it
Zhizhi
Do you still divorce him
want
mom
father
Mom, Yuwei
Are you happy today?
Happy
Happy, let's go home
President Wang
It's not easy to see you
No
Something happened at home
I thought it would be done in two or three days
It was delayed for a week
OK
Last time I quoted Mr. Wang
How are you thinking
I also quoted last time
How is Mr. Pan thinking?
Your offer
Not sincere
President Pan The latest change
Valuation of Lvbao Company
That little storm
No impact on Emerald
This is the latest sale
Completion with purchase order
From the data point of view
Whether it is a distributor or a user
I'm very supportive of Emerald
According to our latest estimates
Emerald's valuation
In this storm
Severely damaged
Your algorithm is outdated
we believe
In the next three months
Will fade
The impact of this storm
We will reshape the Emerald brand
this is us
Rebranding plan
Lvbao Phase III R&D investment is too large
Lead to short-term unprofitable
This fact
Maybe in the short term
No circumvention
But Emerald Three
Market growth rate
Is very high
And how it works
Already mature
Consider from a long-term perspective
The return on investment is very high
Our
Return on investment
Also has a valuation
enough
Are you thirsty?
President Wang
Eight hundred million twenty-two percent
Twenty-four percent
You are taking advantage of the fire
800 million
Twenty-two percent
Mr. Pan
Twenty-four percent
Farewell
President Wang
Twenty-two percent
I think we can accept
I must get it
Twenty-three percent
Just one point
Or we chase them back
Keep talking
The current bribery storm of Emerald III
Already subsiding
If this time
Let's drag on
Once a new investor enters the market
It's even harder to talk
Twenty-three percent
President Chen, your appointment letter
Appointment letter
Congratulations
Is Mr. Wang here?
inside
it is good
Yiming
President Wang
Got notified
Correct
This is for me
For newcomers who just joined the company
Yes is it a bit
Too fast
First of all
you deserve this
You create value for the company
The company should return you
Secondly
I need you for Tianyi Group
Create new strategic assets
The third
I also believe that you can help the company
Create more value
Ok
Manager Chen
Your dedicated parking space is over there
There is also an underground garage
It has your license plate number
thank you
Nothing
Manager Chen
I invested in Donglai
Administration Manager
Your new office
On the 22nd floor
This is your new assistant
Mr. Chen, hello
Hello there
Hold the bag for you
this way please
Mr. Chen, please
it is good
Manager Chen
Here please
Mr. Chen, please
Chen Hao
Chen Zonghao Chen Zonghao
Mr. Chen, this is your office
President Chen, I'm going out first
What's the matter you feel free to call me
it is good
I'll put it on the table for you
thank you
Nothing
Tenth year
Chen Yiming
Tianyi Group
Donglai Investment Co., Ltd.
Deputy General Manager
Mr. Wang, please see
I plan to build another park
Two first
Emerald III's production line
Five years later
If there are ten production lines
That half of China's new energy industry
Must be emerald
Five years
This is the ideal state
Maybe ten years
Mr. Pan
Don’t you want to
The valuation of Emerald
20 billion?
President Wang
Tell you the truth
If not for this equity financing
My valuation
Not interested at all
honestly
in my heart
Core technology is the last word
As for what valuation
I don't like these virtual
Really
Right lad
I'm sorry
I booked a restaurant to gather in the evening
Hello, Xiao Zhao
Hey
Don't forget the meeting at 3:30
I am Li Siyu
Sorry
I forgot that you have been suspended
Hello, this is Li Siyu
You are Li Siyu
I finally found you
You scum
Corruption and bribery
Simply social
It's you
You can't get through
I forgot to recharge my phone
Come in and talk
Just say it here
How is Yuwei?
pretty good
Is the alimony for the next quarter
It's time for me
Can you
Two days off
why
I'm busy looking for a house recently
Deposit
No more money
Yuwei is going to kindergarten
Eat and drink
It all needs money
I know
I don't want to give
You give me two more days
This is your father
Due obligation
I got a job in two days
I'll call you the money
You have been procrastinating for a week
I shouldn't
Hold any hope for you
Zhizhi Zhizhi
Congratulations on your promotion to vice president
You knew already
I booked a seat over there
I may not be able to drink
I drove over
You can find a driver
Come
It surprised me that
Sister Ziru values ​​you so much
I think it can
Put it another way
all these are
Got it by my own hard work
Right
it is good
I have said
You're the best
Now the entire Tianyi Group
No one will say i am
Mixed up by nepotism
Why didn't you tell me earlier
I'm afraid I will be stimulated
Yes
I take a call
Hey
Then you first
Send it to my mailbox first
Let me take a look
Correct
Okay. First of all
Ah bye
Siyu
I am really
I really
Have a lot of ideas
But i don't know
Don't know how to tell you
I used to
It's Caijin Company
The youngest department director
And i now
Donglai Group
The youngest vice president
And in the future
I must be too
The youngest vice president of Tianyi Group
ten years
I have been fighting for ten years
To be honest i am now
There are many in my heart
Feelings and thoughts
but
I can't think about it
I
I am making a set
Brand brand strategy
In the entire financial circle
No one has done it yet
Whether it is Tianyi Group
Or sister Ziru
They all let me do it
Doesn't bind me at all
Hey
what
Tomorrow tomorrow
Yes, you come to the company tomorrow
Find me
Ten o'clock around ten o'clock
No no no
I may not have that long
Fifteen minutes
I happen to have
15 minutes of gap
We can talk a little bit
it is good
OK, that's it first
Ah, see you tomorrow at the company
okay
Bye bye
Siyu
I just said those
Actually I have no other meaning
I just want to tell you
our future
Will definitely get better and better
I have this ability now
To take care of you
Will give you a sense of security
Like you said before
Talk about raising children
Repay the mortgage
You really
Don't worry at all
Those are all mine
Just be responsible for being beautiful
If I'm not beautiful anymore
Does it mean
You won't pay the mortgage
No longer raising children
look
I knew it
You would say so
So I
I have been hesitating
Hesitate what to tell you
Hey
Yes it's me
Reporter which reporter
Hello hello hello
Right
Then you first interview
Send me the outline of the interview
Correct
We chat number
Is my mobile number
Yes you just add me
Yes yes
The specific interview time
We again
Then discuss it carefully
Good good
Yes yes
Goodbye
Ok
These reporters now
The news is really good
Caught up so soon
Honestly i
I really don't want to be interviewed
but
but now
The company needs to promote
So I can't help it
You are so busy
Siyu
I will get busy
and so
Hey
Brother Qian
So soon you will know
That's great, right
Then this time we can
Together to do a big thing
I think I will make sure
Its whole values
Yes no problem
I think before me
The plan I thought
Absolutely no problem
Then we systematically regulate
what
OK, no problem
Then we will meet
Let's talk more carefully
Good um good um
Bye bye
Hello, the user you are calling
Temporarily unavailable
Sorry
Hello, the user you are calling
Temporarily unavailable
Sorry
The user you dialed
Temporarily unavailable
Is that what I said today
Makes you uncomfortable
Xiaoling said you can't get through
Worried about you
Two days ago
Don't know who put my phone number
Leak out
The keyboard man always calls and scolds me
I shut down
Do you want to call the police?
No need to
It's gone for two days
Didn’t you see that I turned it on?
That's good
These two days
Are you ok
that
Where's Liu Yang
Yuwei's living expenses
He has owed more than a month
I go find him
He told me no
He is not working now
Want to rent again
Maybe not
I do not know either
Is he true or not?
But if
If I have your confidence
I will tell him
I don't want your money
But i can't tell
Zhizhi
How much do you want
Is five thousand enough?
Siyu sister
I can't ask for your money
I still have savings
Zhizhi, I am responsible for this
You let me do something
Siyu sister
About Liu Yang
Has nothing to do with you
You now
How did you plan
Wait for him to stabilize
Just go through the formalities
Haven't you prepared before
Did you give him a step?
Why suddenly became so determined
I went to him that day
I have found
He has told Wei Yayun
Live together
Are they still together now?
do not know
I don't want to know
How are you
Take a break
What are your plans
Mr. Pan said
Wait for this storm to subside
Just let me go back
I heard a saying
about what
President Fang
I want to invite Yuan Huizhong back
Back to sales department
Be a director
Mommy mommy
Yuwei, come
Are you happy today?
Happy
happy
What did you learn today
Hello, Mr. Liu
Your resume
We have all seen it
What else do you have about entry
No new requirements
I just want to be able to join the job as soon as
Then report next Monday
Thank you
Yiming
thank you
I got this job