# Google translate version for your reference #
Old Shen
After the summit
you must
Go and sit there
I still have good tea
I know you love tea
Mr. Zheng
Hello
I am Chen Yiming of Yiwen Culture
It's Minister Gong
Let me wait for you here
I know
You are the one that Lao Gong said
From the media big V
Want me to advertise
Correct
You see
This is our company profile
How many fans do you have now
Our company has just started
Although only 60,000 fans
But our company now
Sixty thousand
60,000 wanted me to advertise
You think so beautifully, right
How about this
Waiting for you to pass a million fans
Talk to me again
Mr. Zheng, I
Some people now
I don't know at all
A few catties by yourself
Sell ​​yourself everywhere
This is how the sky is thick
Hey
Hello Mr. Chen
I am the legal counsel of the bank
Your mortgage
Six months overdue
Our bank has submitted to the court
Filed a lawsuit
I have no money
You take my house away
Better let the court shoot me
Mr. Wang, that
The information I gave you last time
You read it
How about we work together
What is the current market value of your company
Two or three billion
Only two or three billion
Just want to cooperate with me
Think too beautifully
Wait until you reach 10 billion
These people now
Really don't know
A few catties by yourself
Sell ​​yourself everywhere
Forget it, walk around
Let's go
This is the money
Teacher Yiming
I am your loyal fan
Look at your official account every day
When will there be a chance
Can cooperate with you
Sorry, Mr. Wang
There is something on the organizing committee
Please go over
I'm going in
I will ask the secretary to cooperate with you
President Wang, please
Hello, Mr. Chen
I'm sorry just now
Just now i
Sorry Mr. Chen
very sorry
The bank called me just now
Say all your debts
Have already paid off
Who helped me pay it back
Isn't it you, Mr. Chen?
Mr. Chen
Yiming
President Wang
Can you give me some face
face
My mortgage
You helped to pay it back, right
And that echo
Also you
President Wang
I don't need you to help me
I don't need you to sympathize with me
I don't need you to pity me
President Wang
I beg you
Can you give me some self-esteem
do not worry
The ones you helped me
I'll give it back to you
But give me some time
Yiming
Can you give it back to me
Only money
I also paid my care
care
respect
enjoy
And love
How do you return these to me
You say you have your self-esteem
Your face
Don't i have my self esteem
My face?
I muster up all the courage
Expressed affection with you
Leave without saying goodbye for you
I am approaching you quietly
care about you
In exchange, you don't need it
Chen Yiming
I am also a person
When i was rejected
Also sad
When i was humiliated
I will be sad and my heart will bleed
I also have my pride
My inferiority complex
But facing you
I put down all my arms
Exposed all my weaknesses
I hope hello
I hope you are happy
Am i doing something wrong
Yiming
I do not blame you
It's me
Put in the dust
I gave it to you
Hurt my right
I will disappear
Disappear from your life
Never bother you again
if it was me
I respect my inner choice
From an economic perspective
Communication between people
All for profit
In other words
Relationship between people
The essence is interest
Relationship
Is also a kind of interest relationship
Survive in the workplace
it's actually really easy
Where is
Just do something
Worthy of the company
Worthy of my contribution
Sister Ziru
When are you free recently
We gather
Five o'clock tomorrow afternoon
Ok
welcome
Walk slowly
long time no see
Complexion is not good
What do you want to drink
Lemonade bar
Waiter
A glass of lemonade
Ok
Thank you
A glass of lemonade
You slow down
Thank you
I remember that
When I introduced Mr. Pan
When I met you
You guys were very speculative
Yes
Then why now
This is the situation
You heard
Sister Ziru
Mr. Pan's temper is a bit bigger
Anxious
But his character
Pattern ability
I have seen entrepreneurs
the best
Sometimes he doesn’t stick to the trivial
Not willing to be bound by rules
But he does all this
Not for myself
But for the development of green treasure
For his homeland
You are right
I admire him
but
Doesn't mean he is an emerald
The best candidate for chairman
Who do you think is more suitable than him
I
You don't understand batteries
Do not understand new energy
But I know
How to make money with emeralds
In your eyes
Green treasure is just a tool for making money
Yes
You befriended me
Actually, I went for the green treasure
Yes
I was following
New energy field
your appearance
Just gave me an opportunity
You know from me
Emerald has equity financing
Out of my mouth again
News from Huaan and Shanghai Bank
After i didn't use the value
By betraying me
Gave Fang Zhan a certificate
I have to correct this
I got the trust of Fang Zhan
I always treat you as a friend
I also treat you as a friend
You keep using me
Siyu
You from me
Also got a lot of benefits
I also saved you
300,000 car repair fees
And your ex boyfriend
It's also the job I arranged
I was a fool
I couldn't see you through
Even recommended you to Mr. Pan
It's not me you didn't see through
Is life itself
As an adult
You should know
Behind every pie
All marked up
I killed Mr. Pan
Hurt the emerald
Don't blame yourself too much
Green treasure in my hand
Will only become more valuable
Mr. Pan now
Although not the chairman
But it's also a shareholder
He will also profit
Will even exceed
The sum of his previous ten years
You think money is everything
I am an investment
Money is everything to me
if it is like this
Then your life must be boring
Because besides money
There are many valuable things
Siyu
The life of my prince Ru
Comparable to you
Imagined wonderful
Do not
Then you can experience it
My boyfriend came to pick me up
Sorry, I'm going one step ahead
Walk slowly
I'm here
Let's go
how is this possible
It's true
No, you must be mistaken
Chen Yiming told me personally
Then he must be lying to you
The two of us are now
Business partner
He can't lie to me
It's not that Chen Yiming did this
Can he be worthy of Li Siyu?
Please, he and Li Siyu
Have broken up for months
But Li Siyu didn't forget him
Still want to get back with him
How did you know
Li Siyu and me
A house asleep
Just her little hypocritical
Can i not know
I really can't blame Yiming for this
Chen Yiming must be for the money
With that old woman
Together
I can't allow
You say that my brother
I just said
Chen Yiming is one
Vain
What you say
Speak from others
I think it's ok
But from your mouth
I don't quite understand
What do you mean
Don't you always think
Marry a rich man?
Chen Yiming has
Helped you fulfill your dream
You should applaud this time
For Chen Yiming
Regard him as an idol in life
and also
Are you scolding Chen Yiming?
Still scold yourself
Moreover
Chen Yiming is not a soft rice man
Prince Ru to us
Cast that point of advertising
He rejected it all
He is still pointing at me when he is eating
Why don't you eat halfway through
I'm so angry
Today’s view is sharp enough
Want to add content
Must be sharp
What to write tomorrow
Wrote the dispute over the equity of the green treasure
OK
Where are you standing
As an observer
Of course I remain neutral
I am looking forward to reading this article
I can now
Interview you
Can know everything
Then you and Pan Zhiyong
Working together for so long
You feel
What kind of person is he
Pan Zhiyong
Have ideals and feelings
But the market
Do not believe in feelings and ideals
What the market believes is
Legal power rules
I also heard
Before he left Emerald
Let it go
Say what
You barbarians
I see how long you can be proud of
Yes
Acquirers are considered wolfish
Because of
Put capital return first
Based on this goal
We hinder
Corporate development management personnel
Idle
Inaction employee
Will be ruthless
and so
We hate and hate
But the market will improve
But from the green treasure
In the past
Pan Zhiyong is indeed a
Very good leader
But not the best
Who do you think is the best
You
Yiming
Ok
You really
Don't you plan to come back and help me
you know
Why did i before
Do you want to leave Tianye?
I know
Scared by me
Is not
Me at that time
Just broke up
I'm really messed up inside
So i need time and space
Quiet down and think about it
I
What is my situation
I know
So at that time
No matter what the situation
I have to leave Tianyi
Yiming
You never rely on me
I still want this
no problem
Listen to you
I'm back
So tired today
Come back so early today
Ok
Siyu
Something
I know
How do you know
I saw it with my own eyes
Siyu, listen to me
Nothing
I broke up with him long ago
Who is he with
It has nothing to do with me
That's the truth
Are you OK
What can i do
Isn't it just a man?
Correct
Let's find
Ok
Find two at once
No find a bunch
More handsome than him
Better than him
More talented than him
But i still want him
Siyu
Cry if you want to cry
I do not cry
Nothing to cry
I have a career
How can i have time
Distracted by these things
Ok
Mr. Zhang, hello
I want to ask
Call about investment
How did you think about it in the end
Ok ok
Then we have a good project
I will recommend it to you
it is good
he
He is not willing to invest
He has no eyes
He will regret it
He is not willing to invest
Alright alright alright
He is not willing
Just cry out
it's okay no problem
Nothing
He is not willing
Cry
it does not matter
correct
I have something
I want to talk to you
Ok
I have been following calls
On the matter
I think this project
Emerald can still
Continue to vote
Can't
why
There are two modes of entrepreneurship
One is fast financing
Burn money quickly and expand quickly
Quickly occupy the entire market
The other one
Is steady and steady
Rely on business to achieve profitability
And then slowly expand
Li Siyu started
Sway on both ends
Eventually lead to this
A dilemma on both sides
Is it possible to reverse it?
That's too late
Has appeared on the market
The same type of product
And the momentum is better than her
She has missed
The best time to develop
Even if Pan Zhiyong is still there
Emerald's Board of Directors
Would not agree
Continue to invest and call
Right
That's really a pity
What a pity
Li Siyu on sales
Is a good hand
In e-commerce and finance
She is a blank piece of paper
Besides, Pan Zhiyong
Self-assertive and conceited
Won't listen
Opinion of others
These two
Together combination
Doomed to fail
You still miss her
I just don't want
Don't want to see her too embarrassed
Yiming
I'm somewhere else
Are very atmospheric
But only emotionally
Is stingy
I don't want you to always mention her
I don't want you to miss her
Alright
I really didn't expect
That prince ru
Turned out to be such a person
now think of it
She approached me at first
It's not just green treasure
And Chen Yiming
That this matter
You can't just forget it
What do you want
At least let Chen Yiming know
The real face of that old woman
Xiaoling
I broke up with Chen Yiming
After all
It's our problem
Has nothing to do with other people
That prince ru treats you that way
You can swallow this breath
Can't swallow
Then we have to find a way
Get out of your anger
Do you know what venting is
Scold her face to face
Even hit her and stabbed her twice
Trust me
These can't give up
Only i called
Do it for a long time
Be bigger and stronger
That's called venting
can you
I must do
Row
You can come to our company
Do research
My background data
All open to you
You know this project after reading it
Must have unlimited prospects
it is good
Then we will contact
Advance
sister
I heard that Lubao
Don't invest in us
There is something wrong with the green treasure
Let's call
Do you want to finish
Never possible
But we now
I have other financing channels
Really
Go work
sister
Whether it's life or death
I stand by you
Your sister me
Never die
Manager Li
I know
that
Believe me i have a way
Good, Mr. Li
I just handed in my resignation report
I know
This month to today
Five already gone
Nothing
We can recruit ten more
Manager Li
I think
Not a question of hiring
People are panicking now
About the company's future
Various sayings
Come, everyone, come here
Come
Put the work in your hands first
All come in first
Hurry up behind
Let me tell you officially
the first
Small problems with capital turnover
already solved
The company is currently operating normally
second
We called and started our business so far
Always one
A company that continues to create miracles
What do we rely on to create miracles
Rely on the market, rely on funds
It’s not our belief
Not only can we overcome difficulties
Can beat my own heart
Inferiority complex
Hesitate to doubt
We can win
Sure to have the last laugh
Pursue perfection Pursue excellence
Correct
Together we will
Pursue perfection Pursue excellence
Chen Yiming
Do you think
I am heartless
Will be very graceful
Tolerate you standing in front of me
Listen to me to finish
I didn't blast you out
Because i don't want
Let my employees see
I'm like a shrew
Listen to me first
I already feel very sick
You do not want
Take our last goodwill
All consumed
I'm not here
Talk about our relationship
Are we still related
I come today
To persuade you
The company shut down the call
You are
Lvbao current chairman
As your current boyfriend?
My relationship with Ziru
It's my personal business
I don't want to explain
But i come over today
All for you
You still say this
Are you disgusting?
If you really want to succeed
You have to know how to choose
Learn to give up
When you first started your business
I'm following
You have been focusing on the product
Walk very carefully
But then you suddenly started speeding up
Afterwards it may be because
Funds are getting tight
You start to shrink again
Till now
You have no rules at all
Don't think you are from the media
Know everything
Row
Then I'll talk to you
The promotion plan I know best
today
Startups want not to burn money
It’s hard to promote mobile software
But if you can do
Creative and unique single-point penetration
It's not impossible
But did you do it
Let's just say you this leaflet
This is the same as the promotion in the mall
What is the difference between direct mail advertising
Let me talk about your marketing highlights
Are you a battery car user
Brings convenience
Or franchisee
Brings business opportunities
Yes you might think
These two are your highlights
But as a publicity
You have to focus
Even if I make a mistake
I still have time to fix it
You have run out of ammunition and food
All entrepreneurs
Will experience the darkness before dawn
As long as it passes, it is dawn
This is not the darkness before dawn
It's getting deeper and deeper
Why do you say that
The status of the call
I believe
You must know better than me
Did you come to see me making a fool of yourself
Go now
Don't worry
I still have a major event in life
Want you to witness with me
Guan Xiaotang, what are you doing?
Sister Li
now
I know you
Nineteenth million
Three thousand four hundred and fifty one minutes
This number has no meaning
But what I want to say next
Especially meaningful
Sister Li
You are the coolest girl i have ever seen
I want to be you
Spanking
Except for one
Beyond the blind ex-boyfriend
You have no shortcomings
I love you
Come on
Come on, brother
Come on, Xiao Tang
Sister Li
I have one
The two-hundred-level godless beast Jiaolong
Two hundred
I decided to dedicate it to you
what is this
This is my account and password
Please accept
Stop it
Get up
I won't get up unless you accept it
Accept accept accept accept
OK, I accept
I'm sorry
Xiao Tang, I want hot pot
Xiao Tang treats
Treat at night
A little too much
You're still not asleep
What are you doing here
You are not afraid of loose skin on your face
In the third grade of elementary school
I took the third place
My mother took me
Beat hard
It seems I was the last one
It was terrible when you were young
later
You arrived at our house
I found every exam
You are not the last one
Is the second to last
But your mother never beat you
Don't even scold you
I was thinking
Why mom and mom
So different
It's not that your mother is different from my mother
But you are different from me
You are studying
So your mother asked you
Take the first test every time
I'm not that material
My mom is used to
She confessed her fate
Actually we are the same
It's late at night
Can you sleep anymore
I'm going to sleep if you don't sleep
Go to bed early
I should admit my fate too