# Google translate version for your reference #
What to eat this
Hello need here
fruit juice
Sorry
We can't bring children here
It's okay, tell your boss
Haowen is here
is it tasty
good to eat
Talk to uncle
What have you been doing
Yiming
Ok
I am in a hurry
I hope to find a job soon
Get out of the current state as soon as possible
Help Zhizhi share a little
But this kind of thing
Can't worry
Am I the same before?
Who is classmate Haohao?
Is before
Classmates in the kindergarten
Do you like him
Not allowed
Can't tell others
Of course only the two of us know
Don't lie to me
Then we pull the hook
Don't tell anyone about this
This is the little secret between us
will not
I will never tell anyone
Don't lie to me
Sorry
I just asked the boss
Still can't bring the kids in
Did you make a mistake?
Did you tell your boss
Lei Haowen, Huangpu District
Sorry, sorry
I asked
You go talk
Okay, okay, okay
This place is not suitable for children
Let's change place
Wait for me at the door
I check out
Go to the door and wait for uncle
what's up
Sorry
I am so sorry
Come on, come on, right here
Right here
it is good
eat and drink
All in place
Welcome to
The parking lot is Xiao Li
Downstairs is Xiao Jiang
The elevator entrance is Xiao Ming
This is Xiaoliang
I am in charge
Speech presentation
Check it three times, no problem
server
Foolproof
Promotional materials
All in place
Let's stop here today
Everyone go back and recharge
Tomorrow the best condition
Welcome call comes online
Come on
Tomorrow is your big day
But i have to work overtime
Zhizhi wants to see Yuwei
We can't even go
We discussed
Send you a flower basket
Siyu sister
The words on this flower basket
You like to make money
It's still a guest
Write as you want
wish
The call was a hit
Li Siyu's wishes come true
Can you write that
Just write
Row
Okay, then I'll hang up
Bye bye
Hello
Did you call the company?
Yes
Your express arrived
Please take it downstairs
what is this
Seems to belong to your company
Investment Manual
I'm down right away
Sister sister
what happened
Guan Xiaotang
Did not you say
Are the promotional materials in place?
How come there is express delivery
Send the investment brochure
I forgot the investment brochure
Hello
This is the courier that has called, right
Yes
Lend me your pen
it is good
thank you
me
I i am wrong i am wrong
You can go today
You can't just let me
Get out of here
I can
you
Is not
I can't completely rely on this
What are you doing
That that
The courier should also
It should have arrived yesterday as planned
It's their own problem
and
I'm not responsible for this
Yes, the propaganda Xiao Sun is in charge
I was forced to resign by you
I came up temporarily
no no
Even my fault
That's not enough
It's a capital crime
I asked you three times
You said it's ok
It turned out to be such a big mistake
Who do you die
No no no
Is there a business brochure missing?
For this manual
I have been busy for a month
Ran 13 studios
Four designers mad
Believe it or not
I can still use it now
A little kid
I believe i believe i believe
Good looks broken
what happened
I
I'm going to ask
It's okay just now
what's up
Deliberately not to let people work overtime
Sister Li, Sister Li
what's the situation
There is good news
And a bad news
Which one do you listen to first
bad
The bad news is
One elevator is broken
For safety's sake
Just put all the elevators
All stopped
what
The good news is
Elevator manufacturers promise
Ten o'clock tomorrow morning
Put all elevators
All overhauled
Guaranteed
What about the freight elevator
It broke a few days ago
This is also good news
Nothing
Let's go online ceremony
It will start at ten o'clock tomorrow morning
It won't be delayed at all
What to do with the investment manual
Put it here first
Wait until the freight elevator is ready tomorrow
Let's ship it up
No way
Guests arrive at ten o'clock
Must be before the guests arrive
Put the investment brochure in the gift box
Two hundred gift boxes
It will take at least two hours
So tonight
Investment manual
Put it in the gift box
No, there is no elevator either
Is not
walk the stair
Sister Lee
We are on the twelfth floor
Our company
Sister
How many times do you have to move
Sister Lee
Why are you so tempered?
Because you don't worry
You always
You have such a big temper
After being broken
The temper is so big
Guan Xiaotang
Do you want to be scolded or beaten
I don't want to
I am
Want to gossip
Let's relax
No gossip
Then tell me
Your ex boyfriend
it's said
You two will get married soon
The one who kicked you again
Guan Xiaotang
Don’t you know after the ninth five
Do I have to be measured to my boss?
Not after nine-five
I'm the only one
There is nothing i dare not say
There is nothing I dare not do
Believe it or not, I will beat you now
Keep your strength to climb the stairs
sister
But but sister
I think you can really
Tell me
Just treat me as a tree hole
Nothing is unhappy
Just say it
Hold your heart
What to do with tumors
roll
Then you two
How did you meet
Talk about it
Say
Talk talk talk talk
A little unexpected
Like love at first sight
An exhibition
They plan and arrange the exhibition
do not know either
What attracted me to him
Started asking me
of course
he is handsome
Talented and clean, handsome
How handsome is he
Am i handsome
I'll stop talking nonsense
Talk about it
All these years
We dream together
Work hard together
We are not only lovers
Best friend
I was in his growth
I grew up with him
But we are two people after all
Like a tree
Two adjacent branches
Although they grew up together
But at some point
Suddenly found
We are getting further and further apart
our future
Also pointing in different directions
But he is not willing to compromise
I don't want to give up
Break up
Became our only choice
When together
Think the other party is redundant
In the way cold-blooded
Only found out after separation
Half of my body is gone
You speak
It's very distressing
Really
I know
What you said behind my back
We are all nonsense
You are all right
I can only let myself
Very bitter very busy very tired
To forget the pain a little bit
I, we are you
It's very hard, very busy and tired, okay
Li Siyu
What's your boss
Squeeze employees
Heal yourself
Thank you guys
Stay with me this time
Have to endure my perversion
Crazy and cold-blooded
It's ok
If you know your mistakes, you will be a good sister
I'm afraid I can't change it
I
I come i come i come
Let let let let me do
I
can you
I'm ok i
Go go let go
not me
Then you take one, I take three
I
My mature hunk
Mature hunk
not yet
There are five more layers
Told me so much
Also talk about you
I
What can i say
I ask you
Why is it always the same
Heartless
Look like a fool
Possible
Because my life experience is too tortuous
I want to have heart and lung
I can't live long ago
The kid is still in life
Really
When i was two years old
My dad died in a car accident
My mother remarried
I followed my grandpa since I was a kid
Grow up together
but
My grandpa has no income
Can only rely on picking up
Keep alive
Edit
I did not make up
I feel like picking up
Nothing bad
At least you can see
Various game consoles
so
I play games very well
sister
I still
I especially like Transformers
Childhood
I picked up my grandpa
Assemble all kinds of Transformers
Into this world
Unique Transformers
then
On my birthday
Give it to yourself
When is your birthday
I give you a transformer
You lied to me
you guess
Guan Xiaotang, let me kick you here
You can't kick
You stop
You chase me
sister
You said we are calling
Can it succeed
Must succeed
Otherwise sorry
Everything i sacrificed
I'm crawling with you
Sixty floors
There is hard work without credit
Do I still use the fuck?
No need to
sister
Actually I think
You don't have to be so fierce
This first
You are useless
I just do
Second one
in fact
I have seen you through
How about you
Serenity
Actually, my heart is quite gentle
Ten nine eight seven six
five four three two one
I declare
The call is officially online
Good good good
Some people say me
Can't make this website
impossible
In such a short time
Make this website live
But at this moment
All doubts
All become miracles
And the creator of this miracle
It's me Li Siyu
This first glass of wine
I respect myself
Good good good
This miracle does not only belong to me
Belongs to you too
My staff
My franchisee
You are my partner
Also my comrade in arms
Without you
I'm lonely
Nowadays
We are all creators of miracles
This second glass of wine
I respect you
it is good
Come on, OK
This way
It's really tough
but
With sincere unity
Work hard
The spirit of win-win cooperation
Finally have today
And i believe
As long as we continue to unite
Work hard, win-win cooperation
We can not only create a
The beginning of the miracle
Can create one more
Glorious future
This third glass of wine
We respect the future together
Respect the future
Come i come i come i come
Drink less
You can drink a little
Okay okay
Mr. Li, Lao Bai
congratulations
Old white old white
Today's big day
Let's drink one
it is good
Mr. Li, let's toast you
Let me drink let me drink
We respect Mr. Li
What are you drinking?
I always make my sister angry
I must drink it for her
Yes ok
President Pan Siyu congratulations
Mr. Pan Mr. Pan Mr. Pan
I know you have been taking care of Mr. Li
I'll have a drink for her
You go
This is the home court between me and Mr. Pan
Good start
But the next line fell to the ground
It's a tough battle
How many outlets are there now
Fifteen have been built now
The plan is within three months
Build fifty more
All franchisees
Yes
Plan to launch several cities this year
How many points
The plan is three cities
One hundred points
not enough
At least twenty cities
Eight hundred points
I'm afraid of running too fast
It will cause problems
Siyu
You call
Although very distinctive
but
It is still different from Lubao
It has no core technology
Easily copied
If you don't run fast enough
Overtaken by others
Then the market is not yours
But now the funds are not enough
Emerald can be added
Just waiting for your words
Li Siyu
As an investor
Green treasure also needs your performance
President Pan, don't worry
I won't shame you when I call
Ok
I believe you
liqueur
coming
Guan Xiaotang
Who asked you to change me grape juice
Give me really
Child immature
After that
Every dream is realized
We will then
Light a firework to celebrate
it is good
Mr. Pan, look
Within three years
Must be listed on incoming call
Ok
I believe you
She really has this ability
Manager Li
We all look forward to that day
Come soon
Wait for that day
I must be with all my friends
Share the dividends of the Internet together
I promise
OK, then it's a deal
Goodbye
Drink less
Let's go back
Go back to rest today
Come back tomorrow
This battle was fought beautifully
Broke up
Why haven't you left yet
Thank you today
what happened to you
I kindly pour you grape juice
Let you drink less
Why are you talking about me
Happy today
If you are happy
Take medicine
Why did you suddenly become sensible today
I learn it from you
Have a bad temper
Also learned from you
Sister Li
I really can't drink like that
Guan Xiaotang
thank you
Don't thank me verbally
If you want to thank me
You can pay me a little bit
Why are you always making money?
Because i am poor
Xiao Tang
Trust me
I will for sure
Take all of you
achive dreams
It doesn't matter if I dream or not
But ah
Let's not just ninety-nine six
Do not worry
From now on we are zero and seven
Li Siyu, I want to resign
Only after the call is listed
Isn't it
Go back to bed after finishing packing
Have to continue fighting tomorrow
Isn't it
Slow down
Ok
Look good
Siyu
The day you succeeded
I will stand at the forefront for you
Cheering and applauding
you must
Looking for a wife who treats you well
for sure
Wait for me
Sign for it
Taobao bought
Ok
how much did you spend
Two hundred yuan
Free shipping?
Yes
Seven days no reason to return the seller
Send me the link
Just our gallery
Can be used at the reception next month
Are you not moved at all
If you put these
All changed to diamonds
I was moved
You are as real as always
You are still as always
vulgar
Let's go, please supper
I want to break with you
After eating
The preliminary layout is basically completed
The next step is to implement
No problem, let go
it is good
President Wang
The people at the aquarium shop are here
Hard work
Still in the original position
Be careful, be careful that door
This fish tank is big enough
When these fish were first bought
It’s only twenty or thirty centimeters long
It's all this big now
Have to give them
Change to a bigger tank
The fish tank before that
Just scrap it
No way
Big fish
Raising small fish in a small tank
Have to be suitable
These big fish
Also need more space to swim
This little tank
There will be new fish
Right
Yiming
I want to buy something recently
Can you accompany me
I think
Your taste, your aesthetic
All pretty good
Can you give me some advice
I'm ok
I do not have
You don't want to
Yes yes
I'll make an appointment with you
it is good
Then go ahead
OK, I'll go out first
Ok
Mr
Please fill in the customer information
Sir your painting
Mr
Can i help you
This meets the Munsell color scale
Thank you
Is he sick
I think he wants to pick you up
how you said that
He asked me just now
What's your name
Hello there
Ask your colleague
What is your name
Her name is Gu Xiaoling
Married
not yet
What happened to her feet
Sprained
What did he buy
untitled
Price forty-eight thousand
The one by Agnes Martin
Ok
Is he registered as a member?
registered
I asked again
But your qualifications
It's too bad
People are very embarrassed
Finally there is a place willing to accept you
And if you work hard
Is a chance to challenge the high salary
I go
Sales
I know where are you and Mr. Yuan
Used to be somewhat contradictory
More than a contradiction
President Yuan has made it clear
She can accept you
But in public for private
I remind you
If you decide to go
Be prepared to be tortured
Then you go or not
let me see
Thank you Mr. Hu
Zhang Zhizhi
Have you seen Li Siyu more recently?
not much
I heard she opened one called
Call
Lao Pan still uses the lowest price
Gave her a batch of batteries
I don't know that
You say Li Siyu
If Old Pan doesn't support her,
In her life
What can be done
President Yuan, I still have something
I'm leaving
and many more
I heard you want to change departments
Ok
My sales department
Welcome
I'm afraid I don't have this ability
up to you
Hey
what