[To Dear Myself]
[Ep14]
Go
Today is great
Yes
The most important thing is to be happy
Being rich comes second
Be happy
Xiaoling
I want to discuss something with you
What?
Be my girlfriend
I promise you
I will be a successful man
Ok?
Lei Haowen
I see you as brother
You...
You even habor this clever idea
No
What's wrong?
Give you...
But I don't want to be your brother
Then you are nothing
Nothing else?
You can be my BFF
All right...
Ok, BFF
Be careful
My shoes
Raise your arms
One, two, again
One, one, two
Two, one, two
Raise arms
One, two, one, two
I'm sorry
Ok  -Take a break
When do you get here?
Just now
As I know, you have dinner with president Wang tonight
I come here after the dinner
I feel confused after sister Ziru talks to me today
But sister Ziru also encourages me
So I am here
Really?
Yiming
I won't leave Shanghai
Why?
First
My competition with sister Yuan is not over yet
Second
Even if I lose and leave Lubao
I won't leave Shanghai either
Yiming
Don't go
We should stick together
I need to get changed
Traffic jam again
Traffic jams everywhere in this city
High house prices, high cost of living
We can't save money
The air is not good
That's not all
It's hard to succeed
Easy to fail
But we have chances here
Siyu
Now I have a good chance
We study hard and get admitted to the college
We go to the good colleges
All we want is to go to a place good for our development
And want to see the world, right?
We get the hang of it here
Why should we go back now?
You think we get hang of it
It's nothing in this city
We have worked hard here for seven years
The money, status and resources we have can't stand consumption
Yiming
What you are going through now is just temporary
It will be the past
Our past superiority is temporary
If you have some problem in life,
we won't buy the house for the time being
We have enough income to live here
Siyu
It's not true that I can't live in Shanghai
I just have no self-confidence here
If I still stay here, I am afraid I will lose the last bit of dignity
Not so serious, right?
You know why I don't go to president Guo's company?
Because I'm stingy
I am narrow-minded
I am skeptical
Why do I become like this?
Because I feel inferior
I'm afraid of losing you
I really hate
I hate becoming like this
But if I still stay in Shanghai like this,
I will hate myself so much
But if you have to leave, we will be separated
Yiming
Stay
Siyu
Go with me
The car is here
Let me walk you there
Just this one
Come
Is that you?
Correct
Driver, be careful
Ok, no problem
Yiming
Stay
Siyu
Go with me
Morning, sister Siyu
Morning
Lin Ling
Sister Siyu
Where are they?
They say, we will lose
And you won't come
So they are having a holiday
Why you are still here?
I know you won't surrender so easily
Tell them
We will have a meeting immediately
Ok
Sister Siyu is back
Everyone, come back for meeting
Hurry...
Liu Xiaojia
You think we are destined to lose?
And you give yourself a holiday?
You don't contact the clients
And you just forget the contract
No
Let me tell you
We can't give up until we meet the deadline
Before that, we still have a chance
But...
But what?
You think they lead us by more than 20 million
So we will lose to them right?
No
Yes, I think so, too
We still can't give up so easily
We can lose this round
But we just can't give up on ourselves
Correct
We need to persist, can't give up
Did you persist?
Did you give up?
Yeah
You think it's persistence when you make 30 calls every day?
I can tell you
You make 30 calls today
35 calls tomorrow
40 the day after tomorrow
That's persistence
Cheer up
Sister Siyu, don't worry
We are in high spirits now
High spirits
Siyu, come out
What happened?
Yuan Huizhong pockets our company's
battery of over 5 million in collusion
It can't be
Who did she collude with?
As I know, it's Meiyi Group
Meiyi Group?
President Pan asked legal department to investigate this
They say, business license, offices, official website
and news links
They are all fake
What?
The battery of over 4 million is my responsibility
According to company regulations
I will accept all the punishment
But I really didn't betray the company
In front of me and Pan Zhiyong
you said, you knew each other
I...
I just said it causally
I also believed your words
I am your side witness
Legal department has called the police
They are investigating this
I went to Meiyi Group's office
I also met the director of the office
Did you lose anything?
The order belonged to Lin Ling
But sister Yuan took it
She deserves it
But sister Yuan is also a victim
No
As I know she knows the fraud for many years
So she colluded with him
No
Sister Yuan doesn't know the fraud
Liu Jie can testify
I saw the fraud for the first time on that day
Liu Jie is in your team
Will anyone believe what she says?
Li Siyu and Lin Ling were there, too
Will they speak for you?
Where are you going?
I need to see preisdent Pan
I need to explain this
You want to help her?
You forgot what she did to you?
But she is innocent
She scapegoated you enough
Don't be stupid
The company has rules
If she is deceived,
Four million
she just needs to pay 400,000
But if she colludes with others at the company's expense
she will be fired
But sister Yuan didn't collude with others at company's expense
She just made a mistake
As I know, president Pan is sure
she acts in cahoots with the frauds
And he wants to fire her
Fang Zhan has been monitoring there
They have quarreled many times
If you come out, you will invite troubles for President Pan
They grabbed my order
In the end, they invited a disaster for themselves
So great
Lin Ling
When you contacted director Luo,
did you find something strange?
Director Luo is a little weird
Why?
He often disappears
He likes bragging
So Liu Jie gave up after talking to him twice
How did he negotiate the contract with you?
He doesn't care much about the price
But the only requirement is
after paying the deposit
we need to ship all batteries
Our project has a tight schedule
So we don't have time to urge the shippment
How about this?
After I pay the deposit,
you should send me the batteries
Within this week
I will give you the rest money
Ok?
I'm afraid I can't
I remember manager Li Siyu wants to talk to you
I don't know if she has the final say
Director Luo
How about this?
You need to pay 20% advance payment
I will cooperate with you on the subsequent payment method
But I have a condition
We need to sign the contract now
Ok, no problem
No wonder
Sister Yuan signed a contract with him immediately
With a good price
I think, sister Yuan made concessions on the shipping method
We were so close
Lin Ling
Do you think we should prove sister Yuan's innocence?
Why?
President Pan is sure sister Yuan colluded with director Luo
He wants to fire her
But we know they don't know each other
Sister Siyu
You should go without me, anyway
Lin Ling
Don't forget what they did to us
Go back
She deserves it
You want to see me?
President Pan
I want to see you, too
Come in
Sit
You know what happened to Yuan Huizhong, right?
Yes
So she can't stay in our company now
So I will leave the government project
and sales department to you
Me?
Yes, you
You should get prepared to take charge of sales department
President Pan
How will you punish sister Yuan?
She benefits at our expense
She will be fired
No one can change it
So you should get yourself prepared
Why do you want to see me?
No
Sister Siyu
Come in
Why close the door?
Sister Siyu
What happened?
Tomorrow, they will announce, you are the sales director
Who told you that?
The whole office knows this
You know what, sister...
Kuaizi looks down on me
He called me sister Jia just now
He is older than you, right?
My boss defeats his boss
And more than that, sister
Huang Bibo and others are very worried
if you will fire them after you become sales director
Zhang Ziting, Liu Jie and others are looking for a new job
Why do this?
You win this time
If they win, we will lose jobs
Sister Siyu
I think we should celebrate it in advance
Not even close
Celebrate what?
Tell everyone
Stop the rumors
Anything else?
Back to work now
Ten o'clock tomorrow morning
We will talk about the punishment for you
Testimony of Li Siyu and Lin Ling is vital
Li Siyu
We are like The Snake and the Farmer
I will be the sales director
What are you thinking about?
Go to supervision department immediately
Or go to see president Pan
Tell him what you know
Or go directly to see sister Yuan
Tell her you can prove her innocence
It's not good for me
But you should do so
If I do this,
sister Yuan can stay in the company
If she stays in the company, she will bid on behalf of Lubao
If she wins the bid, she will be the sales director
What about me?
I have to leave Lubao
So be it
What are you afraid of?
You can go to other companies
Or we can go back to my hometown together
You will be the sales director in Zhu Xiaobai's company
You just want me to leave here and go back with you
Li Siyu
This is your opinion of me?
Then why do you tell me to do this?
Because it's a right thing to do
It's not just about right or wrong
I know things are complicated
But you can be very simple
What?
It's about my future
It's even about my subordinates' future
It's about president Pan
It's even about Lubao
Let me tell you this, it's best that sister Yuan leaves
But she can't leave like this
She wants me to leave like this
You should win her, fair and square
It's the way you are
Sister Yuan's call
For yourself
You have to do this
I have to?
Sister Yuan
Rumor has it that I am in collusion with the fraud
You said it yourself
But you know it's not true
Ten o'clock tomorrow morning
They discuss whether to fire me?
Siyu
You need to prove my innocence
I can't be fired
I can't be fired because of this kind of thing
Siyu
Help me
I can help you explain the truth
But you have to give me the truth
What?
I filed the government bid first
Not you
I can do anything for you
Except this
Why?
It's my sales performance
Who gets the bid will win
Not entirely
What you want is not sales performance
You want to be the sales director?
Whatever you think
I just want to take whatever belongs to me
I ask you to prove my innocence, because I want to stay in Lubao
So I could become the sales director
If you bargain with me, what's the point of it that I stay in Lubao?
At least we have justice
Let me tell you what justice is
I sacrificed so much, so I should be the sales director
This is justice
What about my justice?
You took my clients one by one
Where is my justice?
You shouldn't be against me
That's because you forced me
Will you help me tomorrow?
If you help me, let bygones be bygones
Give the government bid back to me
Li Siyu
Ask you one last time
Will you help me?
Give the government bid back to me
How's it?
If you give her the bid,
you won't be the sales director
But after tomorrow's meeting
I will leave Lubao, till then I have no chance
Who said that?
The result of tomorrow's meeting is to be determined
Brother
I can't stay in Lubao anymore
Don't worry
You have me
Come in
Sister Siyu
When will we go?
Eleven o'clock
Ok
Hello, sister Siyu
Zhizhi
Ten o'clock meeting
In which meeting room?
Wait a moment
10 o'clock
Conference Room 1
I get it
You really want to go?
Lin Ling, what's wrong with you?
What's up with her?
I am writing a resignation letter
Why resign?
I worked overtime last night
Vice president Fang talked to me
Sorry
I can't help sister Yuan
Lin Ling
I didn't tell you to lie
You just need to tell the truth
If Yuan Huizhong leaves because of this
won't you feel guilty?
Vice president Fang
I am sister Siyu's subordinate
I will do and say as sister Siyu says
Lin Ling
I know, you know the fraud
You will be the first to be held accountable
Vice president Fang
I don't know what you are talking about
Don't forget
I'm the vice president of the company
You think she can cover you up?
So you resign?
I will never speak for them
I know they will retaliate
Feiyu battery tried to poach me days ago
I didn't plan to go
But now it's my way out
How's your resignation letter?
I just begin it
You will bow to them?
I will not bow
You don't have to resign
Fang doesn't have the final say
Ok
Xiao Tian
Go
Go to see the client with me
We should leave at 11 o'clock
I changed my mind
What are you doing?
I will send these back with express delivery
So I am packing up
You still go?
Yeah
I promised Zhu Xiaobai
I will go to work within half a month
What's the end to sister Yuan?
I did not say anything
Why?
Because she doesn't deserve it
You do that for yourself not for her
I know
You hope me to be kind and righteous
But what have I got?
I got her suspicion and scapegoat with my kindness
In the end, I got nothing
But at least you have a clear conscience
What's the use of it?
I would have been kicked out without president Pan
So you want to answer blows with blows?
I didn't harm her
I just keep silent
But it's a disgraceful win
As long as I am the final winner, it's a big victory
Victory is so important?
If victory is not important, why do you leave Shanghai?
Because in Shanghai, you think you are a loser
You lost all your confidence
Sorry
Yiming
I don't think you are a loser
I don't have the right to tell you what to do
You are disappointed in me?
I am disappointed in myself
Just go back if you want
So we...
Long distance relationship
Long distance relationship?
I won't leave you anyway
Zhizhi
I don't want to go
You must go
You just go with Yuwei
We must attend the party together
It's attitude
It shows we attach great importance to kid's education
It also shows the respect of the party organizer
But I am so sick of Miaomiao's face
That was before
We have a good relationship now
I need to work
Why give me that look?
You are almost beyond recognition
How do I look?
Great
Mom looks great
Let's go
Come
Let's go play there
Easy
Welcome
You guys, be careful
Miaomiao, Linda
Let's go play there
Be careful
Xingxing's mom
You are here
Where's Xingxing's dad?
He...
He is chatting with William's dad
They are alumni of Ivy League
Yuwei's dad
You graduate from American college?
Which one?
Xingxing's dad is looking for you, right?
No, never mind him
You get your undergraduate and master's degrees in U.S.?
Actually...
Acutally it's the obscure colleges
It's so hard to mention in front of Xingxing's dad
They say my party is much classier than Vivian's sorority
What Vivian?
You know Vivian?
What?
She comes from a rural family
No way
All here
Come
So pretty
Yuwei's dad is here too
Hello
Yuwei's dad
You work in Guangcai Engineering Construction company, right?
Yes
You know Wang Changhai, right?
Yes, he is the director of our department
You are a director, right?
Yes
Really?
Let me tell you
Wang Changhai's wife is my classmate
We often have a party together
You can come if you have the time
Ok
Linda's mom
What do you think of my party?
Awesome  -Really?
Perfect
Look at those kids
They are so happy
Yes, they all like it very much
Yes...  -Great
Well, let me introduce you some friends
Some French designers are here
They can design some nice clothes for you  -Really?
Great
Yes, go
Come...  Go
Hurry...
Come. Go