[To Dear Myself]
[Ep4]
Come in
Sister
Here's team A's list
Huang Bibo, Kuaizi, Afu
Zhou Zhiyu, Yang Tian
And Zhang Jiaqi
I get it
As I know, after we went out today
sister Yuan talked to them in office one by one
And she let them sign to follow her
Really?
So now except you
top ten salesmen go to her team
Show me that
Sister, she did this on purpose?
Please come in
Sister Yuan
You can go out now
Close the door
Ok
Anything wrong?
You deliberately lured me away
Then you talked them into choosing you
rather than me one by one
What are you talking about?
Who am I?
Did I say anything wrong?
You think I need to do so?
How's the trip?
The contract
Siyu
You have said, you wouldn't compete with me, right?
Yes
Why do you care who select me rather than you?
How about this?
This commission will be yours
Ok?
Liu Yang
Time to eat
Time to eat, stop playing
I am running late
I won't eat now
Just put it here after eating
I will wash after I come back
Where are you going now?
I told you yesterday
I need to attend the meeting with Miaomiao's mom
What about Yuwei after you attend meeting?
You are here
I need to work
I am working, too
Goodbye mom
Bye, baby
That's all
Ok
Thank you
You said, your boyfriend would come too
Why he is not here?
Maybe he is on the way
Xiaoling wanted to come, too
But it's her night shift
She wants me to tell you
She is so sorry for the trouble
I'm sorry, too
It's ok
President Wang
Sorry for the lateness
It's ok
Sorry
I hurried but I am still late
Sister Ziru, thank you
I am so grateful for your proposal
It's a little case
It's our fault
But we can't let you pay the price for us
So I will pay the money
Yes, Ms. Wang
Thank you for your kindness
I hope you can accept the money
I can't
Sister Ziru
I can't use it even if I accept it
All the procedures are done
We can't change it now
Please accept it
So we could feel better
You can't make yourselves better by making troubles for me, right?
Sister Ziru
We will owe you a big debt
It's ok
Maybe in the future I need your help
You can pay me back then
Ok
Ms. Wang, thank you
Just tell us anytime you need help
Sister Ziru, thank you
Siyu, are you busy lately?
Very busy
As busy as bee
Great
So your industry is prosperous
Just because it's not prosperous
We have much pressure now
Yiming
What do you do?
Planning director
An interesting industry
It's ok
In which company?
Just a small company
Not small, Caijin company
Highly ranked in the industry
As I remember last year
the market value is 800 million
Almost
Thanks to his planning last year
his company's market value increased by two billion
No, I can't take all the credit
Young and promising
He is the youngest planning director in the history of his company
Stop it, ok?
It's true
Excuse me
President Pan
Let me ask you
What's going on with your team?
They made the choice
What are you thinking about?
I...
Thank you
I think nothing
Li Siyu
You have no confidence in Lubao right?
What happened?
You are scolded again?
He is so tough
What's wrong?
This way please
Not many people today
Yes
Let me show you
I ordered a pink diamond
Not many people today
Come, hurry up
I don't like today's weather
It's cloudy
A good view here
Yes, I ordered here specially
Next to the window
Great
Yes
I booked in advance
Check the list out
What drinks do you want?
How about wine?
My driver didn't come with me today
I drove by myself
I also drove myself
So drink wine next time
Give you some alcohol-free drinks
No need
Juice is great
So who will draw up the plan this time?
You recommend...
Fruit juice
Fresh juice
Alcohol-free?
I can
You?
Really?
Ok
They recommend this
Ok...
Ok, just order that
Ok
When I was CEO in a foreign company
I hated the calls at the meeting most
Yuwei's mom, what do you want to drink?
I want this one
A soda
If I compete with sister Yuan hard,
I will feel sorry for her
Otherwise I will feel sorry for president Pan
Also sorry for myself
I don't know what to do now
Why does it become like this in the end?
Things all changed after I came back from Ningbo
So you don't need to make a decision so soon
Time and tide wait for no man
I usually decide with coins
Do you have coins?
No
I have one here
Let's make a deal
If the pattern is up
you need to compete for the director
If the number is up, you will give up
Ok
It's the destiny
No, Siyu
I am not trying to tell you what to do with this game
I want to let you know what you really want
When you see the number is up
you are so disappointed
It means you don't want to give up at all
Yes
If I were you, I would follow my heart
Yuwei's mom
Can you give me your plan tomorrow?
Ok
We will discuss about it tomorrow night
Ok  -The same place and time, ok?
Ok
That's all for today
Waiter, settle the bill
Hello, 1935 yuan
Ok
Send it to the group, and we will tranfer the money
I have transferred the money
So cold
Yes
Your clothes looks pretty when the wind blows
Really? I like it
You didn't drive, Yuwei's mom?
I didn't drive today
I ate too much
I'll take a taxi after walking
Ok, bye
Ok, goodbye  -Bye
Bye...
Wait
Ok, bye
Bye bye
Bye
Bye, Yuwei's mom, see you tomorrow
Bye bye
See you tomorrow
Liu Yang, just called me
What?
Goodbye
Goodbye, president Wang
I think sister Ziru knows me well
So you will compete against her?
I need to think about it
Who?
No, it's a spam message
Spam message
Why are you laughing so happily?
No
I'm worried
What are you worried about?
I am worried about you
I don't know what's going on between you and sister Yuan
No one told me
I said it, it's unexpected
And that afternoon I called you
you threw the tantrum
When did I throw the tantrum?
Did I?
You should tell me before you go to Ningbo, right?
Otherwise if friends ask me where you are
what should I answer them?
If I say I don't know,
what's our relationship?
Ok...
You have so many things to do and worry about every day
I don't want to disturb you
Let me tell you
I don't mind other things
but you must disturb me with love
Next time do tell me if you go far
How far is it?
As long as house price within 30,000 per square meter
So I need to ask the house price before I go anywhere
So troublesome
That's exactly what I mean
I need to think about it
How's it?
Anti-allergic treatment works
We still need observation
If she has no other symptoms in 1 hour,
you can go home
Thank you, doctor
She is so allergic
You can buy her an EpiPen
It can save her life in emergency
I will find one EpiPen for you
Ok, thank you
What happened?
She wanted to drink milk
I told her to get it herself
But she took chocolate
I prepare the chocolate for you in case you work late
It contains peanuts
I hide it very inside the refrigerator deliberately
I don't know
Why don't you keep a good eye on her?
How can she open the refrigerator by herself?
Why didn't you keep a good eye on her?
I was engaged
Engaged?
Gosh
You talk to mom
What?
Hello
Yang
Mom
I sent you another pack of medicine
Did you receive it?
Yes
Did you finish the medicine I sent last time?
Yeah
So go on taking the medicine
I get it
It can warm the uterus
The medicine is very effective for Li Sanwa's wife
They have twin sons now
Mom, Zhizhi is next to me
You can talk to her
Mom
How's it? Any movement?
What movement?
You didn't boil the medicine in the right way?
Or, I can go to boil it for you personally?
No need, mom
We can do it ourselves
Ok
I will wait for your good news
Mom wants to come here?
Don't let her come
Otherwise we will be in trouble
Why does your mom urge us to have second child?
All the neighbors have given birth
And they are boys
She is jealous and eager
What do you think of it?
Second child?
I will go crazy
It's so hard for us to support Yuwei
So next time if your mom talks about this again
you should make it clear
It's impossible for me to changer her mind
Flowers for you, do you like it?
Yes
May I ask, which friend sends this?
Sir, your coffee
Thank you
You're welcome
As I know, you broke up with Lanke
Who told you?
Someone saw him go shopping with a new girlfriend
I dumped him
Why?
He is so clingy
I can't stand it
Really?
If you don't believe me, you can ask him
Who sends you flowers every day?
So mysterious
I don't know. So annoying
Really?
Latest policy
It will go into force on the 1st of next month
What policy?
The company is so damn poor
Gosh
Even sell group purchase
120 ice cream balls and two cups of coffee with 159 yuan
Yes
Now everyone can come in
It's a membership that costs half a million yuan
Now they can play for half a day with 159 yuan
What a fall in price
We will fall in price as well
I should prepare myself for MBA study
What can you learn with your competency?
At least it can help me elevate myself
Hello, waitress
Yes
Be careful
Ok
Go
A team leader, now you have so many things
Printer, paper shredder
All the tools you need
By the way, sister Siyu
Yuwei's class will hold a party
The theme is I love mom
I drew up the planning
But I am not satisfied with it
Can you help me?
You should ask Yiming for help
It's his forte
I can help you transfer your plan to him
Ok, I'll transfer it to you right away
Sorry
Lin Ling
From your sales department
I know
I guess, she just finished the resignation procedure
She is so miserable
Her dad was found lung cancer for not long
She needs money now
How do you know?
She asked me about the medical insurance days ago
Now it's difficult to find a job
Lin Ling
You want to join my team, right?
Yes, but...
Go to tell Liu Xiaojia
You are joining my team now
Sister Siyu
You will offend sister Yuan
None of her business
Yes
Hello
I am here for an interview today
What is your name?
Chen Yiming
Take a break here
Ok, thank you
Hello
What? She took Lin Ling in?
Yeah
She was going through the resignation procedures
But she stopped it
Sister Yuan
She hired the one you fired
What does she want?
We fire her, why do you keep her stay?
I want to help her
So you are doing something good
Correct
You can give her money yourself
You let the company pay her the basic salary
What is this?
You help her at the company's expense?
President Pan
I have told HR department
I will pay Lin Ling's basic salary
Three months
Her sales performance is zero
What does this mean?
It means she is not suitable for this work
Not suitable for the company
Do you know?
I have read her work log
She worked very hard for these three months
She just lacks some method and luck
Give her another three months
She will make progress
Impossible
Why?
I am preparing for equity financing
Sales revenue in the next three months will
determine the company's valuation
So I don't have time for you to train her
I need data
The rising data
The data that brings capital confidence
Only one month
Let her stay if she signs an order
Otherwise I will fire her
I know you are very compassionate
But the company cares only about interests
Compassion has no place in the company
I know
But I can't...
Li Siyu
Sometimes the blind kindness is very irresponsible
for others, for ourselves
for the company and for the overall situation
I get it, president Pan
Chen Yiming
Sister Siyu
This is the party's plan
When do you need it?
Tonight
Moms group will discuss about it
Then we will split up according to the plan
I'll contact Yiming right away
You are born in 1980s?
Yes
Don't underestimate me just because of my age
Actually I have 10-year experience
No...
Our company products are for post-90s
You are a bit old for us
So you think thirties are old?
If you are mentally young, we can consider
You have good Wemedia's resources
Yes, I am one of those who recognize the power of Wemedia
Wemedia is outdated
Now it's convergence media's world
You are right
The number you have dialed is busy now
No one answered?
What should I do?
I promised Miaomiao's mom
I would give her the plan today
Miaomiao's mom values time
A woman of principles
If I can't give her a plan, she will be angry
Don't worry, I will go to see him
You designed Caijin's Qingyun plan?
Yes, it's me
Last year our company analyzed Qingyun plan
Really?
I think if I have another chance, I can do it better now
Yes, the foundation is very good
But the planning is not good enough
If the planning team can do it,
Caijin company can increase market value by 500 million
Thank you
Zhang Shengyun
I called you but you didn't answer
You also didn't reply my message
I need to see you, it's urgent
I am on the way to your company now
Hello, Yiming
Siyu, where are you now?
I am parking downstairs in your company
Don't go up
I am not in the company now
Where are you?
I am talking with the client
Ok, I'll go to meet you there
Waiter
Wait a moment
Siyu, here
Why are you alone?
Where is the client?
He just left
Waitress
Clean it up
Come
What's the matter?
Help Zhizhi with the plan
Finish it before you get off work
So anxious?
Yes, so I came here
No
I have two meetings in the afternoon
I also have an appointment with a client
Finish this first
It's about Yuwei's status in the kindergarten
It's about Yuwei's social circle
It's about Yuwei's future
You have exaggerated
Zhizhi told me so
Ok...
Ok, I will do this first
What to drink?
No
What's wrong?  A bad mood?
I was impulsive today
I kept an intern that company fired
Why?
Her dad has lung cancer
My mom died of lung cancer
I can understand
But everyone
including president Pan
They think I am wrong
Because the company only cares about the interests
It doesn't care about compassion
Am I wrong?
We are human beings, we have feelings
But the company only cares about interests
Siyu
Do you know where you attracts me most?
My beauty is unparalleled
It's your kindness
I think your kindness conquers all the interests
Thank you Yiming
I know what to do
If she can't work in Lubao
can you find a job for her in your company?
Well, I...
I am afraid I can't
You always complain that you are understaffed, right?
You may not know what's going on
Our company is downsizing greatly this year
Your company developed so well last year, right?
It's last year
It's changed now
I get it
Siyu
If I am fired...
Impossible
No matter how difficult the market is
neither of us will be laid off
So weird
Who? Me?
No, I think you are so weird
How long will this class take?
It starts tomorrow afternoon
Hello
Are you interested in this major?
What's your requirement of the art appreciation
and art institution management?
Do you have a drawing basic?
Yes
Did you bring the works?
Look at my face
I painted it myself
How is your foreign language?
French and Italian
Louis Vuitton, Chanel
Hermes, Prada
Enough...
Xiaoling
Hello
Where are you going? Let me give you a ride
No thanks
This is downtown
It's hard to grab a taxi
It's windy, get in
After you left last time
actually I tried a lot of opportunities
to make an appointment with you
I asked Yiming for many times
My brother is so unreliable
He doesn't help me at all
I didn't expect I would see you again
in the vast crowd on the street
What a serendipity
I have to cherish it
Let's play a game
Ok
The game is Who Talks First Loses
From now on, we will keep mouth shut
Who speaks first will lose
The loser will invite the winner to dinner
Let's start
Xiaoling
You are more beautiful than last time
I lost...
Punish me...
Tomorrow, the day after tomorrow
You can choose the place
The named called Lei is Chen Yiming's good friend?
Actually I have no opportunity
Yes
to introduce myself formally
I will help him
My name is Lei Haowen
L-E-I
H-A-O
W-E-I
You had a little misunderstanding about me last time
What?
The sports car belonged to you last time?
Not mine
It belongs to my nanny
What about this one?
Don't underestimate this car
The price is only 300, 000
I earned it in my college with my part-time wages
So I drive it often
For the reminiscence of my youth
I am a rich son
But I have no vices
I can see it
Really?
You know, what's the biggest vice of a rich son?
It's his richness
And you don't have
If you want to judge a man by richness
the behavior is so superficial
You mean I am so superficial
No...
I didn't mean that
You are right
I'm superficial
People all have shortcomings
I don't think it's a shortcoming
If a girl is vain and mammonish
she will lose a lot of precious things
For example
She will lose a potential, attractive and powerful man
I think with my vulgarity and vanity
I don't deserve an attractive, potential and powerful man
No
You deserve one
Gosh
What's wrong?
Pull over, I have arrived
You want to go to the subway entrance, right?
I can't take it anymore
I feel sick
Carsick?
Sick of you
What are you talking about?
Gu Xiaoling
What do you mean?
I beg you don't say hello to me when you see me next time
You can't hurt my feelings just because you are beautiful
It's my legitimate defense
Serve you right
Who says hello to you will be doomed to be a bachelor forever