[To Dear Myself]
[Ep2]
Sister Yuan
Siyu
Thank you for yesterday
It's ok
It's ok for this quarter, right?
Still not enough
Why?
Not everyone is like you
Let me think, if I can win more orders
Forget it
You have worked for two weeks
Whatever
No way
Here comes the moment whether you will be the director
We can't give up
What's wrong?
My stomach aches recently
Come to my office
Ok, after I leave my bag in my office
Morning, sister Siyu
Morning
Here
I haven't finished those you gave me last time
Keep it just in case
You should pay attention to your stomach
Thank you
Get an invoice
I will get an extra 500 yuan of invoice
It's the reward of your overtime work
I should claim overtime pay
500 yuan for the normal procedure?
Ok
I will tell president Fang
Just need a signature
Go
It's ok, bye
Sister Siyu
Did brother Yiming make the proposal to you?
He wanted to
But I stopped him
Why?
I do not know either
You have other plans?
No
Chen Yiming is the only one I want to marry in my life
Why are you hesitating?
You have been dating for five years
Four years and five months
You should get married
Liu Yang and I get married after we know each other for half a year
Zhizhi
Do you miss being single before you marry Liu Yang
No
I was impatient to marry him
But I...
I am happy when I am with him
But when I think of being his wife and a mom after marriage
I feel flurried
Do you think too much?
Perhaps
Siyu
You are here
You want to see me?
President Pan wants to see you
Go to his office
Come... Gather here
What happened?
As I know, their department laid off some staff
Again?
So will next time be our turn?
Likely
Yes
If it goes on like this, we...
What are you playing at?
Boss
Administration department laid off another three today
Do not worry
It won't happen to us
Boss
Strategy department laid off two, too
Yes
Their departments are overstaffed
Of course, they will lay off some staff
Our planning department is understaffed
What are you afraid of?
Yeah
Back to work
I need Mid-autumn festival plan
the quote of We-Media
and the responses from the advertising company now
Come...
Thank you
What?
After we left yesterday
did you make the proposal?
No
It's a late night
It's so romantic and so suitable for marriage proposal
Yeah
Then why don't you take action?
Maybe not ready
It's you or her?
Neither of us
Girls need the sense of security, perhaps
She lacks sense of security?
Yeah
You are a young and handsome talent
You will be a good option for husband
If I were a girl, I would like to marry you
Stop it
You are not here to ask me if I make the proposal, right?
Of course not
Say it
Help me make an appointment with Gu Xiaoling
What are you doing?
You have Gu Xiaoling's WeChat, right?
She blacklisted me
So fast
I need your help
Sorry I can't
Why?
She blacklisted you
It means she has no interest in you
I have a strong interest in her
Gu Xiaoling's desire has a large property
Maybe she can find the precious true love from me
Wake up
Or, her back-up
You are not qualified
A just-in-case?
Why are you such an asshole?
That's the way I am
Now all of them are worried of being fired
Why are you still thinking about this?
What am I afraid of?
I am a rich son
When do you become a rich son?
My father's name has a rich
What happened?
Come to HR department
I need to go to HR now
Make an appointment for me
Piss off
Help me
I have something to tell you
Xingdian shut down yesterday
Why?
Insufficient orders, and financial crisis
Our sales have been declining
If it goes on like this, it's our turn to shut down
So what's the problem of the sales department?
Maybe...
We haven't mobilized their enthusiasm
How to mobilize their enthusiasm?
President Pan
I need to think it over before I answer you
I have already thought about it
I will split sales department into two
You and Yuan Huizhong will lead a team separately
Three months later
Which team has a better sales performance
Remember, sales performance
The team leader will be the director of sales department
I?
You...
Team leader?
Not just the leader
I hope you will become the director
Compete with sister Yuan?
Is that ok?
What's wrong with it?
I have worked here for seven years
Sister Yuan has worked here for more than ten years
Our company won't care about the seniority
But...
I know
You are good friends
But remember
If companies has good relationship regardless of competition
all of us will be screwed sooner or later
Does sister Yuan know this?
She will accept
Li Siyu
Why do you work here?
Just for a job?
Or you want a platform to prove yourself?
Now this is the platform for you
The rest is up to you
President Pan
I need to think about it
Siyu
President Fang
President Pan is in there, right?
Yes
Ok
Our department has only 8 people
You want to lay off them?
This is the decision of the board
Every department of the company needs to be cut off by a half
The one-size-fits-all approach is so irrational
But it works
Yes
You should downsize overstaffed departments
But my department is understaffed
If we don't downsize, our company will collapse
Well, give me the list before you get off work today
No
Manager Chen
I hired them in
They have worked with me for so many years
They are underpaid
I feel so sorry for them
Now you want me to fire them
No way
I can't do this
Don't be emotional
We are human beings with emotions
But companies only care about benefits
Ok
If you insist, I will resign
I can give you the resignation letter this afternoon
You can give me now
Ziting, where's sister Yuan?
She went to see the client
So much?
A robbery
How can I get so much money?
No insurance?
I asked them, Lanke's car has no car insurance
Asshole
Don't tell Yiming about this
Why?
It's my own business
It has nothing to do with him
He made the proposal, right?
Why?
Your roadshow last month wins our department's praise
And last year
The company was in trouble
They forgot?
Who turned the table?
Who should take the credit for Caijin Company's success?
It's you
Enough
It's so unfair
You are the biggest hero in the company
They can't fire you
The company is short of money now
They want to downsize the department that spends money most
He wanted to fire the whole planning department
Now they got what they desired
You are so honest
They have routined you
Yeah, it's a routine
What can I do?
I think it's pretty good
I feel so relieved now
Really want to go?
Headhunting companies extended the olive branch many times
They let me to name the wage and treatment
But I think I can't abandon the company
Then I rejected them all
It's great now
Now I am free
Free
Don't tell Li Siyu about this
Why?
It's no use telling her
I will tell her after I have a new job
I felt guilty for destroying Chen Yiming's
proposal for a whole night
Actually you don't want to marry him at all
I helped you out
But you even rebuke me
It's ok that you don't feel grateful
Where is your conscience?
It's two different matters
I didn't set you a trap with Lanke
Anyway, you owe me a favor
Without me, you are a married woman now
Don't say that
I am scared to hear that
What's wrong with married women?
Zhizhi
No offense
Sister Siyu
I think you can't hesitate anymore
if brother Yiming make proposal again
Just marry him
I agree
Chen Yiming is ordinary
But he is way enough for you
I think you can't delay the marriage
Some people have dated for eight years
In the end they break up with each other
Don't talk about this
Let's talk about the compensation
What's your next plan?
I am so exhausted after the previous road show
I need to have a good rest
And I need to look for the proper opportunity
You didn't have lunch right?
Yeah
Here
Eat
Bye
Where are you going?
Enjoy a good life
Your stuff
Keep it for me
It's a large compensation
We have to compensate no matter what
We signed a mediation agreement
It's all here
18,000 in total
Your bag is very valuable, right?
So I have no money now
Sister Siyu
Liu Yang and I have 20,000 yuan in deposit
But it goes to financial management
I don't know if I can take it out now
Where are you going?
Buy lottery ticket
Try a fortune
Your name is Liu Yang
Top students of Chiao Tung University
Yes
Mr. Lu, you have a good memory
I have no other advantages but love talents
Liu
I hope you can complete the tender successfully
Yes...
President Lu, don't worry
We won't fail you
Ok
Work hard
Yes
Go back
Ok, bye
Thank you
You are welcome
Good bye, president Lu
Director Wang, it's windy outside
You should go in
Liu Yang
Great
I will tell the financial department to give you the bonus
You should hurry up
Write what you need in the report
I will approve of it
Ok, director
I will send you back
No need. Back to work
Ok, director
Ok
Liu Yang, don't forget
Today we will pick up Yuwei together
Wait a second
Liu Yang
Brother, so unbelievble, you would play alumni card
President Lu is from Chiao Tung University, too?
Don't pretend it
I really do not know
Great
Bonus of 50,000 yuan
And the leader of the tender team
What a promotion
I just proposed a plan
Your plan is exactly what president Lu desires
Brother
Next you will make the tender scenario
If you don't mind, I want to offer a little help
No, Wu
What are you talking about?
How can I trouble you?
Despise me?
No
A deal
I also want to learn from you
Wu
Hello, sir
Can I help you?
Yiming
I have a friend over there
Please
Ok, thank you
Traffic jam
What about the car repair?
Do you know the loss assessment?
Not yet
They need another two days
Why so slow?
Many car accidents these days
Excuse me
Ok
What do you want to eat?
Well, I need two cups of coffee
These two
Ok, wait a moment
Ok, thank you
Hello
Xiao Ni, I am Chen Yiming
Siyu is not around you?
Correct
Siyu is not here now
She went to the toilet
Mr. Chen, here's the thing
I have asked her just now
How much of the loan does sister Siyu want?
Mr. Chen
Hello
How about this?
She will call you back
Ok
Thank you
Sir, your coffee
Hello, Zhou
I am Xiaoling
Beauty
Finally you remember to call me
I have some incident
Can you lend me some money?
You find the wrong person
The most correct thing I did is despise you
Jack, I am Xiaoling
Xiaoling, who are you?
What is your relationship with my husband?
Xiaoping
Xiaoping?
Xiaoping has run away
Something wrong with my face?
How much is the compensation?
I have told you
I don't know now
Li Siyu
This is my own business
You can't do like this every time
Every time you encounter a problem...
I've been independent since childhood
Yes, you are independent
I really appreciate it
I love it so much
But many things in the future
Including me
If you are too independent
it will create a sense of distance
I know
Siyu
You're not alone
You still have me
I know
Ok, say it
How much is the compensation?
A lot of money
How come?
Both are good cars
They have insurance, right?
Lanke didn't buy car insurance
Excuse me
We are recruiting students
Hello, you can have a look
You can come alone
Why do you take me with you?
It's the teacher's request
Dad must participate in the shuttle every week
Education is not just mom's thing
It's also a dad's business
I have a lot to do
I didn't let you come every day
Only once a week
We should let teachers know
our family attach great importance to education
Hello, excuse me
Our dance school are recruiting students
But it's very cheap, 300 yuan each class
Liu Yang
Look, the ballet class
300 yuan each class
Do you think Yuwei needs this?
Ok
Yes
Miaomiao learns ballet from the age of 3
Yuwei is four years old now
300 yaun is a little expensive
Yes
No
Each of Miaomiao's class is 500 yuan
I am echoing your words
We need it even if it's expensive
Even if she is not a dancer
it's good to cultivate her temperament
Look at the girl
it's very good for her temperament
It's very important
Ok
Why are you so generous today?
I got the bonus
Really?
I forgot to ask you
How is the report today?
Guess
The leaders are satisfied?
More than that
He announced that I would lead the tender team on the spot
Really?
So you become the team leader?
Husband, I know you are great
Look at you
Just a team leader
You are so happy now
I am not a director now
Next step is the director
Not sure
Talk about bonus first
I got the annual energy saving innovation first prize for my plan
Bonus
RMB 50,000
50,000?
Great
I will send 30,000 to my mom
And leave 20,000 yuan to Yuwei
Siyu and Xiaoling are in trouble
They need money now
Give your mom 10,000 yuan
Give the rest to sister Siyu
I am afraid it's no ok
What's the problem?
They are closer than my blood sisters
It's ok
4S shop often demands an exorbitant price
We can discuss with them about the price
Yes, we will
But it won't change a lot
Actually Zhizhi has nothing to do with this
As for Xiaoling
she gave all her incomes to the specialty stores
So I have to pay the money
I will pay the money
I saved some money
I planned to pay the down payment for the house
Well, I can take out the half for the compensation
I can afford it
I know you can afford it
But you will have no savings after the compensation
We can re-earn the money
Don't exclude me
Siyu
I don't think it's appropriate
At least, I need to pay at least half
It's not a small number
Yes
Not a small number
But compared with our future, it's nothing, right?
Yiming
Thank you
But I have one condition
Yes
No matter what difficulties, I will be the first one to know
You can't hide a secret from me
I am not an outsider
I'll try
A promise
Now I really have a problem
To tell you
Say it
Miaomiao's mom
Sorry for yesterday
Something happened to my sister
Yuwei was sleepy
So we just went home
Miaomiao -I am so sorry
School is over
Come...
Are you a good girl, today?
Miaomiao
Did the teacher praise you today?
Miaomiao looks so good today
Look at the hairpin
Yuwei's parents
Yuwei
Goodbye
Yuwei has a bad time with other kids today
But it's ok now
You just need to comfort her after you go back
Ok
Goodbye teacher
Thank you, teacher
See you tomorrow
Wait for me
She didn't tell me a word so far
This is a dangerous signal
You can't take it lightly
I...
Did I offend president Pan?
It has nothing to do with you
They come for me
Sister Yuan leads me ever since I work here
She taught me how to talk to clients
She is my tutor
Yeah, the competition between disciple and master is inappropriate
But the director will have shares
One year of salary and the year-end bonus
is enough for the compensation
And president Pan names you as the leader
It's inappropriate for you to refuse rashly
So what should I do?
Have you discussed with sister Yuan?
I didn't have the time
Call her
Tell her about this
Li Siyu
Answer it
Sister Yuan, I have something important to tell you
Where are you now?
I'm in the hospital
I have a fever
I'm here for an infusion
Did you finish it?
Soon
Which hospital?
I will pick you up
I'm at blue cross hospital
Ok
See you later
You should have a good talk
You should make it clear, then you will have no misunderstandings
Bye
Zhizhi
Sister Siyu
I have 40,000 yuan here
Liu Yang just took the bonus today
You can take it
Zhizhi, don't worry about it
I have discussed with Yiming
We will pay the money
I have something to do, that's all
Ok
Ok, byebye
You don't want to give it to her
Sister Siyu doesn't need it at all
Since Li Siyu doesn't need it
I will give my mom 30,000
and Yuwei 20,000
Give your mom 10,000
Yuwei will take 40,000
You want to give my mom money as little as possible, right?
We give your mom money every month
No penny less
Give my mom 20,000
Yuwei will have 30,000
Mom needs to repair the house roof
And my father's grave
What's wrong? Unhappy?
You had a bad time with them?
Miaomiao and them don't play with me
Why?
I do not know
You can play with other kids
You have some many kids in kindergarten
You do not understand
Miaomiao and them have the highest quality
I won't be worried when Yuwei play with them
I don't think Miaomiao's mom is great
Miaomiao's mom just barely talks
Why did elite group kick me out?
Don't answer
Come, Yuwei
Hurry
Baby, change your shoes
Come
Mom, I want to watch TV
Ok
Only one episode
This is for Yuwei
I need a flavored one
Flavor
Why are you in a hurry?
I'll cook
And after eating, you just put it here
I will wash it
You just need to keep an eye onYuwei
Where are you doing?
I need to see Miaomiao's mom
She is the administrator of the parents group
I need to ask, why I was kicked out
Is this necessary?
Of course it's necessary
I said from the beginning, you would ask for trouble with money
You will see
Sister Yuan
Siyu
Thank you for helping me pick up Mengmeng today
It's ok
What did you eat tonight?
Instant noodles
I gave you the money to order takeaway, right?
Ordering takeaway at school will have a bad influence
Did you finish your homework?
Not yet
Why?
You played games again?
I did my homework
Kids have too much homework
President Pan talked to me today
I know
What do you think of it?
I will do as you say
Sister Yuan
Are you ok?
It's ok
I just feel so sad
It's not worth it
I can understand
Thirteen years
I have been drinking and socializing day and night
Overwork and business trips
Company's performance has risen year by year
But what have I got?
Husband ran away with someone
Mengmeng is getting rebellious
I am sick
They have all kinds of rumors about me
Sister Yuan, we all know you have sacrificed for Lubao
So what?
On seniority and contribution
the sales director belongs to me
Why does the company do this?
The company...
may consider something
Who will consider for me?
I am thirty-five years old
The diretor
Now or never
Sister Yuan
Do not worry
The director will be yours
I won't be the team leader
And no matter who is the team leader
I will be in your team
You have figured it out?
I will tell president Pan tomorrow morning
Siyu
Thank you
Sister Yuan
Take it back
We have worked together for seven years
Thank you
He is watching
Let's get in the car
What's the matter? Say it
Where are you? So noisy?
Meng's store
Will you come?
I won't
Haowen
You told me, one of your friends is a headhunter, right?
Recommend him to me
You need some rest and be free for some time, right?
Li Siyu has some trouble
I can't be free now
You are so considerate before you become her husband
Sarcasm
You would be like me if it happened to you
Impossible
Have you helped me to make an appointment with Gu Xiaoling?
Here
You should drink
Go...
That's all
Don't forget, hurry
I'll give it to me
Go, have some drink
Don't microwave it?
It's ok
Miaomiao's mom scolded me
She?
Why?
All because of you
She kicked me out because you didn't take Yuwei
to participate in the activity yesterday
She says, we have no concept of time
We disrespect the rules
Disrespect others
Is she insane?
I think she estranged kids from Yuwei
Great that you are not in that group
We won't talk to her in the future
I'm afraid Yuwei will feel bad
Don't worry about this
Kids will have playmates after all
Don't worry