# Google translate version for your reference #
Manager Li
Give you
There is a problem with the contract
Here here
And here
Adjust again
Ok
Change it quickly
When will the interaction design draft be published?
There are several process designs
Logical loophole
Can't get past now
make life difficult for
It's been three days
If you can't get out again today
No one is allowed to leave work
Work overtime every day until midnight
My parents thought I was in
MLM is organized
Continue like this
How can i find a boyfriend
You make this plan
Manager Li
Ginger
Didn't you say there was an interview?
Here I see him go in
People
Don't you go to the general manager's office
What are you doing here
Wait a moment
I'm done with this soon
You are here to play the game
Still come to find a job
Work is game
Game is work
knock off
Your company's wireless network is good
I think i can stay
you can go now
What do you mean
our company
Don't need someone like you
Why don't you need it
you can go now
You didn't even read my resume
You are going to send me away
Please
As a boss
Can you give someone something
Basic respect
respect
Respect is for someone worthy of respect
correct
I am that
Worthy of respect
Take a look, you'll know
No wonder in 1998
This is your second time
Despised me
How can i despise you
What i ask for is
More than three years of design experience
Please look down
I want a UI designer
Look down
Designing a webpage in the freshman year
Just play around
Ant workout mint
You all participated in the design
that
It's all from childhood
These works
You did it independently
Do you still need someone to help
I can give you one
Internship opportunities
sister
Bye bye
What are you doing you
Don't get excited don't get excited
Come over come over
I have an idea
I have a thought
Friends friends
Come over come over
No you who are you
really
Forget immediately
What are you doing
It's related to our design
Really
Come come
No what are you doing
you give me first
You give me first
Pen pen to me
Young hero, admire
Admire
Remember
Communication properties of interactive drafts
Better than aesthetic form
Guan Xiaotang
Do you want to give me something
Similar to a UI engineer position
Go back and prepare
Work tomorrow
Don't be late Don't leave early
No games allowed during working hours
That won't work
No, no, you can go
You know why i
Come to your company for an interview?
why
on the market
Similar company same position
The salary you give is the lowest
What do you mean
low wage
The requirements are definitely low
I just want to find one
It's nothing, don't worry
The boss doesn't care about my job
What do you think on the market today
Is there a job that meets your requirements
But you give that little salary
I want to find employees of my level
Basically impossible
Or else
As long as I finish the work
Can be late, can leave early
Can play games during working hours
As long as you finish the work
Can be late, can leave early
But you are not allowed to play games during working hours
Deal
Start at 9 o'clock tomorrow morning
You just said i could be late
I plan to come at half past nine tomorrow
Bye bye sister
so fun
Package for mom
Bye bye
Moonlight in front of bed
Suspected ground frost
Look up at the moon
Look down and think about hometown
Yuwei is awesome
what happened
What do you want
Take a thing
Come, mother help you
Ok
The teacher also posted this today
Just say after going home
Give it to mom and dad
mom
Is our family out of money again?
who said it
Our family has this money
Come, let's go
Go
go
crazy
Pretty
This still doesn't work
Still need to change
Pretty pretty pretty
LPL second seeded team
Won won won
Have a relationship with you
Yes
I won't give you a cent bonus
This happy day
What a horrible overtime
My treat
Barbecue and singing
Still alive
Me count me
sit down
Sit down, sit down
I can not go
Don't don't come together
I am definitely not going
How interesting people are together
Yes, President Li will kill
Yes yes yes yes
Hurry back
Must go back
Mr. Li is out on a date
Why let us
Work overtime here
Just
impossible
It is said that
Her boyfriend dumped her
So work hard
That's right
Vent the pain of broken love
Correct
Vent on us at the same time
To you men
Hatred
Stop talking nonsense
Let's get together
Go go go go go
No. Is this okay?
Hurry up
Xiao Meng, want to go together
Together together together
Xiao Jiang, hurry and go
What are you doing
We got off work
Who let you off work
Labor Law
Give me back
This is the client
Business cooperation program
Suggestions made
Before work tomorrow
Give me the revised plan
Sister, we need to rest
Please call me Mr. Li in the company
Or Miss Li
Manager Li
sister
Are you finished
Beijing time
17:10 in the afternoon
I'm done
Then you can go
What about them
They have their job
They have
Worked ten hours
Time to get off work
Guan Xiaotang
You can not be enterprising
But don't influence others
They are not others
They don't want to work overtime
You won't understand
Dream for yourself
When working hard
Is not
Concept of work and get off work
I didn't think they
Fighting for my dream
Totally for
Fight for your dreams
You are too young
Don't understand these
But what I can understand is
Sister Li Siyu, general manager
You can't because
Misfortune in own life
Just work overtime
Punish all of us
what did you say
We are not your ex boyfriend
Don't you on us
Vent your hatred of him
Guan Xiaotang
Go go go go
Trabecula
Stop here today
Go back to rest
Mr. Li, this plan
let's talk tomorrow
it is good
and then
What then
You don't announce
The decision to fire me
According to this template
Redesign
Outline of user interview
And interview record sample
Before eleven o'clock tomorrow morning
Give me
Thank you
Helped us win
One night's rest
Talk about it
Which department do you want to change to
As long as the salary is higher
Any department is fine
I can remind you
Department with higher salary
The greater the pressure
No matter how big
It's not the pressure of life
OK, let me ask for you
I think
In Caijin
Must have no future
You have an epiphany
Xiaoling reminded me
She said after i retired
Should be a man with silver hair
Personable billionaire
What do you think
I'm trying to say what you said
You don't have to stroke
I have deeply
Reflected on myself
I have known her for half a year
Eat and drink
Punch chat
Why not a little bit
Substantive progress
She's still in front of me
Go on blind date to find boyfriend
why
Because she doesn't like you
Is not
Because my offense was wrong
Obviously is a strategic goal
I used tactical missiles
Sure
No effect at all
I should change the strategic missile
What are you talking about
Can you say something
Words i can understand
Gu Xiaoling
I just like it
Panini with meat and eggs
But I can only give her
A fried dough stick
So
In a word
I can no longer exchange my true feelings for my true heart
I have to get rich overnight
I have an elementary school classmate
I don’t even know the multiplication table
Ever since the media
Two months Baojun changed BMW
You want to quit and work in the media
Aren't you familiar
I would like to hear your views
Haowen, otherwise
Don't worry about resigning
Wait for me to slow down
I'll talk to you later
Brothers
How is Siyu
Siyu
Should she continue to start her own business?
Still thinking about it
Or I let
Xiaoling help you ask
I just said that casually
You are in such a good position
Only earn seven or eight thousand a month
Too bad
If joining calls
I promise
Your first year net profit is 150,000
300,000 in the second year
I provide brand training
Technology and promotion
Let's split the rental profit 50-50
I will subsidize you for installation costs
Every new member
I will subsidize you another two hundred yuan
I'll come over and sign a contract with you
You go
You a meat
Why are you shrinking back?
Remaining blood on the opposite side
Right right right first
Zhao Yun Zhao Yun
Hit him first hit him first
I see me
Look at me, cut me
You now
Go on, go on, go on
on
what happened to you
You don't care about my position
Guan Xiaotang Guan Xiaotang
Playing games
phone
Mr. Li
Don't report me
I didn't mean to cheat you
Hey
Why don't you answer my call
I shit
Listen to me
I just talked to a few franchisees
The information has been sent to your email
Before six tomorrow morning
Must put each other's icon
And jump page
Put it on our internal test page
Customers want to see
Ok
You serve me a snack
Can't delay, can't make mistakes
Got it
I asked around
The general manager does not hire people
R&D Department Testing Department
You definitely can't
Where's the planning department
Mr. Pan has suspected that their department
People are superfluous and need to be streamlined
Then it's even more impossible to recruit
As for the library management department
Their salary
Not as high as the administrative department
You definitely don't want to go
What about other departments
For example, the Finance Department
The Finance Department must request
Have an accountant job certificate
What about the Development Department
Your experience and qualifications
Neither support
I think you are still in the administration department
More realistic
This is my daughter
Kindergarten's payment slip
Nine thousand a quarter
this week
Is the deadline for payment
This is my husband's hospital receipt
Beyond social security
I have to bear more than 10,000
Previously saved money
It's all spent
If i still rely on
Now this salary
I can't make it anymore
Row
I'll help you ask
Thank you Mr. Hu
Manager Li
thank you
Trabecula
Has the stress tested?
Report to Mr. Li
First stress test
Passed successfully
Start tomorrow
Second stress test
Good um
Lao Liu
Network promotion plan
The electronic version is sent to your email
it is good
Tingting
Manager Li
Has the content layout changed?
Already fixed
You open the internal beta network
So you can see
Good um
Zhou Tianyu
Newly added
Those franchisees
Did Guan Xiaotang put it in?
I didn't see it
Where's Guan Xiaotang
What i want
I i think
I stayed up late yesterday
I didn't go home
and then
Then I said I'll change my mind
I played two games
and then
Then play games
I hit me a little sleepy
I said i sleep
I'll do it when I get up
and then
And then you woke up
Don't worry
I am before twelve noon today
I will give you
Don't worry
How to hit people
I did what I promised you
How about you
I i am confused
Why not pay on time
Why play games in the office
I'm confused
Something that doesn't count
I'm not
Get out of here
President Fang
Ok
Two days later
I want to give the company board
Submit a proposal
What about
From the perspective of capital
Business model for the company
And industrial structure adjustment
You mean to say
About re
Packaging emerald
Yes
So to ensure
The proposal passed smoothly
Please also in advance
Among the board members of the company
Do work
President Wang
Actually a few days ago
Mr. Pan talked to me once
Ok
What did you say
He asked me to reconsider
About the Lvbao III production line
He hasn't given up yet
President Wang, I'm thinking
If Emerald III goes on the market
Roll out
The valuation of Emerald
Is it helpful too
On the two production lines
Eight billion is basically gone
Can have a year
Tens of millions of profits
After three to five years
Emerald can be valued at 5 billion
Is this interesting
But when we created Green Treasure
Just to build
China's best
New Energy Enterprise
If Emerald’s valuation
Can reach 20 billion
Can you say it is not China
The best energy company?
Pan Zhiyong said
Take five to ten years
Realize this dream
Use my model for one year
But the valuation of a company
Can not be completely separated
Output value and profit
How do you explain Tesla
Still losing money
The market value has reached
More than 30 billion dollars
Still rising
A company's valuation
With output value, net value and profit
It doesn't matter much
Asset operation efficiency
Company growth space
Decided a company
Can you get a high valuation
We should put all the funds
Used to create this concept
Not what production line
This is the same market I used to face
It's really different
is not it
Times have changed
Pan Zhiyong's set
Outdated
Emerald has to change track
Guan Xiaotang
Aren't you fired
Why come back
I have a cup dropped here
Isn't it just a broken cup?
Throw it away
How many dollars
Poor ghost
Why are you working overtime
You left it
What a mess
only you
Mr. Li is here
I'm looking for a cup
President Liu, sorry
I have a temporary problem here
Can i give it to you tomorrow
it's all my fault
What I promised you didn't do
I solemnly apologize to you here
I'm really sorry
I am sorry for you
I promise that tomorrow morning at 8 o'clock
Must be given to you
Okay, thank you
Goodbye
Go home and rest, let me
Aren't you already
Turn off the phone
Sleep steadily
Why go
Carry bag
Why are you here
Didn't I let you go
Give you a gift before you go
Where's Zhou Tianyu
I let him go back
Guan Xiaotang
You deliberately destroy me
sister
Have you recently
Endocrine disorders
what
Fire big
What you told that client
Tomorrow morning at eight
no problem
I promise before six o'clock
Let you see the finished product
You call Zhou Tianyu
Hello
The number you have dial can not be reached
I told him to shut down
Don't worry, sister
My life is fast and good
I do not believe you
But no one under you now
Believe and Believe
Believe it or not
Stop talking nonsense and work
You look like my mother like this
Stared at me doing homework when I was young
If i were your mother
I beat you to the ground
Guan Xiaotang
Where here
Why did you go
Buy you breakfast
You still want to buy breakfast
sister
Can you change
How angry are you getting up
What time is this
I'm done
what
An hour ago
Just send your email
No thanks
Just give me enough overtime
I count you as reliable
Then this time
Do you need to get out?
roll
I'm still rolling
Go home to sleep
Xie Xiaozhu Longen
father
All packed
Let's go
Where to go
Discharged
Go home
Yuwei is unhappy when he comes home
Happy
Sit down
Catch
we
Where to go back
The house you rent
I have already refunded you
Retired, retired
Thank you
give it to me
I'm on it first baby come
Mom, I want to watch TV
Can only watch one episode
Ok
Liu Yang
You sleep in this room
I sleep in this room with Yuwei
Come
Zhizhi, are all home
Why bother
I only hired a half-day shift
Go back to the company
You accompany Yuwei
I'll cook dinner when I come back
Come, dad hug
Three years ago, it should be considered
The golden age of self-media entrepreneurship
But since last year
This craze began to recede
Till today
Since the media has become
A piece of red sea
That means I'm late
It should be said that pure reliance
Personal operating public account
The myth of realization
Now basically
Impossible to show up
Then my road to riches
It's already blocked
Not without a chance
I currently cooperate with a
Self-media company
Its annual income
Still above a million
But they operate as a team
The content goes
Boutique personalized route
And monetization channel
Special clarity
Say these
I don't have any conditions
Then don't worry about resigning
That won't work
Gu Xiaoling has registered online
Start to marry
Actually currently
In the self-media industry
No one has become a financial institution
Brand building content
After the number of fans goes up
Can both put the flow
Convert to ad
Can also be transformed into
Clients of financial institutions
This is also a way
If you can
If you put the team together
I can help you with content
Righteousness
I knew it
I still have this
The life of getting rich overnight
What you asked me about
How's it going
what's up
Didn't you say you were looking for Gu Xiaoling
Can you find out for me
People think about rain now
Must be better than you
Look at you now
Her company
How is the preparation
I don't know
Guan Xiaotang
Do you want to be beaten again?
Before eleven o'clock tomorrow morning
I must see the finished product
I haven't slept yet
You just want to sleep
that's it
Gu Xiaoling
Can you mute
So noisy
Here comes here comes
Take a look
What are you doing lately
Business is so busy
That website
Recommended me a bunch of candidates
A bunch of
Dozens
Do you see dozens of them?
I did a preliminary audition
More than ten left
I'm going to see you together these two days
Sea election
How to follow
It's like recruiting
This is much more important
Is the recruitment inappropriate?
You can quit at any time
If this blind date is taken away
That's for a lifetime
Then do you still have a
First test, second test, finals
You are really right
Show you show you
You show me this
How about how about
You show me
No time
Hurry up, help me see
how about it
what
take a look
Phoenix Group Dark Horse Group
Birth Good Life Group
Resurrection group
correct
Then you divide these groups
What's the use
I'll rate them
According to their height and weight
Family
The most important thing is economic conditions
The data will also be wrong
so
I want from each group
Pick the top two
Then conduct an interview
Then please ask Miss Gu
How many points do you rate yourself
With my beautiful appearance
It's got 100 points anyway
You are not original
My name is original fine tuning
correct
My skin has completely recovered recently
See if i am
Look younger
Can you add 20 points
Take a look
I have another one here
Photos from 10 years ago
Take a look
You show me
Am I better than before
Younger
photo
I actually have another one here
A photo of you and Chen Yiming
When did you sneak a photo
I do not know how
Just you two
At that time
My mother got it
I was very anxious to know
how does he look like
Then I secretly took a picture
delete it
Are you willing
This is out of print
What out of print
Don't think i don't know
You put Chen Yiming
All contact
All blacked out
All the photos
Also deleted
I want to delete it
But there is nothing
delete
it is good
Don't delete send me
I knew it
No talking
Go for a beauty sleep