[To Dear Myself]
[Ep 19]
Sister Siyu
Zhizhi, where are you going?
I am here to ask for a leave, I have some problem
What?
Heart bypass surgery?
According to the angiography,
coronary heart disease is very serious
Most of the arteries are blocked
She needs surgery as soon as possible
How much does it cost?
Self-paying part is quite a lot
How come?
Liu Yang
What?
Ok, I'm coming
What happened?
Liu Yang's mom ran away from the hospital
I need to find her now
Wait...
I will go with you, I need to get the key now
I was about to give her an infusion
She was saying no surgery and she wanted to go home
I persuaded her
But she disappeared in a blink
What's the matter with you?
Why don't you keep an eye on the patient?
Mom
She is not in hospital, not at home?
Ok, you go to the train station
I will go to the bus station
Hello, Chengdu, Sichuan
Hello, two tickets
Sister Siyu
Excuse me
Thank you
Mom...
Excuse me
Mom
Where are you going?
I want to go home
You are hospitalized
You know?
I'm fine now
No
You need the surgery right away
Go back with me
Those doctors don't know anything
Don't listen to their nonsense
Mom
You are worried about money, right?
Don't worry
I have enough money
Yang
I heard you when you made those calls
I don't want to get you in a dilemma
I don't want to be your nuisance
Mom, I have my solution
What solution?
I'm really fine
I am fine
I am strong
See, I am fine
I can jump, look
No
Mom...
Mom
Mom, be careful
Where is your medicine?
In the bag
Be careful
Feel better?
I am fine
I'm ok
Mom
If something happened to you, what should I do?
Yang
I know, it's hard for you
I don't want to be your nuisance
Mom, I am useless
Silly boy, you are great
It's ok
Come, stand up
Send me off, come
Mom
Mom, don't worry
I will cure you even if I go bankrupt
Stop crying, mom
Let's go home
Go home
Ok
He found her?
Liu Yang is taking his mom back to the hospital
Great
I'll take you back to the hospital
Why does Liu Yang's mom run out of the hospital?
All because of the fee
We don't have the enough money?
We borrowed, but it's still not enough
Zhizhi, why don't you tell me?
Liu Yang told me not to borrow money from you
Why?
He says, you are preparing for the bid
Go
I go up now
You should go back to the company
Contact me if you need help
Ok, bye
Is she all right?
She is stable now
Zhizhi, come out
Can I mortgage our house?
Not the bank
We need to mortgage it to a company
But...
The interest rate is too high
I don't care
We need to get enough money for mom's surgery
Ok
Bed No. 34's family
The surgery is arranged on next Wednesday
But we haven't paid the money
You have paid it
Otherwise we won't arrange it for you
Who paid the money?
I don't know
See, Li Siyu
We owe her such a big debt
Mr. Liu
I put the report on your table
Thank you
Brother Yang, why are you here?
I am worried
Nothing particular recently
You should take care of aunt in the hospital
I'll call you when we need you
How is aunt?
It's stable today
But she needs the operation
Well
What are you doing?
Brother Yang, sorry
I don't have much money
I have only two thousand, you should take it
You are an intern
You have a little salary
How can I take your money?
It's little but you should take it
I want to do something for aunt
Thank you
You should take the money back
No, you take it
Don't worry
We have got enough money
Really?
Zhizhi's cousin paid some for us
Welcome home
A bathtub?
The bedroom is quite big
Look, the living room
Finally I have a home
Let's celebrate it
Ok
I no longer need to be afraid of the rent raise
No longer be afraid of landlord's selling the house
From now on, I became a house slave
Finally become a house slave
This city is so magical
I can make you fly high in an instant
It can make you fall deep in an instant
Last moment
You thought the future was at your fingertips
Next moment, you may lose everything
Why do you think like this?
These three months
It's like riding a roller coaster
I became unemployed from an elite marshal overnight
I was rejected over and over again
When I was about to lose my confidence
suddenly everything came back to me
I really feel
Feel it's very unreal
I do not know which is the real me
I even don't know if I can hold everything I have now forever
What?
What are you doing?
Come
Don't move
Past, present, future
I'm in your palm
You can hold me forever
I think we should have sense of game in decorating the kitchen
When we wash the dishes, we think it's not housework
but it's like playing games
Fair enough
Study should be like night market
So when we work overtime in the study
we feel it's like visiting the night market
Ok
It's kind of psychological comfort
What about the bedroom?
I don't know yet
You want it a bit evil charm with my persona
Or a little rigid with your persona?
Rigid?
No
So over the past five years,
rigid is the impression I leave?
Do you have my evil charm?
You win
Pay the renovation cost with your credit card
Why? You spent all your money?
You may not know
Liu Yang's mom had a heart attack
She needs a surgery
I paid him some surgery fee
So I have no money
I really don't know
He didn't tell me
How much did you pay for the surgery?
More than 30,000
They can return the money as long as they can afford
Otherwise we won't need the money back
You have no objection, right?
Of course no objection
What happened?
As I remember right, you want to bid for his company's project, right?
How's it going?
It's two different matters
I am waiting for the result
I think you don't need to wait for the result
Just quit
Why?
If you put these two things together
you are bribing
I definitely didn't mean it
I know
But you can't explain it clearly to others
I just want to help Zhizhi, and Liu Yang
Yeah, you want to help them
So you need to quit
Why?
Why don't you understand?
Think
If it's exposed, what should you do?
You will cause a lot of troubles for Liu Yang
Zhizhi will be implicated, too, right?
No one will know this
Walls have ears
Chen Yiming
You want to do this for Tianyi Group?
What do you mean?
If I withdraw from this bid
28 million is gone
President Pan will lose to president Wang again
You win again in front of president Wang
One more credit
This is your opinion of me?
It's not the first time you do so
I admit
I did that because of my selfishness
I want to prove myself
But now it's different
I really do it for you
For Liu Yang
How about this?
I will resign from Tianyi
I quit
You will believe me, right?
Where are you going?
Write a resignation letter
You don't need to resign
I believe you
Siyu
It's not a joke
I promise you
Quit now? Why?
My friend might be suspected of taking bribes
You have a clear conscience
What are you afraid of?
But it's hard to make it clear
President Pan
We have another chance
Li Siyu
We don't have another chance
It can't be, right?
I am negotiating with Wang Ziru
I think Lubao is at least four billion
She doesn't think so
You know that report
Now she thinks Lubao is only worth three billion
If we lose this government project
Lubao is only worth two billion in her eyes
We still have another two companies, right?
Two weeks ago, they dropped out for no reason
Now we have only Tianyi Group
If we want to change the current situation
Lubao III must be put into mass production
But that requires at least 800 million capital investment
According to the current company's shareholding structure
we can only give out 20% shares
So we can't let Lubao's evaluation drop
We can't lose the government project
We must win the bid. Must
But...
It's not just about Lubao's future
It's about all employees' work
And your dream and mine
We must win
Brother Yang
What?
Ok, I get it
What happened?
President Pan
We won the bid
What did I tell you?
This is the result I want
Ai
Tell president Wang of Tianyi Group
I have time now
I can meet her anytime
At any time
Wang Ziru won't have the chance to bargain with me
Li Siyu
I will reward you a lot this time
Reward you
President Pan, I'm a little worried
I can tell you
This news is worth 300 million
It can let me open another laboratory
Have another production line
Li Siyu
We will be the best power battery in China
We will be the biggest new energy enterprise in China
You will see
We will let Chinese energy move human civilization forward
Definitely
Doctor, these indexes are high
Is it ok?
Doctor
Her these indicators are still high
What is the reason?
Mainly because she is old
It's better if you use imported drugs
But you request the domestic medicine
so the effect comes slow
Thank you
Liu Yang, what did the doctor say?
You even dare to ask
What?
Mom
Aunt, we are here to see you
Aunt, we brought you something
Give it to me
Thank you...
I put it here
Ok
Feelling better?
I have to go now
So anxious?
All because of your company
We have a meeting today
We need to determine the details of the purchase contract
Brother Yang, I can't be explicit sometimes
But you can rest assured
I will remember what you did for me and Lubao in my heart
I know what to do
Don't say like that
I did not do anything
I know
Mom, take a good rest
I need to have a meeting
Go
I have to go now
Bye bye
Aunt
Sit down
Girl, sit down
Liu Yang
What did you lose your temper just now?
Let me ask you
Why did you change the medicine?
What medicine?
How much can you save
when you change the imported into domestic drugs?
You even want to save the little money?
It's my mom
I didn't do that
Why they changed the medicine?
I didn't tell them to change the medicine
The nurse station asked me to refill the deposit
I told them to give me more days
They said, they would discuss about it
Discuss?
So they just changed the medicine?
I know
You have a conflict with my mom
But she is like this now
Can we have some conscience?
Why I have no conscience?
How can you say I have no conscience?
Then why did you allow them to do that?
All because we have no money
I told you to take care of mom in the monring
But you didn't come until noon
What do you mean?
I need to work
You can't ask for leave?
I have taken leave three times this week
How can I ask for more?
Why you can't?
Your job
A pupil can do it
Yes, my job is not important
But I earn several thousand yuan a month at least
I can't just leave the work aside
Zhang Zhizhi
You are my mom's daughter-in-law
Mom becomes like this because of you
So no matter what
you should take care of her
I need to work and take care of daughter at the same time
Now I need to send meals for her
What should I do now?
What do you mean?
Yes
Mom becomes like this because of me
But mom has heart disease for a decade
It has nothing to do with me, right?
Unreasonable, ridiculous
Xiaoling's gallery has exhibition recently
She said she would come here to see you soon
Ok, thank you
What happened?
Nothing
Mom, how's the height?
Adjust it higher?
No need, leave it be
No need
It's ok
Yiming
Yiming, wait for me
Chen Yiming
Yiming
Because of the tender?
So what else could it be?
You have promised me
It's not as simple as you think
You made it complicated
No
It's not just about me. It's about president Pan
It's about hundreds of employees
I don't have the final say
What about Liu Yang?
Have you thought about Liu Yang?
I thought about it
Liu Yang and I did nothing wrong
I give him money because Zhizhi is my cousin
I have a clear conscience
It's your wishful thinking
But people will think it's exchange of interests
Actually it's not true
Why are you so stubborn?
Li Siyu
No one will believe your wishful thinking
No
Only you would think so
Can you stop deceiving yourself?
Let me ask you
If something happens, what will you do?
What will others think of you?
They will think you resort to every possible way
for your sales performance
Resort to every possible way?
I could have got more
But I didn't do anything
Because I believe in Lubao products' quality
I believe in the fairness of the tender
I couldn't ruin Lubao or my colleagues
to prove my innocence when I did nothing
Lubao will not be ruined
As long as your president Pan is not so eager for quick success
Chen Yiming
Resort to every possible way
eager for quick success
How about you?
You think you force us to withdraw not because of yourself at all?
It's true
No
You forgot?
You just apologized for your selfishness
Ridiculous
We are negotiating the details
If things go smoothly, next week
we will sign the contract with the government
Congratulations
After we win the government project,
many friends regain the interest in Lubao
So realistic
Well, I can't stand the temptation
You need to try harder
So I am here
Ok, let's get back to business
800 million, 20%
500 million, 20%
President Wang
If you can't give 800 million, I think we are done talking
800 million, ok
But I need to hold 30% shares
Impossible
So what's your offer?
I will give you at most 21%
President Pan
Lubao III still has many problems
22%
President Pan
Generally, Lubao's evaluation is less than 4 billion
And Lubao is not the unique one
Lubao is unique
22%
If you bargain again, we are done talking
Only sincere buyers will negotiate with the price
29%
President Wang, let me tell you the truth
Some new funds contacted me
I offer 18%
800 million
They are interested
But renegotiation will waste much time
So I want to cooperate with you again
I won't mind finding a new partner if you are not sincere enough
President Pan
I can tell you the truth
Fund negotiations are all the same routine
They are very sincere in the beginning
When you choose the only partner, he will ask a high price
So just forget it
Anyway, financing is not fatal to Lubao
No big deal
28%
22%
This share
Valid within 24 hours
Otherwise we are really done talking
Mr. Liang, I have an appointment with a client at three
It will end at four
Then I will go directly to see you
Ok, see you later
Kuaizi
It's downloaded
It needs three minutes
Still angry?
You didn't contact me for a week
You are so audacious now
I can get off work before ten today
Let's talk
Will you work overtime today?
Should we have a talk?
President Wang
Yiming
In a bad mood?
No
Have you met Lu Bao's Pan Zhiyong?
Yes
So what kind of person is Pan Zhiyong?
He is quite capable and courageous
But he is a little smug
So do you think he will make a bluff or take some risk?
It's hard to tell. He...
It's hard to see him through
Later I will have a little talk with some guys
About the failure of Lubao's negotiation
Will you come?
Me?
Not a formal meeting
Better not
Ok
Pan Zhiyong told me, some fund companies contacted him
It's not good for us
As I know, Lubao's bank loan is due soon
I think it's helpful for our next round of negotiation
But he may not be short of money
Would it be possible that Pan Zhiyong makes a bluff?
Pan Zhiyong is a typical leader
He may be a little smug
But he won't make a bluff
I think it's a breakthrough that Pan Zhiyong changed 20% into 22%
But our goal is 23% at least
We can give an offer of 25%
Will it irriate Pan Zhiyong?
Then we will have no chance
Leaders will not be irritated
He was afraid of being despised
Then we should insist, 23%
But in terms of evaluation, should we make some compromise?
But I think 22% is the bottom line
Otherwise he won't give the deadline of 24 hours
President Wang, we must reply within 24 hours?
Correct
We only have 14 hours to go
You should go back now
I need to think about it