# Google translate version for your reference #
Xiaoling
I dated boyfriend today
I won't be with you
See you tomorrow
worship
You have no dyslexia
You are procrastinating
And procrastination
Often comes from inner conflict
You didn't hide from me
You are suggesting me
Want to break up with me
I
Listen to me first
When i realized this
My muscles started to twitch
My breath and pulse
All disorder
In my brain
Of the ventral tegmental area of ​​the midbrain
Dopamine levels
Far below normal
This directly caused my depression
At the same time cause me
Inability to concentrate
My cognitive function and memory
All started to degenerate
I did not do anything
Xiaoling
You did nothing
it's me
In love with you
My various physiological reactions
When I fell in love with humans
Pathological state
Exactly the same
According to logic
Gu Xiaoling
I love you
No one has ever
Confessed to me like this
I checked again
Our dating data
I find
From you to me
Your sister desperately needs five million
And the day I refused
Is a key point
Since then
You start hiding from me
I thought about it carefully later
All the words i said that day
In my worldview
What i said is correct
But the emotion expert told me
There is no right or wrong in the world of feelings
Xiaoling
Here is five million
Please accept
Do not
I think
My current behavior is stupid
Neither meets
My previous principles of doing things
Also violated
Our prenuptial agreement
Several
but
I am willing to make an exception for you
You don't have to do this
Xiaoling
I found a
Terrible fact
I can't accept
The future without you
So i have to do this
Please accept
How much courage is needed
Give the future a certainty
The road when looking back
Really not easy
And we have already passed
Crying youth
Swim at both ends of the crowd
She suddenly called us here
What's the matter
With you
Sometimes afraid of this day
This time
The only thing
Made me burnt
No time to care about you
You changed to a new company
how about it
Do we have
What love should look like
Wei Yayun
I am now
Where do you not meet in life?
This life
Too slow seems too short
Don't need your promise
If you change the previous
I will for sure
Slap her mouth
but now
Don't know why
I don't feel so angry anymore
What about her
She apologized to me and confessed to me
You won't be like this
Forgive her
I'm not that virgin
But i don't know why
I see her
So please me every day
Trembling
I feel a bit pitiful
Don't know why
Because you are stronger than before
The road when looking back
Really not easy
Walk on both ends of the crowd
Silence comes naturally
And we have already passed
Gu Xiaoling
Don't you say we're leaving
Have a step by step
But at least
I
Signed the prenuptial agreement
what did you say
Maybe i will
I said
I signed the prenuptial agreement
You think about it
I thought about it when I was eight
But you don't love him at all
You don't even like him
But i'm with him
I can forget that day forever
What day
The second year my dad died
My mother took me
Go to uncle's house to borrow money
Then my mom
Just let me wait for her at the door
It was very cold at that time
Snowing
Then the kids outside
Are all snowball fights
I'll wait and wait there
Then they
Just throw me that snowball
Lost on my clothes
All wet
Then I blame my mother
Why not let me
Wait at uncle's house
I learned later
My mom doesn't want me to see
She humbled
The way to beg
Did you borrow money?
My mom wants to borrow two thousand yuan
And then by my uncle
Fifty dollars was passed
When my mother came out
The eyes are red
In my life
I can't forget that moment
did you
Why didn't you tell me?
I knew from that moment
In this world
Can't trust anything
Haowen has always liked you
He Mu loves me too
Then who do you love
who do you like
I
I like money
I thought about stability
Don't worry about future life
I like what I want to buy
Just buy what
No need to look at the price tag
Then you now
Did you get what you want
Yes indeed
So we should be happy
Happy
Xiaoling
Lei Haowen has changed a lot recently
I think you can
Try to look at him from another angle
Maybe your future
Just one more possibility
Don't persuade me anymore
I don't want you to regret later
I may regret whoever I choose
But at least
I have money
what
He Mu gave me five million
five million
Xiaoling, thank you
I can't ask for this money
You take it
Don't think i don't know
You these days
Whole night
Can't sleep
We have got the money
There is no shortage of money for the unique project temporarily
In addition
Even if I'm desperate
I can't use your money
Because i hope
You can take these five million
Return a lot to He Mu
Li Siyu
Why can't you
Bless me congratulations
Why do you keep thinking
Break up me and He Mu
Xiaoling
We hope you are happy
We wish you happiness
I certainly will
I will be happy
Come
Happy
happy
Lei Haowen
Where did you go
I call you and never answer
You won't reply if you send you a WeChat
Me and Mr. Gong
Waiting for you here for a long time
I am going bankrupt
what happened
A dozen consecutive experiments alone
All failed
If now
No more investors
Give us money
That my house
Siyu the next ten years
All over
How to do it
Haowen is here
Mr. Gong
Why didn't i think of you
I now
You don't have to say it
Now there is a good project
I almost got the money
Are you interested
Sit down and say
Alone
Professor Gao Zhengdao
Filmless battery
this project
If it succeeds
The world of new energy
That's ours
I'm in the club
In fifteen minutes
You come to pick me up
Ok
President Wang
They are willing
At a price of ten million
Re-transfer
20% of the shares
Price is second
I must hold a controlling stake in this project
But before you
Talked so many times
None of them agree
Did not agree before
Because of
They haven't run out of ammunition and food
It should be time now
Ziru
Go back first
Why are you so fast
I happen to be nearby
How long have you waited
Not long, a few minutes
Let's go
Ok
I seemed to see
Our Yiwen Company
That investor
Did you miss the wrong person?
I think should not be
That is also possible
Our club
Many people in the financial world
All come to eat
You are looking for me in such a hurry
He misses me
Half right
What about the other half
Where's the other half
I have good news
Teacher Gao's Laboratory
Start the second round of financing
I have given up
Invested in his project
You are not always on that project
Interesting?
I invested
Two other laboratories
Less risk than his
Brighter prospects
understood
Mr. Gong
this is us
All of the lab
Although our laboratory is small
but
Have everything
Every detail
Teacher Gao strictly controls
This is all his hard work
Ok
How does Gong feel
Okay
Does Gong always have any questions?
The question is
Your experiment
Can it really succeed?
I can only say
Since the establishment of the laboratory
Nowadays
Is the closest day to success
Mr. Gong, sorry
I take a call
it is good
Sit down and say, Mr. Gong
Mr. Liang, hello
You also have a share of Dobu
interested
Hao Wen
Come
what happened
Tell you the truth
Ten million twenty percent
I can never accept it
How much can you accept?
five million
You are too cruel
Sixty percent
Just this little money
You still want to hold
necessary
You don't have to
Let's put the money aside
Just holding this thing
Teacher Gao, he won't agree
Then hold
It's boring
Mr. Gong
You said you invested in our company
You didn't even think about holding
How come here
So interested
Your company
I can see the future
And this
I am really betting
About you
I didn't count it alone
Then I and some partners
Discuss again
OK, discuss it first
Tell me after discussing
I'll leave first
I send it
You don't have to send it
You slow down
Ok
Si Yu, Mr. Gong is gone
slower
how about it
The good news is that he agreed to counter-offer
The bad news is that he paid the price
We can't accept it at all
I disagree
I can have nothing else
Only a little
Whether it is success
Still fail
We must hold our own
But the current situation
Can't help us
I think Teacher Gao’s worry
Makes sense
I'm going to die alone
Several of us are still discussing here
Whose name is this child
is it necessary
Stop fighting
Haowen, call Mr. Gong back
Five million forty-nine percent
If he is willing
We sign the contract right away
Unwilling
We think of other ways
Ok
any solution
Big deal
I will sell for another ten years
forty nine
One point two
Six six three
Forty two point three three
It's not impossible
Mr. Wang, the reason why you want to invest
Want to hold
I'm just afraid of success alone
Threat to Emerald
But after visiting today
I can conclude
They won't succeed
why
the first
Their laboratory
I have seen
The most broken laboratory
second
Although on the surface
They seem very confident
But in fact, it’s equally uncertain
Then your opinion is
My advice is
We have no need to invest
Let them who are already exhausted
Give up this project by yourself
They won't give up
But no money
They can only admit their fate
Paranoia
Plus Li Siyu's madness
They can do anything
Sister Yuan
Ok
What do you say to me
the first
Why are you leaving
Second, is she worth keeping?
You have to put these two questions
Think clearly
You know what to do
I am a bit complicated
This person
before
Actually it is
Zhizhi
President Wu
Let me introduce to you
This is my previous leader
No need to introduce
I have seen Mr. Yuan several times
long time no see
Yes
do you know
The headhunting company first asked us
The recommended one is Mr. Yuan
Later, Mr. Yuan
Highly recommended you
Say you are strong and young
And good character
That’s why I asked the Human Resources Department
Messaged you
How is it, Mr. Wu?
The person I recommend is correct
Yes, after she came
This sales situation
Completely opened
So i want to thank you
Take the order if you want to thank you
No problem, talk slowly
I still have things
You are busy
I'm going to see you about the order
no problem
Bye bye
Walk slowly
I always have doubts
Like me
Novices who have been in the industry for less than a year
How can I get this position?
You have been helping me
Easy work
Sister Yuan
Ok
Why do you recommend me
The thing about you leaving the emerald
I always feel my responsibility
So I recommend you this time
It's a compensation for you
but
I have never been a manager
You are not afraid
I do not know what to do
Are you qualified for this position
Zhizhi
You must be competent
First of all
You have a good character
Second one
Can endure my torment back then
Show you are strong
third
After being tortured by me
Still not holding a grudge
Still be friends with me
It means you are open-minded
And the above three points
Is to lead the team
The most basic elements
I am so good
Of course you also have shortcomings
You are easily influenced by emotions
Thinking about the problem is not rational enough
But you have strong learning ability
So put you on
Manager's position
You can overcome personal likes and dislikes
Start from work
Think about the problem from the overall situation
correct
The one you just said
Who are the people who are going to quit?
Who is this guy
No longer important
I know what i am going to do
Sister Yuan
I will toast you with water instead of wine
Thank you
That's OK, that's it
As you said
Five million forty-nine percent
Let's continue
carry on
Don't continue, Teacher Gao
This is
Our last chance
Can only succeed, cannot fail
You say it
Haowen, thank you
You really want to thank me
Tell Xiaoling
My great achievement
You have to tell her
I, Lei Haowen
He also has a reliable side
I must tell
Say it three times
Try this
See what's wrong
Xiao He
Fill in this and sign
Wei Yayun
Come in
sit down
I heard you are resigning
No no
Because of me
Yes
It's me
If it's because of me
It's not necessary at all
Since i have
Sat in the position of manager
The first thing I have to consider
Is the benefit of the company
in case
You can create benefits for the company
Personal matters
I can put it aside
but
I did that to you
Can you forgive me
indeed
We go
Used to be very unpleasant
but now
I've lost things
Got it all back
Even more than before
So even in a short time
I can't forgive you
but
I do not hate you
Manager Zhang
Sorry
Don't talk about it later
These three words
When you are with me
When I say sorry
I didn't feel moved
Did not feel relieved
Because you're sorry
Zhang Zhizhi from before
Me now
No need to be sorry
I got it
You just arrived at the company
Less than three months
But you have been working hard
As a newcomer
Able to win a big customer
It can be said
Very good
It should be said that this company
This job
Very suitable for you
You should cherish it
I don't want to go
just
If you must go
At least get this commission
Go later
After all, you worked hard for three months
Working alone
Not easy
You have more money
Can solve many problems
Sister Zhizhi
I didn't think of you
You unexpectedly
So, so to me, me
I am wrong
I was really wrong
Sorry
Hello there
Miss Gu
I want to increase my rent next year
How much do you want to increase
I want to rise to
Four thousand two hundred yuan a month
Why are you up a little bit
You have gone up a lot
It's only two hundred yuan
How are you two hundred
You have risen by seven hundred
If it goes up by 700 yuan
I will take you
Four thousand seven hundred yuan
No. Did you make a mistake?
I have always been
Three thousand five a month
Are you wrong
I keep accepting you
Four thousand yuan a month
Sister, go slowly
Come again
Transaction is being processed
Please get your banknotes back
Started again
Is there any hope this time
do not know
Fill in here
President Gong invested 5 million for us
How much is left
More than thirty thousand
Then it will fail this time
We are all over
In theory
Then why didn't you say it earlier
Keep your voice down
Didn't you say it last time
Is there more than two million?
After last time
Teacher Gao changed the plan again
The instrument has also been re-adjusted
Is there any hope this time?
can
Yes you always say yes
Then what do you want me to say
Is there really hope this time?
What did Teacher Gao say?
Forget it
Teacher Gao is not quite right now
What Liu Yang said
Can you calm down
Ten million was spent before and after
How do you keep me calm
You go to the casino
Didn't you spend money like that?
To shut up
Over over over over
It's all over
Lei Haowen
Can you grow up
No wonder Gu Xiaoling looks down on you
Correct
Xiaoling, Xiaoling bless me
Xiaoling bless me
Xiao Xiao Xiao Ling
How are you doing
Just like that
I have been
I didn't care about her
Congratulations and bless me
Is something wrong with Xiaoling?
What did her friends post?
speak
You look
Xiaoling
Xiaoling signed with He Mu
prenuptial agreement
Who
Xiaoling open the door
Open the door
Open the door, I have something to tell you
What are you doing
Open the door
No what are you doing
You can't marry him
What's up with you
What's so good about He Mu
He Mu can give me what I want
You sell yourself for money
You know a fart
Since you are all selling
You might as well sell it to me
OK
He Mu now pays 5 million
How much do you pay
Five million i give you
Then you transfer to me now
I have no money now but
You have no money
What are you doing
I have no money but temporarily
You have no money
You are a pauper for the time being
Your temporary is forever
After I succeeded alone
I am worth 300 million
Waiting to regret you
You wait
Get out of here
Gu Xiaoling
What's so great about you
I told you you must regret it
Don't you look more beautiful?
Don't you just have a good figure and a good character
I must buy you
Hao Wen
Be more open
Maybe you and Xiaoling
Really no fate
I don't understand
For five million
Sold myself
Don't you say that Xiaoling
How good is He Mu?
What is good about him
Doesn't he have two bad money?
Must succeed this time
It will definitely succeed this time
rest first
Don't watch it, rest first
What happened
I do not know either
Teacher Gao suddenly
Stopped the machine
What is the result?
Not out
Haven't entered the testing phase yet
What do you think
Are you persuaded
I am high in this life
Never counseled
Then why at the last moment
Suddenly called out
You in my heart
Always one
Repeated defeat and repeated defeat
Teacher Gao who can't die and lose
But this time
I am a little scared
What are you afraid of
I'm afraid if it fails
Our laboratory has to close
What are you afraid of after closing
I'm not afraid, I already admit it
I am a loser in my life
but
But these staff
Liu Yang, you
And Hao Wen
They pinned
So much hope
Paid so much
Money time
Even bankrupted
If it fails this time
I do not know
How to face them
Before thirty-two
I haven't failed
But the business call
Made me lose everything
At that time everything was lost
Escaped back home
But now thinking
Let me grow the fastest
Most harvested
Instead, it’s the failed experience
You are not afraid of failure
afraid
But I am more afraid of giving up
Just don't give up
Failure is the step to success
But if i give up
Then failure is really a failure
But if it fails this time
We have to give up
Do not
Just pause
I will do my best
Put the laboratory back in operation
Maybe in this life
You can't see the day of success
If halfway
I will never see it in my life
The day of success
We continue
carry on
Teacher Gao
When i left home
My dad told me
Happiness is the most important
Enjoy the fun of struggle
is the most important
Your father is wiser than you
Ha ha
Xiao Wu
High teacher high teacher