[To Dear Myself]
[Ep18]
Do you get used to it?
It's ok
What do you mean?
I know, you are excellent
So what have you been up to?
I have researched Lubao's market
Research?
About what?
You shouldn't ask this
I can't tell you even if you ask me
Why?
Because now president Pan and president Wang
are opponents in the negotiation
We are in different companies
It's all about work
Why do I feel we are estranged?
No
It has nothing to do with the two of us
It's work
What if I think it has something to do with us?
If you think so
We need to know this
I can't inqure about your work
And you can't ask me about my work
Ok
Well. Let's change the topic
Are you satisfied with this house?
Of course I am satisfied
I am satisfied
as long as the house belongs to you and me
Sorry, kept you waiting
So...
We want to buy that house
The house on Jiangyang Road?
Correct
Mr. Chen called me yesterday
I remembered it wrong
I mistook it to another one
We have sold it the day before yesterday
Or, you can see other houses?
Here, good bye
Ok
Brother
Get me one
You bought one that day, right?
I want to buy another one
For you
For me?
You have stomach problem, right?
Take it, you need to drink warm water
Brother Yang, I know this brand
It's so expensive
It's just a thermal mug
Thank you
Look at you
Why are you teary?
You are so kind to me
Silly girl
You said, it's an art exhibition
Yes
All the designers here will attend Florence Biennale
It's top art
So beautiful
Actually
When it comes jewelry design, it has classicism
orientalism, abstractionism and the influence of abstractionism
Like Picasso's daughter
She is the representative of surrealism
Tiffany represents modernist style
What style do you like?
Me?
I like Tiffany's Flower Rhyme series
She integrates the modernism with rigidness and softness
It's romantic and harmonious
I get it. Wait for me
Thank you
Xiaoling, I know you will like it
You are right
Designers are so particular about lights,
shadows, colors and lines
Every design is the works of art
Yeah
If you think he loves me
He has the expensive watch, car and villa
But he just gives me this?
But if you think he doesn't love me,
he invites me to dinner every day and contacts me actively
I can feel his true affectionateness
It's not love, or romance
He is stingy
If a man really loves a woman
he will spend money for her as long as he can afford it
Xiaoling
Just break up
No
Why?
I don't want to regret it after I get old
I don't want to give up when I have such a good man
But he doesn't love you
No, he loves me
He is stingy, that's all
It's ok
His money will be mine after we get married
He can be stingy as he likes
You think, a stingy man like him will share money with you?
Xiaoling
Do you love him?
I love money, he has money
So I love him
You love money, you should earn it yourself
Why do you rely on the man?
Li Siyu, you are smart, capable
a good student in a top university
But I am not that stuff
My family can't help me
My only advantage is my face
Rich people are not stupid
Even if he loves you, why he must marry you?
So I try to enrich myself
I need to be more capable
I go for fitness every day
I am a good golf player
I have subscribed all the official accounts
Can you?
So I am learning art appreciation
I resign from a real estate company
Then I work in a golf club
Then I work in the gallery
My next plan is to learn English
I am not taking a shortcut as you think
I'm very tired
You think everything is fine after you marry a rich man?
What if he has an affair?
You think a poor guy won't have an affair?
Anyway, I believe Liu Yang
Don't listen to her
I believe Liu Yang and Yiming
Well, how's it going between you and Liu Yang?
He gave me an expensive vacuum cup yesterday
Just vacuum cup, you are so happy?
It's better than a picture album
Zhizhi, you are mocking me
You are good now
We have endless disputes in family
Zhizhi
Why you didn't wear my clothes?
Why you still didn't change your bag?
It's too expensive to wear it
Silly girl
Well, Zhizhi
I asked you last time
Would you work with me in the sales department?
Thank you, sister Siyu
I have discussed with Liu Yang
Yuwei is still young
I need to take care of her
We should talk about it in the future
I told them
Liu Yang won't have an affair
You women can't talk about anything meaningful?
Meaningful?
Why you didn't throw the cup away?
I can still use it
Why throw it?
Use the new cup
It's the same
Both for drinking water
Where did you put my vacuum cup?
I returned it back
Returned?
It's so expensive
I asked them to return it
They declined me in the beginning
They said, I had no invoice
Guess what
Then I told them if I couldn't get the refund
I would call the police for their occupying the public area
A cup
Then they gave in
means a lifetime
Then they refunded the money
But the refund is a shopping voucher
It's ok
When will your mother go back?
I will persuade her
So we still differ in the evaluation of Lubao
I think you lack the confidence in Lubao
Confidence comes from strength
But don't forget
I still have Lubao III
Its performance far surpasses Lubao II
Mr. Pan
As I know, Lubao III has flaws
Gao Zhengdao said it, right?
He just wants to sell his theory
He is so ridiculous like a mad dog
When I have the time, I will critize him with an article
I need to teach him a lesson
I attended professor Gao's lecture
But my conclusion doesn't come from him
My company did a little research
Wu
I inquired a lot
I found nothing
He is guarding against us deliberately
We should expose the relationship between Liu Yang and Li Siyu
It's a sure thing
But if we don't take action now
we will have no chance after 5 experts' evaluation next week
How do you know it's five experts?
The director told me to entertain them
I am in charge of round trips and meals of those experts
Do you know who they are?
Yes
Take a good look
Carefully
Why?
Why Wang Ziru has the report?
But I don't have
Wang Ziru knows the problems better than me
Why?
President Pan, we are working on this
We plan to give you a full report at the end of the month
They have the report in advance
It's your negligence of work
President Pan
From the test data, Lubao III has no problem
User experience is much more important than your data
But the problems reflected in this report are biased
But I am passive in the negotiation, you know?
Li Siyu
Don't think it has nothing to do with you
Let me ask you, what are you doing recently?
I am working hard for the target of 500 million in three months
How much did you make?
More than 200 million
After the report comes out, we lose 300 million
As a sales director
you only care about performance
rather than the products
It's also dereliction of duty
President Pan
I think this report reminds us of something
Before Lubao III becomes perfect
it's a bit risky if it comes to the market on a large scale
Let me ask you
What's perfect?
What is perfect?
Product upgrade is perfection
Improve product performance during use
You think it's risky?
If it's risky, I am totally in this
Study this report carefully
Find out their weakness
I need to turn the table in the next negotiation
Dismiss
Li Siyu, you should stay
How is the bidding?
Almost ok
President Pan
Before printing the package, do you need to check it?
No need
You won't check the quotation?
You will make the decision
I only have one request
We need to win the bid
President Pan
No one can guarantee this
You have to promise me
Li Siyu
The situation is here
This report comes out
We are going to lose our last hope
So we must win the bid
Otherwise I and you
will be kicked out out of new energy circle
You did this, right?
Yes
Why do you research Lubao in secret?
First
I didn't research in secret
I did it in broad daylight
Second
I mentioned it to you before
But you didn't say you would research Lubao III
How can I tell you?
Do you know?
Your report ruined my one-month work
It shows your dereliction of duty
Pan also said so
Pan scolded you?
A bloody scold
So president Wang taught him a lesson
Right?
You are laughing
My work paid off
Of course I should be happy
What the hell?
Look at your words
It's malicious slander
Every word in it is the fact
Lubao is less than four billion
It's a fact?
If Lubao III can solve my questions
Lubao's evaluation may reach 4 billion
But now absolutely impossible
Why do you see Lubao III's problems rather than its strength?
This is my duty
My responsibility is to remind my boss of the possible trouble
Or what she should be cautious about
Have you ever thought if my boss knew you did this,
what would he think of me?
It's two different matters
No, the same matter
He might even think I revealed something to you
Wang Ziru would think so too
So you sacrificed me
I didn't want to sacrifice you
I just do my duty
You don't know anything
The question is who will believe it?
Believe it or not
We need to do our part in our respective scope
The thing is you have a lot to do
Why do you make this report?
This is Tianyi's largest project for now
I work in Tianyi now
I need to prove myself, right?
You prove yourself by putting me in dilemma
You exaggerated it
I have told you, it has nothing to do with us
It's the battle between two companies
Before that, we are battling now
I didn't mean that
You can deceive yourself
But don't deceive others
Siyu...
For this report
Every one of you should give me a solution
Put it on my desk the day after tomorrow
Ok
Also remember to keep it secret
Yes
Don't tell others
Ok
Back to work
Thank you, brother Yang
During the bidding, your help is much appreciated
To be honest
I am the team leader
I don't have the final say
You need to speak with your products
I know
Don't worry, I won't get you in dilemma
We will follow the rules
I just hope you can tell me the news in advance
I want to be better prepared
As long as I don't violate the principle
I won't be caught of practicing favouritism
I will help you
Next, experts will be responsible for this
We will just assist them
To avoid suspicion
we'd better not meet or contact each other
Are you ok?
You should make the decision
I only have one request
You must win the bid
President Pan, no one can guarantee this
You have to promise me
Director Li
President Pan is out
It's ok
Zhizhi
Liu Yang just called
He needs to work overtime
He won't come back for dinner
Mom, I'm hungry
You just finished the diner, you are hungry now?
Come, go...
What are you eating?
Potato chips
Who gave it to you?
Me
Mom
It's expired potato chips, I threw it away
Why did you pick it up again?
You even give it to Yuwei
It just expired a few days
It's food
I have tasted it, it's ok
No
You can't let Yuwei eat it
It's expired
Why?
Why she can't eat it?
So picky
Mom
Yuwei is my daughter
She is not picked up or adopted
It's my blood
I want to give her the best things in the whole world
I can't allow her to eat expired potato chips
Whatever
You should take credit for having a daughter, right?
Ridiculous
Mom
What?
You have said so many times
I have had enough now
Let me tell you
If you say so to me and Yuwei again,
you should leave
You'd better go home
Why?
It's my son's home
I will live here as I want
Want to drive me away? No way
Go
Grandma
What are you doing?
You don't go, I will go
Stop it
She doesn't like you at all
Grandma...
Grandma
Mom...
What's wrong, mom?
Hello
What?
Dad
Liu Yang
Bed No. 34's family
The doctor is ready to see you
Yuwei
Wait here
Good girl
You come here in time
The patient is safe now
Doctor
What's wrong with my mom?
My initial diagnosis is, it's an acute myocarditis attack
It may have arterial blockage
Is that ok?
We won't know until she has a coronary angiography
The patient needs to rest in bed recently
She needs a light diet
And don't irritate the patient
Ok
You need to prepare for angiography now
Why did mom suddenly get sick?
We quarrelled
I knew it
I don't know it will be like this
If I knew it, I would...
Usually, you often contradict my mom
Why do you have so much resentment?
No
Why do you blame me indiscriminately?
It's ok that you lose your temper in front of me
My mom is so old with a poor health
You even contradict her
You are so ridiculous
Dad
Come
Brother Yang, is aunt ok?
She is safe now
Are you ok?
What can I do for you?
Thank you
Mom gave Yuwei expired potato chips I tossed in the trash can
So we quarrelled
I can bear whatever she says
But when she despises Yuwei, I really can't tolerate it
I am sorry for my harsh words
Sorry
You should take some rest
Finally you answer my call
I am busy
Where are you now?
The company
I will pick you up right now
Now?
Siyu, I want to see you
I want to talk to you
We will talk tomorrow
I am busy today
No
I need to see you today
I know you didn't have dinner
I made some porridge
I have no appetite
You need to eat
Go
Still angry?
No
I have thought about it for a whole day
You questioned me today
I have so many things to do
Why do I have to do this?
I really forgot your situation
I am so impatient to prove myself in Tianye
The negotiation with Lubao is the top priority of Tianyi Group
So I take it as a breakthrough point
And I think
Researching the quality of the brand has
nothing to do with the sales director, so...
Sorry
It's my fault
My apology
You're right
It's our problem
I have told them to make up for the loss because of your report
Here
What is this?
In my research, I inquired about your advertising and after-sales service
You should give it to president Wang
Why do you give it to me?
She doesn't care about it
But you as the sales director
I think you need it
The last few pages are my suggestions
I hope it can make up for my fault
Thank you
Siyu
Let's go to see the house tomorrow
Then sign the contract
What happened?
Still blaming me?
No
Thinking of something else
What's the matter?
Lin Ling has a client
Very important to her, to everyone and the company
She needs to get it
Now there is a grey channel
It can help her win the client
Do you think she should use the grey channel?
What's your take?
I don't know
You have said, it's grey channel
You have your own judgement
But I am also afraid to lose the client
Siyu
We have known each other for five years
You are never afraid to lose clients
Because even if you lose, you can find them back soon
Am I?
Of course
Actually losing clients is not a big deal
But if you lose another thing, you will never find it back
Sign the contract and buy the house tomorrow
Liu Yang
Director
I want to ask you a favor
Don't be so polite
Say it
My mother is sick and hospitalized
I want to borrow some money from you
Well, wait for me
Who?
It's Liu Yang
His mother is sick
He wants to borrow some money
Borrow money?
Will he return the money?
Did your cousin return the money last week?
Mom
How do you feel?
I'm fine, much better
Drink some water
No need...
I'm fine
Excuse me
Hello, Liu Yang
My wife disagrees
I can't do anything
I can give you my case-dough, 5000 yuan
Director, no, thanks
I will think about other ways
I'm sorry
Thank you, anyway
Xing
I want to ask you a favor
My mother is sick and hospitalized
She needs a bypass surgery
Just bought a house?
Congratulations...
Classmate, I need to ask you a favor
I can understand
Yes, it's not easy to have a startup
It's ok
Thank you, anyway
Bye
Hello
Hello, sir, do you want to have a real estate?
No
Bed No.34's family
Did you pay the money?
Not yet
Hurry up
Many people are waiting for surgery
Pay early
You will have the surgery sooner
Mom, what do you want to eat?
I will tell Zhizhi to make it for you
How much is my surgery?
Never mind it
We have the money
I don't want it
Mom, you need to do the surgery
You really have the money?
Yes
Don't worry about it