# Google translate version for your reference #
Twenty years ago
I leave my work to start a business
Everyone said I was crazy
Fourteen years ago
I take out all the money
Invest in Emerald One's research and development
You said I was crazy again
Five years ago, I insisted on the green treasure
Must transform and upgrade
You guys still say i'm crazy
It turns out I'm not crazy
I succeeded
Mr. Pan
This previous market
And the current market
It's not the same
But courage and vision
In any era
right
Mr. Pan
That's also out of date
And cautious
President Wang
This is the rule of your financial circle
about us
For business people
Only one way
That's going forward
IMHO
Want to make the green treasure bigger
There are many ways
But you
I chose one
The dumbest and most adventurous
But the most effective
Make money in five years
too slow
President Wang
If you want to make quick money
You shouldn't invest in Emerald
Because of my original intention to create Lubao
Not to make money
But to open up history
Ok, deal
Green treasure next step
Just rebuild the park
Rebuild the production line
I object
invalid objection
Effective or not effective
Let's vote by show of hands
well
Agree to emerald three
Two more production lines
Please raise your hand
Four votes in favor
Fang Zhan
Is it
Do you want to abstain
I vote against
I object
Five votes against
Now that the result is out
Then we proceed to the next agenda
Discuss Mr. Wang's proposal
Adjust business layout
Create a future concept
First, Mr. Wang
Tell us about the background of the proposal
Ok
Chairman, directors
No need to understand
I object
According to the articles of association
Board of Directors
When discussing important matters
Chairman has no decision-making power
but
He has a veto
More than ten years
I never use
This power
But today I decided to use
And I will use it often in the future
I have seen it today
Pan Zhiyong is overbearing
This is his style
Not making money for five years
But he can tell
Not making money
Pan Zhiyong's first purpose
But as an investor
Nor my money
It's a strong wind
I still have
How about countless limited partners
They treat me
There are performance requirements
Does Lvbao really have such a charter?
Have
Written at the beginning of the establishment
Just never used it
I almost forgot
Can it be changed
Difficult
You have followed Pan Zhiyong
More than ten years
Do you have any idea
Can convince him
Almost impossible
He is very stubborn
Things he decides
No one can stop
Coincidence
What i want to do
No one can stop
what's up
Don't see it
What do i ask you
I will hand in my homework
Go aside
Count you again
that's it
So what
No raise
Don't you just think
Looking for a low-paying job?
Why are you still asking for a raise?
that
The premise of low wages
You have to live less
How much work have you sent me recently
Yes you promised me
Can be late and leave early
I left at three in the afternoon
But you at eleven o'clock in the night
Give me a voice call on WeChat
Talk about work
Why don't i ask for a raise
Do not worry
Wait for the call to go online
You deserve a lot of rewards
Speak for words
Not leaving yet
I think you should
Compliment me
You behaved well recently
Keep going
Sister Li
You cursed recently
Much less than before
Good performance
Keep going
That's it for today
Let's end
Chen Yiming, you stay
You come with me
That don't take it
President Wang
Where are we going now
You better let me breathe first
I'm so prepared
boarding
Sister Ziru is here
How to trim it today
It's not me today, it's him
Ok
Come on, wash my hair first
Please wait
Mr. Wang, I
Go
Hello, please
Wash here
beware of the steps
Can it be tight?
can
How to trim it today
Just look at it, I can do it
Good good good
All right
This is what I want to subvert
The brand strategy of Tianyi Group
Chen Yiming
This is the vice president I value most
Miss Gu
Thank you
This panji is really good
To be honest
There used to be a chef in our family
The dessert made
Really great
I can still eat it now
Does he make desserts?
If you want to eat, you have to go to France
He is a maasai
Go back after retirement
I kind of like France
I do not like
The overall feeling of Europe now
Behind
If there is no business at home,
I won't go once a year
Where do you like best
to be frank
When I went abroad at 18
I am very reluctant
my favorite
Han Tang
That's a brilliant
that
What year did you go abroad
That year you were eighteen
I am 51 years old
Is the plan I want available?
No way
Before twelve o'clock this evening
Must be given to me
Then I will wait for you until two o'clock in the morning
If two o'clock in the morning
You can't deliver yet
I stayed up all night
Drive to your house and beat you up
Take you five minutes
I met someone today
He was me for half a year
The best condition among people I met
Which group
Across the birth life group
Upstart group
We both added WeChat
In my experience
After breaking up
I should also chat on WeChat
But after breaking up
Never show up
People don't like you
impossible
At dinner
Have a good chat
If you think it's an opportunity
I won't find you
You take the initiative to find someone
This
Will it appear to me
Too unreserved
From a sales perspective
It's never wrong to take the initiative
have you slept
What are you doing
This grandson deleted me
What happened to him
You laugh at me
You still laugh at me
People deleted me
what's wrong with you
I don't like you
How could I be so good-looking
He doesn't like me
Miss Gu, hello
Where's your sister Zhou?
Miss Gu, I'm here
Sister Zhou
You introduce me to the 57th
Isn't it a marriage trust?
What is this
Do you have any misunderstanding
So don't worry
We sit there and talk slowly
Go
Bring me the tablet
Thank you sister Zhou, we are leaving
I wish you happiness
Bye bye
Come
Come sit here
Sit here sit here
let me see
The fifty-seventh you said
Is this Mr. Zhao?
Yes it's him
You guys are dating
Yes indeed
When we meet
Still had a good chat
But a break up
He blacked me
You say this behavior
What is not a marriage
How could it be a marriage care
It's even more unexplainable
We both make an appointment
Went to see penguins in Antarctica
Two hours later
I can't reach him anyway
It's weird
So don't worry
I'll ask you
There must be a misunderstanding
OK, you turn on the hands-free
no problem
Hello i am jerry
Hello, is it Mr. Zhao?
I come from your club
Miss Zhou
Miss Zhou, what is it?
Is such that
I am here
Want to give you a return visit
Make an appointment with Miss Gu
Do you feel okay
quite pretty
We can talk
Then you think you still have
Is it possible to develop
I think it's okay to be friends
If you get married
A little older
She is too old for you
I still love
Girls under twenty-five
I still don't think you are old
Miss Gu
You let me slow down
You have some tea to cool down
You say how old i look
Twenty six up to twenty six
such
I still have one
Fifty-eight-year-old professor
Billions of assets
Very good conditions
Like you
Around thirty
He should be able
I have fallen to
Only old men can see it
Miss Gu, you know
Woman's age and worth
Is inversely proportional
Man
Age is not too big a problem
You just said
I look like only twenty-six
No matter how well you maintain it
Where is the ID number
This one looks good
I want this
Send to me send to me
Ok ok
Come pick me up
I knew there was a happy event today
You are winning
It's still a new stock
See what you said
How vulgar
What's that happy event
I'll go first
The boss is coming
You cover for me
Bye bye you
Don't be afraid
I'm here to save you
You are too exaggerated
You have a rare foot
I must cherish it
What did you say
See which one you like
Let's apply ice first
Give me the foot
slower
Why are you twisting so serious
Does it hurt
It hurts
Why
Bear with me
Bear with it, bear with it, bear with it
Yu Wei
Mom butterfly
Yuwei, Yuwei, don't move
do not
Yu Wei
Mom helps you catch butterflies
do not move
Not later
Catch butterflies like this again
do you know
Ok
Why did you go
I went shopping
How can you take Yuwei
Throw it at home alone
Windows are not closed
Almost something happened just now
Just downstairs supermarket
I was back in five minutes thinking about it
Five minutes will not work
She is so young and active
Don't know what is dangerous
Can't be distracted for five seconds
There is also a supermarket downstairs
Caibi Farmers Market
50 cents expensive
The price of onion ginger garlic
Nearly twice as expensive
If you can't buy it, don't buy it later
Yu Wei
I can't climb higher anymore
do you know
Ok
Very dangerous
Pitiful dad
Why do you say that
You scold dad
Dad didn't say a word
Here, shoes on
Go to the room to play
Ok
I just spoke a little harder
I have to tell you something
Changsheng Community
There is a Fangcao kindergarten
I plan to turn Yuwei over
I know that kindergarten
Than Blue Sky Kindergarten
A big difference
Hardware facilities are a little bit worse
But the price
More than half cheaper
Zhizhi
prior to
I am against you taking Yuwei
Send to Jin Gu Duo
Because that is indeed beyond
Our class
But now this
Fangcao Kindergarten
Is it too low?
We couldn't reach golden bones before
And now
We can't even afford the blue sky
In addition to fragrant grass
No other choice
Sorry
it's all my fault
But i still
Worried that Yuwei is gone
Will not get used to
She will get used to it
Zhizhi
Hard for you all this time
The old Chinese doctor didn't let you
Taboo?
Don't you instigate
Can you drink less
Drink
Can't you drink less
Pour me up
Drink less
Upside down
Drink you to death
Come come drink
Lei Haowen
I ask you something
You must answer me honestly today
You let me answer you honestly
It depends on what punishment you use to me
Chili water tiger stool
Regardless of the role
If it is a beauty
My superior name recruit
Subordinate names are also recruited
You said
How old i look
I'll just say if you don't drink
Say
Say you look like eighteen years old
It seems that I have an attempt to you
If you say you are twenty-six years old
It seems I can't eat grapes
Say grapes are sour
So transparent, fair and open
you
Twenty-four years old
Why am I young and beautiful
But i am now
Can't even get married
That might be fate
It's not here yet
When will the fate arrive?
There is another possibility
The destined person has arrived
Your consciousness didn't feel it
Don't drink
What are you doing
Say you still don't listen
Gu Xiaoling
I can't get married anyway
Why are you stealing my wine
Gu Xiaoling
You're a little good
you do not say
I want to fight for another ten years
Where is this?
what happened
What is this
Don't lie on the table, dirty
Come come
Get up
Fight for another ten years
I'll be 40 years old after another ten years
I can't even get married
Come
Dirty table
Get up and say okay? come
You want to marry
Isn't it easy
Do not cry
The one who fell in love with me
I don't like it
The person i like
People don't like me
do not Cry
You won't be pretty if you cry
Stop crying, okay
you
If you want to cry again
me
I want to take your ugly picture
Make an emoji package
Put it in the circle of friends
Take a look
Lei Haowen, dare you
Do you see me dare
I shoot
I can't take pictures if you turn around
Come, keep crying
I will show you
Various angles
Yes yes this angle
exactly
Cry cry keep crying
Unless you promise me not to cry
Come take a selfie, come
You sit down
Then unless you promise me not to cry
look
Just don't cry
Let's eat well
do not Cry
Come, let me pick you up
I'm very annoying lately
So annoying
I'm really really annoying lately
Is very annoying
So annoying
I think
I want to find a boyfriend
I want to marry
God
Find her a boyfriend
Don't let her go crazy
Oh my god
Where is my man
Give me quickly
I want i want to eat this
Above this
Above
OK, no problem
I'll pick it for you
Ok
on
Which
On it
This one
Ok
There are dogs
Are you okay, Xiaoling
Lei Haowen, come
Come and help me
Come and bite me
Why another one
Withdraw
Lei Haowen
You can't save you bastard
Come, come, come, hurry up
More than one dog
Come here, let me carry you
Lei Haowen
I turn it quickly
Run fast
Go go go go go
how is it going
Have the three dogs chased you?
No, no chase
I'm exhausted
Tired to death, tired to death, tired to death
Why are you laughing
I just suddenly felt
Mood improved
You said
I want a man
It gives me some cherries
what's the meaning
Cherries are good
In China
In traditional culture
Cherry refers to
Cherish the person before you
What you said is true
Of course it is true
Confucius has said
Cherry refers to
Marry this person
Abbreviated as courtesy, justice and shame
Can't talk nonsense
really
Really
You just have a good foot, keep it for use
Stop noisy
Mother Liu Yuwei
The financial notice says
Liu Yuwei's living expenses for the next quarter
Haven't paid
Please apply as soon as possible
Don't affect
Liu Yuwei's admission in the next quarter
Manager Hu
Is there any hope for my transfer?
Don't go to this kindergarten
I want the original kindergarten
Yuwei, obedient
This kindergarten is also very good
Mother don't want me
I want to wear teacher
I want Teacher Liu
I want to play with Susan
I want to play with Xiaoxiao
I want to play with Brother Haohao
Yuwei, obedient
This kindergarten
There are also many good teachers
And many good kids
I don't want me
Yu Weiguai
Mom will be late if I don't go in
I won't go i won't go
Teacher, what do you do
The child goes to kindergarten on the first day
It's all like this
It depends on your parents
I'm so ruthless
Come
Yuwei, gone
Mom, you don't want me
Mother, don't want me
Go in with the teacher, be good
Hello, Mr. Wang
Yiming, are you in the company?
I'm here
I'm in the office
I have something
Only you can help me
OK, I'll go up right now
it is good
Ok
The information here
All very important
Let others fix it
I really don't worry
I will plug in this memory stick
What's the reason
Can't turn on the machine
I just tried
Its memory stick and motherboard
No problem
I think it might be
System reason
It was fine yesterday
All right
I didn't plug it in
should be
Gosh
All right
Am I stupid?
If you are stupid
In this world
There are no smart people
Don't tell anyone about this
This is the little secret between us
will not
I will never tell anyone
Don't lie to me
Obviously sold for 20 million
You let me write a hundred million
this is not
President Fang, President Yuan, go ahead
Bye bye
Isn't this fake
This is not fake
This is called data
Pan Zhiyong will not agree
Did that
This is the decision of Mr. Wang and I
Which President Wang
She is a master in this area
But now the sales are under the control of Pan Zhiyong
He has to read the report every day
And also
Call me to the office and ask
In case something is wrong
I can't hide from him
Then we will make two sets
Show him one set
One set for our own use
This
This issue
I haven't done it
This also matters
Your vital interests
Your equity
Will be cashed soon
Emerald's valuation goes up
Your net worth will increase
Xiaoling said
Siyu's company
Officially launched next Monday
She always feels a wolf is chasing
Xiaoling also persuaded
Let her not fight too hard
Of course I can't persuade
Gu Xiaoling recently
Blind date is hit
You say i want
at this time
Come in
Lei Haowen
Die if you want to die
I won't stop you
Hurry up and say hello to uncle
Yuwei, why are you here?
I miss Uncle Haowen
Zhizhi said she was going out
I said, let me take Yuwei
You suddenly said you want to meet
I still want to see you
Our place
Is it not suitable for children
Or let's change the place
It's ok
I know the boss here
Yu Wei
Uncle, give you some juice
good or not
Ok
sit
Has Yuwei adjusted to the new kindergarten?
Anyway, these two days
Stop crying
But obviously can feel
She is very unhappy
How about the new kindergarten
Just like that
I was
Should really listen to you
You said that if I am transferred
Have a skill
I am not now
Make Yuwei suffer such a grievance
You were too unconfident at that time
Think of it now
Actually lazy
I always feel
I just rely on Liu Yang
My day
How can I live on
who knows
When Liu Yang is unreliable
This day
There are times when I can't go on
No one in this world can trust
Only you can trust
How are you and Liu Yang
Just like that
Two days ago
He suddenly said something to me
Sorry
Also told me
Worked hard
You said
I have been with him for so many years
Never heard of
He talks to me like this
Instead, I'm getting divorced now
He suddenly said this
I really do not know
I should be relieved
Still helpless
can only say
People will change
Yes
People must also change
People will get old
Why are you still sighing
Do not sigh
No time to sigh
I'm trying my best
How can there be a better way
Can go to catch
The person i want to catch