[To Dear Myself]
[Ep7]
I believe the police will prove my innocence
You think you can withstand the investigation?
If I can't stand the investigation
the whole sales department can't either
You even want to get the sales department implicated?
I can tell you, it's impossible
We have only one solution
You should resign
I will never resign because of invoice
Ziting, where's sister Yuan?
Went to see the client
When will she come back?
I don't know
The number you have dialed is busy now
Sorry
Where's president Pan?
He went abroad
Ok
Ok, I'll call you back
Hello
The number you have dialed is powered off
Sorry
It's powered off
He is on the plane now
Sister
Sister, what's going on?
Sister Siyu
Someone wants to find sister Siyu troubles
You should go back now
Sister Siyu
Something's wrong?
Yes
What they said is true?
What?
The rumor has it that you have
embezzled several hundred thousand yuan
Nonsense
I never embezzle
They have called the police
Police are underway to arrest you
What happened?
Someone did this on purpose
Who?
Sister Siyu, I believe you won't do such things
But...
Will it be ok?
No idea
What should we do now?
Hurry
Excuse me
What?
You have a problem or miss me?
Why are you so silent?
You want me to appreciate your beauty quietly?
Wait for me
I am coming now
What happened?
I need a moment
Doesn't answer the phone?
Chen Yiming doesn't answer my call, either
What's going on?
I do not know
As I know, president Fang and HR department want to fire her
So be it
She should resign
Whether she is fired or resigns,
her career will be ruined
It's hard for her to find a job in the future
Li Siyu is a workaholic
It's such a torture for her
So I am worried
Siyu, go in from there
Pal, stop
Why do you kill a good guy?
I can't tell who is good or bad
Go
Water
Thank you
Can you tell me what's going on now?
I want to resign
What happened?
Can you raise me?
Of course
That's what I am thinking about
I knew you would say so
And I will do so
So can you tell me why now?
It's ok, you have me
Hello
President Mao
Hello...
Yes... I am Chen Yiming
Now?
Ok, no problem
Ok, I'll be there right away
Ok...
No problem...
Ok
Thank you
Goodbye, Mr. Mao
Ok
Goodbye
Siyu
My friend introduced me to a job
But the boss wants to see me now
You are going?
I need to raise you
So I need to find a job, right?
Can you understand me?
Is Li Siyu with you?
Come, she needs someone to talk now
Siyu
Xiaoling is coming now
I'm running late
I have to go now
Li Siyu hasn't changed her mind?
No matter what, we need to fire her
before Pan Zhiyong comes back
Are we too cruel?
Don't worry
Li Siyu can find a new job soon with her ability
And she will have a better treatment
I led her for seven years
I really hate to see this
You led her for seven years
So you must know her well
Will she give the post of director to you?
No
So with her ability and ambition
will she go easy on you in the end?
The destiny is settled the moment Pan Zhiyong starts the competition
You don't need to feel guilty
After sister Yuan ran the sales department
I could apply for PR fee with her signature
to get rid of the troublesome overtime pay application
So sister Yuan did this to you on purpuse?
Except her, no one knows my reimbursement of 500 yuan
And she could prove my innocence
But she said she knew nothing
And she is out of touch so far
Bitch
What if you ask your colleagues for help?
If your colleagues can prove the unwritten rule
I think you can prove your innocence
Most of the colleagues go to sister Yuan's team
You think they will speak for me?
So sister Yuan is the solution
You need to talk to her
I think she won't be so cold-hearted to you, right?
From Lin Ling's case, I know she is no longer the one she used to be
No compromise
First, don't resign
unless they find out the truth and prove your innocence
Second
If Yuan Huizhong does this on purpose,
you should fight against her
How?
Discredit her and ruin her
Liu Yang got promoted
A chief or a director, I am not sure
Anyway, he is promoted
He is so busy every day
Of course I live in Liu Yang's house
His house is big
I have a private room
Ok, stop it
I am busy
I will call you back later, bye
What the hell
Yuwei, drink some water
Ok
Ask you something
Say it, mom
Did your wife drink my medicine?
She did, I think
She didn't drink at all
She hid the medicine in kitchen cabinet
I see it all
Don't force her to drink it
And we didn't plan to have a second child yet
When will you plan to have?
Not now
No, Yuwei is in kindergarten
And our country encourages a second child
You should answer the country's call, right?
Yes, it's a new policy
But it's based on each family's specific situation
The specific situation of our family is
you need to have a second child as soon as possible
Understand?
I have a good health now
Otherwise I will be too old to take care of your kid
Mom, I'm busy now
We will talk about it another time
It's important
Think about it
Ok
I'll discuss with Zhizhi
No, no need to discuss with her
It's your decision to make
Grandma, I want cookies
No
Your mom says, you can't eat too much
I am talking to you, can you hear me?
Yes...
Wait
I'll get you cookies
Here
Be careful
Have a good rest after you go back
Don't think about anything
Watch out for steps
Yes  -Be careful
You have so many things to do tomorrow
Ok
I asked Chen Yiming to pick you up
Thank you
Tell us if you need any help
Ok
I have seen all the dramas about harem fight
I know all the means
Go
Be careful
Bag
Bye
Come
Drink some hot honey water
Sorry
I can't be with you all day long
Is there any new progress?
I don't want to talk about it anymore
How about your work?
You know I am innocent
We used this way to get overwork reimbursement for half a year
Sister Siyu, I want to help you
If I admit it now,
I will ask for troubles myself
But if you don't help me
they will report you in the future
I...
Let me think
Li Siyu
Please come to finance department
Here you are
Take all the false invoice back
Resubmit an application for overwork payment of the same money
What do you mean?
And in the future, overtime pay is overtime pay
PR fee is PR fee
Don't mix them
What happened?
President Pan came back in advance
Come in
President Pan
I want to explain it to you
From beginning to end
I never overapply for reimbursement
It's over now
I need to explain even if it's over
I do not want to hear it
Why?
Because I know you
You won't do things like this for 500 yuan
You are innocent
President Pan
Li Siyu
I helped you this time
But I can't guarantee I can help you again next time
You know what to do?
The solution is you need to stand tall enough that they can't touch you
President Pan, I understand now
Do not worry
I will be a good leader
In three months, I will be the director
Great
Xiao Jia
Sister
Do you still have that wine?
Yes
I need it
Ok
Sister
Pour the wine
Since you trust me and follow me
I will never disappoint you
Let's work hard together
It doesn't matter who is the director in three months
The important thing is we live up to the company and friends
And ourselves
Cheers
Sister Siyu, we all listen to you
We speak with quality
Strength proves everything
We will be better than them
Come on
Drink
Sister Ziru
3, 2, 1
Another pose
Change the angle
Here...
Come, 3, 2, 1
Take a picture of us three girls
Ok
3, 2, 1
One more
One more...
Take more pictures
It's a bit too long
You haven't changed your work for ten years
You lack some experience
I dare not recommend to my clients
Our products are for post-90s
They won't want you
I think you should need a few more years
You are too old for us
Where are you now?
Near your company
I'll go to see you
I have a good news for you
Send me your location
Ok
When are you interested in this circle?
My dad likes it
So he forces me to work for this direction
So boring
I want to go now
Wait a moment
My dad made an appointment with a connoisseur for me
Go with me
Ok...
Excuse me
The colors and lines have strong visual impact
I like the brushstroke
So I think you like early works of Mondrian
Who?
The master of style
Don't tell me
You don't know him?
Of course I know
She has a lot of the works that you are talking about
You have a collection of Mondrian's paintings?
Which one?
The most famous one
It can't be Red, Yellow and Blue right?
Exactly
That's it
Miss Gu
The biggest dream of my life
is to see Mondrian authentic works with my own eyes
Can you invite me to your house?
We will talk about it another time
I need to see a friend
Excuse me
Miss Gu
Mondrian
Neoplasticism
Pure abstraction
Mondrian. Neoplasticism
President Pan came back in advance
He helped me
Finance department tells me to reapply for the reimbursement
Then it's over
So simple
It's out of thin air
It's just back to the original point
Great
But sister Yuan and I are completely over
Our relationship for seven years comes to an end
What a pity
Am I wrong?
No
It's so complicated
We can't become a sales director unless we experience these?
The workplace is so brutal?
I wouldn't lose my job if I had known the answer
Well
How about your job?
Can we stop talking about this?
Pure abstraction
Sorry
It's ok
Amazing
You can understand?
Deconstructivism
My friend recommended me to buy it
Do you think it will appreciate?
Deconstructionism appreciates every year
But Mbappe and Suarez
are believers of deconstructionism
Of course
Ronaldo and Pogba will disagree
Miss Gu, do you think so?
Sorry
Those you mentioned are all artists?
Yes
Why does it sound so familiar?
Excuse me
I think, the painting, you can consider about it
Really?
Amazing
Well
Sister Ziru called me
She invites us to a new energy lecture on the weekend
Let's go together
No
Sister Ziru specially invited you
I do not want to go
Go...
Anyway, you will idle around
You should go for a walk rather than stay at home
Maybe you will have a chance
How do you know I idle around?
I have been to a lot of places today
I mean
Sister Ziru has many friends
Maybe she can introduce a job for you
I can solve it by myself
No need her help
Your formal competition with sister Yuan will begin
Are you sure?
I will not lose to her in terms of ability
On the team
she almost has all the elites in the sales department
But my team is younger and more courageous
I can poach more outside
My only disadvantage is I don't have as many clients as she does
I can find some of my former clients for you
In case you need it
No need
What I need is mature sales
For the fierce fight
You will be busier than before, right?
I have no choice
Only three months
I can make it
I believe you can
But what about your body?
Are you sure?
I think it's ok
You travel almost each week and work overtime every day
And you need to drink with clients
Can your stomach stand it?
You want to talk about business trip, overwork, drinking
Or stomach?
What I want to say is you don't need to push yourself so hard
But...
But what?
But I have no job now
I don't need you to raise me
I can rely on myself
No, don't get me wrong
I know you wish me good
I also know you are in a bad mood
Can we stop quarrelling, ok?
You can't be out for too long, right?
You should go back now
How about you?
Me?
I will just sit for a while
Bye
The exhibition is so boring
Where do you want to go tonight?
I'll talk to you later
What are you doing?
Miss
The chair is very long
I can sit in the car
Why are you here?
I am here all along
I am not talking to you
I am talking to my girlfriend
It's your girlfriend?
I'm sorry
I need to talk to my girlfriend
Talk to you later
Are you sick?
You are haunting me everywhere
What do you want?
I'm helping you
Are we familiar?
I don't need your help
I can tell you
His name is Xiao Ke
My middle school classmate
I know him so well
He is worse than Lanke
Don't believe it?
Look the Moment
Look
He is a good classmate
But he is a disaster for women
So dangerous
So you can't judge a man by money
Don't go
I saved you
You should invite me to dinner
Or I invite you
Your name is Lei
Yes
Listen
Go as far as you can
Why are you so ungrateful?
Your conscience won't hurt?
Gu Xiaoling
Listen
I won't intervene in your business in the future
Otherwise I will be thunderstruck