# Google translate version for your reference #
Wait a minute, Mr. He will be there soon
Thank you
Miss Gu
Mr. He, hello
Hello there
Please sit down
Your coffee
Thank you
Mr. He, I'm going out first
Mr. He, we meet again
Yes
I only have fifteen minutes
This is from our gallery
Member Handbook
Miss Gu
The member manual can be couriered to me
You can also send an electronic version
Or i next time
Give it to me when I go to the gallery
you
Why do you want to go there in person
because
You are our most distinguished member
I judge
You are for me
I just made this trip
In order not to let Miss Gu
Run for nothing
Also to save time
Improve efficiency
I'm straight to the point
My name is He Mu
Male thirty-five years old
Graduated from Stanford University
Department of Computer Science
Returned home the year before last
Founded this company
Current year profit
Around 50 million
This is my diploma
This is my business license
This is my tax record certificate
I am very healthy
Love sports
Don't smoke, drink some alcohol occasionally
No family history of genetic diseases
This is my genetic test report
This is the last two years
Body test report
I have no history of marriage
But there are three love experiences
And the woman broke up peacefully
After breaking up
not any
Economic and emotional ties
I have no brothers or sisters
Where's the parents
Engaged in the education industry
Now retired
Retirement at home
The body is also very healthy
This is my account book
This is my certificate of honor
It's your turn
what
I have eight minutes
I do not quite understand
You can
Start with your living habits
I have good habits
very healthy
I also like sports
In addition
My parents are in my hometown
I
Miss Gu
Your thinking is a bit messy
Or else
I ask you to answer
OK
Do you smoke?
Do not smoke
drink wine
a little bit
Willing to give birth
Two or more children?
Willing
Can briefly introduce
Is your family structure
When i was eight
My dad died
Then my follow
My mother takes me
Married my stepfather
My stepfather is nice
Is an engineer
My mother is an ordinary clerk
In addition, I have one
Half sister
Now also starting his own business
The cause of father's death was
Car accident
No family history of genetic diseases
Absolutely not
Ok
height
One seven zero
whole
body weight
48 kg
Net weight
Wear underwear
Ok
Miss Gu, you fit exactly
My request for my future wife
I'm going to a meeting soon
next Thursday
Four forty four
By six twenty one
I have time
hope
Can date you
You you too
Miss Gu
My secretary, Miss Chang
Will send all my contact information
Give you
See you next week
Mother Yuwei
How about you take Yuwei
Go to the hospital
teacher
Yuwei has never before
This happened
Not before
Maybe it didn't happen
Yuwei has no problems
She already
I peeed my pants three times a week
This is not normal
She may have just changed to a new environment
A little uncomfortable
She has been in the kindergarten for half a month
Not used to
This daughter is too squeamish, right?
Teacher, will it be
What did she eat
Something not to eat
How can this be
Children in the garden are the same
If you really eat and drink
If there is any problem
Then other children have to have seizures
Why is your Liu Yuwei
Alone
mom
I want to go home
alright
It's almost time anyway
Today
You go back with your mother in advance
Thank you teacher, you bothered
Yu Wei
You never wet your pants before
What happened recently
Is it on purpose
Is not
why
mom
I want to go back to my original kindergarten
Is this kindergarten bad now?
This kindergarten is bad
why
Yuwei, don't be afraid, tell mom
Mom will protect you
The teacher scolded me
I am afraid
Then don't know what's going on
Just pee out
Why did the teacher scold you
The teacher said I eat slowly
Slow motion
Stop letting me eat
what
go
Mother Liu Yuwei
Are you to me
What's the misunderstanding
Liu Yuwei already
Told me all
There is no misunderstanding at all
Can you believe it all?
Is it hydrated?
Didn't you scold her
What am I scolding her for
She got into trouble
I as a teacher
Simply speaking two sentences won¡¯t work
Then stop and stop eating
That's because of your Liu Yuwei
She is peeing in her pants
The kids are still eating
I just let her
Stand aside for a while
Is this wrong
Is there a teacher like you
Director, have a few words
Good good
About this matter
I already understand
How about this
Teacher Fang, go out first
Let me and
Talk to Liu Yuwei's mother
Go
Principal
I ask for Yuwei
Change a teacher
Can't change
why
Actually, Teacher Fang
It¡¯s just getting a little short-tempered
Everything else is pretty good
She has no love at all
Unqualified teacher
We have standards here
Director, this is my daughter
Is our family's baby
I'll pay her to come here
I hope she gets
Best care
I'm not disgusted by the teacher
Mother Liu Yuwei
How much did you pay
Just want the best care
that
I can't be scared by the teacher
So scared to pee your pants
The teacher is
Louder
Your baby
Mental retardation
I'm still peeing my pants
Who can you blame for this?
Director, what is your attitude?
I think
As a parent
the first
Don't be too glassy
Are ordinary people
Family child
Frustration education
This is all good
second
Don't have to make an inch
How much do you do
Everyone knows this truth
I want to report to the superior department
I want to expose you
It's up to you
Best to let everyone know
Kindergarten like us
Only more than 1,000 yuan a month
The children eat and drink here
Not touched or hurt
And the teacher took the game
Able to read and read
Kindergarten like this
Where to find
let's go
go
Mom, I have more tomorrow
Come to this kindergarten
Mom, I can't come
I'll stay with dad at home
I promise not to eat randomly
No noise, no peeing
Mom, why are you crying
Mother guarantee
Not in the future
Let you be bullied again
Ok
Let's go
According to Mr. Li's proposal
Five hundred cities will be realized by the end of next year
Target of 8,000 service points
I pushed
Our monthly promotion fee
Should be at least
1.58 million
I will give you this number at most
Then i can't do it
is it possible
Exchange resources with other websites
Then our number of users
Must be at least one million
People will talk to us about resources
When will it reach a million
As long as the promotion is in place, I¡¯m fine
I'm fine as long as the money is in place
As long as you earn money back
I'm fine
Whoever kicks the ball
If not considering promotion
Before the end of this year
Can you reach
One million users
Do not consider promotion
But service must be considered
Our current franchisees
And the service point is not up
Even if it is measured
Will also lose
Within two months
Won another two hundred franchisees
Mr. Li, kill me
Even if one is implemented a day
I can at most in these two months
Implement sixty me
Row
I'll run with one hundred and forty left
Manager Li
Sister Tian
You help me book the nearest class today
Train ticket to Hefei
Ok
Xiao Lu, last time you said
Someone in Hefei wants to be a regional agent
Give me his information
it is good
That's it. The meeting ends
Gosh
President Li is going to die
Sister Fan
Take it out
Isn't it enough?
No money
Don't our company still have money
You figured it out
I figured it out
What about me
Other aspects are good
It's a small heart
President Yuan
Sorry
I didn't do some things well before
I apologize to you
You can talk
Pretty smart
I am not smart
But i won't be lazy
OK, I accept
But be my subordinate
Stress will be great
Can also learn something
I still don't understand
Li Siyu is not
Have you opened a new company?
If you want to make money
Why not go find her
She just started
Also quite difficult
sister
Why are you here
See accompany you
Accompany you on a business trip
Who asked you to accompany me on a business trip
You put your hands on
So much work
I'm not doing business right here
Water in your head
Is not
Sister, don't be so irritable
Sorry, let me
Sorry
I help you
Sit sit sit sit sit
sister
First
Work on my hands
It's all done
second
I made this specifically
Jump to Hefei website
You take this to talk to people
Guaranteed to do more with less
When did you do
Just now
People want to design for me
Any doubts
I can answer on the spot
What's the problem
I can also modify it on the spot
Wait to finish Hefei
I want to go to Nantong
You ask Xiao Lu for information
Before the train arrives in Hefei
I want a page from Nantong
Obey
Hello how many people
Have reservations
Hello there
you are late
Five minutes and thirty two seconds
Sorry, traffic jam on the road
This time
The city center will definitely be blocked
So before you go out
Should at least be reserved
Fifteen minutes
I know
Waiter
Do you order food?
Steak set meal soda
Thank you
The same thanks
What drink does the lady drink
Ice latte
Unsweetened skimmed milk
You drink ice
what happened
Women drink ice easily
Bad for future births
So hope you in the future
Don't drink ice
This is for you
Hello there
Change her to hot lemon tea
Thank you
it is good
This time you choose
Very interesting
Four forty four
By six twenty one
Is there any special meaning
I end the meeting at 4:30
Go downstairs and pick up the car for three minutes
From company to here
It takes nine minutes
Stop for two minutes
So ask you
Four forty four
It's six forty-five
I have a video conference
Although it is the evening rush hour
But it won't block
There are only three traffic lights
Back to the company from here
It takes twenty minutes
Park upstairs for three minutes
and so
At six twenty one
Our date is over
What are you doing
Weighing
My fitness coach
Made me a
Diet plan
My daily calorie intake
All have strict restrictions
Look at them
Don't mind the eyes of others
I don't mind
But did not expect
You are so strict with yourself
Self-management awareness
Is to measure the elite
Important standards with the grassroots
This management
Not just at work
Also includes self-size
Manners
And family run
Child education
Makes sense
I'll make one for you later
What to formulate
Self-management plan
next Thursday
Twelve fourteen
Till three forty four
We can have lunch together
Then watch a movie
See you next week
Date at least once a week
This is good for
We know each other
And enhance the relationship
next week
I'm not sure next week
Am i free
If there is no time
You can contact Miss Chang
She will help you arrange
Next date
Ok
See you next week
week after next
see
Fell asleep
Ok
I am trusting
Brother from my university
Help me contact work
Didn't the doctor let you rest?
What anxious
You stay here
Just be optimistic about Yuwei
I want to find a job earlier
So as to relieve your stress
I carry the pressure myself
Xiaoling
wait for me a while
Wait for me wait for me
wait for me
Lei Haowen, open the door
No one looks at you
Faster
Here comes here comes
Why don't you even wear shoes
Come put on the slippers
Are there any band-aids?
Broken foot
Yes yes yes
Where is it broken
Let me see
Your feet are just right
Why wear high heels
Still so high
I have an appointment
Is it easy
Who did you date
Dated a bookworm
and then
I do not know either
Should there be then
All right
Do you have anything to eat here
In the kitchen, take it yourself
I am too lazy to move
Pity me
Help me get it
Go quickly
Row
Why do you come every time
Don't say hello
In case I am Jinwu Cangjiao
How embarrassing it was
just you
impossible
Don't underestimate me
Someday if i really have
You can't cry
Who
My girlfriend
No, why are you going?
I let your girlfriend in
You stupid
We are a lone man and a widow
You grow so violently
Let her know
Don't worry about me
What do you say to me
You go into the house
Go in and hide
Not me still
You go in and hide
I'll take her away in a while
Leave you and come out
Remember, don't come out
I am still
Don't come out, listen
I said you come out, you come out again
Sir hello your
Takeaway
How many times have I told you
I don't eat dinner at night
I lose weight, don't you know
do not you know
Don't cry
Why cry
Don't contact me anymore
What's the call
Walk around
Xiaoling
Come out
Girlfriend left so soon
Ok
Gave me something delicious
I said i don't eat
Let me persuade me to go
Your girlfriend
Surname
Yes
I still have a girlfriend
Hungry
Is the name?
The two of them
Be jealous for me
It's a great fight
Then you
I have to treat them both well
this is mine
What happened to your noodles?
You just finished the meeting
You follow me
People who didn't eat dinner
Can you get by inside
I
I tell you
I have my saliva here
so what
You are not afraid of my illness
What can you get sick
if serious
Might die
Then I will die in your saliva
Die well
Not worthy of mine
Affectionate
You said, they told me
So nutritious
I feel bored
You talk nonsense to me here
I feel very happy
Who am I
Because you are like me
The two of us
Are all domestic counterfeit goods
I labeled you a domestic second
Come here, hit you
Come, you hit
You come down
Hit hit hit
You give me you
Come in the bedroom
Come come, you give me
Enter the bedroom
you come down
You come out
Lei Haowen, open the door for me
You have the ability to come out
Return my shoes to me
Qijue Group's list
Didn¡¯t you sign all the contracts?
Why lost again
President Yuan, I really don't blame me for this
Who is to blame
You do not know
Their group
The manager in charge of this project
How strange is your temper
Every time i go to see him
Legs are shaking
I asked you about the contract
Manager Su has too much appetite
I dare not agree
He turned back
How big is it
Definitely beyond our bottom line
Your performance this month
How to calculate
I
I confess
There is
Zhang Zhizhi is coming to our department
What is she doing
Sales
Can she do it
She won't
Is there any other purpose?
I asked human resources
Said it was difficult at home
Want to make some money with us
She is too naive, right
She has today
When I scolded President Yuan,
How arrogant
President Yuan
Take advantage of this opportunity
Teach her a lesson
Let her know
What is regret?
I have an idea
We put here
Decorate more warmly
So the customer is coming
Happy to look at
it is good
chopsticks
Put this green plant over there
Lean to that side
it is good
Stay closer
President Yuan, I'm here to report
President Yuan
these files
What about this chair
Where to put it
Vacate that room
When the utility room
Put it all inside
it is good
Hurry up
Xiao Wu Bibo
Do a favor
President Yuan, I'm here to report
Move this over
Xiao Liu, push this shelf back
Yes come
Come on
Put this one more
Put some green plants
Put this put this put this
Let me see
Put this here
Put this right right right right
Right these put here
Zhang Zhizhi, why stand silly?
Find a place to sit down
Waiting for others to serve you
No one in this seat
Sit here
Thank you
Why are you jumping here
Isn't this asking for trouble?
As long as there is still something to eat
Whether it is bitter or sweet
President Yuan will definitely not let you
Have a good life
Without her
My life is not easy
Zhang Zhizhi
Come here
You go visit this customer
I'm alone
Why let me match it for you
Assistant driver
Babysitter, hair stylist
That was not what I meant
I'm afraid of messing up
After all i today
When the first day of sale
Just because you are the first day
So give a
Good customer for you
As long as he signs
Your mission this month
Even finished
Go
Thank you Mr. Yuan
Lin Ling
Put this in that room
Move away quickly
chopsticks
You come with me to move
Take away
Advance
Is it Mr. Mei?
it's me
Mr. Mei, hello
I'm Li Siyu from the company
This is my colleague Guan Xiaotang
What's up with me
We come today
Just want to talk
Regional agency
Cooperation
So what
Sit first, don't stand
You are
Call
Yes
Will this play?
Played before
Come a game
OK
Rarely encountered now
The girl who can play the King of Fighters
Do you usually play anything else?
this one
This is good
Then you should be pretty good
Hit hit
Legs legs
With legs with legs
With legs
Your hand
But a bit raw
Haven't played for a long time
President Mei
If you can guarantee
Get two hundred points
I can put
Hefei regional agent for you
I heard
You have some
Franchisee's operation
Not like you at all
The promotion is so explosive
That's because our customers
Haven't started loading
But our trend
Still pretty good
trend
I don¡¯t think the trend is optimistic
Fuck him, beat him
You look
Boring
Stop playing
In front of a master like President Mei
I was convinced to lose
on
At this level, I am convinced
President Mei, this is us
Latest statistics
You know
We called
Still very stamina
I am
Least believe in
Statistics
or
Two for you
come
I play this game
But never defeated
I am called
Young and Beautiful Thanos
Young and beautiful
Okay
Then I'll come to learn
Your little Thanos style
Advance
Mr. Su, hello
Ok
you are
I i am
Salesperson of Lvbao Group
Zhang Zhizhi
Can you take you fifteen minutes
Can't
I want to introduce to you
Our company's latest products
I do not want to hear
but
Where's the salesperson from before
My colleague has something with her today
So
So we lead
Send me today
Send one today
Come here if you can't even understand
right
Your Lvbao Group is really
More and less good
No i am today
What is it
Trouble you to go back
Tell your leader
We Qijue Technology
Won't use your Emerald Group
Any product
Since then
You and your colleagues
Self-esteem
Stop harassing me
Don't
President Su
This is our company
Introduction of the latest products
If you are free
Please take a look
If you need
You just call me
I just used my success
I was attacked by you
Don't be proud
Who are you looking for
How did you come in
You are lucky
Ok
Change game
I don't believe it
You pick whatever
League club
I can
Go alone
Don't stop me
Have a phone number?
You are also calling
Not high, only five drills
Send me to pull you
This one
You are love
Exactly under
Isn't it
Is not
I am your diehard fan
is it
All your game videos
I have seen it all
Hope this time
Happy cooperation
happy
Surely happy
Happy, happy, happy
I saw the living god
keep it up
I add you a friend
Good good good good
Take a look
You look
Guan Xiaotang, I love you
Don't regret this time
Bring me out
I ask you
I asked you to let Mr. Mei
Why don't you listen
Why should i let him
You want to do business
You have to make people happy
But ah
I do things
I have to make myself happy first
You never worry
How others feel
I worry about myself
Can't worry too much
I worry about others
I will
I won't show you to customers anymore
why
No, without me this time
You can't take Mr. Mei
You are a mistake
I speak with strength
You don't know how to socialize
Is not
I'm just too lazy to be hypocritical, okay
Moreover
Are you stupid for those customers
I can't see your routines
Rather than let people see it first
Might as well take the initiative
Slaughter
Beat them so subdued
This business
It's a matter of course
Where do you come from so much truth
In the genes
But
Some customers still
Eat your set
Most customers
So, sister
Take me next time you go out
Our two swords go together
Invincible