[To Dear Myself]
[Ep6]
I worked till 4 a.m. from last night again
Shaozi, come here
Everyone, gather here
Everyone, come here
What's up?
Our team is rewarded with 20,000 yuan
Awesome
Sorry
I woke up late in the morning
Saw your message and I wanted to reply you
after I was in office
But I was too busy and forgot to reply you till now
Sister Siyu
The company rewards us
Calm down...
Team leader Li Siyu's salary will increase by 20%
And will be rewarded RMB 20,000
Lin Ling is rewarded 10,000 yuan
Team B will be rewarded 20,000 yuan
What? Let me see
To praise the outstanding performance
and perseverance
Did you see it?
20% pay rise
And a bonus of 20,000 yuan
Cake...
Sister, we have to go now
Bye
An order of 500,000 yuan
The reward of 50,000 yuan
Does the company have any rules?
The company has rules
But it doesn't work for Pan Zhiyong
We just do it as he says?
The company belongs to him only?
He is a major shareholder
President and general manager
You are also a shareholder
You are the vice president of the company
I have no say in the finance department and HR department
I am in charge of security, customer service and sales
The core department of sales
You are impacted because of my management
Brother
I didn't blame you
Sit
Actually
On seniority, ability, you are the best candidate for sales director
But Pan Zhiyong rejected my proposal in the meeting
He insisted to select a director in this way
The most fundamental reason is
You are under my direct leadership
and you don't need to listen to him
You are my direct leader all along
Of course I listen to you
So
In his eyes, you are not on his side
He won't give you the post
So Li Siyu is on his side?
She was not before
But after this notice, she will be
Siyu promised me personally
She won't compete with me
Then why does she work till the early morning with her team?
She's going all out
You still think she won't compete with you?
Siyu won't do that
She values friendship
People will change
Especially in front of interests
Li Siyu is no longer the one that she used to be
Don't hesitate anymore before it's too late
Let me think about it
Indecisiveness will lead to troubles
Sister Yuan
What happened?
We want to ask, anything wrong?
Just go grab orders
Sister Yuan is watching
Come, cheers
Cheers
Sister Siyu
Thank you
Cheers
Why thank me?
You get the order
Just thank yourself
I can't get the order without you
No order without you, either
Actually before yesterday,
I give up on my dad's disease
But after I get the order
I have hope again
As long as I don't give up
As long as I persist
my dad will have miracles
Lin Ling
Best wishes
There will be a miracle
Yes, best wishes
Come on
Come
Sign more orders with sister Siyu
Win more bonus
We will get better and better
Come on
So ridiculous
I declare
This time I will give my bonus to Lin Ling
Pay your dad's hospitalization fee
Sister Siyu
I'll follow you for the rest of my life
Just a little money
Look at you, didn't see much of the world
Sister Siyu, don't worry
I will work harder in the next three months
For myself, also for you
I will help you be the director
Exactly
Director...
We can do it
Come on
Don't say like that
We will defeat team A
And sister Siyu will become the director
We will win
Cheers
Director
I said it long ago
Sister Siyu will be the director
Absolutely
Come on
Everyone, listen
My...
My stomach aches
Sister
I don't say anything
Let's take a picture
And we will work hard
Ok
Work hard
Xiaowu...
Leave it to you
Me...
Closer
Come...
1, 2, 3
Ok
Let's cut the cake
Cut the cake
3.5
So sweet, 23 is great
Want a zucchini?
Ok
Come
I am in a meeting
Hello, dude
A radish, 1.5
It's fresh
Edamame, right?
Correct
I need some
Ok, how much do you want?
One jin
Ok
Come, ten yuan
How much?
Ten yuan
It's 12 yuan yesterday
Why it's ten yuan today?
Dude, I lower the price, any problem?
It's the yesterday's edamame
It's still yesterday's quality
How can you lower the price so abruptly?
It doesn't sell well
Of course I need to lower the price
I don't need it
Are you crazy?
All the concerns will go after a meal
Otherwise, have another meal
So a good cooking skill
is the root of happiness in life
Burn the oil to 70% hot
Then quickly pour it on the chili rings
Shred green and red peppers
Shred green onions and green Chinese onions
And put shallots, ginger slices spices
and marinated chicken together
Till the chicken is fully cooked
Then soak it quickly in ice water
Soak dried chili in hot water
Ans peel marinated chicken
Why are you here?
You are at home
Put some pepper oil
Put more of it
Add the chicken broth
After mixing
let it stand for a while
Sprinkle some white sesame seeds after filling
You are in a meeting, right?
I am here at the wrong time, right?
This spiced chicken with chili sauce is authentic?
So if there are friends from Xinjiang?
Welcome to leave a comment
Xiaoling is right
Men are so unreliable
What?
Chen Yiming
Tell me the truth
Who do you cook these dishes for?
Myself
You still lie to me?
I did not lie to you
I found you had a problem for some time
I just didn't say it
What's wrong with me?
Dare you give me your phone?
Siyu
Don't touch me...
No, it's not like what you think
Go back with me first
Let go -I will tell you
Siyu
Let go
Don't force me
I lost my job
What?
Yes...
Two weeks ago
I was laid off
Impossible
Yes
I also think it's impossible
But it just happened
So...
So I have nothing to do every day
So I just cook to kill the time
Great
Are you insane?
Why do you say so?
You are unemployed
I thought you had an affair
Dad
Where's mom?
She went out
When did she go out?
After dinner
She left you home alone
So ridiculous
Son
You're back
Mom
Did you have dinner?
I'll cook for you now
I brought your favorite...
No... mom
When did you come?
This afternoon
This afternoon?
Zhizhi said, you are busy
So I didn't call you
Yuwei, I'm back  -Mom
You are back
Why you didn't tell me at the at the first time?
I planned to tell you after I find a new job
Are you looking for one?
Yes
I began to look for a job one day after I was fired
But I didn't find one
It's ok, just unemployment
Not a big deal
Caijin is a sting company
If you stay there, you will waste your life
It's your fortune that they fire you
A better and stronger company is waiting for you
I thought so
Within two weeks, I sent almost 50 emails
But no reply
The time is not come yet
Job hunting is the same as courtship
It's all about time, place and people
Maybe I should reassess my ability now
No need
You are the best
No
I...
You can doubt yourself
But you can't doubt me
I have faith in the man I love
Siyu
Thank you
Go check it out
New job is knocking on the door
No
Go
What is it?
I was rejected again
I have lowered salary requirement
But still no company hires me
These are your favorites
Zhizhi called me
She told me Yuwei misses me
I miss Yuwei too
So I come here directly
Mom
You should have told us
So we can pick you up at the station
You carry so many things, so heavy
Not heavy, it's ok
I have come here for many times
After I get off the train, I take the bus
Then I just get home
Mom, you should stay here for more days this time
You said, your heart hurts, right?
You should go to do the checkup
I'm fine
Well, Zhizhi will register for you tomorrow
No need
I know myself
Besides, I have medicine
Look
Heart medicine and pain killer
The temperature varies a lot
You can drink some if you feel unwell
Mom, don't eat the wrong medicine
You should do the checkup
Ok, I got it
Grandma... play with me
I am coming
I have to play with my granddaughter
Mom
We still have to go to the hospital
We should find out the problem
Ok...
Why did you call my mom without telling me?
What are you talking about?
It's your mom, I can't stop her
Mom said she has a heart attack
So I have to say, she should come for a checkup
Did I do something wrong?
I know what you are playing at
You need my mom to take care of Yuwei
So you can play around with the so-called elite moms
I do this for Yuwei
Nothing wrong
Ali
Fubu
This is our homespun
Nonsense
I have been selling cloth for many years
I know it so well
It's made by my machines
I know it
Uncles
Stop arguing
Three of it are Shaanxi homespuns
Impossible
No
I just cut it from the loom
So great?
If it goes to the market...
Hello
Is it Mr. Chen Yiming?
Yes, it's me
We received your resume
Your experience meets our company's demand
Can you come this afternoon?
Our president wants to have a job interview with you
Yes
When and where?
I will send you the address and time later
Ok
Which company are you from?
You will know after you see our president
Nanjing West Road 3:00 PM
3:00 PM
Chen
Here
Siyu
Why are you here?
I have an interview here at 3:00 PM
He will come soon
Mr. Chen
I am your interviewer
Stop it, ok?
Mr. Chen
Please give me a short self-introduction
I have no time to play with you now
I have an appointment at 3:00 PM
Anyway, it's all on your resume
What are your strengths?
You made the appointment with me?
How's your driving?
Mischievous
I have an offer for you
You should check it out first
This post's salary is zero
But it has promotion
You can be promoted as father, grandfather
If you live long enough
you will be promoted as great grandfather
I know
You have been rejected during this time
But it's not because you are not excellent enough
But because the time is yet to come
Look
Our company has an eye for you and takes initiative
So don't depressed
Don't look down on yourself
Well, our company prepared a gift for you
What is this?
Open it yourself
Siyu
Thank you
Mr. Chen
If you are interested, please come to work with diamond ring
I believe
You will be a very good husband
Siyu
I accept the offer
Also, I will accept the gift
I will go to work
But not now
Why?
Because I think I am not eligible enough
Give me more time
I will go to work with a real offer
Thank you
This is the introduction and brochure of the new products
How many do you want?
Ask sister Liu
Ok
Excuse me
This is the introduction and brochure of the new products
Just ask sister Liu
Ok
Excuse me
This is the introduction and brochure of the new products
How many do you want?
Our group don't need it
HR department should keep it for us
Ok
My proposal failed
How come?
Impossible
Why?
Miss Gu
Coming
Serve you right
Come, eat more
Eat
Thanks
Yuwei usually eats little
Today you eat a big bowl of rice
Grandma's large meatball is so delicious
Ok
Thank grandma
Thank you, grandma
You're welcome
I will cook you more in the future
Mom, thank you
It's ok
Liu Yang gets off work so late every day?
He is a little busy recently
So he needs to work overtime
I'm full, mom
I have to go out
Help me take care of Yuwei
Ok
Go...
She can't eat peanuts
Can't watch too much TV
Ok
Don't worry
Be a good girl
Bye
Go...
You are back
So fragrant
Go, wash your hands
I cooked your favorite dishes
Go out?
Mom is here, she won't disturb you
Hurry...
Where is your mom going?
Prepare the party with Miaomiao's mom
What do you mean?
I love mom
I don't understand what you are talking about
Mom, stop asking
Never mind it
Ok, hurry
The dishes are getting cold
Wash my hands first
These are available online
It's half cheaper than here
I don't like buying things online
Linda's mom gives a budget
Every family needs to hand in 1500 yuan
Do you think it's low?
Still low?
If it's 3000, we can invite
foreign children's drama clubs to perform
If it's 1500, only domestic clubs
They will do the makeups and wear masks
it's hard to tell it's domestic or foreign
A big difference
One is London's accent, one is New York's accent
It's two different things
Really?
By the way, Yuwei's mom
Did Yuwei tell me
Doudou fought against others?
No
Miaomiao cried many times for it
She told me Doudou often pulls her hair
Even kicks her
Did you tell the teacher?
Yes, but it's useless
Today Doudou still grabbed her toys
Really?
What kind of people are Doudou's parents?
Such a brat
Did you see team B's sales performance this month?
What did you eat for dinner?
Did you finish your homework?
Did you recite the book?
And vocabulary
Ok
Leave it there
I'll sign it after I go back
Sister Yuan is here
Go ahead
Sister Yuan
Team B is going crazy now
Yes, sister Yuan
Lin Ling works till midnight every day
Their interns are so workaholic
Xia Xiaotian is the most ridiculous
She even harassed my client
This is exactly what someone wants
But as I know, Xia Xiaotian outperforms Huang Bibo this month
Really?
As I know, Jia Shu the top saleman of Degao battery
will come to our company
And he demands to go to Li Siyu's team
If it's true, I am afraid we can't outcompete them
You underestimate sister Yuan
But Li Siyu has a strong momentum now
Sister Yuan
We can't take it lightly
Li Siyu is no longer the one that used to be
Don't hesitate anymore before it's too late
Cheers
My goal today is 5 effective visits
Then I will continue to contact Alaide company
I will contact the new clients
Come in
Sister Siyu
Vice president Fang wants to see you
Ok, excuse me
This is great
This is the last month
VP Fang
Mr. Zhou
Siyu, sit down
Zhou has something to tell you
You gave this to finance department last month?
Yes
What's going on with 500 yuan ticket?
You want to reimburse PR fee on 25th
But this invoice is on the 4th day of last month
This 500 yuan is for overtime
We have another application process for overtime pay
That's because application process for overtime pay is
too complicated
So I used meal invoice
Sister Yuan knows about this
This is her signature
You think you can get away with it
just because you have her signature?
What do you mean?
You cheated the PR fee
I am a good salewoman
I don't need to cheat 500 yuan, ok?
You have commissions of several hundred thousand yuan
Now you want to take advantage of the company
I have seen a lot of people like this
How can you say so?
I have evidence
Please investigate it in sales department
before you makde the conclusion
Li Siyu, you think we can't punish you
just because you are a team leader?
Whatever
I didn't cheat and I mean it
All right
Zhou
You two go out first
I need to talk to Li Siyu alone
Li Siyu
Sit down
We have checked all your invoices
You cheated over 7000 yuan
It's overtime pay
Strictly speaking
it's a fraud
And the crime of embezzlement
The whole sales department is committing crimes these years
But they didn't report others
They only report you, Li Siyu
These data are in my office now
According to the finance department,
we should call the police
I have consulted the lawyers
The amount exceeds 5000 yuan
According to the criminal law
you have to be sentenced to at least three years
What?
If it's true, your life will be ruined
Let's be honest
You made a lot of contributions here these years
We don't want to go hard on you
We want to be lenient
As long as you resign
we will let bygones be bygones
I will not resign
Why?
Because I never cheated a penny
You still deny it
I did not do anything
Why should I admit it?
So we have to call the police
Have it your way
You
You know, you still need to leave even if the police come?
Till then, everyone will know it
Our company brand will be affected
You still want to stand in this industry?
I believe the police will prove my innocence
You think you can withstand the investigation?
If I can't stand the investigation
the whole sales department won't either
You want to get all of them implicated?
I can tell you, it's impossible
Today we have only one solution
You need to resign
I will never resign because of the invoice
Li Siyu
The company has given you a chance
If you insist, you can't blame us